Chapter 495: Opening

Leylin watched the performance of these Warlocks, indifferent to it all.

In fact, it was very clear to them that small organisations like the Arm of Vengeance were being used as scapegoats by the hidden forces.

Were Gilbert and the rest to appear, they would just throw out these scapegoats to suffer their wrath, without caring for their life or death.

And even if these small organisations were to find success, they wouldn’t end up with much resources. They could only give the majority of the resources to their backers. Thus, these forces could reap the benefits without getting their own hands dirty. It was a great deal indeed.

Although these Warlocks were completely aware of this, they only dared curse these small organisations that had gone insane in their desire for revenge, but did not dare touch the existence in the background. In the back of their minds, even though they lacked Morning Star forces on their side, they definitely did not have the guts to provoke those acting behind the scenes. To them, on their side, they would not have the guts to challenge the masterminds.

“Never mind that. This place is soon going to become a battlefield, so every one of us must take up our responsibilities. Do you all agree?”

“Agreed!” “Agreed!” “Agreed!” Numerous high ranked Warlocks nodded one after another.

“That’s great, we still have the two Kemoyin Gargoyles and the spell formation left by the elders. We can still handle a Morning Star Magus if we activate everything… We just need to persist for a period of time, then the three mentors will be able to return from the astral plane!”

The red-haired Warlock was still trying his best to boost the morale, and hence he maintained the delusion.

After he spoke up to that, everyone’s sight immediately shot to an old Warlock who was wiping his spectacles with a white handkerchief.

This old Crystal Phase Warlock was the head of their technical department, Schadt.

Schadt put on his spectacles with a bitter laugh, “Our tests have confirmed that the elders really did open the astral gates and entered another world. However, we couldn’t confirm that it’s the Purgatory World. However, we’re trying really hard to calculate the coordinates. I just need ten days… No! Five! We’ll have it in five!”

The expressions of the numerous Warlocks dulled when the reply they got wasn’t the one they wanted.

The red-haired Warlock forced a smile, and immediately began to assign missions as a leader, “Marquis Schadt, continue to study the astral gate. Headquarters will allocate resources to you as you wish. You have to rescue our three Mentors!”

“I will!” Schadt nodded. There was a great scholarly temperament to him as he still seemed like nothing had happened even in this kind of critical moment .

“Next, Marquis Lucian…” There was pride in the tone of the red-haired Warlock when he heard the other party agreeing to his orders.

Although he was the first disciple of the Grand Elder, his authority was not much greater than that of the remaining Marquises present here. But now, when the circumstances required the presence of a powerful leader due to both internal and external pressures, it seemed like he could try to take control!

“Very well! Next…” The Warlock started to assign missions to everyone. Finally, it was Leylin’s turn. “Marquis Leylin, it’s no problem if I leave you in charge of the defense of the West Zone of the city, right?”

“Sorry, I do!” Leylin raised his hand up. He’d heard from Lucian about this Warlock before, although he hadn’t met him in person many times. He was Faisal, and he had held power for a long time in the Ouroboros Clan. Right now, it seemed that even in all this confusion, his first thought was of grasping power.

Leylin was immediately fed up by this sort of thing. With their current situation, perhaps the entire headquarters would be breached tomorrow, and everyone would be finished. He still wanted to scramble for power and profits?

“What?” Faisal wrinkled his brows. He’d met a challenger moments after he set up his authority. This triggered his immense dissatisfaction, so he decided to suppress the challenger ruthlessly.

“I have an extremely important experiment…”

“Experiment? Just for the purpose of an experiment?” Leylin was interrupted by Faisal before he could complete his words. “Did I mishear? You want to abandon your responsibility in this kind of critical moment just for an experiment?”

Numerous high-ranked Warlocks around the round table also started whispering to each other after they heard Faisal words.

“Let me finish!” Leylin pressed his hands down.

“The experiment I’m working on is an interplanar experiment. I’m confident in being able to find the coordinates of the Mentors in three days. Marquis Schadt can testify to this.”

Schadt, who’d been still as a statue from the beginning, also nodded, “Indeed. Marquis Leylin’s fundamental knowledge about astral experiments far surpasses mine. Especially in accurately searching for coordinates, he leaves me ashamed of my meagre ability.”

“Even so,” Faisal ground his teeth, “The defence of the West Zone…”

“I’ll take care of that as well,” Freya interrupted.

“You?” Faisal was a little astonished.

“Yes. Anyway, my own defence zone is not far from Leylin’s. It’s alright for me to take care of both, right?” Freya looked at Faisal challengingly. The other Warlocks had a knowing smile on their faces when they recalled the rumours about Freya and Leylin.

“You can if you say so, but what if your area has problems first…” Faisal dragged out his speech, looking at Freya who had an unyielding expression. He thought Leylin was getting more and more out of hand.

Freya ground her teeth and stated stubbornly, “It’ll be my responsibility!”

“Fine, I hope you remember what you said today!” Faisal nodded and sat back down.

The person involved, Leylin, sat foolishly at a distance from the beginning. Only after it ended did he respond and look at Freya. This woman had helped him over and over again, even at the expense of her own family’s interests, and was already facing criticism from her elders.

He hadn’t expected that she would be willing to help him to this extent.

Actually, this so-called important experiment was just to pull the wool over Faisal’s eyes. With his knowledge, it was easy for him to convince Schadt by exposing a bit of his abilities.

If Faisal hadn’t agreed even after that, he would’ve looked for an opportunity to shirk his responsibility.

However, Freya unexpectedly took it on for him. Leylin suddenly felt a bit of a headache as he looked at her.

“You don’t need to do this, you know…” Leylin walked to Freya’s side and said softly after the meeting dispersed,.

“It’s my choice.” Freya gathered her black long hair together and left quickly. She seemed stubborn and firm.

Leylin shook his head, then communicated with the A.I. Chip and took a look at the latest data.

[Progress on deduction of information about the Morning Star realm: 52.7%]

After more than ten days, the A.I. Chip had finally finished analysing the flesh of the Azure Mountain King’s clone. His information about the Morning Star realm had crossed 50%!

With this, the final requirement for his advancement to the Morning Star realm had been fulfilled.

“The future seems exciting. I will look forward to it….” A smile hung on the corner of Leylin’s mouth. He then took a glance at the meeting place and at last moved his legs, leaving with incomparably firm footsteps.

……

In an unknown place, several mysterious [conscients] were communicating with each other.

A conscient is a high-level projection of one’s perception across the land. The person themself is not present, physically nor spiritually, only observing casually from a distance.

“The attacks of the plant legion have had pretty good results! The progress this time is pretty smooth. The air force has also taken down Greenflame City. It seems like the Morning Star Warlocks are already lost in the astral plane.”

“Not necessarily. Gilbert and the rest are very cunning. It’s possible that they’re feigning weakness in order to bait us into exposing ourselves,” another voice immediately retorted, “The lifespan of a Morning Star Warlock is nigh endless. Even temporary gains and losses of territory are nothing to them. They can always expand their influence again in the future…”

“What you said also makes sense. We must consider this, and continue to test them. Try to attack their headquarters in Phosphorescence Swamp!” the previous voice said. A powerful stream of thought swept out, “Where’s that old Azure Mountain guy?”

“Hehe… he lost a clone to the Ouroboros Clan. With his main body settling a debt with Felix, I’m afraid he won’t be available for a period of time…” a woman jokingly said.

“His clone fell? It must have been at rank 3. Even then, who interfered?” The voice who spoke previously seemed sluggish.

“No one! Azure Mountain’s clone unexpectedly fell at the hand of a member of the younger generation without the interference of any Morning Star powers. It’s even someone who had just advanced to the Crystal Phase. I’m afraid he’ll feel too embarrassed to meet people before he thoroughly washes himself of his shame…” The female voice answered

“To have his clone killed by a member of the younger generation. It’s simply a humiliation to all Morning Star Magi!”

“That’s right!” The numerous thoughts descended into chaos.

“Silence!“ the first voice said with immense dignity behind its tone. It immediately suppressed the disturbance.

“Let Azure Mountain’s matter go for now. The area he’s responsible for isn’t that important anyway. The next test will be crucial in determining the existence of those three. This matter also concerns how we’ll be treating the Ouroboros Clan in the future, so we should be serious about it!”

The powerful conscient¹ stated, its imposing aura full of dignity.

“We got it!” Numerous thought backed up a step as if expressing surrender.

“Great! The plant legion still needs to advance and push the battlefront forward. As for the air force, remain on the defensive for now. The defence abilities of the headquarters of the Ouroboros Clan are still decent…”

The most powerful thought immediately started to distribute tasks. Soon after, the thoughts in the secret space left one after the other, and the region quieted down immediately.

A deadly stillness permeated the surroundings.

After this meeting, the attacks that were originally planned against the Ouroboros Clan grew in intensity.

Among these, parties such as Azure Mountain City and Nefas broke apart all pretense and flagrantly dispatched their elite groups into the territory of the Ouroboros Clan. This resulted in a great slaughter.

The frontline also approached the headquarters of the Ouroboros Clan in Phosphorescence Swamp continuously. In moments, it was like a storm was raging in the region, which practically affected the weather of the entire central continent.

Numerous Morning Star Magi, Radiant Moon Magi, and even Breaking Dawn Magi all diverted their attentions to the sky above Phosphorescence Swamp.

For the central continent which is in dire straits, any minute changes would be able to cause a huge variation.

Chapter 500: Duo Serpent Annihilator

“Have you decided, my Lord?” The black shadow couldn’t help but feel delighted in front of Faisal.

The satisfaction in being able to threaten the leader of the Ouroboros Clan, one of the largest clans on the continent, was something that could not be described with mere words. It was only furthered by the conflicted expression on the other party.

The rewards if he succeeded at this were so great he wouldn’t even dare to think of them before.

“Reporting in, my Lord!”

At this timing, a high-ranking Magus pushed opened the door. Ignoring the shadow’s existence, he began his report, “The operation was a success! We’ve captured seven traitors and killed twelve. The energy of the combined spell formation has been conserved, and we’ve only lost a mere 2.75%…”

“What is this supposed to mean?” the envoy questioned, his voice growing deeper and gloomier.

“What is this supposed to mean? It’s exactly what you think it is!” Faisal suddenly gave an empty smile as his body instantly appeared before the shadow, grabbing his neck and lifting him up.

“If you do this, the Lords outside will definitely not let you off!” Surprisingly, even at this moment, the shadow was calm.

“I’ll be waiting,” Faisal nodded his head as he said seriously, “If you think that I’m unable to deal with you just because you’re a spirit projection, you’re wrong. You’re very, very wrong.”

The moment he finished speaking, there was a visible change in the expression on the blurred face of the black shadow and he couldn’t help but give a cold smile, “It’s a pity, but it’s too late!”

*Boom!* Huge amounts of blue electricity rushed towards the shadow, blowing him to pieces.

Faisal sighed. “With such a huge stream of disordered data rushing in, even the main body would have its sea of consciousness suffer irreversible damage!” he said in an unhurried manner.

“My Lord, this is brilliant!” The Magus that had just entered immediately bowed.

“This is nothing, it’s just a little scheme, and it definitely won’t affect the general situation,” Faisal said. He then exclaimed, “The Ouroboros Clan is my family and the pillar of support for all Warlocks of our Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline. I want to be in control of it, not let it be destroyed…”

*Thump!*

The green-haired Magus who was standing outside the city fumed upon listening to the grievous news as he witnessed the death of one of his envoys.

“Release the Kyasha Beast immediately!”

“But, my Lord…” Just as he was about to continue, the attendant at the green-haired Magus’ side was interrupted, “I know I have limited authority. I’ll explain things to the other Lords later, but for now, I want those ignorant Warlocks to pay with their deaths!”

“Coo coo…” After the order of the release of the warbeast, the brave and blood-soaked Magi standing on the frontline heard a bizarre roar.

The roar resembled the beating of a broken drum, and carried a heavy pant with it. It created a sense of oppression that made one feel like they were suffocating the moment it fell on their ears.

*Thump!*

*Thump!*

The ground started to shake. How scary was it for only one creature to cause the entire city to shake with its mere footsteps?

Faisal couldn’t help but feel uncomfortable in that moment, as he quickly ascended to the highest vantage point.

From there, he saw an incomparably large creature, a four-legged beast with a horn on its head. The creature was so huge and tall that in order to avoid it, the enormous airships in the sky could only wave their flags and ascend further into the sky, opening a pathway for it to walk through.

The earth rumbled under this creature’s arrival, its enormous aura even causing Faisal’s breathing to stop momentarily.

When it finally stopped right outside the Ouroboros Clan headquarters, Faisal thought he was seeing a mountain range instead.

The Kyasha Beasts roared in anger. A terrifying and violent wave of energy swept across the battlefield, causing everyone to lose their balance.

“Morning Star! It is a Morning Star realm creature!” Faisal’s expression blanked out as he clenched his fists tightly. “I’m afraid the cleansing operation this time provoked the enemy so badly that he’s using the deadly weapons that were used in the last big war. .”

On the other hand, the enemy who’d lifted the restriction on the warbeast didn’t feel too good about it either.

“My Lord, is it okay to lift the restrictions now? After all, we haven’t performed final adjustments on it… Besides, a lot of our soldiers will be injured by it as collateral damage…” One of the Magi smiled bitterly as he looked at the giant Kyasha Beast with a heavy heart.

This giant beast was absolutely not a natural creature. It was a precious experiment created by a Morning Star Magus.

When the creature was not in use, it would be sealed in ice. The Morning Star Magus that created it even warned that if they didn’t provide enough food for the beast to eat, even a large troop of Magi would be eaten alive by it.

Naturally, despite such shortcomings, a Morning Star realm creature had its own worth. This was a beast that had a physique at the Morning Star realm. Together with its enormous body and terrifying defence system which included the ability to heal itself, the idea of battling such a creature was a joke.

Moreover, because its intelligence was sealed, even a rank 3 Magus could, albeit barely, control it. This resulted in a great increase in its worth.

After feeling embarrassed and insulted by the other party, the green-haired Magus immediately lifted the restriction on the warbeast.

The green-haired Magus, their leader, clapped his hands. “Don’t worry! The other Lords have given me the authority to lift the restrictions whenever I want to.”

“After all, this is the last experiment. The warbeast summoned by the other party has to be at a Morning Star level to be able to defeat this creature. Since we’ve already made the first move, it’s up to the Ouroboros Clan to retaliate with their last resort.”

The warbeast’s roars shook the earth as it moved closer to the defensive membrane on its long legs. A large number of Warlocks were eagerly showering it with any spells that they could throw.

*Bang! Bang! Bang!*

Blizzards, lightning, flames, and acids were all aimed at the Kyasha Beast. Yet, they were unable to so much as slow the rate of its advance.

While a rank 3 spell occasionally broke through its defences, it was not enough to cause any significant damage in comparison to its enormous body. This left the Warlocks disappointed.

By the time it reached the defensive barrier, the wounds on its body had been healing so quickly that it appeared to never have been wounded at all.

The thought that this creature was invincible caused dismay among the Magi. Adding to the fact that it seemed impossible to wound the creature and they could only wait for their deaths, the Warlocks were extremely discouraged as they felt like the world was coming to an end.

The enemy’s passion for battle increased greatly with the boost in morale brought by the warbeast. This further decreased the chance of the Ouroboros Clan winning the battle. The enemies depended on the strength and ability of the warbeast, it was able to kill all Warlocks standing in its way.

“This won’t do. If this continues we might not even win against the enemy even if we use up all the energy within the Magus Towers…”

Faisal’s expression became gloomier as he snarled into his own secret imprint, “Activating Kemoyin Gargoyles, I need all of you to authorise me to activate it!”

“Agreed!” “Agreed!” “Agreed!” Immediately, Lucian and the rest could be heard as they brought out the runes specially designed for them.

“Two-thirds of the council has agreed, Kemoyin Gargoyles activated,” a robotic voice announced.

Following that, a large and powerful energy wave swept across the battlefield.

The numerous Magi and Warlocks were stunned. The large Kemoyin Gargoyles that were always standing in front of headquarters as if mere decorations opened their eyes, a ferocious glint revealing the huge amber gemstones within. Beams of light were emitted from those eyes, heating up everything in their line of sight.

The stone ‘skin’ on their bodies snapped off as if a huge jacket was being taken off. The statues grew rapidly, and within the blink of an eye had reached half the size of the warbeast.

“Hiss….” The Giant Kemoyin Serpents hissed as energy waves at the peak of rank 3 erupted from them.

“These two gargoyles that are peak rank 3 together have power equivalent to that of a Morning Star. Yet, this is not enough,” Faisal fumed, “Combine!”

*Buzz!* On top of the headquarters, the main defensive spell formation shook as it released a wave of energy, drowning the two heads of the giant snakes.

The two giant snakes hissed as they tangled with each other. A large layer of black light wrapped around their bodies, and when the creatures rose up as one, the body had reached the same standard as the warbeast.

*Rumble!* The Kyasha Beast was no longer relaxed, and its eyes showed caution as it stared at the enemy that was just as strong as it.

The huge two-headed snake in front hissed, and both heads spit out their scarlet tongues even as their amber eyes emitted rays of light.

“It’s just like the rumours say. The “Duo Serpent Annihilator” is a capable puppet that has the power of a Morning Star. Indeed, this is the last resort of the Ouroboros Clan.” Freya looked at the double-headed black snake from afar as she showed a complex expression.

This ultimate move was actually used on the first day of the battle. Did this mean that the reign of the Ouroboros Clan would end? Just like this?

Freya and the other high ranking Warlocks suddenly had an ominous premonition.

Despite facing an enemy that was far larger than itself, the Duo Serpent Annihilator took the initiative as it whipped its large tail at the Kyasha Beast.

*Thud!* The large warbeast that looked like a mountain range was actually swept off the ground by the snake’s tail.

*Rumble!* It was almost as if meteors were falling from the sky. The moment the huge body of the beast came into contact with the ground, it formed a depression and created a magnitude 8.0 earthquake.

The allied armies that were unable to run fast enough were eventually squashed under the huge body of the Kyasha Beast, resulting in chaos.

*Rumble* The warbeast that was stuck inside the hole roared, and a large amount of glittering light gathered on its horn.

*Hiss!* The Duo Serpent Annihilator fearlessly fought the warbeast as it wrapped its long body all over it, layer after layer.

Chapter 501: Timely Appearance

A wild blaze surged up as corrosive artillery shells created a blanket of lightning across the sky.

　　

The glows of numerous attacking spells revolved around the Ouroboros Clan headquarters, unfolding in layers continuously at the Phosphorescence Swamp.　

　　

In order to protect their organization and their homeland, the formidable Warlocks went all out against their equally-powerful opponents. The earth was stained with blood and bones.

　　

Outside headquarters, two behemoths roared ferociously in their entanglement. Every strike sent tremors through the land, as if forming an unending earthquake. This sort of remarkable battle was uncommon even in the central continent, and deserved to be recorded as a legendary one.

　

The intense confrontation had lasted a full day, yet not the creatures, nor the Magi nor the Warlocks showed traces of backing down. The Magi could bear the intensity of the battle, and the two giant creatures could do it even more easily.

　　

On the other hand, Faisal wore a displeased look from within the command room.

　

“The East Zone is 37% damaged, the city walls 55%. The energy consumed by the Duo Serpent Annihilator is too large, 67% of our combined storage is already depleted. We can’t keep going much longer…”

　　

How could there not be a price be paid for them to maintain a Morning Star realm combat strength?

　　

The Kyasha Beast depended on a frightening amount of food as sustenance. On the other hand, the Warlocks of the Ouroboros Clan could only use the stored energy from the multiple Magus Towers to power the Duo Serpent Annihilator.

　　

Faisal understood that a puppet would always remain a puppet. Once the energy supply was terminated, the Duo Serpent Annihilator would revert back to its original form.　　

　　

The remaining energy was insufficient for them to continue holding the fort.

　　

If this went on, with the exhaustion of their trump card, the Ouroboros Clan looked to be set for extermination… 　　

　　

“Mentor! Please come back as soon as you can!” It didn’t matter what Faisal thought previously. His pleas now were extremely sincere.

“For the Family! For the bloodline! For the glory of our Warlocks!”

　　

At the battlefield at the West Zone, Freya was covered in blood from head to toe, multiple cuts all across her body. Yet, she fought on through sheer force of will and obstinance, directly blocking the Demon Magus ahead of her.

　

“Admit your defeat! You no longer have the protection of your Morning Star Magi, you are destined to fall…”

　

The Demon Magus chief’ was out of breath, as he spoke sentimentally, ”There are few Magi who can sustain battle with me for over 30 hours…”　　

　　

“…” Looking around at the messy battlefield filled with corpses of bloodline Warlocks, Freya shut her eyes for a moment. When she opened them again, they glowed with ferocity.

　　

“I vow not to yield! The glory of the bloodline Warlocks cannot perish in my hands!” 　　

　　

“What a foolish decision!“ the chief chided, ”If it is so, I will not show any mercy!”　　

　　

As if a seal had been unlocked, the iron chain on his right hand cracked apart, snapping off and dropping down in segments. Dark black flames rose continuously from the arm, and Freya’s previous sense of danger had increased tenfold.

　　

“This Demon’s Arm is a precious treasure that I acquired after braving countless dangers…”

　　

A terrifying arm, completely coated with scales and tipped with sharp claws, was revealed as the chain broke. Compared to the transformation of the other members of the Demon Magus Army, the horror that this arm exuded was far more terrifying. This could be considered a true Demon’s Arm!

　　

“The Crystal Phase Magi that have fallen to this arm number seven. Today, you shall be the eighth!” The chief roared, swinging his arm towards the front. A frightening black blaze erupted, barricading the whole area like a cage.

　　

With the allied army winning, a loud humph sounded, audible to the entire region. A Magus appeared in the middle of the battlefield.

　　

With eyes of silver and brows as sharp as swords and a Magus robe, decorated with the images of tortured demons, draped over his body.

　　

Although he just stood silently in empty space, his presence generated a strong domain that had the whole Ouroboros Clan headquarters engulfed.

In but a moment, the chaos of the battlefield had died down, giving birth to a deathly silence.

　

Even the Kyasha Beast and Duo Serpent Annihilator had stopped in the middle of their intense battle. They felt a huge, imminent threat from this tiny human body.

　　

“It’s Demon Hunter Cyril! Why did he show himself in advance?” the red-haired female Magus asked in disbelief.

　　

“Cyril, it’s said that you’re a person who doesn’t bother with reputation!” the green haired Magus looked unimpressed, ”Seeing the positive circumstances on our side, you must have rushed here to forcibly take credit for it!”　　

　　

“He’s an exalted Morning Star Magus, why would he snatch anything from you?” The female Magus covered her mouth and sniggered.　　

　　

“Hehe… Cyril’s reputation amongst Morning Star Magi… You will find out soon enough…” the male Magus smiled bitterly. In the world of Morning Star Magi, everyone knew that Demon Hunter Cyril lacked all form of chivalry. He was overbearing and shameless, seizing the resources and treasures of lower-ranked Magi.

　　

“Are you not going to act anymore?”

　　

“Me? How can I interfere?” The male Magus spread out his hand and gestured, “Everyone clearly has made some deals with the Demon Hunter. In front of a Morning Star Magus, I am but a slightly bigger ant, no more than that…” 　　

　　

Thereafter, he laughed at himself and continued, ”No matter what, with the addition of the Demon Hunter, this battle will end soon.”

……

　　

On the battlefield, the Warlocks who had yet to reach the Hydro Phase were confined by the enormous pressure, and even moving seemed to be difficult.

　　

Even rank 3 Crystal Phase nobles were helpless as they realised that their ability to gather elemental particles had been halved. Even activating their spiritual force proved to be extremely difficult.

　

Under the effect of the domain of a Morning Star Magus, all lower-ranked Magi were like ants.

　

“It’s over! It’s all over!” Faisal slid to the ground, witnessing the ruthless massacre of the Warlocks. His expression turned deathly pale as he felt the life draining out from him.　　

　

With the support of the domain of the Demon Hunter, the allied military immediately stomped out many regions of defence, even as the last bit of the defensive barrier was destroyed.

　　

At the centre of it all, Cyril sneered in mid-air. A projection of huge sharp claws appeared and it reached out and attacked the source of energy at the city center. 　　

　　

*Po!* A colourful barrier appeared, blocking the sharp claws. Then, both the barrier and the claw in an instant before turning into ashes, disappearing into the emptiness.

　　

“A rather good item! Pity that it could only block one attack at the Morning Star realm!” Cyril laughed heartily, his body’s radiance growing brighter. Horrifying amounts of elemental particles coagulated once again, as if a tsunami had crashed into the bright barrier.

　　

The membrane cracked, and the energy source was extinguished!　　

　　

The huge defensive spell formation supporting the whole city had been under the attack of the army for an entire day. The combined Magus Towers, as well as the various spell formations, collapsed loudly.

　　

Like a screen of water being dispersed, the membrane disappeared, and the entirety of the Ouroboros Clan headquarters grew visible to the enemy.

　　

“No!” Two rolls of tears streaked down Lucian’s face as he cried out. An enormous carnivorous flower that was almost ten meters high devoured him completely.

　　

Even though he’d suppressed the other party with all his might, after being weakened by the Morning Star domain he could only await his death.

　　

“Is this it?” Freya’s jaws were clenched hard. She knew she wasn’t a match for her opponent. Under the attacks of the Demon’s Arm, she now cut an extremely sorry figure, collapsing on the ground after sustaining heavy injuries from the domain.

　　

Seeing the sharp claw advancing towards her and the cold, ruthless eyes of the Demon Magus who owned it, Freya was dazzled.

　

In the blink of an eye, time seemed to slow to a crawl. Her life flashed in front of her eyes as if she was reading a picture book, flipping page to page.

　　

In the end, her thoughts drifted to a young, black-robed Warlock. He smiled warmly at her, the passion in his eyes enough to sent the hearts of all female Warlocks fluttering. They would be attracted to him like a moth to the flame… Regardless of the danger of the blaze… Regardless, that attraction would end up fatal…

“Goodbye… Leylin…” A single sparkling tear slipped out of the corner of her eyes.

　　 …….

　　

The sharp, scaly claw with its dark flames and terrifying energy brought with an intensely violent wind as it aimed at her body.

The Demon Magus across her was very confident in his abilities. He could handle a Crystal Phase Magus that was armed to the teeth easily, forget a Warlock who was seriously injured and suppressed.

　　

He was even imagining the death of this female Warlock in front of him, the blood and internal organs spilling everywhere.

　

However, nothing was set in stone.

　　

Suddenly, The chief felt like his hand had been trapped in an iron hoop, rendering him unable to take another step forward.　　

　

He looked up and was stunned. A Warlock wearing a black Magus robe stood in front of him. He had long black hair, an extremely handsome face and had traces of a demonic charm on him that could attract the attentions of all female Warlocks　　

　　

He seemed to have appeared in a flash. His right hand gripped the Demon’s Arm, and the other radiated a black serpent-shaped airflow which held Freya in place.

　　

Freya’s shut eyes popped open, and she saw Leylin. Unable to contain herself, she blurted out, “Ley… Sir Leylin! Am I dreaming?”

　　

“No. You’re not dreaming. You’ve exhausted yourself. Take a rest while I handle everything else!” Leylin’s bright smile was soothing and it put Freya’s heart to rest. Drowsy, she fell asleep.

　

“Who are you?” The chief was shocked beyond words. For someone to be able to remain calm under the Morning Star domain and even cause the chief himself to be helpless, this person must not be easy to deal with.　　

　

Besides, he couldn’t even see through the opposing party’s energy. The feeling was as if…　

　　

The Demon Magus shook his head, forcing his mind to abandon such thoughts as he didn’t want to frighten himself. He was afraid he might lose all confidence, kneeling and asking for mercy if his train of thoughts was to develop further.

Chapter 503: Morning Star! Morning Star!

[Beep! Injected spiritual force reaching critical levels!]

With his sea of consciousness swelling up, and the reminder from the A.I Chip, Leylin realised that not only had his spiritual force reached the value of 399, even his sea of consciousness were filled with black—with a tinge of red in the centre—spiritual force crystals.

Inside his sea of consciousness, the three layers of the spiritual force core nucleus started to emit dazzling lights.

‘The results of the first time the bloodline ignition experiment is performed is the best, and they decrease over multiple uses.’ As he could still feel the strong surge of bloodline energy, Leylin ordered, “A.I. Chip, initiate the promotion to Morning Star!”

[Assignment received! Vital signs under observation, initiating Morning Star deduction, starting from the prototype of the point mass…]

Numerous amounts of data, both numeric and otherwise, relating to the construction of the point mass began streaming in front of Leylin’s eyes. If not for the Azure Mountain King’s clone, Leylin could never have gotten a hold of all this secret information about the Morning Star realm as easily.

“Lamia fingerbone!” Looking at the other bloodline treasure, he realised that it was actually his biggest gain from Quicksand Castle. If he were to use it then, he could have advanced immediately to the peak of Rank 3, skipping the Hydro and Crystal Phases.

Yet, Leylin was one who did not give in easily to temptations, forcing himself to control his impulses and merely using the radiation emitted by the fingerbone to slowly nurture his bloodline.

Even though the Lamia fingerbone could help him advance tremendously, but under comparison with the advancement to the Morning Star realm, he knew which one was more important. So what’s there left to think about?

*Peng!* The milky white fingerbone disintegrated into ashes, and one of the rays of lights that appeared during the explosion pointed directly towards Leylin’s forehead.

*Hong!* The Lamia fingerbone was absorbed into his body.

A terrifying change started to occur immediately. In Leylin’s sea of consciousness, under an enormous compressive power, numerous amounts of spiritual force crystals moved towards the centre.

His face paled under the enormous pressure exerted at the heart of his spiritual force. It was so bad that his whole body started twitching.

The sea of consciousness was essentially the home of the soul. The moment that it experienced any damage, the Magus would be in deep trouble.

Under the immense pressure that the spiritual force was experiencing, sounds could be heard coming from the centre of Leylin’s sea of consciousness. It wasn’t a good sign.

“Construct the fourth innate spell!” Leylin commanded with red eyes.

[Beginning assignment. Supplementary work initiated, transferring atomic microscope!]

the A.I Chip replied loyally.

Leylin’s sea of consciousness consisted of three layers presently. The outer layer held runes for two innate spells— one for Kemoyin’s Scales and the other for the Eye of Petrification. On the layer beneath was the rune for rank 2— Toxic Bile. The innermost layer held rank 3 spiritual force crystals, consisting of his rank 3 innate spell— Intimidating Gaze.

Under a sudden flash of red light, the three layers of runes perfectly combined, forming the exquisite image of a Warlock’s rune. Yet, it was missing one final thing.!

At this very moment, a fourth layer of crystals started to appear in the centre of the third layer.

As the centre of the core nucleus had a unique structure, the crystals became smaller as one went closer to the centre, but at the same time, the details on each rune became more intricate and they grew much more specialised.

At the centre of the fourth layer, even though it was a quarter the size of the first layer, it was still important that there be no errors when one was carving the rank 4 rune. That was an out-of-the-world request of a Magus’ spritiual force manipulation abilities.

“It’s no wonder that most Magi fail at advancing to rank 4. Even with the assistance provided by the A.I, Chip, this task seems to be too difficult …”

With the help provided by the A.I. Chip, Leylin who had already initiated the atomic microscope had started to carve down the Kemoyin’s Pupil innate spell on the fourth layer with the innate runes he’d recorded.

This was something every Warlock must choose and only in high-grade meditation techniques do innate spell models like these exist.

The attention to detail required to carve a rune in the sea of consciousness was much greater than carving a statue, and the act was much more difficult. Once Leylin completed the final stroke of the rune, his body almost collapsed due to exhaustion.

Under the immense pressure, it seemed like completing the fourth level rune properly was a big challenge. It took a while for Leylin’s consciousness to stabilize.

Once the innate spell had been completed, his entire sea of consciousness started to tremble.

Boundless rays of lights started to radiate from the centre of his sea of consciousness. The four layers of intricate runes started to bind together in a picturesque order, much like a piece of artwork.

Once the centremost part was filled up, the entire crystal started to shake violently, strengthening tremendously within seconds and the immense pressure that was present previously had disappeared.

“This rune?” Leylin observed the rune that was a combination of all his innate runes. It represented all of his achievements so far, and hence he commanded the A.I. Chip to record it down.

Perfection! The first impression this rune would leave on a person was that of perfection!

A gigantic rune was created by the combination of these small runes, which cirulated continuously and looked pretty much 3D. Regardless of how one looked at it, it was flawless.

“Is this… the path of my bloodline?” Leylin mumbled. At this very moment, he was almost moved to tears.

*Rustle!* Once the four layers perfectly crystallized, they started to crumble inwards, shrinking to a point that rapidly started revolving. Much like a black hole, it started to suck in everything in its surroundings.

The spiritual force crystals inside his sea of consciousness started to shrink as they got sucked into the black hole.

[Initiating the construction of point mass. Guidelines activated.]

the A.I. Chip reported.

Leylin, too, started to construct his personal point mass according to his understanding and the information from his A.I. Chip.

*Boom!* An immense suction force could be felt coming from the mass point of the spiritual force. Not only were the spiritual force crystals sucked in, even the sea of consciousness was broken through and more energy, flesh and soul aura were pulled in.

*Slap!* Leylin’s consciousness suddenly blurred. Time seemed to pass extremely slowly, and at times it felt like eternity was squeezed into an instant.

It took the sounds of glass shattering for Leylin to wake up again.

This time, his sea of consciousness felt empty. There was a dim light shining at the centre of the core, the result of shrinking the spiritual force a million times over such that the nucelus core’s density and purity had reached an remarkable level. This was the point mass of a Morning Star Magus!

The source of the light shook, and the purified energy of the Morning Star realm, the energy of the point mass that was also known as soul force, started to leak out into the entirety of Leylin’s body.

At that point, he had entered the Morning Star realm!

[Beep! Host’s Kemoyin’s Pupil meditation technique has advanced to the fourth level. Host has advanced to rank 4!]

The A.I. Chip sounded out.

[Host’s spiritual force has undergone a qualitative change. Data is inaccurate, recalculating…]

It was a long time for the new data to go up.

[Leylin Farlier, rank 4 Warlock Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent (complete form) Strength: 50, Agility: 45, Vitality: 65, Spiritual Force: 503.7, Magic Power: 503 (magic power in synchronisation with spiritual force) Soul Force: ???] [Due to a lack of information about soul force, it is currently not possible to calculate stats.]

Looking at the A.I. Chip’s report, Leylin touched his chin and went into deep thought.

After advancing to the Morning Star realm, the original spiritual force would undergo purification and turn into soul force. This energy was on a whole new level compared to spiritual force! Yet, as the information and data that the A.I. Chip had on soul force was limited, there was too little knowledge in the database to display a value. It could only display numbers in terms of spiritual force.

He had to wait until the A.I Chip had collected sufficient data to thoroughly calculate his soul force statistics.

“The boundary of the Morning Star realm is 500?” Leylin felt the terror of having such strong energy and sighed, “This is nearly a hundred higher than a rank 3’s spiritual force value. It is no wonder rank 3 and rank 4 are worlds apart.

“Soul force!” Something came into Leylin mind and a gloomy light appeared above his palm. This was the mutated spiritual force from the point mass, it is also an energy of a greater level.

All Magi at the Morning Star realm and above used soul force. It was only when one reached this stage that they could find their own path in life.

“This is why in ancient times, Magi below rank 4 weren’t even deemed to have entered the world of Magi yet.”

There was a huge difference between rank 3 and rank 4, and the same was true between ranks 6 and 7. Leylin had no idea about what happened one reached rank 7, but after advancing he now clearly knew the differences between ranks 3 and 4.

“Magi at rank 3 and below mainly use spiritual force. However, once that is crossed, the Morning Star, Radiant Moon and Breaking Dawn Magi will have to come in contact with the soul force and pay extra attention to explore the potential in their soul”

Leylin couldn’t help but look at his own point mass. In the heart of his sea of consciousness, that small glow of light continued to spin around, forming a nebular spiral that pulled many of the energy particles around within, only to regurgitate them upon purification.

From this point forth, his spirit had been concentrated into the point mass, creating a truesoul. At the same time, due to the protection from the point mass, his resistance toward the previous spiritual force and soul attacks were largely maximised.

The point mass, with its extreme density, was the last defence of Leylin’s truesoul.

“My truesoul…” Leylin subconsciously remembered the last moment before he advanced.

In that instant, it seemed as though he saw the life and death of the universe, and also the rise and fall of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent clan. It was also at that very moment that his soul truly bonded with his bloodline to form one body, making him a true Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock!

Chapter 505: Great War of the Morning Stars

‘Although the data paints a similar picture, the magnificent beauty of the edge of the world can’t ever be fully described by mere words and pictures…’

Leylin sighed faintly. Currently, he was in a mysterious space surrounded by darkness. Multiple silver rays of lights streaked across among the stars, and it was like the universe in his previous life, boundless and magnificent.

Cyril sat opposite him with gloom clouding his face. Subtle chaotic flows of turbulence struck him, but were rebounded by the layer of soul force on his body, unable to cause even the slightest of injuries.

All Morning Star Magi possessed the ability to survive in the crevices of space. They relied on it to pass through the different worlds.

Of course, it also depended on the grade of the crevices.

The one that Leylin chose was situated at the edge of the world. The space there was comparatively stable, and the slight spatial turbulence could easily be held off by one’s soul force.

If, by any chance, the space encountered violent turbulence similar to that caused by ancient battles, or due to the wild and violent storms occurring within the crevices of two worlds, leave alone Morning Star Magi, even Radiant Moon Magi were likely to succumb to the force, leaving just ashes. The Scorpion Man from the Icy World had met his death in that exact same manner.

Clashes between Morning Star Magi caused extensive damage. A battle between two could destroy the entire continent. As such, if any Morning Star Magi desired to take revenge, they would choose to settle scores inside these spatial crevices instead.

No matter how extensive the damage was, it would not affect the stability of the world.

The venue of the big battle this time was the Ouroboros Clan headquarters at Phosphorescence Swamp. If their clash had occurred there, regardless of the outcome Freya, Parker, and the rest would certainly meet death. In fact, the entire Ouroboros Swamp could cease to exist.

Leylin definitely would not want that to happen. Hence, he voluntarily dragged the opposite party here.

“You’re good!” Cyril raised his eyebrows in rage, traces of blue current circulating between them.

He felt insulted at being outschemed by a junior. Even though he didn’t want to be criticised by the other Morning Star Magi for starting a battle in the main world, he felt he was entitled to choose another location as the battleground instead of being forced here by the opposite party.

“Cyril! This and he matter at the Forgotten Land, let’s settle everything today!” Leylin’s voice was soft yet strangely firm. He had not let go of his grudge from when he’d almost been killed in a single blow and was forced to take refuge in the main headquarters for over a century.

He’d shelved the idea of revenge then due to lacking power, but now the time had come.

“How dare you bring up the past?!” Cyril fumed as he recounted the interference of these fellows who took away a portion of the gains. If not for them, the natural resources at the Forgotten Land and the Quicksand Organization would have all been his.

He had also been suppressed by the three Morning Star Warlocks and been left with no possible means of escape.

“You have to account for your teacher’s sins too!” Cyril’s silver pupils shone with a sharp icy chill. A long black pike appeared in his hand.

Faint, yet audible demonic cries were sounding out from its tip, chilling to the bone.

“You’re a brat who just advanced to rank 4, just how much do you understand about the abilities of the Morning Star realm? Prepare to accept your fate of failure!”

Cyril’s growl was steely, ”Rank 4 spell— Demon’s Wail!”

He tossed out the pike from his hand. *Boom!* The horrific scene was like history repeating itself, when the legendary giant Argyle threw the ahlspiess that destroyed the sun and killed the Sun’s child!

Violent waves of torrential power descended, and the black pike transformed itself into a ray of black lightning, streaking through the turbulent space before arriving at Leylin.

Powered by a Morning Star Magus’ soul force, the results of the spell were earth-shattering!

“Demon Hunter Cyril, you are indeed worthy of your name!” Leylin gasped in admiration, ”Unfortunately, I too am not as weak as you think!”

He had prepared to advance to rank 4 for a long time. During this period, he had managed to acquire some badly damaged rank 4 spell models. With the A.I. Chip’s simulations, he had managed to repair the content, and skillfully grasp them.

Besides, the numerous memories he’d inherited from his bloodline also net him a battle experience that was even marginally better than Cyril’s!

The phantom of a Giant Kemoyin Serpent, with large amber eyes, smooth scales, and ferocious razor-sharp teeth hissed from behind Leylin.

“Complying with the ancient contract, I call upon the power of the bloodline, serve me now and transform into a resolute shield…” Leylin spoke with a delicate yet intense tone, similar to the hissing of a giant snake, as he chanted awkward-sounding ancient incantations.

With every syllable distinct and audible, Leylin chanted the incantations before the pike arrived, completing the spell’s preparations and causing everyone an eerie sensation of time disorder.

“Bloodline Shield!”

As if an existence from ancient times, a black-scaled shield that had ferocious Giant Kemoyin Serpent images portrayed on it appeared out of empty space. Crimson lightning still bounced across its surface.

*Bang!*

Like a clash between the sun and the moon, or the impact of a star hitting the earth, the long devilish spike that had transformed into black lightning suddenly bombarded the shield. Blood red and coal black tangled, and the explosive aftermath was horrifying.

A huge spatial turbulence resembling the gushing of a tsunami struck from both sides. If it were the main world, one single wave could have left the entire Ouroboros Clan completely destroyed.

“No– No way!” Cyril yelled hoarsely from afar. From the connection with his soul force, he clearly witnessed the crimson point on his pike fade to its original dull colour. The Giant Kemoyin Serpent on the shield seemed to have come to life as it opened its mouth and ruthlessly chomped the tip off the pike!

The black pike cracked, and violently blew up.

Space itself rumbled as the turbulence started wreaking havoc. It created enormous sharp rifts that even Leylin and Cyril had to avoid temporarily.

“Shield Strike!” The huge shield collapsed like a mountain, taking aim at Cyril. With Leylin following closely behind, the attack was incomparably fierce.

“No way! No way! No way!” Cutting a sorry figure, a defensive Cyril yelled despondently, ”You’re a newly promoted Warlock. Why…”

He was clearly agonising over his situation. Leylin was not like a newly promoted Morning Star at all, being extremely familiar with battling in spatial rifts. His ability to handle difficulties even exceeded that of Gilbert and the rest!

‘It looks like my inherited bloodline is indeed rare!’ Assessing his expression, Leylin understood his display of abilities had been too outstanding, even exceeding that of the three dukes.

“The exceptional purity of my own bloodline must have meant that the bloodline inheritance I received is more complete. As for Mentor Gilbert and the rest, what they’d received was much weaker…”

The inherited memories of a creature were always stored in its bloodline. Thus, if the descendant’s blood was pure, the arousal of the inherited memories would be greater, and the inheritance itself would be richer, resulting in more benefits.

With the A.I. Chip having purified his bloodline and the Lamia fingerbone’s supplementation, Leylin could potentially be the best of the Kemoyin Warlocks!

Suddenly, Leylin was clear about his fate and he had no intentions to be lax about it.

*Crackle!* Multiple black scales appeared on his right hand, morphing into a sharp blade.

The runes of the rank 4 Kemoyin Scales were even more simplistic and reflected only a minimal amount of light but still carried a uniquely daunting aura.

*Swoosh!* A layer of menacing black light surfaced on the blade, and Leylin mercilessly cut across Cyril’s chest.

The soul force from both sides came into contact. With Leylin’s formidable strength and the razor-sharp blade, he successfully broke through Cyril’s innate defence. The knife-like blade left a huge wound across his chest, and blood splashed everywhere. It left a hole so large even the organs could be seen within.

“How… how can it be?” Cyril attempted to cover his chest while stumbling backwards, disbelief in his eyes.

“How can I lose? And to a newly promoted junior?” Cyril yelled fiercely, his face distorting with anger. The poise he previously possessed evaporated, and the fury tinged his silver eyes blood red.

“No! I have not lost! I have my last trump card!” Cyril suddenly looked up, his body filled with an extremely dangerous aura. ”Leylin Farlier! Today I will show you what it means to be a true rank 4 Morning Star Magus!”

The halo of an innate spell appeared from his body before brightening.

“Rank 1 innate spell— Anarchic Forcefield!”

This was followed by the halo of his rank 2 spell…

By the end, Cyril’s aura had risen to the maximum, and four unstable rings revolved around his body.

This was the Morning Star Arcane Art! Forced to the edge by Leylin, Cyril he’d ended up brazenly using his final trump card!

“The Morning Star’s final technique…” The corner of Leylin’s mouth curved up in a smile. His old memories of witnessing one being performed had been refreshed, and it came to life.

“I have one too!” Restraining his smile, the brilliant red glow on Leylin’s body started twinkling.

“First, the rank 1 innate spells— Kemoyin’s Scales! Petrifying Gaze!” A fine layer of black scales covered Leylin’s body entirely, and his pupils glowed amber.

“Next up, the rank 2 innate spell— Toxic Bile!” A poison from the ancient times surfaced, swiftly surrounding him.

“Then the rank 3 spell— Intimidating Gaze!” After his promotion to rank 4, the dignified aura exuded by Leylin’s body had grown even more terrifying. His body had rightfully regained the power and influence of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent itself. He now radiated the aura of an ancient first-rate predator.

“Finally, the rank 4 innate spell— Bloodline Metamorphosis! Combining to form the ancient Morning Star Arcane Art— Kemoyin Serpent Transformation!”

The point mass in Leylin’s sea of consciousness started rotating violently, with his and his soul force spurred him on. The four innate spells synchronised with each other, with an amplification that caused a horrifying change.

Chapter 509: Celebration

Based on the traditions of the central continent, high-grade meditation techniques had a minimum of four levels, allowing Magi to enter the Morning Star realm. Top-grade meditation techniques needed to have six or more levels, allowing Magi to understand the path to the Breaking Dawn.

Kemoyin’s Pupil had merely four levels and was considered the bottom of the pack among high-grade meditation techniques. Leylin naturally hoped the A.I. Chip could simulate the rest of the levels.

Leylin had been trying to solve the issue of the bloodline shackles since advancing to the Morning Star realm.

The simulation of meditation techniques was very important. The Wing of the Sun was also a meditation technique for bloodline Warlocks, and there were six complete levels. It would surely be extremely helpful in completing Kemoyin’s Pupil.

Since he had the bloodline of the Sun’s child as well, he could attempt to purify it. Though the Oakheart Clan had already confirmed that the bloodline had lost all vitality, Leylin still had some confidence that he could restore it.

The ancient Sun’s child was a being that could reach rank 6 when it matured. It was even a fixed sun for multiple small worlds, and was, therefore, the best bloodline Leylin had gotten to date.

“With this, I can begin the bloodline experiments…” After advancing to the Morning Star realm, many ancient bloodline experiments, and things like the interplanar experiments, could be undertaken independently. Leylin was extremely eager to spend all his time on this.

However, he still took some time to meet the emissaries from Spirit Circle and Wind Wolf Lair the next day.

It wasn’t only the Ouroboros Clan that held bloodline Warlocks in the central continent. There were other organisations and families that had inherited ancient bloodlines, forming a giant alliance.

However, the three Morning Star Magi of the Ouroboros Clan had disappeared all of a sudden, resulting in a drop in their value. Hence, no aid had been given.

Leylin understood this very well, since even when saving allies, one had to see if they were powerful enough. Otherwise, they would only be bringing trouble upon themselves.

Besides, the various Warlock organisations weren’t exactly tight-knit. There were conflicts, and a loose alliance was basically as good as a nonexistent one.

Of course, things were different with Leylin’s ascension. It was especially so after he displayed his strength. All these former allies rushed forth to mend their relationship.

Spirit Circle and Wind Wolf Lair were the two largest bloodline Warlock organisations that the Ouroboros Clan was close to.

“Hehe… Sire Leylin is so young. This was entirely out of my expectations!” The moment they met, the two Warlocks were blown away by the plentiful life force brimming in Leylin.

Magi obviously did not rely on appearances to determine age. They usually had their own unique methods to determine it.

However, no matter which angle they looked at him from, Leylin was extremely young. He was not like those Magi who were approaching their end and looked young from the outside, yet held a rotting scent.

“Hehe… The two of you, please!”

Leylin was now dressed in a platinum robe that was a piece of magic equipment, giving him a more elegant aura. With his experience in controlling places like the Twilight Zone, he had already developed a distinct aura of a ruler in how he treated others, which made him all the more convincing.

Meanwhile, while the two emissaries were stunned at Leylin’s age, Leylin himself was also shocked.

He could feel the energy of the point mass on these two emissaries. In other words, they were actually Morning Star Warlocks as well!

“Looks like these two organisations are taking this very seriously!”

The smile on Leylin’s face became even more welcoming as he invited the two Warlocks to the couch in his room. Freya brought three cups of coffee over, bowing to the three of them unreservedly as she quickly left.

“By the way, I’ve yet to ask you for your names!” Leylin smiled as he spoke.

“Oh, look at me! I was so surprised when I came that I didn’t introduce myself. How impolite of me!” A Magus with countless tentacles on his face that looked like a giant octopus head palmed his forehead with a tentacle and answered, “I’m Paul, from Spirit Circle!”

“Sir Paul!” Leylin nodded in recognition, seeming serious.

The bloodline Spirit Circle had inherited came from a strange creature— the Spirit-sucking Oddity! It was said that this being not only had a unique spirit body, it even enjoyed sucking the brain juices of intelligent beings, and had the strange ability of peeking at someone’s spirit.

What caused countless bloodline Warlocks to rip their hair out in frustration was that this Spirit-sucking Oddity was no bloodline creature! However, the original Spirit-sucking Oddity Warlock had fused the ability of this creature into his own bloodline and passed it down, resulting in this strange branch of bloodline Warlocks.

This branch was named the ‘Spirit Warlock’ and had a very special strength. They were more partial towards attacks on the mind, and it was difficult to resist them.

At this point, Leylin couldn’t help but look into his eyes.

On the giant octopus head were a pair of dark eyeballs with no pupils, looking like a dead fish’s eyes.

However, the moment their gazes met, Leylin felt as if his heart was being stripped and laid bare before him.

*Weng!* The point mass in his body rumbled, and soul force swept through. The discomfort instantly vanished, and Leylin immediately put on his guard even though he smiled at the other party.

“I am Philip of the Wind Wolf Lair. Greetings, Sir!” The other was a middle-aged, burly white man. His face and body were filled with hair, and his sideburns were very straight.

Compared to spirit Warlocks, Wind Wolf Lair was an orthodox bloodline Warlock organisation that had inherited the bloodline of the ancient Wind Wolves. They were exceptionally sensitive towards wind elemental particles.

On top of that, Wind Wolf Lair was a very well-known bloodline Warlock organisation in the central continent that maintained good relations with other Warlocks. They had very deep roots.

“Sir Philip, and Sir Paul!” Leylin nodded, “It is my honour for the two of you to attend my ceremony…”

Whether it was Leylin or the other two Warlocks, all of them were very satisfied. Though there weren’t any deep discussions, this was a good beginning.

After that, however, Leylin could not bring himself to feel happy, as the two Warlocks brought him shocking news.

“Jupiter’s Lightning?”

After unexpectedly finding out who was responsible for attacking the Ouroboros Clan, Leylin’s expression turned grim.

Even if he hadn’t been privy to the knowledge among the Morning Star circle before his own advancement, even he had heard of this organisation’s fame in the central continent.

Compared to organisations such as Nefas and Azure Mountain City, Jupiter’s Lightning was even more tremendous, and perhaps even surpassed the Ouroboros Clan.

It was a shadow that loomed over the continent, and was perhaps more similar to a bandit guild. It regularly took on assassinations, bounties, and the like, preferring to stir up chaos and exploiting it.

The reason why they were so fearless was due to the manipulator behind them. It was a Radiant Moon Magus!

A Radiant Moon Magus was also a great rank 5 Magus, and they were even rarer than Morning Star Magi, as well as much more formidable. In the entire central continent, there were probably less than twenty of them. It could be said that besides the few Breaking Dawn Magi there were, the rest of them split the central continent amongst themselves.

Hearing that Ouroboros Clan was being targeted by such a person, even Leylin couldn’t help but break out in cold sweat.

Paul and Philip exchanged a glance and, noticing Leylin’s peaceful expression, nodded.

“Don’t worry. As allies, we will provide a certain amount of assistance, such that at least the Radiant Moon Magus will likely not deal with you personally…”

‘Do you mean that if the other Morning Star Magi of Jupiter’s Lightning attack, I have to take them all on myself?’

Leylin rolled his eyes inside, but his expression was that of gratitude, “Thank you so much.”

In reality, he had serious suspicions that these two organisations wanted them to fight. Perhaps they had been the ones to provoke Jupiter’s Lightning, and yet were now pretending to take the brunt of the damage for the Ouroboros Clan, and were insincere about sending aid.

Of course, he was no child and would not believe everything these Morning Star Magi told him. He would only trust them after performing his own checks.

This was a very simple matter. Though he was unfamiliar with the Morning Star’s conscient, he had already recorded the aura fluctuations. With more Morning Star samples, he would be able to make comparisons.

He even had a spy like the Azure Mountain King, so information was not an issue.

At the thought of the Azure Mountain King, Leylin’s gloomy mood was lifted, and he began to anticipate ascension ceremony.

……

*Boom! Boom! Boom!*

Countless giant fireworks exploded in mid-air. The headquarters of Ouroboros Clan had been painted over, and now no longer had any traces from the battle. There were even fresh flowers and streamers along all the pathways.

The guests from the other organisations in the central continent all had sincere grins on their faces. Under the guidance of the Warlocks of Ouroboros Clan, they headed towards the heart of the city.

This was a palace that had been constructed in a hurry for Leylin, the location of the ceremony.

In order to curry favour with the only Morning Star Warlock in the organisation, as well as the husband of their family’s leader, the Blood Serpent Family Warlocks had done all they could and arranged everything tidily. They had even gone out of their way and brought out lavish liquor and delicacies, many of which were unique resources in the Magus World that could increase spiritual force and the effects of meditation. There were so many that they seemed dirt cheap, and it resulted in looks of admiration and surprise.

Many guests were gathered in a hall, though they were separated clearly into tens of little circles.

Bloodline Warlocks and Magi had two large circles, and within those, another ten or so were formed based on various factors like power, ranking, level of intimacy and so on.

The Warlocks and Magi were like the ladies and gentlemen of high society, conversing courteously and occasionally toasting each other. The atmosphere was harmonious, and it was unthinkable that some of the people here had been eager for the death of the other party just a few days ago.

Chapter 511: Attitude

After some haggling, Leylin and Zack finally reached an agreement.

　　

The Oakheart Clan would bear the burden of building a Morning Star level Magus Tower, as well as provide him with all the resources for an astral gate. In return, Leylin guaranteed that he would never divulge information regarding the stardust bugs in any shape or form.

　

The two of them had even made an oath under the Trial’s Eye, which was at the request of the Azure Mountain King. However, he did not notice the look of mockery in Leylin’s eyes.　　

　　

After that, Leylin got Zack to narrate the details of the allied army’s attack on the Ouroboros Clan from start to end.

　　

After receiving this information, his eyebrows furrowed.　　

　　

“Jupiter’s Lightning…” After sending Zack away, Leylin half laid down on the couch, massaging his forehead and sinking into deep thought.　　

　　

“I never expected it to be them. Why would a haughty Radiant Moon Magus have any interest in the Ouroboros Clan?”

　

Before Gilbert and the others reappeared, nobody would be able to give him an answer. Leylin himself could only make wild guesses.　　

……　　

　

Most emissaries had yet to leave after the end of the ceremony, when another monumental event occurred.

　　

The Morning Star Warlock, Duke Leylin, had announced his engagement with the leader of the Blood Serpent Family, Freya!　　

　　

Bloodline Warlocks were generally very picky when it came to picking partners. This would affect the passing on of bloodlines, and determined the rise or fall of a family.　　

　　

The engagement of a Morning Star Warlock implied that new Kemoyin blood would spread, forming another formidable family!　　

　　

Though there were only two people in the family, Leylin and his fiancee, nobody could deny the strength of a family with a Morning Star Warlock within.　　

　　

Based on some faint rumours, Duke Leylin’s bloodline was unbelievably pure, and perhaps even surpassed that of the other three Morning Star Warlocks! His fiancee was also of a prestigious Kemoyin Family, and her bloodline was pure.　　

　　

The emissaries and Warlocks could envision an exceptionally powerful Kemoyin family rising to power in the Ouroboros Clan.

　　

Though they were cursing within, these emissaries all looked elated at Leylin’s engagement, and gave their ‘sincere’ blessings to them.　　

　　

Only after the engagement ceremony was over did the emissaries of the multiple organisations leave Phosphorescence Swamp. They had seen far too much at this celebration and ceremony, and needed to report back to their masters.

　

Leylin could finally relax, handling some miscellaneous work.　　

　　

“Your Grace!” On the way, many Warlocks stepped aside when they saw him from afar, bowing to him from the sides of the road.　　

　　

Leylin’s expression remained solemn. At most, he sent a nod of recognition in the direction of high-ranked Warlocks, his movements revealing boundless dignity.

　　

His status in the Ouroboros Clan made it such that he could move without obstructions. He headed for a building that seemed like a beehive, formed of countless giant laboratories.　　

　　

This was the headquarters of the technical department. Upon noticing Leylin’s arrival, there was a flurry of activity at the entrance. Schadt, who was wearing glasses, was escorted by Warlocks donning large white gowns as he welcomed Leylin. It made him feel as if he had returned to the research centres in his previous world.

　

“Your Grace!” Schadt bowed respectfully. He was extremely grateful towards Leylin. If not for his advancement, the Ouroboros Clan would probably have been done for.　　

　　

“Mm! Bring me to the astral gate!” Leylin said indifferently after a nod. He then followed Schadt as they went in deeper.　　

　

After passing through the layers of isolation and detection spell formations, Schadt brought Leylin before a gate formed entirely of astral stones.　　

　

The entire gate emanated a starry radiance. The innermost layer actually possessed a stony surface and there were multiple bright runes, floating above the surface of the stone gate.　　

　　

“This is Lord Emma’s astral gate. We’ve moved it here…” Schadt sighed as he took off his glasses.

“We’ve determined through multiple experiments that there is no problem with the gate itself. However, there was an unknown interference that stopped us from locating the coordinates, making the second attempt at finding the coordinates even more difficult!

　　

“What level of power do you think is needed for this to happen?” Leylin’s eyes shone as he asked.

　　

“I’m afraid…” Schadt’s temperament suited research perfectly. He explained things as they were and did not beat around the bush, “Only interference from a Radiant Moon realm Magus can cause the three elders to make an error in judgment!”

　　

Radiant Moon realm! A great rank 5 Magus! The moment the words exited Schadt’s mouth, the rest of the researchers all trembled, evidently feeling weak.　　

　　

Just a Morning Star Magus was enough for the Ouroboros Clan to be on the verge of being destroyed by the allied forces. What if a Radiant Moon Magus were to do the job himself?　　

　　

The bleak future immediately caused these high-ranked Warlocks to tremble in fear.　　

　　

“Don’t be so negative!” Leylin patted Schadt on the shoulder, “Just focus on saving Mentor and the others. You must work hard on this…”　　

　　

“Understood, Your Grace!” A hint of shame appeared on Schadt’s expression as he lowered his head deferentially.　　

　　

Initially, he had boldly bragged that he could find the coordinates within five days. However, multiples of that time period had passed, and he had yet to determine which world Gilbert and the others were trapped in.　

　

Every time he was about to find the coordinates, he would be obstructed by berserk spatial turbulence, barring him from finding the real location.

　　

If there was the slightest discrepancy in the coordinates, the two areas could be millions of kilometres away from each other, being two separate worlds!

　　

With trouble both internally and externally, the Warlocks would definitely not dare have Leylin take the risk.　　

　　

On top of that, they had no clue if Leylin would listen to them.　　

　　

In actuality, even if they had determined which world Gilbert and the rest were lost in, Leylin might not aid them.

　　

Since they had already determined the other world was a trap set up by a Radiant Moon Magus, how could he go in like a lamb to the slaughter?

　　

Leylin was not so selfless as to take this risk.　　

　

“I should find a chance and take care of those Warlocks.” Leylin touched his chin, eyes glimmering with a dangerous light.　　

　　

Those who had been urging him from the shadows to save the elders were not anyone else, but the many descendants and students of the three Morning Star Warlocks. Of course, they did not dare request anything of Leylin in the open, but as long as they was no evidence, they were bold in their discussions.

　　

In Gilbert’s case, Leylin was one of them and they thus had the least complaints. With Emma, Freya was a mediator and they were less impatient. Only the students and family of the other Morning Star Warlock pressed him on, and Leylin was preparing to make use of them.　　

　　

He was no saint, and would not save others and then give up his power to be shared. And yet, Gilbert was his Mentor and had taught him much. Thus he would save him, but now was not the time!

　　

Leylin was confident that with a bit more time, he could set up his own authority and spread his influence. By the time the three Morning Stars were back, they would not be able to affect his status!

　　

Hence, he had to make use of this time. Though he could use his strength and force everything, Leylin did not want to end up with an Ouroboros Clan that was divided.

　　

Schadt’s report was exactly to his liking. This way, it was not because he was not trying hard enough, but that he was lacking information and had no way to do this.　　

　　

Leylin had long since secretly determined their coordinates. But for his own purposes, he had kept mum until now.

　

After consoling Schadt and the other members of the technical department, Leylin returned to his castle. There, two precious guests needed to be attended to.　　

　　

“Lord Paul, Lord Philip, sorry for the long wait!”　　

　　

Leylin apologised to the two Morning Star Warlocks. After the other organisations had left, these two emissaries had stayed behind for some unknown reason. As they were Morning Stars, this was also good for Ouroboros Clan, which was why Leylin had no complaints and was so welcoming towards them.

　　

“We only just arrived as well. Duke Leylin must have investigated thoroughly, right?” Paul grinned, the beady eyes on the octopus head seemingly able to see into the Leylin’s soul.　　

　

“Yes, Jupiter’s Lightning! They went too far!” Leylin clenched his fists, face flushing red and showing his anger.

　　

Through the investigation of the Shadow Snake department as well as the Azure Mountain King’s story, he had confirmed that Jupiter’s Lightning was behind this.　　

　　

In this case, he would not reject the good intentions of these two Morning Star Warlocks.

　　

“I’m going to be frank with you. That Radiant Moon Magus of Jupiter’s Lightning has been finding us bloodline Warlocks an eyesore and caused conflicts with the union. Even the organisations backing us are in a cold war with them…” Philip said. The burly werewolf smiled wryly.　　

　　

Leylin vaguely understood their meaning. The intentions of these Spirit Circle and Wind Wolf Lair Warlocks was to seek external aid.

　　

However, he would definitely not reject them. Radiant Moon Magi were not existences he could deal with as of yet. If he could pull someone else over to contend against them, the pressure on him would be slightly lesser.

　　

For this reason, Leylin did not seem to even hesitate as he exclaimed, “If there’s anything you need me for, just say the word!”

　　

While that was what he had said, Leylin would not be so stupid as to rush to the frontlines without any benefits.　　

　　

Paul and Philip exchanged a glance and saw the elation in each other’s eyes. No matter what it was, Leylin’s attitude meant that this trip had not been made in vain.

Chapter 512: Revitalisation of Bloodline

“Of course, we hope you can form an alliance with us. We wish to take on Jupiter’s Lightning together…”

Philip interrupted, “With your current status as Duke, you can definitely represent the Ouroboros Clan!”

“This… I need to think it over… After all, there are many seniors who I need to pacify…” When it came to proper business, Leylin seemed to draw back.

Paul silently cursed at Philip for being too hasty, and also Leylin, for not being willing to be more open until he saw benefits. He merely continued smiling, which was difficult enough with his octopus face.

“Duke Leylin, you don’t know this yet, do you? We Morning Star Warlocks organise a gathering every once in a while, where everyone will exchange information. Sometimes, we even have trade meetings…”

“This gathering is only for bloodline Warlocks, who must be at least at the Morning Star level. Someone even needs to vouch for them. A few elders from Spirit Circle and Wind Wolf Lair will attend as well. How about we continue the discussion there?”

“Gathering?!” A gathering amongst Morning Star Warlocks was still very attractive to Leylin.

Furthermore, he was not worried that their leaving the Ouroboros Clan would bring any harm to them.

To be frank, the Ouroboros Clan’s safety all depended on him. As long as he was fine, it would be well fortified even if there was nobody here guarding them. If anything happened to him, the allied armies would immediately level the place.

In fact, if he managed to slip out of headquarters without being seen, it would put his foes under a lot of pressure instead.

With this in mind, Leylin answered, “Sure. When the time comes, please notify me!”

Seeing Leylin agree, Paul heaved a long sigh of relief before he laughed in answer, “I’m sure that our other comrades are eager to see an up-and-coming youngster like you!”

It looked like this gathering was a small circle where bloodline Warlocks interacted.

Watching his expression, Leylin nodded inside and began to anticipate the gathering more fervently.

Since everything was settled, Paul and Philip had no reason to stay longer. They chose to leave.

With how hurried they seemed, Spirit Circle and Wind Wolf Lair had probably fallen on hard times. As important deterrents, they would not have been able to squeeze out the time to attend if not for Leylin’s ceremony.

“We’re rich, my Lord!” Within the hall, Parker’s eyes glinted as he gazed at the account book in his hands, “Just the gifts from the other organisations is equivalent to dozens of fiefs…”

“But of course. You only ascend to the Morning Star realm once. And it’s a good time for other organisations to form good relationships with them…”

Though Leylin seemed as calm as an ancient, unused well, he was actually very happy; he just kept it in. At the same time, he had gained a better understanding of the great status Morning Star Magi held in the central continent.

The destructive power of a Morning Star Arcane Art was far too high. If a Morning Star Magus were to let go of all qualms and act as they wished, the geography of the entire central continent would be destroyed. Radiant Moon, and even Breaking Dawn Magi would regret the damage caused.

As a result, every time a Morning Star arose, everyone would express their goodwill, and intent to be on good terms with each other. These were actions that large organisations were used to.

“The moment I stepped into this realm, everything changed…”

Leylin sighed to himself, the look in his eyes even more intense. “What would be the scenery be like after the ranks of Radiant Moon or the Breaking Dawn throne?”

In his eyes, rank 4 was far from the limit. His goals were on higher peaks, and he did not pay attention to even the shackles to his bloodline that had troubled bloodline Warlocks for many years.

Of course, he could overlook his opinions while strategizing, but tactics needed to be done properly. Hence, he sent Parker away and ordered for all his gifts to be stored. After handing over the important items, Leylin returned to his laboratory.

He was now the highest power in the Ouroboros Clan, and could mobilise all resources. The laboratory he used was the best they had, which was usually reserved for Gilbert and the other two. This was just another one of the many advantages.

That was not all. The treasury of the Ouroboros Clan was completely open to him, and the treasures accumulated over thousands of years by a large-scaled organisation such at this had Leylin’s eyes going green in envy.

The first thing he did was to take a pile of astral stones and keep them in his spatial pouch.

Though the Oakheart Clan had agreed to build him an astral gate, it was better to have more astral stones in reserve. After all, passing through planes required the usage of astral stones, which was why they were so highly valued. They had always been a strategic-class resource.

“Beep! Ascertaining identity! Welcome, Duke Leylin Farlier!”

After passing through the stringent aura detection system and numerous disinfecting procedures, Leylin finally stood in a room seemingly cast entirely in crystal.

The translucent crystals emitted beautiful light, and the area was spotless and unbelievably glossy.

Seeing the data the A.I. Chip provided, Leylin, couldn’t help but sigh. “Though the strength setup is different, in terms of disinfecting and dust, it can achieve the same effect!”

Such an environment was extremely similar to the sterile laboratories in his previous world. Ancient Magi were no fools, so how would they not have noticed the effects germs and the like could have on research? Even without scientific methods, they could use magic to achieve the same effect.

Within a giant glass container at the heart of the laboratory, a broken sword was soaking in a translucent green liquid. This was the same blade that held the bloodline of the Sun’s child and the Wing of the Sun meditation technique. Numerous transparent air bubbles could be seen arising from the hole-filled dull blade, and only the area with the blood was glowing brightly.

He’d already recorded all the information about the Wing of the sun through his A.I. Chip. The only thing left of value was the blood, which he had yet to extract.

The golden blood was like warm light as it slowly grew on the sword, somehow moving automatically as if breathing.

“As expected of the blood left behind by a rank 6 creature. Even if all its vitality has been lost, a slight simulation from the external world allowed it to regain its instinct…”

Leylin was full of praise. The ancient Sun’s child was at the peak of Breaking Dawn, and was an existence he could only look up to. Just a single drop of blood could multiply, enough to form life.

If it placed its spirit branding inside, an almighty ancient being could definitely revive itself from just a droplet of blood. The bloodline of the Sun’s child was that terrifying!

Of course, confirmed by the appraisal of top-notch masters, the bloodline of the Sun’s child on the blade had long since lost its vitality and was impossible to stimulate. This breathing movement was only an instinctual reaction and not a display of full revival.

If the bloodline of the Sun’s child could be made use of, the broken sword would not have been sold off at such a low price. Even if the Azure Mountain King, Zack, had to fall out with Cyril over it, he would definitely use force to keep the bloodline.

However, for Leylin who was an expert in ancient bloodline experiments and had the support of the A.I. Chip, it wasn’t an impossible task to stimulate the revival of the bloodline.

He was now gazing at the broken sword in the glass container, a look of satisfaction appearing on his face. “The restoration is coming along quite well! I can begin the second phase…”

He, who had acquired the research data of the Quicksand organisation, had grasped the finest technology of the ancient era. This naturally included many methods to restore bloodlines.

At that point in time, due to his lack of strength, he could not display all his skills. Many of the methods required the coordination of soul force, and Leylin who had only been rank 3 at the time would only be working in vain. Now, however, this was no longer an issue.

“Soul Web!” Threads of black soul force brought with them a simple radiance as they shot out from between Leylin’s brows, forming a web-like structure that disappeared into the green solution. Large amounts of fine runes with unknown functions emerged from the thin web.

The soul web seemed to have no effects on the broken sword and went straight through the blade. However, the golden blood seemed to be attracted, gathering onto it.

Minutes later, all the blood on the broken sword had been shifted to the soul web, causing it to turn golden.

*Gulu! Gulu!* As the last thread of golden luster left the blade, the metal immediately corroded into nothingness in the green solution, leaving no residue behind.

“It was only made of the plainest materials. Only because of the will of the Sun’s child had it been preserved for over ten thousand years. The moment the blood is removed, it instantly reverts to its original form!”

Leylin’s eyes shone, no longer focused on the sword. All his attention was focused on the soul web, as he manipulated the golden web to float over to another large breeding pool.

Countless loach-like long fish poked their heads out of the dim yellow pool, translucent bubbles being spat out from their lips.

These were blood-sucking loaches, and were rarely-seen bloodline creatures. All the reserves of the Ouroboros Clan were stored here.

“Go!” Leylin controlled the soul web until it was atop the pool. Drop by drop, the golden liquid fell, being devoured by countless blood-sucking loaches that were trying to outdo each other.

Water splashed everywhere in the cultivation pool, and Leylin watched the changes in the loaches without blinking.

Golden threads appeared from the stomachs of these blood-sucking loaches. Then, their eyes rolled back and they began floating in the pool.

“The bloodline of a rank 6 creature is too powerful for these loaches…” Leylin shook his head, but did not stop the experiment.

Chapter 515: The Tomb

The residents of the small town were evidently prepared to join the army of scrap collectors. This might also have been the reason why they decided to live here, or their aim in being here.

At the same time, they were very unfriendly towards the foreigners who stayed in the inn, casting grave and stern looks at them from time to time, clearly treating them as prey.

As compared to the residents, who were great in number, the adventurers and mercenaries were outnumbered and divided. They gathered together, and couldn’t help but grip tightly onto the cleavers and swords they held.

Although they knew that the others did not harbour good intentions, these people who they could consider ‘one of their own’ made them feel more at ease in comparison to the sea of residents outside.

It was fortunate that although the two groups of people both shot glares at one another, they didn’t land themselves in a more heated conflict before the Spirit Wave could begin.

At this moment, a bizarre energy wave spread across the town, sending chills down everyone’s spine.

As for Leylin and the other Magi, the feeling was more distinct.

“It’s beginning…” Leylin gazed at the haloed moon in the sky.

According to the A.I. Chip’s readings, the intensity of a type of dark and cold energy waves was rapidly rising. So much that the region around the small town seemed to be enveloped in what seemed like a domain barrier.

‘The Morning Star realm? No! Its intrinsic qualities slightly fall short, it can only be a force field belonging to rank 3 Magi at most!’ The appearance of such a barrier made Leylin’s pupils contract, but he relaxed soon after.

“It’s… It’s appearing…” At this moment, a voice sounded, trembling either due to dread or excitement.

Leylin followed the crowd. Numerous rays of light that resembled shooting stars converged into a long, glittering river, flowing slowly from the perimeter of the small town.

Brilliant rays with resplendent streaks splashed across the horizon. Leylin’s eyesight allowed him to see the items in the rays of light clearly.

A single yellow leather shoe flew past, with tiny white wings on each side. The shoelaces were left on the side in a mess, yet the tip of the shoe was polished and shiny.

Behind the leather shoe was a black walking stick, likely processed directly from some sort of vine. Similarly, it was flying with the wings below its handle.

“What… Is this thing…” Leylin’s looked baffled.

Soon after, he also saw a rag doll, a shabby table and chair, and other items fly past, such as the kind of flower vases that were usually placed on counters.

“Is this a gathering of dilapidated commodities?” He was speechless, but still commanded the A.I. Chip to record this scene and monitor the energy waves.

After the junk flowed away along the river, Leylin could no longer bring himself to laugh.

Right behind the flow of light, a faintly discernible white line gradually drew nearer.

When it came closer, he could see numerous unfeeling faces. They had long, jet black hair, and were clothed entirely in white, slowly walking over along the ray of light… Perhaps walking would be an inaccurate description, because a cloud of mist hung under their feet. Their entire beings seemed to drift forward continuously while suspended in mid-air.

Although the adventurers and mercenaries next to Leylin had long heard about such a phenomenon, their legs still trembled with fear. They couldn’t even keep their jaws shut, and the sounds of teeth chattering could be heard as they shuddered.

In comparison to those people, the residents of this town ought to have gone through this before, and had experience. Although their faces were also deathly pale, they could still compose themselves, and were not humiliated.

The densely-packed silhouettes converged to form an enormous tide, which surged up violently next to the small town.

Leylin stood at the side, solemn, as his A.I. Chip frantically recorded the data. “There are so many spirits. Perhaps something major once happened in the vicinity, and it might be related to high energy radiation…”

In actual fact, many of the strange sightings observed across the entire central continent were caused by battles between high-ranking Magi or contamination by radiation. Such phenomena usually did not die out even after thousands upon thousands of years, and instead expanded outward unceasingly, vying over territory with the humans who lived there.

Hence, the prevention and cure of such contamination was a hot research topic for many of the large forces.

Numerous white phantoms squirmed towards a particular direction unhurriedly. Among them were males and females, children and the elderly, yet they were all expressionless. Their hair was let down, and covered their pupils.

Such an odd phenomenon made even Leylin’s scalp tingle.

Souls have always been seen as something highly bizarre and idealistic. In his quest for more knowledge, he had no choice but to carry on.

“Huh?” At this moment, the grandfather and grandson he had been observing with his soul force suddenly made a move.

Upon seeing the wave of numerous spirits, the elderly Magus seemed excited, and fished out a yellowing notebook. He appeared to be making comparisons, and even left the town secretly.

On the other hand, the other rank 2 Magi exchanged looks, then went to their separate corners and took out various materials from their robes to display on themselves.

“They are likely trying to use the power of the Spirit Wave to alchemize the magic items that are coming through!”

Leylin’s alchemic skills were high enough for him to be a grandmaster. With merely a slight glance, he immediately found a clue. Feeling that it was beneath him, he snorted coldly and didn’t bother about it.

He thought of leaving a phantom at where he was, while he himself would slip into the cracks of darkness so that he could follow the grandfather and grandson out.

In the notebook that the grandfather had taken out earlier, Leylin had seen something incredible.

“If that’s really the case, it will be interesting!” A brilliant light flashed in Leylin’s eyes.

“Grandfather… Are we… Really going to be around these spirits?” The grandson was only a cowardly acolyte. Seeing the translucent spirits, he tugged the elderly Magus’ sleeve in fear, his face pale.

“These spirits are of the lowest level, and aren’t likely to attack, what’s there to be afraid of?” The old Magus reproached, seemingly feeling a little helpless.

Although his grandson had pretty decent innate skills, he didn’t have much courage to speak of.

“But… We’re about to integrate into the sea of spirits directly! Once they discover that something’s not right, they’ll definitely rip us into pieces!” The old man’s reassurance did not calm the young boy down, but instead made him more fearful.

“If we don’t integrate into the spirit channel, how will we get to the tomb and obtain ‘that’?” An unyielding look was written across the old man’s face. He grabbed his grandson’s arm, then took out a few scrolls and ripped them apart.

*Buzz!* Upon ripping open the black scrolls, the pair was enveloped in a dull white glow.

After the radiance dispersed, both of their figures started to become ghost-like, and they even emitted energy waves similar to those of spirits.

The hostile glares that the spirits had been shooting at the pair also vanished immediately.

“Done!” The elderly Magus, who was becoming translucent, patted his chest. “This is a spell that has been passed down our family for generations, which can make these spirits temporarily view us as their kind…”

Seeing this, the boy was finally at ease, and squeezed into the stream of spirits together with the old man.

“What an intriguing spell!” A ray of light flashed in the air, and Leylin’s silhouette appeared, “It’s unlike the traditional spells from the central continent, and instead has a style reminiscent of the astral plane!”

Although the spirits were rich in number, most of them were of very low rank. They were absolutely incapable of detecting any flaw if a Morning Star Magus chose to conceal himself deliberately.

It was only until Leylin integrated into the Spirit Wave that he finally felt different.

“Space! It’s the power of space! No wonder that guy called this place a spiritual channel!” Leylin muttered under his breath. And he realised the path that the spirits were taking was oddly isolated from the rest of the central continent, forming a special channel.

Here, even if something was visible to the naked eye, it might actually be as far as hundreds of thousands of kilometers away.

If one could grasp the rules of this channel, they would be able to use it to do things that many Magi would think unimaginable.

The old man ahead seemed very familiar with this place, and dragged the young boy along, advancing quickly. A blue light twinkled in Leylin’s eyes as he followed them closely.

“He’s using the spirit channel to hide something! I’m sure he must have been a Morning Star before his death!”

The further they went down the path, the more serious Leylin became. There were many dangers here that even he would be unable to ignore. If not for the fact that there was someone leading the way in front, he could not be sure if he would make his way through successfully.

There were fewer spirits lingering around at the back of the wave. A silver ray of light had appeared on the ground, and the old man was walking on it together with his grandson.

The minutes ticked by, and when they finally arrived at a particular site, ecstasy spread across the old man’s face. “Found it!”

Leylin’s footsteps came to a halt. The elderly Magus in front of him was standing under a huge butternut tree. The enormous forks in the branches formed an eerie symbol with three heads.

Upon seeing this tree, which seemed like some sort of landmark, the old man choked up in agitation, even shedding a few tears, “We’ve finally found it! The ancestral tomb!”

“Right here?” The young boy looked at the forked and ostensibly demonic branches, as the silver moon shone with an oddly nefarious glow, making him shrivel in cowardice.

“Yes, right here!” The old man was so excited that he nearly broke into a dance. “Our family’s cemetery is almost always hidden in the spatial rifts. Only when the Spirit Wave hits once every hundred years can we pass through the spirit channel to get here…”

A blazing radiance lit up in his eyes. “In the tomb lies the meditation techniques and magical equipment belonging to our ancestor. Just these items are sufficient to revive our family…”

“If that’s the case… Why didn’t our ancestors just leave this behind?” The young boy asked doubtfully.

“I’m not too sure myself. Anyway, this tomb is our family treasure, that’s for sure!” The old man seemed a little baffled himself, but it would soon be replaced by an even greater madness.

Chapter 516: Gargoyle

“All my efforts in coming here are for your sake.” The old man watched his grandson lovingly.

“You have the best talent in our family. As long as you have a high-grade meditation technique and magic artifact, advancing to rank 2 and rank 3 will definitely not be an issue. You even have hope of reaching Morning Star!”

The old man was so emotional that he trembled, on the verge of spitting froth.

This immediately caused Leylin, who was hidden, to roll his eyes. He was the most qualified to talk about the difficulty of reaching Morning Star, and this old man was just spouting nonsense.

If one could reach Morning Star with just better talent and a high-grade meditation technique, the continent would not have so many Crystal Phase Magi who had lived out their lives without being able to advance.

However, Leylin did not think them completely wrong. The many planes were so vast, and if their ancestor really had some method of reaching the Morning Star realm unimpeded, it could very well be possible.

“But…” The young grandson seemed to hesitate, seemingly not believing in this judgement. If not for the tomb of his ancestor, and his blood-related grandfather bringing him here, he might even have had plans of leaving.

“Awakening the ancestor’s spirit and honour with my blood and heading towards the door of success, with hell as the final destination…”

The old man took a silver-white dagger and sliced his wrist, dripping the blood on the roots. He continuously chanted something, as if conducting a solemn ceremony.

With the blood spreading everywhere, coupled with the eerie surroundings, the young boy shrunk back.

“Grandpa, look!” All of a sudden, his pupils shrunk and he tugged at the old man’s sleeves while beginning to yell.

Following his gaze, the blood on the tree roots had been absorbed by the soil and roots quickly. It was as if water had been sprinkled on a sponge.

“This is a defensive mechanism that our family set up. Only the blood of the descendants, coupled with the correct chants, can open it…”

The old man spoke slowly. However, Leylin’s eyes lit up with suspicion, “A bloodline lock. A bloodline lock again! Could they be a Warlock family? They don’t have any Warlock undulations on them though…”

*Huala!* After absorbing the old man’s blood, the giant walnut tree’s messy arrangement of branches began to tremble, and the trunk turned a bloody red.

*Ka-cha!* All of a sudden, the middle of the trunk cracked apart to form a hole, and a passageway that led downwards could be seen.

“Follow me!” The old man walked ahead, and the young grandson followed closely behind, hands tugging tightly on the old man’s sleeves. He appeared terrified.

Leylin bowed his head in thought for a moment, but eventually followed behind them.

The passage was short, and in no time they reached a tomb.

The old man lit an oil lamp in the middle, and under the dim light the tomb presented itself to Leylin.

This underground room was very small. There were two gargoyles at two ends, seemingly standing guard over the place.

Between the two gargoyle guards, a stone coffin appeared before them, with sealing runes on the surface.

The young man’s teeth began to chatter as he pulled at his grandpa’s sleeves tightly, “This- There’s nothing here at all. Let’s leave as soon as possible. I have a bad feeling about this…”

“What are you afraid of?” The old man flung his sleeve in annoyance, and a stream of air began to flow. The light breeze blew over the lights and darkened the tomb.

“Look closely!” The old man’s voice was hoarse and full of emotion that he could not conceal, “I lit the lamp just so you could see this…”

The young man could not help but widen his eyes, his pupils enlarging as well. Through the dark yellow flames, he could see a great number of coloured murals on the walls of the tomb. Through the murals, he could see the process of a Magus acolyte struggling ahead, from rank 1 to rank 3.

After that, there was a legendary battle. The Magus in the mural, who was also the owner of the tomb, seemed to have obtained something in the battle and reached Morning Star.

The young man’s eyes widened. However, other than a scaly monster with multiple eyes and arms battling his ancestor, he recognised nothing else.

“This is the most brilliant piece of our ancestor’s history. It only appears when this oil lamp is lit…”

The old man’s voice showed his pride, “If it’s an outsider who doesn’t know this mechanism, they will be attacked!”

Leylin had hidden in a crevice in the shadows. He was surprised by the mural on the wall. The monster that had eventually been killed was one he had seen before, on another mural. “We meet again, Beelzebub. Or should I say the Sovereign King of Gluttony?”

Leylin’s voice was light but resolute.

In ancient times, a clone of the Sovereign King of Gluttony descended upon the Magus world, causing large numbers of casualties. It was eventually killed, body split into countless pieces.

One of the pieces fell into the hands of the Quicksand organisation, becoming the cause of the Parble Family’s tragedy after Robin obtained it.

It seemed like the owner of the tomb had once been a participant in that great war, and had been extremely fortunate to obtain a gluttony imprint.

‘Then it’s obvious how this fellow advanced to Morning Star after victory,’ Leylin touched his chin, “With the power of gluttony, spurring on one’s spiritual force to break through and reach the Morning Star realm is quite possible!”

He already had an imprint like this in his hands, and had even been prepared to use it to advance to the Morning Star realm. However, he had already made ample preparations and ended up not needing external support. Leylin had no wish to be connected to Beelzebub anyway.

This was someone who was probably at or above rank 7! Just a finger would be enough to crush the current Leylin. It was obvious why he would not want to have any connection with him. Even if something related to Beelzebub fell at his feet, Leylin would want nothing to do with it.

“Based on the records of the ancestor, his meditation technique, as well as the treasure that can help one break through, are all within the coffin, accompanying his long sleep…”

The elderly Magus’ eyes shot out a piercing glare as he ambled forward slowly, arriving in front of the coffin.

A mechanism was activated, creaking sounds coming out as a red light shot out of the two gargoyle’s eyes. They shrugged off their stone skin and pounced towards the old Magus.

*Weng!* A golden membrane suddenly rose on the Magus’ body, separating the sharp claws of the gargoyles from his person.

A look of disbelief appeared on the old Magus’ face, “I am his descendant and came with directions. Why am I being attacked?”

*Creak!* The gargoyles would not answer him. The two immediately let out piercing sound waves, and as the berserk waves swept through the acolyte immediately fainted.

“Blu!” The old man’s eyes turned red, hands morphing into beast talons.

*Ka-cha!* He grabbed hold of one gargoyle and viciously ripped it into two. Great amounts of soil and rocks flew everywhere, and the other stood very still, the light on its body reserved. It began to emanate a violent energy.

“Want to self-destruct?” Light burst out of the old Magus’ eyes as he charged to the front. A thick layer of light, alike to the kind emitted by a Spear Spell, covered his sharp claws.

*Pu!* A single claw swept forward, and went through the gargoyle’s body like a knife through hot butter. With a twist of his hand, a giant mechanical heart was gouged out.

After losing its power core, the aura on the gargoyle crackled and disappeared, leaving it dead.

“Blu, Blu! Wake up!” The old man undid the transformation of his hands, and a green radiance that was full of vitality wrapped around the young boy.

Minutes later, the young boy came to, looking dazed.

“This is probably not the ancestor’s tomb, but a place sealing some terrifying thing. If not, why would this sort of guard be around?” The first thing the young man did after waking up was warn his grandfather.

“I’m not willing to leave just like this!” The old Magus’ eyes turned red, and he looked stubborn, “Perhaps, those two protectors were a test by the ancestor, or a joke on the younger generation…”

Even so, even he himself could not believe his words.

However, his perseverance and the cry in his heart were urging him to open the coffin and obtain the things within.

“I’ll take just one look, I promise! Then we’ll seal this place and leave immediately!” The old man’s eyes were distant as he approached and pushed the cover of the stone coffin away, revealing the items within.

“Hm?!” Leylin, who had been watching at the side, suddenly had a change of expression.

What was inside the giant coffin was indeed the remains of a Magus. His body was rather thin, but his hair and eyebrows were still present. He looked lifelike, and the imposing aura of a Morning Star emanated from his body.

Though his eyes were tightly closed, his features were extremely sharp, with a steadfast resolution and strength. His hands were folded before his chest as if holding something.

With Leylin’s eyes, he was able to see a stone rune without any trouble. Though it was different from what he had, this was definitely a true gluttony imprint!

“I told you there’s a treasure!” The old Magus was in a bad situation. He looked dazed, as if he was being controlled by something. He went forward, hands reaching for the rune.

“Grandpa!” Just as his fingers were about to touch the rune, the young boy’s cries pulled him back.

“What’s going on? Why am I here?” The old man was bewildered, but immediately after, a stranger situation occurred.

With wailing that sounded like hell reappearing, multiple black shadow fingers appeared within the tomb, threads of black gas being dispelled from the old man’s bosom.

Chapter 517: Killing the Clone’s Projection

“Why is the temperature rising at this rate?” The old man swiftly took out the black notebook from his chest. Not only was the notebook heating up, traces of black currents swirled around it.

*Buzz!* With a sudden spike in the book’s temperature, the old man scrunched his face up in pain as he subconsciously tossed it from his hand.

A big patch of the old man’s hand was scalded from the momentary contact. White blisters started forming on its surface.

Even with a Magus’ physique and the protection of his innate spell, he was still injured this way!

*Woo woo…*

“The almighty Beelzebub, you are the king of hell, the darling of the original sins, with the control over gluttony. The desires for all cuisine lies in your hand….”

The phantom became more intense as the chants and songs of praises filled the entire tomb area.

Leylin had seen such situations in the past, hence he immediately became vigilant. As for the old man and his grandson, they huddled together in a corner with looks of regret on their faces.

A black ray of light swept out from the notebook, and like a remnant of an illusion seeped into the stone rune on the coffin.

After the flow of light had dissipated, as if it had completed its mission, the notebook burned to ashes in front of their eyes.

Colourful light flowed out of the stone rune, and traces of this light started connecting with the Morning Star corpse.

Like lightning, the ray scanned through the tomb as the Morning Star corpse opened his eyes and once again descended upon this world!

“I… I… Am I Ezekiel? Or Gordius?”

“No! I am Beelzebub! Sovereign King of gluttony, Beelzebub!”

The Magus’ eyes looked lost in the beginning, but they soon glowed brightly. His Morning Star domain had apparently descended, and both grandfather and grandson fell to the ground.

“Morning Star! It’s our Morning Star ancestor!” By now, the corpse was sitting partially upright. The old man was ecstatic and was about to speak when a flash of ruthless light sparked from the corpse’s face.

A ray of crimson red flashed across the old Magus and he disappeared immediately without a trace.

“Mmm! A pretty good supplement! And it appears to be a direct descendant of the corpse too!” The red glow in the Morning Star Magus’ eyes intensified. He stroked his belly and darted his eyes towards the young teenager.

“Ah…” The scene a moment ago left the young teen on the verge of collapsing. He opened his mouth and attempted to speak, but could only murmur some incoherent words as his body froze up and stiffened.

The gaze from the Morning Star Magus did not linger for long on the young teen, as it swept its line of sight behind him instead.

“Eh….” Following an indistinct sigh, Leylin’s silhouette emerged from the crevice.

“Morning Star Magus?! You’re the kid from before!” The words spoken by the corpse in the coffin were filled with much astonishment, and a lot of deep seated hatred.

“That’s right! It’s me! I’m a projected clone of Beelzebub!” Leylin admitted his identity magnanimously.

With the opposite party’s gluttony imprint on him, Leylin couldn’t deny the facts. And by now, he should have been able to discern all that had happened anyway.

During ancient times, Beelzebub’s clone died and the remains had transformed itself to become a huge rune of gluttony, and thereafter he attempted to invade the different coordinates of the world of Magi.

Magi who attained the gluttony rune would have been tainted by the sin of gluttony, and hence have their appetites awakened. They would also get the ability to advance beyond their realms, and additionally with the power of gluttony in their body, they became potential host bodies for Beelzebub himself!

The Magus buried here was lucky to have obtained a remnant. And after his own Morning Star breakthrough, he seemed to have noticed something amiss and hence sealed himself in and isolated himself from the probe of Beelzebub.

Unfortunately, the notebook that he regularly carried around had been tainted over a long period of time, and it was even entrusted with by of spirit fragments.

After a very long time, his grandchild, bewitched by the notebook, had come forth to open the coffin and release the clone.

“Unexpectedly, you have advanced to Morning Star!”

The Magus possessed by Beelzebub looked extremely imposing. Every single move was filled with an imposing aura, and behind him the image of a huge demon appeared that vaguely resembled the king of hell.

“How do you intend to compensate for my previous losses?” It was odd that this clone did not pursue the matter further, and instead hinted at settling it.

Leylin looked even more baffled as he stepped up to the clone. He looked it right in the eye, “Do you take me for a fool?”

Once the words were spoken, the clone immediately changed colour. Leylin continued, ”As you are now, you aren’t even a clone, but just a fragment of a spirit with some power of projection! Besides, this Morning Star Magus corpse’s point mass has followed its spirit and returned to the astral plane. While this high-quality body has been contaminated by the power of gluttony, with your current reliance on this Morning Star body, how much strength can you exhibit?”

*Buzz!* As the darkness loomed in, the earth looked like it had been isolated them from the outside world. Silver radiance filled the whole sky, and the stars scattered all around.

A real Morning Star domain had descended! Once the clone’s domain came into contact with Leylin’s it immediately shattered.

Witnessing the outcome, the expression on the clone was hideous while Leylin heaved a sigh of relief.

His previous prediction had been accurate indeed.

Of course, he could have stopped the old man, but he wouldn’t have been able to deal with the Magus inside. Allowing both dangers to happen simultaneously and dealing with both issues at once was Leylin’s preferred style.

After all, he did incur some hatred from the Sovereign King some time ago, and he naturally couldn’t let the matter rest and allow the opposite party to develop their plans.

Even though this was just a projection of a clone, it wasn’t wise to ignore him. He could have gone out to replenish himself well, and someday might even become an uncontrollable threat!

Leylin definitely wouldn’t want that to happen, yet letting it go was also not an option. The best course of action then would be to destroy him completely when he was at his weakest.

“You…..” Beelzebub’s clone was a mess, with strands of hair standing on end, exhibiting his extreme anger.

“Goodbye!” Disregarding his opponent’s rage, Leylin waved his hand. Terrifying energy condensed into his palm, forming a red flame that then morphed into a huge blazing serpent that coiled around him.

Under the terrifyingly high temperature, the original stone coffin immediately turned to ashes. Leylin eyed the blaze indifferently.

A black radiance appeared, gradually glowing as it sucked in all the fiery blaze. After the fire died out, Beelzebub could be seen opening his mouth wide and swallowing the flames.

What was even more bizarre was that after swallowing them, his aura seemed to have grown stronger.

“Devouring capability! Your understanding of the power of gluttony has reached the level of laws!” Leylin clapped without flinching. Based on the power of the opposite party’s body, attaining this level was no big deal.

“It’s a pity, though. Your foundation is too weak. How much more energy can you absorb?” Leylin’s words angered Beelzebub so much that his face contorted in rage.

Any absorption of power would have a limit to it. And since the opposite party had no mass point belonging to the Morning Star, there was an obvious upper bound to it. Leylin focused on this point and attacked him mercilessly.

It was advantageous that the opposite party was currently weak. It wasn’t likely that Leylin would have such opportunities in the future.

*Boom!* A torrential blaze, like a huge wave, swallowed Beelzebub. He became unsure, not daring to swallow any more. Uncountable black tentacles appeared on his body, wrapping him up.

Upon contact with the scarlet red flame, the black tentacles immediately started dissolving. Counteracting each other, the attacks from both sides gradually weakened.

“Ivory Devourer!”

Ferocious black teeth, that seemed to have melted in the void, surrounded Leylin. Yet, it was blocked by a red shield that had Giant Kemoyin Serpents carved on it.

“Indeed, how many more attacks can you sustain?”

The huge black teeth grazed across the surface of the shield, leaving deep grooves and creating big sparks. At this moment, Leylin’s looked like he had a plan in mind.

“You…” Bundled within the black tentacles, Beelzebub could only blurt out a single word and was soon enveloped by the fiery red blaze…..

“This….. What is happening?”

The teen lying on the ground looked up and saw what looked like the aftermath of a big battle. At long last, the Magus with a head of black hair appeared and stood among the stars in the sky. He looked like a God descending onto the earth, moving the fiery red blaze to swallow up the strange creature in the coffin.

A long time later, the shimmering stars started to dim, and the black hair Magus came before the teen. His face looked tired but was filled with delight.

“Your name is Blu?” Securing the other gluttony imprint well, Leylin smiled.

Leylin obviously would not want to keep the consciousness of the opposite party. To deal with a rank 7 and above, one could be drowned in their layers of crafty schemes. Unwittingly, the radiation contamination would have become a handful, similar to the example of the old Magus and his ancestor.

However, these gluttony imprints were very much worth researching. And the laws themselves were of much importance!

The power of laws! It was like a door separating rank 6 and rank 7. Only after attaining the necessary power of laws could one be promoted to the Breaking Dawn realm and above. As such, Leylin showed no traces of politeness and kept the gluttony imprint to study thoroughly later.

Although at the present moment, his rank was considerably low, he would definitely come into contact with it in the near future.

“Yes, Master. I am Blu!“

The young Blu bowed respectfully to the Morning Star Magus. It was the kind of respect that the whole central continent would give to one!

Chapter 519: Picking up Scraps

“Lily’s Cosy Cottage?” Leylin looked at a shop’s signboard made of oak leaves and written in both the continent’s characters and elven language.

Compared to all the other shops, this shop was evidently more attentive to details. Even the corners had greenery with plants and flowers sprouting, emitting pleasant flora scents.

“Welcome!’

As he stepped foot into the shop, a boyish-looking elf greeted Leylin genuinely with respect and a smile, ”Respectful customer, how can I be of service to you today?”

“Oh, I am just looking through, I see you sell many miscellaneous things here?”

Leylin’s eye swept over to the sales counter. There was a huge clutter of spell materials like ore, furs from living creatures, scrolls and other handcrafted articles. There was great variety, but almost all of them were without tags and placed haphazardly. And despite that, it looked like an organised mess.

“Yes, from the islands of the south coast to Sky City, everything in existence can be found here!” The elven shop owner beamed and replied proudly.

“Really?” Leylin plastered a smile on his face. These days, the number of objects that could garner his attention had been dwindling. However, from his observations a moment ago, he did notice some valuable materials on display. For a tiny shop like this, it was rather rare.

“Eh?!”

Leylin was about to exit the shop when an item in a corner caught his attention.

“Is this item for sale too?” Leylin casually picked up a spell scroll.

It was a very old scroll covered with dust and marks of damage. Wrapped up between both the horizontal axles was not common spell paper but some kind of beasty skin, with a hint of glossiness in the texture.

Leylin unfurled the scroll and saw the records of a rank 2 spell model. It looked like it was well used as the content had become very faint.

Magi could use their spiritual force to break and extract the knowledge and spell models within scrolls, and many methods of learning included the use of them. When a scroll was repeatedly used for study, it would eventually deteriorate to this state.

Magi required the spell model’s structure to be stable, and would thus demand extreme precision and quality. Hence, a scroll in such a condition would have totally lost its value.

Afterall, an unstable spell model could prove to be fatal!

As such, this old scroll had just been left there, unsold for a long time. Thus, seeing Leylin pick this up, a light of puzzlement flashed in the elven store owner’s eyes.

“This is the spell model of a rank 2 spell— Hand of Illumination. The original price was five thousand magic crystals, but since it is your first visit here, my offer is three thousand magic crystals! Just three thousand magic crystals and it will be yours!”

“Is that so?” Leylin gave a smile that was not a smile and looked at the elf till he felt somewhat ashamed and hung his head down.

The price quoted had exceeded way past the original value of the scroll, causing the usually noble and elegant elf a little embarrassment. However for the sake of his livelihood, he had to do it.

“You are a wind elf, right?”

Leylin could feel the wind elemental particles hovering around the opposite party. It was unusually light and graceful, so Leylin couldn’t help but ask.

“Yes! Yes, my Lord!” The middle-aged store owner lifted his head. There were many Magi who could recognise him as an elf, but not many were able to specifically identify him as a wind elf.

“The wind elven tribe is rumoured to be close to going extinct in the continent. I didn’t expect to meet one here!!”

Leylin smiled and rolled up the scroll. He picked up a black ore from the sales counter, ”Including this item, a total of three thousand magic crystals!”

The elven store owner scrutinised closely and upon confirmation that it was just an ordinary ore that wasn’t particularly valuable, he nodded his head in agreement.

Noticing the shame in the elf’s eyes, Leylin did not criticise further. After settling the transaction, he left the shop.

“Sigh… even a graceful and elegant elf cannot escape from nature’s laws…” Leylin turned around to take another look at the exquisite door of the shop.

According to ancient legends, the elves had migrated here from the other world and had many different branches elsewhere.

Among the elves, the moon elves, gold elves and wind elves possessed the highest grade of bloodline, similar to the nobles of the human race, possessing high prestige and good reputation. They were also regularly depicted as protagonists in the works of many poets.

As for the dark elves and such, they were regarded as the odd-one-outs among the race, hence not comparable to the rest.

And so, for a noble and elegant wind elf to fall to this stage, Leylin couldn’t help but sigh under his breath.

“But, since you are the one who started this, you can’t blame me…..”

Leylin laughed as his palm stroked the cover of the scroll. The strange texture of it made him gleam with joy as his eyes lit up.

[Beep! After the database comparison, item confirmed as the epidermis of an ancient creature— Horned Rhinoceros!]

the A.I. Chip reported and Leylin’s mood lightened.

Although the spell template on the surface of the scroll was not very useful, the material used was remarkable. An ancient living creature, the Horned Rhinoceros was similar to the Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Both of them could reach Morning Star in their adulthood. The epidermis contained a high level of spell resistance and was a necessary material for many Morning Star Magi equipment.

For Leylin, being able to obtain this for a mere three thousand magic crystal was indeed a fabulous deal.

Not only that, but the ore he’d picked out was also made of a high-grade material— secret silver! Although it was embedded under layers of ore, Leylin’s A.I. Chip was still able to detect it.

‘This small shop made a huge loss from our transaction, their two most valuable items had been bought by me…’ Leylin sniggered silently.

After his promotion to Morning Star, and after attaining the supplementary assistance of soul force, his A.I. Chip’s probing capabilities had increased by leaps and bounds, and could be considered unprecedented in history.

Very few items could hide their true form from its scans at this juncture.

As such, his current advantage was too huge. Even if he did nothing substantial every day and just browsed the multiple shops casually, he might be able to pick up items that were needed for his Morning Star research and breakthroughs.

‘It’s just…’ Leylin stroked his chin, ‘Doing so would be too pompous and would attract the wrong kind of attention. If the secret of the A.I. Chip is leaked, there might be more trouble…’

“Besides…..” Leylin’s pupils sparkled.

He helplessly shook his head and arrived in front of a teleporting spell formation at a crossing, where two Magi were waiting.

These two Magi had obvious characteristics of a different race. One had a head that resembled that of an octopus while the other’s body was covered with wolf fur.

Leylin walked up and gracefully made his salutations. “Lord Paul, Lord Phillip! It’s been a long time…”

“We hope we are not imposing on you, Lord Leylin!” Paul laughed and pointed at the ore Leylin held in his hand, both exhibiting a tacit mutual understanding.

“Morning Star Magi are indeed not easy to deceive, your soul force’s probing ability is commendable, detecting the secret in this ore so quickly! “

Leylin rolled his eyes silently but did not mind it much.

After all, the probes by his own A.I. Chip were usually done covertly and until now had not been discovered. Other Magi would have thought that he had depended on his acute soul force to uncover the treasures, and so it wasn’t considered a big deal.

“Yes, we apologise for interrupting your leisure. Our social gathering is about to begin, come…” Philip courteously replied.

Leylin didn’t reject him, “Sure, please show the way!”

He was absolutely sure that the entirety of Creevey City had a specialised spell that was used for detecting Morning Stars. However, he did not use any spell to alter his own appearance and energy waves, as he was confident in his abilities and was certain he would not be easily discovered.

After some careful consideration, he concluded that it was understandable.

Creevey City was the main headquarters of the entire Warlock Union, it held a lot of symbolic importance. They’d provoked their fair share of Morning Star Magi already. If they didn’t have an increased alertness and powerful warning system, the prosperity of the city was going to short-lived.

Leylin unenthusiastically thought about this as he followed Paul and Philip to the front of the teleporting spell formation.

These two made no attempt to conceal the energy waves on their bodies, and caught many looks of reverence. The Warlocks voluntarily stepped aside and left a wide berth for the huge teleporting spell formation, so much so that only the three of them were left using it at that moment.

No matter where they were, Morning Stars carried a terrifying amount of prestige.

Rays of silver light flashed, and when the scenery was visible again Leylin found himself at an unfamiliar place.

Every building was short, and the concrete slabs on the road had many depressions on them, appearing very shabby. Even the density of energy particles in the air appeared to be very weak, similar to the rest of the central continent.

“Surprised? For the core area of the Creevey City with its four elements to be so simple and crude is unexpected?” Paul remarked as he led Leylin onto another path.

*Ka-cha!* When Leylin stepped foot on one of the slabs, it seemed to come alive, floating up and carrying Leylin forward at the speed of lightning.

“A little, yes!” Leylin nodded his head in agreement.

“To the core of the castle!” Paul spoke to the concrete slabs and all three accelerated.

Once that was done, he looked back at Leylin, smiling as he explained, “Due to the limitations of our bloodline, we Warlocks in the central continent have experienced a long period of darkness. As such, many of the Masters suggested during the construction of the city that the core shouldn’t be too extravagant, and needs to be equipped with a good sentry system.”

“I see!” Leylin nodded.

Chapter 522: Changes in Contract

After the banquet ended, Leylin decided to stay at the Blood Castle for a while. During this period, he constantly received intelligence about the situation at Crystal Mountain.

The Crystal Mountains was the main area where the conflict with Jupiter’s Lightning happened, a mountain range that was located near the aisle of Arcelor. The Crystal Mountains were named so because of its production of a type of high energy crystal ore.

This ore could, to an extent, replace magic crystals as a power source for puppets, or to build formations and artifacts. This led to a decent demand for the ore, which kept the prices high.

It could be found everywhere on Crystal Mountain, even on the surface. This made extracting the ore easy, causing the place to be regarded as a natural source of wealth.

Of course, even so, it could only entice weaker Magi. It wasn’t nearly enough to draw the eyes of Morning Stars.

Ore mines of such quality were already present in Jupiter’s Lightning, Spirit Circle, and even within the Ouroboros Clan. It wasn’t worth a fight between Morning Stars.

The real worth arose from a rumour about the place. Legends recounted that this was originally the headquarters of an ancient large-scaled Magus organisation— Scarlet Crescent. During the war, the ancient Magi had peered into the future and decided to conceal the entire region with spell formations. They left their heritage there, and it would only appear when it was time.

Many Magi had brushed this off in the beginning in mockery, calling it nonsense. But on-site inspections by Cybel and the others revealed that those remains indeed existed, and even hid enormous wealth!

Jupiter’s Lightning had learned of this information at the same time. As such, there was a disagreement about the ownership of Crystal Mountain. Battle soon ensued.

Both sides had shown restraint in the beginning. The battle was restricted to a small spatial rift, and only involved those at or above the Morning Star rank.

But when the Radiant Moon Magus found himself at a disadvantage against the combined forces of the three Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks and Cybel, he felt extremely embarrassed. Thus, this matter abruptly intensified.

What followed was the three Dukes being lost in the astral plane, and the allied armies besieging the Ouroboros Clan in the midst of trickery.

Were it not for the unexpected factor called Leylin, the Ouroboros Clan could possibly have been annihilated in this tempest, ending the legacy of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks in the continent.

‘You merely had a small disadvantage, and your revenge was already so vicious…” Leylin had already formed an image of the Radiant Moon Magus of Jupiter’s Lightning. He was a cruel, petty man. Normally, such characters were not to be feared, but once one fellow possessed such enormous abilities, Leylin would dread meeting him.

“According to rumours and the data collected by mentor and his team, the surfacing time of the remains of the Scarlet Crescent would be when the sun, stars and moon converge and when the arc of Oake appears…”　

Leylin put down the ‘top secret’ documents, and the A.I. Chip began calculations.

[Time format identified to be from the ancient era. Converting into the calendar used by the central continent, date is approaching soon…]

Leylin stroked his chin, “No wonder the struggle got so violent that they even wanted to get me involved…”

As for the intentions of Spirit Circle and Wind Wolf Lair, he was very clear on what they wanted. They might have made some pact with the three Morning Star Warlocks of the Ouroboros Clan previously, setting regulations about the distribution of the spoils.

The other party in the pact had disappeared, but the contract still stood. And yet, they were unwilling to just transfer these benefits to him.

As such, getting him involved and having him represent the Ouroboros Clan, they wanted to rework the pact imminently. If they didn’t they’d have to share all the benefits they painfully acquired with Leylin, and it was not a welcome thought.

However, even Leylin agreed with this matter. Simply put, the benefits were meant to be for the three Morning Star Warlocks. And now, although the benefits had been reduced by a little, they were meant solely for him.　　

He was, after all, the sole representative of the Ouroboros Clan, possessing the right to negotiate on their behalf. Thus, it was understandable that they’d give up a few things to garner his support.

In this scenario, the gains of the Ouroboros Clan, on the whole, would reduce, but he would have good profits himself. With that being the case, why wouldn’t he agree?

”Lord Leylin, are you there?” Paul’s voice suddenly sounded from outside.

”I’m here!” Leylin replied as he opened the door.

”If you have made your decision, we can proceed with the contract alteration ceremony!” Paul smiled as he conveyed the message.

“Certainly!” Leylin nodded his head and followed Paul to the hall.　

Those present numbered five. Along with two spirit Warlocks were Cybel, Palesa, and Philip. In the centre of the tiny hall was a long table dressed with a red tablecloth. On it was the contract, along with a goose-feather pen and ink.

Leylin trembled the moment he stepped foot into the hall. He felt as if he’d entered a boundless domain, one filled with an air of righteousness.

“This is the domain of righteousness! This place was the witness when we signed the contract with the three duke the last time too….” Cybel explained.　

Contracts made among Morning Star Magi could not be broken. With the included effectiveness of this binding, the pact was absolute. No wonder Cybel, that old monster, still had no choice but to follow the rules and make allowances for Leylin, getting him to alter the contract.

Leylin walked towards the table, scrutinising the slight differences between the old contract and the new.

The new one halved the Ouroboros Clan’s benefits, causing Leylin to knit his brow. But under the column that noted the beneficiary, the name had been changed. The names of the three Dukes had been replaced with Leylin Farlier.

The three Dukes had placed the condition upon Cybel that, were they to die, the benefits would be transferred to the Ouroboros Clan. Now, it was all being handed over to Leylin.

“How is it? If there is any problem, feel free to tell us. We will address it and make the changes right away!”

The urgency in Cybel’s tone was evident; the time for the revelation of the remains was drawing near, after all. If they hadn’t even solved internal issues, how were they to vie over other things?

Leylin closed his eyes for a second as he pondered before asking, “The contract states that additional spoils will be distributed on the basis of military strength and contribution. Exactly what are the criteria?”

“Of course, it will be based on the achievements of the Morning Stars!” Cybel answered without hesitation. In his opinion, the troops below the Morning Star realm weren’t even worth consideration.

“Very well. I wish to add another clause, regarding emergency evacuations. In the event that one encounters an irresistible strength, namely an opponent at the Radiant Moon realm, we are permitted to use any methods we wish to exit the battlefield. This will not change the distribution of the spoils. Any objections?”

Leylin presented himself like one who specialised in law and litigation. Cybel and the others were stunned and they exchanged glances with one another. 　　

　　

“If that is what you wish, sure!” Cybel nodded his head, and Philip immediately stepped forward, making the alterations with the goose feather pen.　

　　

“I have no other issues!”　

　　

After ironing out some disputes, Leylin finally nodded his head in agreement. He took out a seal from his chest and stamped on the contract. 　　

　　

*Weng!* After the seal was stamped, an image appeared on the light yellow paper. It was that of a black snake biting its own tail swivelling around unceasingly. 　　

　　

This was the official seal of the Ouroboros Clan. It was originally held and controlled by the previous three Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks, and now it was in Leylin’s hand. 　

Fortunately, due to some unknown reasons, the three dukes had signed the contract under the Ouroboros Clan’s name, otherwise, Leylin would not have been able to make the amendments.

After the last seal had been stamped solemnly by the last Morning Star Warlock on the contract, the power of righteousness in the hall rose to the limit.　　

　　

The new contract gradually floated into the air, glowing a beautiful golden yellow as the old contract silently turned into a pile of ash.　　

　　

“Alright, let us discuss the next arrangements…” 　　

With the contract successfully altered, Cybel and the other Morning Star Warlocks seemed to have been refreshed with confidence and started to develop positive feelings for Leylin. Cybel impatiently urged everyone to begin planning battle strategy; he clearly couldn’t wait.

Leylin plastered a smile on his face, but deep inside he rolled his eyes.

‘How could I not alter it? I’m alone, unlike the three mentors. If I’d persisted, I would end up with nothing in the end, even attracting the malice of your two organisations…’

Weighing his options, Leylin had ultimately chosen to alter the contract. It was the best option under his current circumstances.

He believed that even if the three Dukes were to return from ‘Purgatory’ they would not be displeased by his decision.

“Within Jupiter’s Lightning, other than the Radiant Moon Magus, there are over ten Morning Stars…” In the middle of a room that resembled a command center, Cybel slowly explained the details of Jupiter’s Lightning, and Leylin was finally exposed to their strength.

“The other party’s leader will be pinned down by the Radiant Moon Warlock on our side, don’t worry. We just need to take care of the remaining ten plus Morning Star Magi.

“Many of Jupiter’s Lightning’s important territories and missions required Morning Star Magi to oversee them. As such, I suppose not more than nine Morning Star Magi will be at Crystal Mountain!”　　

Cybel seemed to be very familiar with information about Jupiter’s Lightning. He either had a specialised channel of information, or managed to ambush a spy.

“Spirit Circle can take care of three!” Paul remarked with surety.　　

　　

“Very well, Palesa and Philip will hold up two of them. That means we are down to four Morning Stars!”

Chapter 524: Marine Tribe’s Original Form

Leylin chose to battle here right away. He was confident in his energy control, and on top of that, he didn’t want to move too far away. It would be too tragic if he failed to be the first one to detect the reappearance of the remains.

He was also prepared to try out an interesting idea.

For Marine Giant Siebel, Leylin’s attitude was nothing but a provocation. He shot Leylin a piercing gaze, and soon released the massive power of his domain.

The power of one’s domain would only be perfected at the Morning Star realm. The effects of amplification and suppression would intensify, and the range of effect would also be extended. Morning Star domains were a far cry from rank 3 forcefields.

Turbulent, vast and immeasurable!

White ocean waves and the crystal clear sea surface formed a horrifying scene.

The depths of the ocean were darkened by the frantic waves, giving one an ominous premonition.

The enormous tides engulfed Siebel, completely hiding his body. Yet, his voice was transmitted clearly, “This is my domain— Ocean!”

In a split second, the ocean engulfed the entire area, burying the alpines and the wreckage left by Philip’s spells.

The boundless blue ocean roared at Leylin in rage.

‘A real Morning Star domain, and the rules he controls are those of the water element…’ A glimmer of blue light flickered across Leylin’s eyes as the A.I. Chip recorded all data about the fluctuations and the power of the domain.

Siebel’s aura rose quickly in this ocean, causing Leylin to be thrilled.

“So you’re of the marine tribe. No wonder your domain is such, changing the battlefield to be underwater.” Leylin’s voice trembled a little. It managed to traverse the depths of the ocean, but there was no reply.

The marine tribe was a non-human species. However, they cohabited the Magus world with humans. They occupied the ocean while the humans occupied the land. It wasn’t like there weren’t any wars, but most of the time it was peaceful.

There were legends and records about a Great Magus Serholm who led all human magicians and fought off the enemies from the ocean.

There were also Magi amongst the marine tribe, but they were extremely rare, as their chance of advancement was even lower than humans.

To be able to meet with a Morning Star Magus of the marine tribe thrilled Leylin. He was puzzled as to why Siebel was a part of Jupiter’s Lightning, but soon came to a realisation.

Despite the fact that Jupiter’s Lightning had the help of a Radiant Moon Magus who was one of the top forces of the central continent, it was difficult for even them to nurture a Morning Star Magus.

Other than resources and experience, luck was an important factor in becoming a Morning Star Magus.

Given their high status in the central continent, it was extremely hard for any faction to have ten or more Morning Stars like Jupiter’s Lightning did. It was impossible to rely on training their own, so they would recruit foreign Magi as well.

The auras of the previous bowman and Marine Giant were pretty much impure. Leylin was rather puzzled back then, but now it looks like they could be from a different tribe or are hybrid Magi!

The enormous waves surged into the sky, forming two dark blue crystal-like hands that gushed down towards Leylin.

The sharp increase in the air pressure formed unstable currents and caused the space in the region to be unstable.

[Beep! Data about the Ocean domain has been fully recorded!]

 Leylin smiled upon hearing the mechanical voice of the A.I. Chip.

“Corrosion!” Gently, an ancient Byron runic chant slipped out of his lips.

*Hiss! Hiss!* A large amount of uneven black pores appeared on the dark blue hand, corroding almost the entire arm within a second as if turning it into a beehive.

*Crack! Crack!* The gigantic arm lost its support and fell apart in the air, soon turning into a huge stream of water that merged back into the sea.

“In the name of the Warlock! My power of bloodline!” Leylin chanted out loud as a crimson barrier appeared on his body.

“Absorption of bloodline!” Blood red lightning flashed across his eyes, piercing through the pitch dark ocean as it revealed everything. Meanwhile, aiming at a specific spot, Leylin stretched out his right hand and made a grasping motion with great force.

An invisible air current appeared, causing a massive whirlpool in the middle of the ocean.

“AAAH!” a voice bellowed in agony from the whirlpool.

“All bloodline creatures will be under my bloodline’s control, show up now!” said Leylin, and the blood red glow on his hand converged in his hand as he lifted his right hand into the air.

Water gushed up into the sky and rained down like a huge fountain as a gigantic blue figure slowly appeared from the middle of the whirlpool.

Numerous veins protruded from the blue skin, as if about to burst out at any moment. The wriggling veins looked like earthworms, sending shivers down one’s spine.

The giant groaned in agony, forced out of the sea while being battered by crimson lightning.

“Multilimb Strength!” Leylin’s eyes glittered, and the humongous phantom of a Multi-Armed Race member appeared behind him. This phantom was much clearer than the previous ones, every single scale and pore on his body distinguishable.

Even after reaching the Morning Star realm, this foreign Arcane Art could be of great use.

Leylin even felt that combining the nourishment of his spirit with the body refinement of Multilimb Strength, he would be able to reach the peak of the Morning Star realm at a much quicker pace, and would end up far more powerful than the rest.

The phantom punched out in tandem with Leylin.

Even a single arm of the humongous phantom was as large as Siebel. It felt like seven huge mountains appeared out of thin air and came crashing down at the same time when all seven arms smashed towards him.

Siebel placed both arms in front of his chest, forming a dense shield of water that was to reduce the shockwaves from the attack. However, it was all in vain. The water shield was destroyed under the force of the phantom’s arms.

*Bang!* Siebel was shot backwards by the explosive force of the collision.

At the same time, threads of luminous blue liquid shot out from his pores and gathered to form a thumb-sized ball that landed on Leylin’s palm.

“The bloodline of a Marine Giant at the Morning Star realm!”

Leylin nodded with satisfaction and kept the bloodline in a test tube. This was a rare material for bloodline experiments, and could earn him a good sum even for his current realm.

“You are not an ordinary Morning Star Warlock. Who are you?”

As Siebel regained consciousness, he stared at Leylin cautiously. With the amazing defensive and recuperative abilities of a Morning Star Magus, this sort of injury was nothing to him. Yet, Leylin was completely relaxed as before, clearly indicating that this wasn’t his full strength.

Siebel gazed at the black haired Morning Star Warlock in front of him, running through all the top ranked Morning Stars in his mind, but did not manage to match the face to anyone. That is, until he recalled some more recent information, something that detailed Leylin’s background.

“You are Leylin Farlier! The Morning Star Kemoyin Warlock of the Ouroboros Clan! The one who killed Demon Hunter Cyril!” Siebel was in shock. Demon Hunter Cyril was considered a powerhouse among Morning Star Magi, but he’d been easily slain by Leylin.

This accomplishment was much more challenging than a win-lose in an ordinary face-off and Siebel was well aware of that.

‘For now, the best case scenario is that I keep up my defence and sustain myself. I might even have to request reinforcements!’ He smiled bitterly at his own thought. Just then, a ring of pearls glowed around his waist, and he heard urgent voices shouting around, “It’s the Third East Region, we need immediate reinforcements! We’re under attack by Spirit Circle! ”

“West Region calling for reinforcements, three layers of defence have been destroyed! Damn it, the Warlocks seem to be fully concentrated in this region! ”

“No, you bloody liars! Cybel is in our North Region, we should be the ones getting reinforcements! Ahhhh…”

The transmitted voices had a lot of interference, and there were also loud sounds of explosions in the background that added a violent shudder.g.

Siebel’s heart hit rock bottom. Knowing that Cybel was here as well, he felt hopeless.

“So this is your plan?” Siebel looked fixedly at Leylin, but could not get any details off that expressionless face.

“Even if it is so, I signed an agreement with Jupiter’s Lightning. Don’t think you can get rid of me so easily!” Siebel thought in his heart and roared out a jumbled chant of sacrificial phrases.

The serenity of the ocean was broken again by the violent movement of water as large amounts of it gathered around Siebel. When the rumbling ended, a monstrous creature that was a thousand metres tall appeared in front of Leylin.

The monster had the head of a cow, the body of a human and tentacles for feet. It growled like a raging bull.

“This is your original form?” Leylin fended off the water bullets, looking at the humongous form of the magician and chuckled.

Chapter 525: Scarlet Ruins

The marine tribe were not humans. Born of the ocean as they were, their bodies were like a manifestation of the laws of nature.

Those of the marine tribe seen on the continent were similar to humans, and had at most a few scales on their bodies. However, that was only the form they used specifically to communicate with humans. This monster that had appeared in front of Leylin was over a thousand meters tall, and it was the true form of the marine tribe.

After he revealed his true form, the undulations from Siebel’s body surged wildly, inspiring much greater terror than before.

Leylin, however, revealed a grin of excitement. ‘A.I. Chip, begin calculating the trajectory of the homing light rays!’

Endless blue light glowed in Leylin’s eyes, and most of the A.I. Chip’s power was allocated to this task.

[Setting up model of opponent. Calculating trajectory.]

Siebel in his true form growled wildly, and soul force at the Morning Star realm mixed with enormous amounts of seawater, compressing it into just a centimetre wide ball. Flickering with a blue light that transcended any normal brightness, it reached Leylin in the blink of an eye.

“Good timing!” Leylin burst out in laughter. Bloodline power and soul force converged in his palm, the formidable energy undulations finally colliding with the blue ball with a rumble.

The air buzzed and trembled, but there were no intense explosions or spatial cracks that appeared, causing the marine tribe Magus to be confused and his movements to slow.

*Shua!* At this moment, the blue ball of energy was enshrouded by crimson light as it streaked through the horizon like a meteor.

The light arched in the direction it headed, similar to a rainbow that suddenly filled the heavens.

“Oa-Oaker Arc!” A shout of disbelief was let loose from the marine tribe Magus’ lips.

He raised his head and saw a bizarre scene. A giant sun suddenly emerged despite the fact that it was night, fusing with the moon and the brightest star, Venus.

The dazzling yet harmless light formed a thin line that descended to the earth.

*Rumble!* The air was unstable, and it seemed as if another large space was ‘squeezed’ into the place, causing the two spatial forcefields to overlap.

“It’s a success!” Leylin rejoiced covertly.

Using the A.I. Chip’s terrifying calculation abilities, he had mixed the opponent’s strength with his own, causing the time of opening of Scarlet Crescent to be brought forward.

This had not been his original intention, but he had suddenly been inspired after seeing the other party’s Morning Star Magus. It ended up being an advantage for him.

The early arrival of the ruins would likely cause the specific plans of the the person behind all this to be affected.

The more chaotic the situation, the more advantageous it was to Leylin.

“This– this– this is… the ruins of Scarlet Crescent!” The Marine Giant’s eyes grew wide as he mumbled in disbelief.

Though he knew it was possible that the ruins could appear at any of the 13 strongholds, it was too much of a coincidence that it had appeared where he was.

Seeing the image gradually becoming more distinct and forming a spatial passage glimmering with dark silver light, Siebel hesitated. However, he still choose to contact the other Magi and even their leader, the Radiant Moon Magus.

However, when his soul force touched the communicative device, Siebel was suddenly startled.

Their leader, the Radiant Moon Magus, was still in a spatial rift! Messages would definitely not be able to pass into the place. Even his other comrades were busy with the Morning Star Warlocks from the other side. The situation wasn’t going well, but where could he go to find reinforcements?

Seeing the look of hesitation on his opponent’s face, Leylin chuckled and had no intentions of continuing.

Though he was certain he could kill his opponent, he would need to use his Morning Star Arcane Art, and it would consume too much time. This was not the time and place.

Thus, like pulling open a curtain, Leylin’s hands pushed at the spatial crack and he walked in without the slightest hesitation.

After Leylin completely vanished into the spatial crack, Siebel gritted his teeth and spoke a few sentences to the communication imprint. He then followed and allowed the spatial waves to swallow him.

The bodies of Morning Star Magi were able to go through even spatial turbulence. Spatial passageways like these that were similar to teleporting to pocket dimensions generally had no specific teleportation spell formation, and could only be entered through force.

“What? The ruins have already appeared? So quickly?”

The Magi of both sides who were battling at the other strongholds seemed to receive the information at the same time. They, who were stunned by this sudden news, stood opposite each other for a moment without acting, then immediately rushed in the same direction.

At this moment, in the outer regions of the rift in the world.

Boundless stars and vortices were part of the background, filling it with a sense of vastness and might.

Here, it was as if a great war on the same level as that of ancient times was being replayed. A majestic lion that had a body of golden fur and three heads that kept spouting flames, ice and lightning suddenly stopped, seeming to be deep in thought.

In front of it was a Magus with a luxurious pitch-black magic robe, a strange moon-shaped rune on his forehead.

“Hehe… Wayde, you made an error in your calculations. Though you might be able to stall me, someone else is benefitting!”

This Magus was obviously the great rank 5 Magus of Jupiter’s Lightning. Now, however, his expression held a rare expression of exasperation.

This strange creature was not Wayde’s main body, but one of his most powerful clones. It had inherited the innate skills of the ancient clans, and its strength almost reached rank 5. Even he would find it difficult to take this being down, and might even be suppressed here.

“It’s a mistake on the astrologer’s part! It has nothing to do with the original plan!” A middle-aged man’s icy words sounded from the middle head of the three.

“Furthermore, I’m different from you. I’m just a clone…” The three-headed lion raised its claws, looking pleased.

“Could it be that you…” The Radiant Moon Magus’ expression suddenly changed as he tried to break through the seal and return.

“Trying to leave? How could it be that easy? Stay!” The three-headed golden lion roared, its three gigantic mouths opening.

A terrifying suction force similar to that of a black hole shot towards the Radiant Moon Magus. Even the rays of light in his surroundings were not spared as they were all sucked in. Howls and cries of indignance sounded every once in a while.

In the main world, a golden meteor streaked through the horizon.

Within the golden rays was a male Magus with long flaming hair that looked like a golden sunshine. His body and face seemed to be formed entirely of gold, and was full of dignity.

Meanwhile, however, he seemed to be deep in thought.

Outside, in the direction of the ruins of Scarlet Crescent, two groups of Morning Star Magi, and even Philip as well as Hunter Bolix, returned to their factions. After persisting with the confrontation for a while longer, they still charged into the spatial passageway at the same time.

The air suddenly became tranquil, and only the deep depressions in the ground and large puddles of water proved that there had been a battle of Morning Stars here.

Due to the extremely intense spell radiation, the region would be barren and void of life for a long period of time. There could even be formed a range of phenomena that would attract creatures of different planes, becoming another fearful area that would become famous in the central continent.

*Whoosh…* The air rippled as a breeze blew past, revealing the sudden appearance of another human figure.

“What’s going on? I calculated the timing based on the records of the ancestors. How could it have been brought forward?” A simple-clothed old man with a full head of white hair muttered, eyes without focus.

“The opening of the Scarlet Crescent ruins was initially an opportunity for our organisation to rise, but unexpectedly such complex issues are involved in there…”

The old man began to mutter to himself, “First was the discovery of our secret, causing several Warlock organisations and Jupiter’s Lightning to covet it. It even resulted in a war, and the diary that stated the time of appearance of the ruins was wrong. What exactly is going on?”

Because of Leylin, this old man whose origins were unknown was beginning to have doubts in his outlook of the world.

However, his education from a young age and the philosophy he had developed over the years allowed the old man to quickly regain his calm.

“No matter what it is, my ancestor was a member of Scarlet Crescent. My organisation is also one of the branches that has inherited part of the teachings of the ancient Scarlet Crescent organisation. This ruin should be ours!”

The old man’s expression instantly turned vicious, and a halo of resplendent starlight burst forth.

The spatial passageway opposite began to tremble as if it had sensed something. It, too, shot out a large amount of light, fusing with the splendour on the old man’s body and absorbing the whole bundle of starlight, leaving nothing behind.

“What a strange setup!” Leylin currently had his hands behind his back as he strolled along a spatial corridor filled with starlight, his own body shrouded in crimson.

There were multiple spatial rifts that caused turbulence within, but they could not cause even a ripple on his body.

“To completely isolate this region, I can only wait until a specific time. Only then can I enter the passageway through the spatial flow…” Leylin’s eyes were full of praise. “Such an intricate set-up, as well as space-division spells. This is truly frightening.”

The Morning Star realm that he had reached was only the bare minimum of ancient times. There was still a long way ahead, and he would naturally not feel conceited or complacent.

On the contrary, the more he knew, the more Leylin felt that the information he had acquired was much too little. He became increasingly humble.

The power who had set up such a spatial spell formation was an existence he needed to look up to and learn from…

Chapter 529: Obstruction and a Grin

“No! No matter what, I have to get it back!” The old man took out his light yellow notebook. A map with many black dots appeared on it immediately.

“Find him! Rip him apart! And bring everything back!” Following the old man’s growl, streaks of crystal-clear light flashed in the secret chamber and a few translucent puppets suddenly widened their bloodshot eyes.

As if they understood the old man’s words, they rapidly shuttled through the void, gradually vanishing.

“This feeling, something bad’s about to happen”

Leylin’s eyebrows furrowed. He’d actually been feeling a sense of discomfort ever since he exited the Path of Quandary. It was as if someone was secretly spying on him. However, the scanning of the A.I. Chip and his own soul force could not discover anything.

And now, this feeling of discomfort suddenly intensified, even to the point of turning to anxiety!

“The malice that’s pervaded the atmosphere…” Leylin shut his eyes and quickly opened them again. At this moment, his pupils had already turned into a pair of amber slits. A thin, blood-red line flashed across them.

Suddenly, rumbling sounds rang out as a large amount of spell runes flickered. A colourful radiance shot into the sky and formed a gigantic ice cage, trapping Leylin within.

“What? I definitely didn’t trigger any traps… Unless…” Leylin squinted his eyes slightly. This situation caused him to become clear-headed.

“Haha… I, who have gained control over the entire core secret chamber, am an invincible existence in Scarlet Crescent!” In the core control room, the old Magus’ face shone brightly, his hands still grasping a piece of ruby with its tips connected to numerous crystal threads.

Strings of complicated commands were continually transmitted through the ruby in his hands.

Numerous crystal-clear hexagonal snowflakes suddenly condensed within the trap, forming a large quantity of icy blades, shields, axes and such. They all smashed loudly towards Leylin’s head.

Leylin thought of an idea. “Kemoyin’s Scales!” “Blood Flame!” His body was immediately wrapped in a layer of dense, black snake scales as a blood-red flame raged above him, subliming the large quantity of ice.

As if it was provoked, the ice condensed once more with a sizzle. Its blue core became even more crystal-clear, emanating a piercing chill.

The ice, which was covered by the blue radiance, stood firmly while it was being roasted by the flames. A large quantity of cold air was emitted, even breaking through the Blood Flame’s seal. It shot in front of Leylin, who smashed it apart with a frown.

Sharp icy blades slashed his body, only enough to create thin, long sparks. They couldn’t even break through the outermost energy defence.

“Absolute Zero Kelvin!” Leylin’s pupils narrowed and his face no longer had the previous relaxed look.

”This was undoubtedly set up by ancient Magi. Such a formation that unifies all the runes in the area is definitely difficult for ordinary Morning Stars to withstand… However, It doesn’t seem to be working at full force… That means…”

Leylin seemed to be in a deadlock with the huge icy spell formation on the surface. However, he was actually calculating something in his mind.

*Whoosh!* Suddenly, space twisted and a few rays of white light seemed to have broken through the boundary as they appeared right before Leylin.

The handle, which bore the sharp broken sword, had already pierced the edge of Leylin’s chest.

“So fast!” It was difficult for Leylin to react in time. The only thing he managed to do was strengthen the Kemoyin Scales’ defence to the maximum.

Compared to other spells, the innate spells of Magi were activated purely by thought. With such incomparable speeds, they were the common last-ditch resorts when their lives were in danger.

*Schlick!* A broken sword, seemingly forged out of pure crystal, pierced through the energy defence as well as the runes outside the black scales with much difficulty, coming into contact with the scales themselves.

*Pop!* Leylin frowned, as if at something bursting. Behind him, a large Multi-Armed Race phantom came into existence and channeled a dark green energy to cover his body.

“My goodness!” The muscles on his right hand flexed, hammering a punch at the opponent. This made the translucent figure retreat.

After waiting for the opponent to put a certain amount of distance between them, Leylin looked at his chest with a gloomy face.

A bright white line in the shape of a crescent had been carved on the Kemoyin Scales. The sword had left behind a deep pit, taking a few smaller scales with it.

“Puppet?!” When Leylin got a clear view of the figures making a sneak attack, he shouted in surprise.

In front of him were a few translucent figures in pure white, body-fitting Magus robes. In their hands were a large quantity of physical weapons, including the broken crystal sword from before.

“A puppet that is able to break through my Kemoyin’s Scales defence, such a rank… I’m afraid can only be created by an ancient Magus…”

Leylin looked at the bloodshot eyes of the puppet before him, confirming his conjecture, ‘Someone’s behind all this.’

“So this is the power of a Morning Star? Even the Void Assassin could not take down the opponent!” In the core, the old man’s dignified face warped as he clenched his teeth.

“It doesn’t matter. I have the spell formations to control the core and the puppets on hand. Even if it takes up a little more energy, I have to take down the enemy!”

With his orders, the arms of the Void Assassins surrounding Leylin warped, revealing daggers, knives, and even weapons that looked like power saws. They were all translucent except for the golden runes twinkling on them, seemingly made from crystal.

Space twisted once more as these Void Assassins vanished into thin air again. It was as if they were vipers hiding in the dark, preparing to deal a fatal blow at any time!

With these enemies around eyeing covetously at their prey, in addition to the pressure of the icy cage above their head, any ordinary Morning Star would definitely have sustained serious injuries.

“It’s a pity that you met me!” A sneer emerged at the corner of Leylin’s lips. Wasn’t the shadow-attribute Giant Kemoyin Serpent even better at concealing itself in the void? He’d previously used spells such as Shadow Stealth to lay in ambush, and he naturally knew about the weaknesses and disadvantages of such spells like the back of his hand.

Although the ancient spell formation was a little more troublesome, the enemy evidently did not have complete control over it. This gave him an opportunity.

“Only…” Leylin laughed coldly as a radiance sparkled in his eyes.

A translucent figure shot out from the void with a whoosh, the dagger in its hands aimed ferociously at Leylin’s eyes.

Leylin’s face remained unchanged and he suddenly stretched out his wrist. When it came to a stop once more, he was holding one of the puppet’s arms in his hands.

A gigantic blue iceberg, with a great blazing flame at its bottom, started to exert pressure on everything below as it rumbled. At the same instant, a sharp aura suddenly shot out in the other three directions.

“Good! Very soon, that thing will belong to me…” In the control room, the old man watched a pale Leylin. Looking at his wounded body, he could not help but let out a carefree smile.

“Haha… So what if you’re a Morning Star? I’m the king here!” The old man spread out his arms and cheered, but his voice was instantly silenced with a grunt, as if he had been strangled at the neck.

When it came back, it returned as a frustrated curse, “How did he escape?”

In the projection he’d been looking at from the control room, Leylin’s condition had already hit rock bottom. His entire body was soaked in blood, and he seemed ready to die at any moment. However, every opportunity to kill him was thwarted by small problems in the coordination of the Void Assassins, letting him evade it by luck. At least, that’s what he’d seen it as.

And right when he was in the most desperate straits, that lucky Magus had actually discovered a flaw in the spell formation, directly breaking through space and escaping.

The old man roared in anger, smashing his fist violently on the platform of the control room with a bang.

“If I had known all the control spells, and obtained the highest authority, even a Radiant Moon Magus wouldn’t be able to escape this place, let alone this Morning Star!” What followed the bout of rage was a sense of helplessness.

Indeed, he’d used his map and reached the control room, obtaining partial authority by following his ancestor’s notes. In fact, he didn’t encounter much danger at all. However, his ancestor did not have a high position in Scarlet Crescent. This naturally meant he had no way to gain complete control of the place.

That previous spell formation was actually the limits of what he could accomplish with his current authority. As for those Void Assassins, he had to thank the fact that their creator was none other than his ancestor. That was why he had a backdoor method to take control of them.

“Damn! Damn! DAMN!” The old man’s face was full of indignance, “Just these Void Assassins have already made this trip worthwhile, but the most important item is still not in my hands. Not to mention, this place will definitely be monopolised by great forces in the future. I’ll no longer have a place here…”

He subconsciously shot a glance at the other black dots. They were already very close to the core area, especially the one that represented the Radiant Moon. It seemed to have an unstoppable force, barging its way through and already sweeping past several small-scaled resource points, making the Magus secretly hurt.

Such desire and the strong indignance led this Magus to a decision, “Try again, no matter the result, you have to leave!”

He looked at another screen, pressing the jewel down without hesitation. A huge flame exploded forth, forming an enormous blazing giant that blocked Leylin’s path.

“So it’s fire after ice? But it’s still of the same degree of power as the previous one…” Leylin shook his head, becoming more confident in his judgment.

“Catch him! Catch him!” The old Magus grabbed the jewel with both hands, his eyes full of excitement and desire.

And at this time, Leylin, who was in the screen, suddenly lifted his head and laughed at him. The old man’s hair stood on end…

Chapter 530: Sweeping of Obstacles

“Found you, you little rat!” The Magus was able to make out Leylin’s words from his mouth’s movements, immediately causing his eyes to turn red.

“Void Assassins, don’t hold back. Kill him!” As if having lost his self-control, the Magus held onto the command stick and roared.

*Whoosh! Whoosh! Whoosh!* At least eight Void Assassins appeared instantly, charging straight for Leylin. In front of him, the large flame giant was also snarling as it brandished a large flaming metal whip.

The sealing formation, the flames, and the surprise attacks from multiple Void Assassins would be extremely troublesome for normal Morning Stars to deal with.

Even Demon Hunter Cyril would probably be seriously injured under such an attack!

[Beep! Found spiritual force link. Eliminating three areas with fake signals, determining coordinates!]

The A.I. Chip’s robotic voice sounded by Leylin’s ears, causing a smile to rise up on his face. Ever since he realised that there was probably someone behind the scene, Leylin had commanded the A.I. Chip try and identify the location of the core control room.

The slip ups and injuries sustained from before were all intentionally done to get his opponent to take the bait.

A spell formation was not able to supply adequate data and information, but the other party had obviously not been satisfied. He had dispatched someone to attack, allowing the A.I. Chip to discover his traces immediately!

‘From my guesses and the A.I. Chip’s simulation, the other party probably isn’t that strong, and may not even have access to the core control room of the ruins. Otherwise, it wouldn’t be an attack just of this level!’

Leylin watched the sharp blade and flames coming towards him, a strange smile appearing on his face.

A splendid layer of crimson-red rays suddenly emerged from his body, turning into four rings that floated up and down.

“Rank 1 innate spells: Kemoyin’s Scales, Eyes of Petrification!”

“Rank 2 innate spell: Toxic Bile!”

“Rank 3 innate spell: Intimidating Gaze!”

“Rank 4 innate spell: Bloodline Metamorphosis! Combining to form the Morning Star Arcane Art: Kemoyin Serpent Transformation!”

*Rumble!* A humongous serpent that measured tens of thousands of metres long suddenly descended on the region.

Spell formations fell apart, the earth cracked, and multiple buildings turned to dust. Even the air was beginning to shake.

*Po!* The flame giant from before, as well as the many bindings and fire elemental spell formations, were swept away by the large snake’s body. All the runes were destroyed, and even the the spell formations at the base of the buildings flickered out.

In front of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, the Void Assassins that were the size of a regular human were like ants. Their sharp swords could not even pierce through the scales, and instead, were sent crashing to a random area with a swing of its tail.

The Arcane Art of the ancient Morning Star Warlocks— Kemoyin Serpent Transformation. This trump card that would allow Warlocks to transform into a terrifying ancient beast appeared once more!

The giant black snake hissed as it aimed its head in a specific direction, its starry amber eyes the very personification of ridicule. Its body was like a black storm as it crushed the area.

*Thump! Thump! Thump!* On the way, various little flickers of brilliance could be seen on the giant serpent’s body, which then dimmed.

“Wha- What’s going on? Is this a Morning Star Arcane Art? He- he dared-”

Having been locked onto by the aura of an ancient, giant beast, the Magus in the core control room went limp and fell to the ground. As he made contact with the other party’s eyes, the fear hidden deep in his genes exploded forth as his body went stiff, unable to move even a finger.

The direction in which the giant serpent had looked in was evidently the location of the core control room. Seeing how the other party was crushing everything in its way, it would probably take seconds to reach him.

This old man shuddered, now regretting provoking this fiendish person.

*Boom!* Like in a magnitude 9 earthquake, all the items in the core control room jumped up and fell loudly onto the ground.

Hearing the accompanying hisses, the old man shuddered even more in fright. He knew that the terrifying ancient, vicious beast had now reached the outside of the core control room.

“I have the defensive spell formation of the core control room. It… It’ll be fine!”

The attack from before had been obstructed, giving the old man some confidence. However, before he could struggle to get up, an even more powerful tremor could be felt.

*Rumble!* Bricks fell everywhere and the roof was torn open. Two eyes that were like stars shot out terrifying rays of light.

“Ah!” The old man went limp, a fishy smell even travelling from the crotch of his pants.

“Little worm, do you think you can hide?” The gigantic serpent suddenly turned small, regaining the size of a regular human. Large amounts of black gas turned into armour that merged onto his perfect body.

Leylin charged into the control room and held the old man by the throat, eyes flashing with a dangerous glint, “A mere Crystal Phase Magus dares attack a Morning Star on the sly?”

His own aura had weakened slightly, the consumption from before had not been small.

Due to the limitations of the peace agreement, Morning Star Magi were not allowed to use Arcane Arts that would affect large areas in the central continent. However, this was the Scarlet Crescent ruins, and technically speaking was not on the central continent. Naturally, that agreement did not extend to this place.

But why did the other Morning Star not use it?

It was because there were usually extremely powerful spell formations in the ruins. If the range of the Arcane Arts were too large, there would definitely be a chain reaction that would not be beneficial to the Morning Star Magi.

The second was because Magi had entered in order to plunder resources. How could they use such a powerful technique and destroy everything? Did they not want the loot?

Only people like Leylin, who thought nothing was taboo and had the A.I. Chip to find the specific location of his opponent, dared to bulldoze through after determining there were no traps or counteracting spell formations.

This also had to do with the old man having yet to gain complete control. If not, with the activation of any of the true ancient spell formations, Leylin would definitely be unable to break through and might even be trapped to his death by the spell formation.

“But since I started it, the situation will immediately change…”

Leylin laughed wryly inside. This was the consequence, but thankfully, he’d already prepared himself mentally. Even if he did not gain much here, it was all worth it.

“Hm? These undulations? Morning Star Arcane Art?!”

Vicious energy undulations immediately passed through the range of the ruins. Almost all Morning Star understood in that instant.

“Since someone has already made the first move, we need to hurry up!”

Cybel glanced at the wall made of large amounts of vines, and immediately looked annoyed, “Get out of the way!”

“Of course, my lord!” Paul, who knew what Cybel was planning on doing, immediately retreated far into the distance in case he got injured.

Afterwards, frightening energy undulations gathered at Cybel’s body, and a giant, all-annihilating storm even more terrifying than Philip’s swept through the place…

“A bunch of youngsters who don’t know how to follow rules!”

At the other end, a middle-aged man, golden all over like a god, shook his head helplessly. He put down a document in his hands.

“Anyway, someone has already taken control of a portion of the detection spell formation in the ruins. There’s also that feeling of being spied on…”

The middle-aged man’s brows furrowed, “I’m afraid that this truly must be the headquarters of the ancient Scarlet Crescent, and must have a high value. If news of how I had come here with a group of Morning Stars and yet was one-upped by someone else spreads, it’ll definitely be a huge joke…”

“In that case!” The phantom of a giant gold lion appeared behind the middle-aged Magus.

*Boom!* Just the pressure from the aura was enough for the entire building to collapse, the air shattering like iron chains.

“This feeling… These undulations… It’s a great Radiant Moon Magus!”

Collins, as well as the other Morning Star Magi, began to look grim at the other end.

The phantom image of a golden lion in the horizon gave them a very bad feeling.

It was not just the Morning Stars of Jupiter’s Lightning. Even the Warlocks of Spirit Circle and Wind Wolf Lair immediately sped up their movements, berserk energy waves emanating from them.

When they no longer had reservations, the terrifying destructive ability of Morning Star Magi were showcased completely.

“As expected, after I made the first move, it caused a chain reaction among the other Morning Stars. None of them are holding back anymore and charging in this direction…”

Leylin looked at the notebook that lay wide open. Many buildings had already been broken through by a few black dots, and there were warning sirens everywhere.

*Gurgle… Gurgle…*

The old man was almost unconscious.

Never did he expect that, in just a short instant, these Morning Stars would suddenly turn into ancient oppressive beasts, the defensive spell formations like a mere joke in front of them.

At the thought that he had even thought of relying on the spell formations here to deal with them, cold sweat unceasingly dripped from the old man’s forehead.

Leylin had yet to come up with a way to deal with the descendant of Scarlet Crescent. He had a very soft personality, and just by being threatened, he had immediately handed everything over, which included even the jurisdiction to control the Void Assassins. This saved Leylin some time, and also allowed the old man to escape the gruesome fate of having his soul searched.

It was not just this. On the other party’s body, Leylin found the inheritance from his ancestor, which was quite a large harvest.

From his eyes, Leylin could tell that the old man still seemed to be hiding something. Time was scarce, however, and Leylin could not waste more time to settle it.

“What are you afraid of? The setup of an ancient Magus won’t be that simple…”

Leylin shot the man a glance and spoke disdainfully. Though his earlier actions might have seemed reckless, the route had already gone through the A.I. Chip’s meticulous probing and calculations, and he had not triggered any fundamental, large formations.

After all, for ancient Magi, Morning Star was the bare minimum level. How could there not be specific countering spell formations? Those Magi would probably soon be in trouble.

Chapter 532: Setup

Previously, hidden in the control room, the scenes of Siebel’s death were displayed on the crystal screen for a pair of crimson eyes.

When the point mass was caught by the person behind this whole situation, the power bar increased by one unit on the side of the screen.

“…” The crimson light in that pair of eyes flickered intensely, but it soon subsided.

The chamber turned deathly silent again. A dark figure stayed at its spot, unmoving, unbreathing.

Meanwhile, news of Siebel’s death swept through the entire ruins like a hurricane.

“What’s this feeling?” Leylin’s face changed the moment the astral plane opened automatically upon Siebel’s death. He felt the fluctuation in the atmosphere of the astral plane and the point mass.

It was the same feeling he’d gotten when he’d killed Cyril, something he’d never forget.

“The death of a Morning Star Magus? The point mass returning to the astral plane?” Leylin mumbled in disbelief.

He took a long breath afterwards, “Sure enough, ancient ruins aren’t this simple. Even this core control room could be a mere disguise, with another true one hidden somewhere else!”

Leylin had gotten this suspicion a little earlier. Even if the old man didn’t have full authorisation, the defence of this place was far too weak. Now, it seemed it was only to be expected if this place was just a ruse that could only control the simplest spell formations.

Those powerful spell formations that had the power to suppress Morning Star Magi, and were even strong enough to kill them, were all hidden somewhere in the dark.

Leylin looked at the old man who was lying on the ground with sympathy when he thought of this.

It was obvious that his ancestor was of little importance in Scarlet Crescent, he had not even gotten a single bit of information about such matters.

“Anyway, all these things is none of my business. I’ve gotten what’s important, and therefore, it’s time to leave…” Leylin smiled, then flipped open the pale yellow notebook.

Even if the old man’s ancestor did not have much status, they had been very careful and had even noted down a secret passageway for the sake of their descendants. It allowed Leylin to leave Scarlet Crescent directly without returning through the original route, which greatly reduced the level of danger.

“If this works out, the mission this time will truly have gone perfectly!”

Leylin rubbed his chin, “The others only know that I have entered the ruin, but they don’t know what I have gained, there’s still room for manipulation.”

At the bottom of his heart was an idea about how to break apart the bloodline shackles, a gift from the ancient Wisdom Tree. This was priceless information for bloodline Warlocks.

Because of this, Leylin had to safeguard the secret, or else he could be rejected and even persecuted by the bloodline Warlocks.

“The timing’s just right. I know Siebel’s dead, but the rest of the Morning Star Magi aren’t aware of this, which means he can be my scapegoat!”

Leylin could not help but sneer as he thought of what he saw in the core control room earlier on.

The other Morning Star Magi did not have the spell formation of this control room to monitor the entire ruin. At most, they only knew that one Morning Star Magus had perished, but they would not know which one it was.

In this case, it was possible for him to disguise himself as Siebel, it wasn’t like the dead could talk.

“Transfiguration! Projection Technique!” With a thought, Leylin’s aura changed, becoming similar to Siebel’s.

But this was far from enough. His cover would be blown the moment a Morning Star Magus scanned him with soul force.

“I planned to use this for research or just to sell it off. Who knew I’d be using it now…” Leylin flipped his palm, revealing a translucent test tube. There was a tinge of blue blood in it, emanating light.

This was the blood Leylin had extracted from Siebel during their fight.

“Conceal the bloodline! This is going to remove all light and resist detection…” Leylin spoke in a half-singing and half-chanting voice.

These were Arcane Arts that the A.I. Chip had deduced from the inherited memories of the bloodline.

It enabled one to use the bloodline of the target, covering up their own aura and imitate the energy fluctuations on the target. Soul force would be unable to detect it.

Moreover, this was a long-lost arcane art of bloodlines. Leylin had witnessed it when he’d awakened his own Kemoyin bloodline. Other Morning Star Magi would definitely not have thought of it.

The spells sounded out as the test tube opened up in tandem with Leylin’s incantation. The blue blood drifted into the air, turning into a hazy shadow that enveloped Leylin.

In the blink of an eye, Leylin looked as if he changed into another person. Not only did he have the same look as Siebel, even his aura mimicked those of the marine tribe.

It was so much so that the energy fluctuations of a Magus were emitted from him, as opposed to those of the vastly different Warlocks.

Even the Radiant Moon Magus of Jupiter’s Lightning would find it hard to recognise him under such circumstances.

“Ma– Master?”

The old man who sat on the ground saw Leylin changing completely into someone else, and he could not help but stutter.

Leylin soon turned and looked at him, a trace of hostility flashing in his eyes.

Tremendous golden flames crackled and melted the void within seconds, clearing out a path of lava.

A blonde-haired middle-aged Warlock walked out with both hands behind him, followed by the phantom of a humongous golden lion.

“Right here! This is the first location where the energy fluctuations of a Morning Star Magus appeared. The core control room must be nearby!”

His brows furrowed while he glanced through the scenery on both sides. Looking at the huge depression and the remaining seawater, he frowned.

“Was I too late?”

*Bang!* Just then, the core control room nearby exploded, and a ferocious blaze engulfed everything.

The Warlock snorted with disdain, and a huge amount of fire was absorbed by the phantom at his back in an instant. His powerful soul force scanned around and discovered a blue figure immediately.

“Are you still trying to leave?” He smiled sarcastically, while a ray of golden lightning shot out immediately from the phantom behind him, quickly arriving at the blue figure.

“Arcane Art— Myriad Waves!”

An illusory domain in the form of a blue ocean was emanated from the blue figure, and a large surge of waves rushed ahead to form a huge wall that shielded him.

*Ka-cha!* Golden lightning split the waves apart, revealing the original form of the trembling fellow.

This was a giant who was a few meters tall, covered in blue skin. The inhuman aura was obvious.

“Marine Giant Siebel? Indeed, he was the fellow guarding this region, and one of the first to enter the ruins…” The middle-aged Warlock nodded, then he saw Siebel’s figure flicker before he fled quickly.

“You can’t escape!” Wayde, the Radiant Moon Warlock followed after him right away. As the blue giant was the first to reach the core control room, he must have gotten lots of treasure. Just the structural plans of the ruins would have him green with envy.

“Hand me everything you’ve obtained, and I will allow your truesoul back into the astral plane!” Wayde looked indifferent, but the phantom lion behind him started to fidget.

‘Only a fool will stay still…’ Half of Leylin’s body was severely burnt, but his figure moved swiftly in the ruins to escape. Even though the situation was bad, he had managed to escape from Wayde for the moment with the guidance of the map he had acquired.

Leylin put in huge effort to disguise himself as Siebel in this time period. Not only had he changed his aura completely using the Arcane Art, he had also used the data recorded by the A.I. Chip to imitate his domain, perfecting the facade.

With the aura, domain, and even the face matching, even if Leylin told him the truth now, Wayde wouldn’t believe him.

Not to mention that he’d spent a lot of effort to conceal his powerful spells. With the rush he was in, his opponent would not have a single clue about his identity.

As for the old man and the core control room, Leylin had destroyed them both; he would never let someone who knew his secrets to live. After all, once the old man fell into another’s hands, his disguise would be rendered useless.

‘I didn’t expect him to be this fast… Moreover, he’s a rank 5 Magus who excels at lightning-based attacks!’ Leylin smiled wryly. He had disguised himself as Siebel, and even had to mimic his spells. Despite the fact that Leylin knew water could not outpower lightning, he continued to use water spells to fight against Wayde as he could not risk exposing himself.

What was worse was that the opponent was way too fast. He had been caught unprepared.

However, it was all worth it.

A trace of a smile showed up on Leylin’s face, and blue light flickered in his eyes as he tested Wayde’s patience with the help of the numerous spell formations in the ruins.

At last, Wayde fumed with rage at the slippery moves of the Morning Star Magus before him, and did not want to probe Siebel any longer.

“Void Devourer!” His hand reached out ferociously, and the phantom opened its monstrous mouth in an attempt to swallow him.

*Buzz!* As if a massive black hole had appeared in the void, everything distorted and disappeared into the lion’s monstrous mouth.

‘This was what I was waiting for!’ Leylin’s eyes glinted, and he hid behind another huge bell tower.

*Crack!* The bell tower was broken, and even the foundation was uprooted by the suction force.

*Buzz!* A strong wave of energy appeared, unveiling a complex spell formation hidden underground.

“Hmmm, what’s this? Power from the core?” Wayde’s brows furrowed. Soon, he was buried in crimson spell formations that came out of the blue.

“Intruder spotted, Radiant Moon Warlock!” A cold mechanic voice sounded.

Chapter 533: The Continuation

“Success!” Not far away, the golden lion phantom was trapped in a crimson spell formation. Seeing it growl continuously, Leylin clenched his fist resolutely.

Since he had the guts to take Siebel’s place, he naturally also had a way out.

Many important locations were marked out on the notebook he had seized. The energy hub was one of the most important places. Leylin was confident that once this area was attacked, the hidden defense program would immediately be activated.

After all, he had intentionally avoided many spell formations along the way, and used Morning Star Arcane Arts with restraint. Thus, he appeared relatively harmless. Needless to say, the program would deal with the more terrifying rank 5 Warlock first.

A Radiant Moon Warlock was not to be trifled with. Even in the ancient times, such a Warlock was a strong contender that conquered.

The collisions between these two would instantly devastate their surroundings, causing an already chaotic region to become even more disordered.

Even if there were any problems or clues left behind, they would have been quickly wiped out in the destruction.

As the golden lion phantom continued growling, Leylin smiled coldly, his body completely fading into the void.

The ruins no longer held any attraction for Leylin. The dangers would increase exponentially, and forcing himself to stay wouldn’t bring him any benefits as well. Leylin thus decided to evacuate.

Half a month later, Phosphorescence Swamp, Ouroboros Clan headquarters, inside of Leylin’s huge castle.

“How were the ruins of Scarlet Crescent?” Leylin was now wearing a loose robe and conversing leisurely with someone else through the screen in front of him.

Paul’s figure surfaced on the screen, just that he seemed a little gloomy. Even his tentacles were drooping listlessly. Evidently, he didn’t receive any good news.

“It has been confirmed that the ruins of Scarlet Crescent have been completely closed. The coordinates have all become invalid, and I reckon that it has undertaken a spatial jump!” Paul didn’t look too well.

Previously, with the directions from the notebook, Leylin had managed to escape unharmed through a spatial path that had opened up. Hence, he also missed the drastic changes that had taken place afterwards in the ruins. Of course, this was how he avoided danger.

It was only after Paul and company emerged in a fluster that Leylin found out about what had happened in the ruins.

It turned out that the ancient Magi from the Scarlet Crescent had left behind an Adamantine Golem in the ruins, which acted as the control centre.

This Adamantine Golem had an intelligence on par with humans, and could think like a normal human being, except that it was equipped with a program to comply with orders.

What was even more special was that not only had this Adamantine Golem mastered all the ancient spell formations in the ruins, it could also recharge itself by devouring Morning Star Magus point masses!

During the previous fight, upon discovering that it couldn’t defeat the rank 5 Warlock, Wayde, the Adamantine Golem immediately started attacking the other Morning Star Magi in the ruins.

Numerous ancient spell formations had surfaced, costing Paul and company dearly.

In front of spell formations specially deployed by the ancient Magi, even Morning Stars were destined to fall. Blair and another Morning Star had fallen straight away from Spirit Circle. On Wind Wolf Lair’s end, Philip was seriously injured while Palesa fell directly. Even Cybel, the strongest of them all, was severely wounded, and was rumored to have almost fallen from his Morning Star position.

On the other hand, Jupiter’s Lightning was no better. At least half of their men suffered grave injuries, while the remaining few had superficial wounds.

After recharging through absorbing numerous point masses, the Adamantine Golem started to show its prowess. With the assistance of the many ancient spell formations, even Wayde was wounded and eventually chased out.

The other Morning Stars had to get themselves out of danger one by one. Paul was lucky; he had managed to jostle his way into a spatial crack, and was teleported to the border of the Magus world, which saved his life.

From then onwards, the Scarlet Crescent ruins vanished from Crystal Mountain. Other Magi came forth afterwards, but no matter how hard they tried to scout it out, not even a trace of the place could be found.

According to the judgment of a few specialists, the Adamantine Golem must have activated a spatial jump right after attaining sufficient energy, teleporting the ruins away.

Under such a situation, these Magi were so stunned that they could only drop the idea of going in for another round of looting.

As for Leylin? He fabricated a lie about how he hadn’t gained a lot after entering the pocket dimension, and had immediately backed out after the rank 5 battle started.

This, of course, raised doubts from Cybel and the others, but those were only suspicions. Furthermore, as they had just lost a great deal of strength, they were in no position to question Leylin.

Additionally, someone else had taken the limelight away from Leylin.

“Oh right, has Sebel been found?” Leylin asked seriously, trying to contain his laughter.

Due to Wayde’s allegations and other evidence, many Morning Stars unanimously agreed that the Marine Giant Siebel of Jupiter’s Lightning had gained the most fortune from the ruins, and had even intruded into the core control room.

Jupiter’s Lightning reacted relatively strangely. They declared that Siebel had already fallen and perished. Even the deity egg in the Magus Tower was damaged. This did raise some suspicions.

However, the Warlocks led by Wayde were enemies with them, and thus did not receive any response. They could only try to probe for information on the sly.

“He hasn’t! As you know, prophesying about a Morning Star Magus is really troublesome, especially with the presence of the Morning Star domain. Coupled with the radiation from the Magus himself, even a Radiant Moon Magus specializing in prophecy spells cannot solve such problems. We need someone that is at least a Breaking Dawn, and he has to be an expert in prophesies…”

Paul gave a forced laugh. A Breaking Dawn throne specializing in prophesies? Leylin smirked. Such a person has never been seen before in the central continent.

“We suffered many losses this time round, and returned with only injuries. Only you managed to reap some decent gains!” Paul seemed sour, which was rare. He stared at Leylin’s right ear.

Leylin gave a light laugh and touched his earlobe. A crescent accessory covered his ear, casting a crescent shadow.

This was a high-grade magic equipment: the Scarlet Earring! After confirming that it didn’t pose any danger, Leylin immediately put it on.

A high-grade magic equipment! Even Morning Star Magi would be envious. After all, even the raw materials of such an item have disappeared from the face of the central continent for a long time, thus it would be impossible to produce it again.

Perhaps only the Breaking Dawn noble powers who have explored other worlds and obtained loads of resources might own a few of these items.

Most of the magic equipment that Leylin had seen before were low-grade items, and even middle-grade items were rare. It wouldn’t be hard to guess the value of this high-grade piece magic equipment.

Not only did Leylin escape unscathed, he even reaped relatively huge gains. It was no wonder that Paul was envious of him.

It was only after much deliberation did Leylin that decide to display this magic equipment. His previous actions may have appeared suspicious; if the first batch of Magi who entered left without a single piece of loot, it would attract unwanted attention.

Now, the appearance of the Scarlet Earring would serve as a reasonable explanation for all that happened.

Paul thought to himself, ‘If it was me, perhaps I would have been satisfied with the discovery of the Scarlet Earring as well. It would have been enough for me to stop there and find my way out instead.’

What was more miraculous was how the complete disappearance of the Scarlet Crescent ruins had made most of the contract that Leylin signed with them obsolete. He didn’t even have to redistribute what he’d obtained.

Initially, when they decided upon the allocation, they had included the entire ruins as one of the most important lands. Now that they had suffered a dead loss, the agreement would naturally lose its validity as well.

This was definitely beneficial for Leylin.

He was prepared to keep the secret of the ancient Wisdom Tree until his death. It was only an intelligence report anyway, and didn’t occupy much of his share. Withholding this piece of information and then distributing his profits fairly would deceive everyone.

Now that he was the sole owner of all the shares, it was even better.

As the previous agreement was made obsolete, anything obtained from the ruins would be belong to the person who found it. No matter how jealous Paul was, he couldn’t do anything about it.

With such a high-grade magic equipment, it was needless to say that Leylin’s strength would increase exponentially. Now that Cybel was suffering from heavy losses, they couldn’t make things ugly even if they wanted to, as their strength could not be compared to Leylin’s.

Not only that,Spirit Circle and Wind Wolf Lair had suffered great losses in terms of strength. The successive fall of their Morning Stars caused problems to surface in their rule. Enemies from before also started getting themselves ready for action.

In such uncertain times, they would be more than willing to receive external assistance from Leylin, who had good connections. This would be more favourable than allowing him to side with their enemies.

That was how this matter passed.

‘If it were not for the two Radiant Moons!’ Leylin secretly added on.

Although Leylin had tried his best to cover his tracks through questioning himself, it was hard to guarantee that he didn’t leave any traces behind at all. If the Scarlet Crescent ruins were found, or even broken into, it would be possible to find gaps through on-site tests.

There were many tricks up the sleeves of those Radiant Moon Magi, many of which he would not have even thought of. Thus, there was still a hidden danger.

But what was a little risk compared to these returns?

Furthermore, the Radiant Moon Warlock on Leylin’s end, Wayde, was very certain that the Marine Giant Siebel was the main culprit. This imperceptibly lifted immense pressure off Leylin. Since he had long offended that Radiant Moon Magus from Jupiter’s Lightning, a little more enmity wouldn’t make much difference.

“Oh right, Sir Leylin, you seemed to have gained a lot from this trip to the Scarlet Crescent ruins. I have a few items here as well, how about a mutual exchange?” Paul finally revealed his true intention of making the call.

Although both he and Leylin had obtained a few items in the ruins, they might not be fit for use, thus it was vital to exchange items of equivalent value.

Chapter 541: Determination and Action

The spiritual flame of a Morning Star Magus had an intricate relationship with their body. Its strength also reflected the time the Magus had remaining.

That Freya’s necklace had encountered such a situation meant the original body of Blood Duchess Emma had likely been dealt severe damage in the foreign world.

Trauma would weaken a Magus’ vitality, which in turn caused such a change in the spiritual flame they left behind.

“Mentor… Mentor!” Freya’s eyes turned red as she covered her mouth, but Leylin’s secret imprint twinkled before he could try to console her.

“Yes, Faisal?” Leylin frowned as he tapped the secret imprint open.

“Your Grace, my Mentor… the spiritual flame of the First Elder was extinguished a minute ago…” Faisal’s voice was husky. It was as if his heart had sunk, and he was feeling hopeless.

“Extinguished?” Leylin touched his chin. If the spiritual flame had been extinguished, the Morning Star Warlock’s originally body must have perished.

The only thing that supported the First Elder’s group was that he was still alive. There was still hope for them to return from the foreign world.

And now, that final hope had been shattered. Faisal’s change was understandable.

“But what happened? Wasn’t it all good until now?” Leylin felt puzzled, it seemed like a conspiracy was afoot.

Another connection request came up before Leylin could end Faisal’s secret imprint call, and Kesha’s panicked voice sounded out.

“Leylin! Leylin!” She called his name directly, forgetting about his current status. It showed how desperate she was.

“What happened?” The ominous feeling in Leylin’s heart grew stronger.

“… Forgive me, Your Grace!” Kesha paused to correct her misbehaviour before continuing, “It’s Mentor. The spiritual flame Duke Gilbert left behind has grown extremely unstable, and is flickering strongly. I… I’m very worried…”

“I got it!” Leylin nodded, and his voice turned serious and solemn, “Pass down my orders, all Crystal Phase Warlocks are to report to the meeting room. We might be in trouble…”

The Warlock elites were now congregated here instead of residing in their own territories. Since they were all in Phosphorescence Swamp, they could gather immediately after Leylin’s orders were passed.

Leylin reckoned that these people would not have come so fast if it was not related to their teachers.

“Duke Farlier!” The panic-stricken Warlocks calmed a little upon seeing Leylin dressed in his huge robe.

“Please, sit down and be at ease!” Leylin sat at the head chair. With his battle experience, he had long since acquired a dignified aura that turned the meeting room solemn.

“Thank you, Your Grace!” A number of Crystal Phase Magi bowed and settled down in order.

By virtue of being his wife, Freya occupied the seat next to Leylin, a fact that left some of the rest in envy.

Leylin sighed while looking at the handful of Crystal Phase Warlocks in an upright position. The last war had caused tremendous loss to the Ouroboros Clan, and the loss of their elite forces was especially tough to recover from.

It would take at least a few hundred years for them to recover to peak condition.

“Schadt, report!” Leylin said after glancing across everyone and called for Schadt only when everyone settled down.

“Master!” Schadt wiped off the fog that was on his thick spectacles, bowing to Leylin immediately after he stood up. He spoke in a dignified manner, “The spiritual flames of the elders that we’d kept in our technical department started fluctuating vigorously 24 minutes ago, and the First Elder’s has completely died out. I’m afraid that…”

Leylin too felt somewhat frustrated and aggrieved. After all, this was the fall of another Morning Star Warlock.

Even though Schadt did not continue his words, Faisal and one of the Crystal Phase Warlocks had lowered their heads. Losing the First Elder was definitely a huge blow to their morale.

“I’ve asked the other two Morning Star seeds as well. It’s not just a single spiritual flame that flickered, it’s all of them. The other two elders must be in the same plight as the First Elder in the foreign world…”

There was not much to say for now. After Schadt sat down, the rest of the Warlocks placed their focus on Leylin.

Upon seeing their reaction, Leylin cleared his throat, “Schadt, have the coordinates of the foreign world been confirmed?”

“My apologies! The technical department and I have been working on this problem endlessly. There are two possible coordinates on our list, I will send them to you after this!”

A tinge of shame surfaced on Schadt’s face. This incident was a humiliation to the entire technical department. They had been overconfident and bragged that they were going to solve the problem in a few days’ time, but took them nearly five years. It was such a dereliction of their duty.

The Crystal Phase Warlock who had tears in the eyes just like Faisal slammed the table and shouted, “Schadt, you old fogey! Are you pulling strings and intentionally not revealing the coordinates of the foreign world?”

The moment he heard these words, Schadt fumed with rage. “Nonsense! I vow in the name of everyone in the technical department, never have I orchestrated something like that!”

Before, he’d suffered in silence because it had been difficult for him to locate the coordinates. Afterwards, there seemed to be another strange interference that added to the complexity, leaving him grasping at his hair.

‘Could it be the interference of another organisation that is not eager to see our Dukes being saved?’ A thought surfaced in Schadt’s mind, but was quickly suppressed as it was too sinister a plot.

However, Faisal remained silent. Hid reaction affirmed the Warlock’s suspicion, but before he could snarl at him, Faisal dragged his arm with force.

“What the hell are you doing, Faisal!” The Crystal Phase Warlock growled.

“Watch your manners, Marquis Ordofol!” Faisal’s voice was equally low, but it carried within an undeniable order.

“I’m sorry, I acted out of line! Please forgive me, Marquis Schadt!” The Warlock’s face blushed, but he stilled apologised to Schadt and bowed to Leylin who was in the head seat, “Please forgive me, Your Grace!”

“Never mind!” Leylin waved and stared at Faisal with intrigue until sweat glided down his cheeks.

Leylin took a last look at the Warlocks before he spoke in a low voice, “I have come to a decision, I will set off tomorrow to rescue the Elders!”

There was a minute of pause, which then quickly recovered as excitement and joy could be seen in everyone’s eyes.

Still, they did not dare to show their emotions. They kept reminding Leylin not to fall for tricks.

“My dear…” After all the Crystal Phase Warlocks had been dismissed, only Freya was left behind, her eyes filled with worry.

Emma was her Mentor, but Leylin was her dearest husband. This situation was complicated, like a spider web that pulled her heart apart.

At last, she asked, “This time round… is it going to be dangerous?”

“Yes, there will be danger, but it’s a chance too! Trust me, I’ll bring your mentor back!” Leylin gave Freya a reassuring, heart-warming smile.

Seeing Leylin with such confidence, Freya felt more at ease. However, she had missed the trace of complication in Leylin’s eyes.

After returning to the Magus Tower, Leylin went straight to the astral gate and fell into deep thought.

“This time… I’m afraid that I really have to make the trip!” Leylin was very clear on the fact that there were voices asking for his help being circulated in the Ouroboros Clan, and they had grown stronger now.

He had suppressed these messages as long as he could. He had to do something now, otherwise the entire Ouroboros Clan might fall apart.

Luckily, he had already gotten what he wanted during this period of time. Even if the other two Morning Star Warlocks returned, his power in the clan was unshakeable.

Also, Leylin was not too worried about the trip as he had already formed a more complete strategy after getting to know the existence of the puppetmaster behind the scene.

Almost at the same time, high up on a throne that was made from eternal darkness and rumbling thunder.

The rank 5 Magus that had a moon rune on his forehead was exchanging thoughts with someone through telepathy.

“How are things going with the Ouroboros Clan?”

“Everything has been prepared and we are ready to take action! As long the opponent enters the foreign world, we can block him completely from this world and wipe out the entire Ouroboros Clan!”

“You disappointed me the last time. I do not wish to see it again!” The Radiant Moon Magus warned with great dignity.

“There is no need to worry, Master!” The Morning Star conscient dispersed on its own, and the Radiant Moon Magus sat still in the throne, pondering.

“Was it really that kiddo in the ruins of Scarlet Crescent? What an interesting pup!” A mysterious voice sounded in the air, but the Radiant Moon Magus did not seem surprised at all.

“I wasn’t quite confident, but Siebel’s already dead; he’s the most suspicious!” Radiant Moon Magus spoke in a cold tone, “I have to get him!”

“He’s just a Kemoyin Serpent Warlock, even if he had any trump cards, the bloodline shackles will be his Achilles heel!” the mysterious voice sounded in disdain.

Chapter 543: Lava World

Knowing that it was a trap, those who still jumped straight in were idiots!

Leylin was obviously not an idiot. Since the other party had revealed that they had the ability to interfere with astral gates, Leylin obviously would not ignore them.

In fact, in these five years, he had been silently surveying the other world. He had even attempted projecting spiritual seeds, all in order to thoroughly understand the other party’s ability to interfere.

Through the five years of probing that seemed to only last a day, he had long since understood the methods they could use like the back of his hand. He’d even prepared a contingency plan.

“It’s offensive pattern number 3. Activate corresponding countermeasures!” Leylin’s eyes glinted with intelligence.

[Task initiated. Spatial anchor being projected. Tracing target’s coordinates…]

The A.I. Chip began to operate methodically.

A layer of mysterious spatial undulations was emanated from Leylin’s body.

[Target coordinates have been determined. Proceed with attack?]

The A.I. Chip asked with a robotic voice.

“Yes!” A smile appeared about Leylin’s lips.

*Bang!* *Boom!* A glass meter exploded, and many pieces of apparatus burst into flames. Collins, who was watching on, was about to go berserk.

“What’s going on? Who can tell me what’s going on?” Collins roared, his eyes red.

Even Breaking Dawn Magi would find it difficult to obtain this high-grade spatial interference apparatus. This time, so many pieces had readings that went off the charts, and his master would probably murder him.

“The other party seems to have grasped some sort of spatial technique and is counter-attacking!” An old man pushed at the lens in his glasses and concluded.

“Are you kidding me? Do you know how valuable research on spatial techniques is? How did he get it?” Collins’ first reaction was that of disbelief.

“But that’s the only explanation! If the other party’s spatial knowledge reserves are vaster than ours, we’ll probably have to be on our guard against the following spatial attacks!” The old man spoke rapidly.

“Spatial attacks?” Collins was stunned, and immediately after, saw the earth-shattering spatial turbulence that submerged the area…

“The effects aren’t half bad!” Listening to the prompt from the A.I. Chip, Leylin’s mood immediately improved.

Arcane Arts and knowledge regarding spatial coordinates were obviously insanely expensive. They were rarely seen, even in the Morning Star area.

However, he had the A.I. Chip and did not need very complete information. Hence, he had purchased just a few incomplete ones.

Though he could not be considered a great master in this area, attacking a few guys who were similarly newbies wouldn’t be a problem.

“You dare—” An enraged voice sounded. Another Magus with a black moon rune on his forehead suddenly appeared at the boundary of the world, trying to intercept Leylin.

“I am your opponent!” Along with the sounds of a lion growling, another Warlock with hair that seemed to be cast out of gold appeared in front of that Magus.

“Wayde…” The Radiant Moon Magus called out in a low tone, his expression revealing his fear.

“The other plan has been launched! Is that the Radiant Moon Magus from Jupiter’s Lightning?” Leylin turned and took a glimpse, storing the other party’s appearance in his memory.

*Whoosh!* As he was breaking through the protective sphere of a world, enormous astral forces had been activated and Leylin felt himself go dizzy. His body seemed to turn into a streak of light and then completely disappeared.

Compared to a prepared teleportation formation, the strength one required to move freely about the astral plane was much higher.

The huge pressure was as if a slab of steel was pressing down on Leylin’s body.

Cold, stifling, frenzied! Leylin immediately felt his bones creaking, and the defensive aurora on his body began to shatter bit by bit.

‘Perhaps even the pressure tens of thousands of meters under the sea can’t compare to this…’ This was the last conscious thought Leylin had. Before he completely fainted, the only thing he could do was to use Multilimb Strength and cover his body with dark green energy.

In a world of lava, large crevices could be seen in the earth, magma surging inside like a network of red rivers.

Space distorted on the surface of a large black rock, forming a translucent gate of light. It incessantly generated lightning in the surroundings.

The lightning crashed down more and more frequently as the entire area was filled with a dazzling white light.

*Boom!* The white light exploded, forming an eye-piercing radiance. When all the light vanished, the original gate of light and the lightning had all disappeared, leaving behind only charred traces that recounted the strange events that had just occurred.

“Hah… I’ve finally entered!” Leylin furrowed his brows, sensing the large amount of fire elemental particles surrounding him. “This concentration… Magi would believe it if someone said this was the fire elemental world!”

Intense pain could be felt from various parts of his body, causing him to groan and bend his back.

“A.I. Chip!” Leylin immediately ordered, “Check my current condition!”

[Beep! Host body’s soft tissue damage is at 30.87%. Fractures found at 7 areas, and signs of bruising observed on internal organs. Immediate treatment is recommended!]

The A.I. Chip loyally intoned, transmitting a 3D human figure to him. The blue image held many signs of wounds.

Even with Leylin’s current vitality, he was still injured to this degree. Other regular Magi would probably have completely disappeared without a trace.

His astonishing vitality and Warlock bloodline were slowly mending the injuries in his body, allowing his tightly furrowed eyebrows to relax.

“That was really dangerous. I almost died outside the protective sphere…” While recalling what had just happened, Leylin couldn’t help but break out in cold sweat.

The protective sphere! This was the edge of a world, and even included part of the void. It could be said to be a large world’s strongest defence!

In general, every world had this protective sphere, though its strength varied. The most famous protective sphere was probably the World of Gods’ crystal wall.

Its powerful isolation ability was enough for even Magi at ranks 7 and above to be forced to return in defeat. It included a large world and various planes, forming the World of Gods’ unique culture of strength. It even cut off attempts at peeping from other worlds, save for that one time when the ancient Magi had invaded them.

Before reaching the Lava World, Leylin was able to regain consciousness with the protection of Multilimb Strength, preventing him from being in a bad situation.

If one wanted to use a metaphor, a large world’s protective sphere was like customs upon entry to a country. If Leylin had not woken, he would need to force his way in, and would definitely be met with attacks, especially from the malicious intent of the World Will.

The method Leylin had employed this time was akin to slipping through a barrier. He had not been discovered by the World Will, and the focus on him was evidently minimal, which would aid in his later movements.

“And this!” Leylin pulled a silver necklace full of astral light from his neck. After sensing that the connection was undamaged, he could completely relax.

This necklace represented his connection with the astral gate in the Magus world. As long as the connection there was not broken, he could teleport back at any time through the gate.

Right when Leylin had left the Magus world, Collins’ attack had been in order to completely cut off this connection, leaving Leylin stranded in another world and unable to find his way home for eternity.

Gilbert and the other two had been defeated using this method.

Of course, Collins had been made a fool of by Leylin, and would probably not be able to emerge for a long time. The largest danger had been obstructed by Wayde, and Leylin finally had some time to do what he wanted.

Saving the two dukes also fit with Leylin’s plans for benefits.

After all, he was not strong enough to go head to head against Jupiter’s Lightning. He needed a few other people to relieve the pressure, and Gilbert and Emma were very good candidates for this.

Furthermore, Gilbert was Leylin’s mentor, not someone he could abandon so easily.

After considering for some time and finding the best way out for himself, Leylin still chose to come forward and save them.

“But… This world is so huge. Where am I to find them?” Leylin watched the lava lake that stretched as far as he could see, as well as the burning clouds in the sky, and couldn’t help but laugh bitterly.

[Beep! Testing surroundings…]

At this moment, the A.I. Chip immediately projected the analysis of the surroundings before Leylin.

“This…”

Leylin’s soul force was sent out to explore, and he immediately sensed the difference from what he was used to. In the Lava World, his spiritual force seemed sluggish, a result of the laws of this world not being harmonious with his own.

“As expected, with a switch in worlds, the dimensions, energy levels and even the the interactions between particles are starkly different. The changes in laws are definitely a huge obstruction to Magi who travel between worlds.”

A thread of understanding flashed in Leylin’s eyes. This was the precious experience that many ancient Magi had gathered through their blood and sweat.

“Thankfully, I’ve already condensed my point mass. Soul force is still useful in most worlds, and only needs some slight alterations. If it was still spiritual force, I’m afraid…” Relief rose in Leylin’s heart.

Soul force was a high-grade power, and could be used in many worlds. Its practicality trumped that of spiritual force.

Leylin estimated that if he still used spiritual force here, he would probably have to deal with the awkwardness of not fitting in. He might even need to cultivate it from the beginning and turn his spiritual force into the spiritual strength unique to this world. Though there would be no bottleneck, it would definitely require a lot of effort.

Now, with the use of soul force, this issue was mostly solved.

“It’s no wonder that ancient Magi placed Morning Star as the minimum rank to attack other worlds. So there’s this factor!” Leylin touched his chin.

[Beep! Data on surroundings completely gathered. Generating elemental map. Analysing world’s laws. Beginning fine-tuning of host body’s soul undulations…]

Chapter 547: Woking City

“Mister Ley!” The rest of the Wooks celebrated upon Leylin’s return, worship in their eyes. There was a respect for power that was imprinted into their very bloodlines, and now it had shown itself.

“It’s all settled, let’s continue!” Leylin returned to the seat in the giant snail shell, looking calm.

Indeed, the two rank 1 Magi did not warrant Leylin’s attention. However, it had surprised Leylin how much the A.I. Chip had advanced after deriving the energy transformation formulas of the rank 1 Magi.

[Beep! Decoding of 15 rank 1 Fire element spells, 7 rank 2 spells and 3 rank 3 spells has been completed.]

Leylin’s face broke into a smile after hearing the notice from the A. I. Chip.

Due to the difference in the rules of the Lava World, spell models of the Magus world could not directly be used in it, and had to be slightly altered.

For other Magi to do such a thing would require a lot of research; something that was potentially troublesome. The spells had to each be studied and analysed individually.

However, Leylin had the ability to analyse the spells in batches and instantly managed to understand many of the spells.

‘In this case, I can recover most of my strength before we reach Woking…’ A streak of light flashed and he slowly closed his eyes.

The giant caravan started to move slowly after the short pause, the Wook clansmen at ease.

After all, with the almighty Mister Ley overseeing them, there was not much to worry about during the journey, be it the bandits of the wilderness or disasters of nature and beasts.

As a matter of fact, with Leylin around, they were rarely affected by natural disaster, and even avoided huge crises many times.

After some time, The one-horned race eventually worshipped Leylin like a god. They had never been at such ease before, usually losing more than half their merchants and consuming large amounts of supplies for every trip.

Their parting with Leylin was full of reluctance. The chief of the caravan tried his best to persuade Leylin not to leave, even hinting that he could stay even if the Intellectual One refused.

But how would Leylin agree? He left with a smile.

Woking City, the largest city in the Blazing Thorn Land.

The entire city was built in a huge barren desert, with raging winds roaring every once in a while. The place appeared desolate.

But Leylin knew that such living conditions were considered exemplary in the Lava World. In the Lava World, the intelligent creatures thrived best in the areas where there was no lava flow. Other than the pure fire elemental creatures, few species would enjoy living near the edge of the lava. In here, other than the shortcoming that the temperature was slightly higher, it wasn’t very much different from that of the deserts in the Magus World, and hence was considered conditions that were good enough.

“Nevertheless, these non-human species are really…”

The dress code and appearances of the Magi in Woking City differed greatly from what he was used to. Leylin was a little speechless at the unique structure of the buildings and the large crowd of passersby, who were predominantly non-human.

To Leylin’s surprise, the one-horned race whom he had encountered early were actually more human than most, at least they looked similar to normal humans.

With non-humans who had numerous eyes and limbs were barely considered normal, Leylin was completely shocked when he saw a humongous green caterpillar, with hat and stick, in a store. It, ignorant of his gaze, was in a heated argument with the store’s owner.

Despite his adventure experience in the Magus world, Leylin had mostly only been exposed to humans. Although the central continent held many non-humans, humans were still the majority while the rest eked out an existence in the shadows, even if they were mixed bloods who looked human.

However, in this place, Leylin felt like he was the odd one out. This feeling of isolation was new to him, and interesting.

“No wonder the antique books say that the process of conquering a foreign world is actually a great challenge for Magi. It’s extremely difficult to even think of such a thing now, especially the act of going against the whole world by oneself. Truly, insane…”

Flames fumed in Leylin’s eyes as he mumbled under his breath, his eyes flashing with excitement. “I really wish to give it a try… The feeling of conquering a world…”

His exclamation was well and good, but time had arrived that he settle serious matters.

Leylin stopped a long-haired, two headed green being that was drooling out some unknown liquid.

“I need to get some information, is there any place can fulfil my needs? If u can bring me there, this will be yours!” Leylin took out a pinkish crystal and tossed it in front of the non-human, making his eyes brighten up.

“I– I’ll bring you there!” The sturdy man by the side of the two-headed being hemmed and hawed, as if he had to invest a lot of energy in speaking each and every word.

“Great! After you!” Leylin’s eyes flashed with a trace of a smile.

Clearly, the two headed being was pretty familiar with streets of Woking, every step of his long legs taking him a few meters ahead. He was originally worried that Leylin could not keep up with him, but after seeing Leylin at ease he sped up.

When they reached a remote alley, the two-headed fellow turned around and stammered, “Right– right here!”

“Is it?” Leylin looked around. The huge shadow of the building covered the region, blotting out the sun and leaving the entire place in darkness.

A tinge of a sombre mood was felt, and there was not a single person around.

“Hehehe, look, what Strap brought us!” A green, multi-limbed being who looked like a grasshopper climbed along the side of the wall. The pair of crimson eyes on top of its triangular head stared at Leylin with a malicious intent.

“Ant Tribe? Or Winged Tribe? Whatever, Old Hawk will surely pay a high price for his meat anyway… ”

In concert with his voice, many other non-humans climbed out of the corners, all looking bloodthirsty and ferocious.

“I knew it… I just knew it would turn out this way…” Leylin sighed helplessly, “Why do you want to force me to use violence when we can resolve this peacefully?”

Leylin’s puzzled look made the nonhumans tremble, feeling as if they had done something wrong.

“Just as well! In any case, I’m short on quite a few foreign specimens!”

Leylin played with the ring on his finger, gracefully taking out a silver surgical knife. He looked focused and devoted.

“Oh no! Please let me go! I don’t know anything, they forced me…”

Half an hour later, the alley was filled with the reek of blood. All the non-humans had disappeared, leaving behind only the two headed being kneeling on the ground, begging for mercy.

However, it was a high-pitched female voice this time, coming from the other head.

“Really?” Leylin wiped the silvery surgical knife, mirth in his eyes. It terrified the two-headed being, whose hair stood on ends.

“I can help! I know the best information broker in the city, it’s Old Jake. I’m telling the truth! He even knows things about other worlds! I can bring you there right now!” The being revealed its intelligence at the boundary between life and death, finally securing its life from the surgical knife Leylin had placed in front of it.

“Good! Bring me to him now!” The surgical knife stopped right before the being’s eyes, only a millimetre away.

“Yes, Master! I will bring you there now…” The creature wept, even wanting to die. If not for the fact that it was in its resting period and if it had let its younger brother go out instead, it would never have come near a malefic like Leylin.

It was useless to say anything now, though. It knew very well that it would end up like the scattered piles of flesh and bones if it did not bring Leylin to his destination and help him get what he wanted.

It was no doubt that he was the local tyrant. In a short while, he had brought Leylin to an extensive basement area.

Leylin got excited upon entering the place. This atmosphere of this place was pervaded with feelings of passion, madness, and death, causing the darkness elemental particles to be very concentrated here.

‘It wouldn’t take too long for this kind of place to give normal humans a mental disorder…’ Leylin stroked his chin, followed after the two-headed being.

“What brings you here Strap? Do you wanna play some games?” A creature with the head of an ox patted the two headed creature’s shoulder with great strength. His right leg was missing, instead replaced with a giant metal limb.

Leylin smelled an odour similar to that of marijuana from the ox-head, coming from the crimson drink in his hand. It seemed to be an alcoholic drink of this world.

“No, I’m here for Old Jake! You see…” The two headed being pointed at Leylin and started to whisper to the ox-head with flattery.

“Off you go!” The Ox-head took another look at Leylin, perhaps it was the attractive thin figure of Leylin that set him off guard.

Chapter 548: Underground Wrestling Match

Passing through a rusty metal door, Leylin entered a large underground arena.

There were cheers, howls, even berserk roars sounding incessantly. At times one could hear the sound of weapons clashing, at others the sound of a body being pierced.

The atmosphere was insane. The audience, who were composed of multiple races, waved pieces of paper in their hands as they yelled towards the middle of the arena.

“This…” Leylin looked down towards the centre with interest, and immediately made a discovery.

In a large cage made of steel was a were-lion with golden fur. It was matched against several large monsters.

These monsters looked like eight-legged crocodiles with mouths full of sharp teeth.

Their mouths actually looked like saws with all the sharp teeth, boasting a viciousness and frightening power that would cause weaker beings to faint.

Their opponent, the were-lion, was unarmed, and could only fight these monsters with its own fists. Heaps of muscles bulged on its body, holding in store its formidable strength.

Just as Leylin glanced over, it mercilessly grabbed onto one of the crocodiles’ tails and ruthlessly flung it onto a metal bad. A large number of metallic thorns stabbed into the creature’s body, and blood gushed out. The injury looked fatal.

In exchange, the were-lion’s back now had several bloody scratches that were dripping with blood.

“A place for underground wrestling, with bets and alcohol?” Leylin nodded, beginning to have some expectations towards Old Jake.

The heads of such underground organisations were usually the people who acquired intel the most effectively. He would definitely have a huge network.

After all, selling information was very profitable, and he would definitely not let this opportunity go.

“Come with me!” The ox-head limped as he led the way, guiding Leylin through several bar counters where many were raising their wine cups and roaring madly. He then opened a small wooden door.

This door truly was tiny. Leylin’s physique would be considered slender among the races of this world, and even he had to lower his head, half bowing before he could enter.

*Boom!* The sturdy wooden door closed, isolating the room from the clamour outside.

The moment before the door closed, Leylin vaguely saw the were-lion successfully taking care of two other monster crocodiles. Though it had paid a large price, it had still managed to keep its life.

Large numbers of bets failed, and those who had lost their money bellowed, the cacophony almost overturning the entire arena.

And still, when the wooden door closed, it was as if everything outside had no relation to this place.

“Serenity and insanity are only separated by a single door. Isn’t that feeling amazing, Mister Ley from the one-horned race’s territory?”

A dwarf that was around a metre tall walked out. It had on a long silver robe, the bottom dragging on the ground. It held the same wine cup as the rest, an excited blush on its face.

Its eyes, however, were cold. They were like a mass of ice, not a single ripple within them.

‘A rational lunatic!’ That was Leylin’s first impression if this dwarf. For it to be able to take control of such a large organisation, it was evidently not a simple character.

“You know me?” Leylin had arrived at the Lava World a few days ago, and he had only made contact with the one-horned race. The knowledge that the other party had found information on him so quickly caused him to be delighted. In this case, there was a higher chance of his plans being realised.

“Of course! There are few who can defeat the summoner, Klito. A Sky ranked master is definitely worthy of my respect!” The dwarf bowed slightly, and Leylin was moved.

It must have been a member of the ant race with its brown skin and two little antennae. For some reason, it had broken away from its community and formed a large underground organisation in Woking City.

“Was it the merchants of the one-horned city?” Leylin pondered over it for a moment and immediately answered. Pretty much the only ones who knew him in the entirety of Woking City was that lot.

“Indeed, it was them! Since they were escorted by Mister Ley, I’ve already sent down orders that all their goods will be sold off at 10% higher than the market price!”

The dwarf of the ant race invited Leylin to take a seat, and personally poured a glass of something similar to red wine for him slowly.

The slight smell of alcohol, mixed with all kinds of fermented items that had anaesthetic effects immediately surrounded Leylin’s nostrils.

“The alcohol of other races is really terrifying. They aren’t even afraid of harming their bodies…”

Leylin shook his head, a little speechless. Though he was not afraid of these with the quality of his body, his tastes were well-developed. Such a crudely-made thing was not worthy of his attention, even if this alcohol was the best out of this dwarf’s collection.

“Alright, respected guest! May I know your purpose in seeking out pitiful old Jake?” Seeing Leylin putting the wine cup down without taking a sip, Jake’s expression did not change. He’d taken the initiative to bring up the topic, his eyes smiling.

“Everything!” Leylin chuckled lightly.

“Everything?!” Jake cried out involuntarily. “What do you mean by everything?”

“All the intelligence you have. Everything you know. That includes this region, as well as other areas. Whether it’s a big or small issue, I want everything as long as it’s valuable…” Leylin’s voice was low, and had a unique charm to it.

“Hehe… Mr Ley, do you know how much this information will cost?” Jake laughed, but his voice turned cold.

“I know, but I can definitely afford it!” Leylin answered without hesitation.

“What are you going to use to pay for it?” Jake had already assumed he’d met a lunatic, or someone with a screw loose.

“Your life. Is that enough?” Leylin spoke coldly.

“Crap!” Upon hearing Leylin’s words, Jake immediately bowed and retreated, throwing himself behind a study table with a jump. With a push of some mechanism, a defensive layer of energy appeared instantly.

Its movements were fluid, as if it had trained for this countless of times.

Only after the layer rose did its expression become calm. A sneer raised on its lips, “Mr Ley, don’t you think you’re going too far for a mere guest?”

“I’ve never felt that way towards the weak!” Leylin’s voice was dull, and that caused Jake’s face to flush.

As if Leylin’s words had touched on some nerve, Jake instantly grew furious.

“Get him!” It called out suddenly, and a pink mist filled the room. Two figures rushed out from within, emanating powerful energy undulations.

“The two mice finally dare show themselves. You’re only at the Sky rank, is that so amazing?” Leylin laughed slightly, a dark green layer of energy appearing from his body as a large hand grabbed forwards.

*Boom!* Space itself seemed to freeze in place, and the two fierce black figures halted abruptly. Leylin held each of them by the neck.

What appeared in his hands were two other dwarves that looked very similar to Jake. Energy undulations similar to that of a rank 3 Magus were continually emitted from them, but to Leylin this was far too weak. They were like a candle in a hurricane, a random wisp of wind enough to destroy them.

“Is this all you have to depend on? Any others?” Leylin opened his mouth, and a vortex appeared in the air. The pink mist that had pervaded the air was sucked into Leylin’s stomach.

One of those that Leylin was holding suddenly seemed to recall something, and even began to stutter, “This powerful? You– You’re a Star rank…”

He sent the two flying, and they fell with a thud, fainting from their injuries.

*Swish!* Seeing Leylin unravelling his trap and defeating two Sky ranks so easily, Jake, who was within the defensive layer, could only grit his teeth and remove it, kneeling before him.

“Revered Master Ley, please forgive the petty me for offending you unknowingly. Jake is willing to hand over all power and information to you…”

“You’re smart and understand the situation. Good, I like people like you!” A smile appeared on Leylin’s face, but to Jake it looked like that of a devil.

“I don’t want your organisation or anything like that. I just need some information from you. Because you’re tactful, I’ll only purge a portion of your memories. Don’t worry…”

Hearing Leylin’s words, Jake immediately knelt in gratitude, while forcing a laugh inside.

Just a Star rank was enough to destroy Woking City, and he had no means of fighting back.

A few hours later, Leylin who had obtained what he wanted, left the Underground Wrestling Arena, satisfied.

The atmosphere in the arena was still very heated. Now, however, there were great battles between various races. Leylin even saw a few one-horned clansmen who were mere cannon fodder.

The soundproofing effects of the wooden door were superb. There seemed to be some spell formation, and even though Leylin had caused a mess inside, nobody outside found out.

Even that ox-headed person would not know that over the course of the past few hours, the leader of their organisation had thoroughly bowed down at the hands of this young being of a different race.

Of course, Leylin spurned the head of an underground organisation. After using methods of psychological hints to confirm that it had handed over all the information, he had immediately modified its memories and even created a fake experience. This completely concealed the happenings of the day.

After leaving the arena, Leylin found a random inn and, after paying with precious gems, received a large house.

Of course, this wealth had been obtained with the generous sponsorship of Old Jake.

Chapter 549: Emberwing Race

The Lava World was vast, and a few hundred years would not be enough to traverse the entire world.

Based on the information hr obtained from Jake, this continent that Leylin was on was the largest in the Lava World, called ‘Blazing Crown’.

Around Blazing Crown, was an ocean formed of lava. Within this lava ocean were all kinds of terrifying high-energy beings, and it was a much more dangerous place than the oceans in the Magus World.

Hence, communication between Blazing Crown and the other continents was minimal. Even the most powerful extraordinary ones rarely left the continent.

To Jake’s knowledge, Blazing Crown was the heart of the Lava World. The other ‘continents’ were merely slightly large islands.

‘What an interesting world! An ocean formed of lava? If those fire-elemental Magi were to find out about this place, they would be willing to migrate over even if it cost them a fortune.’ Leylin touched his chin, beginning to browse through the intelligence he had obtained from Jake.

Though the information was very complicated, the A.I. Chip had recorded everything and could quickly filter out the wrong and useless information, leaving behind the great amounts of valuable intel. It then combined a few pieces that seemed to be linked.

Soon, Leylin managed to form an image of the true Lava World.

This was a world of flames. Fire elemental beings and lava creatures occupied over 80% of the area here. The one-horned race, as well as the ant race that Jake was a part of, could only somewhat survive at the edges of the continent.

On the complete map of the continent, there were no signs of the single-horned city. Woking City was merely a black dot at the edge, and was basically a remote and desolate place.

Three organisations stood at the apex of Blazing Crown.

There was the Divineflame Empire made entirely of fire elemental beings. The Atlan Union was made up of the Emberwing race, a life form similar to humans, and then the Allied Kingdom was made up of the rest. There weren’t any others at the same level as them.

Of these three, the Divineflame Empire was the most powerful. The Atlan Union and Allied Kingdom had to collaborate to stave off their invasions.

Wars were incessantly fought as they tried to seize good territory from the lava and fire elemental beings. It was to the point that huge military campaigns were launched every few years.

As for the divisions in their ranks, it was the same as what he’d already encountered. The weakest was Exemplary, followed by Earth, Sky, and Star.

As for those above the Star rank, beings that possessed the strength of Radiant Moon Magi, he hadn’t come across any such thing. Although it could just be that Jake’s organisation hadn’t acquired that level of information yet.

Even so, Leylin’s current strength allowed him to do as he liked in the Lava World as long as the other Star ranks or Jupiter’s Lightning didn’t set their sights on him.

“If I were Gilbert and the others, I would either find a place and hide myself completely, or build an organisation in secret that would give off a distinct signal to the outside, letting any rescuers know where I am.…”

Leylin’s eyes flashed, and the A.I. Chip immediately began to search through the data.

Soon enough, a distinct heading attracted Leylin’s attention. “Riot at Eastern City of Atlan Union. Rebel army ‘Triserpent Sect’ has taken responsibility for the event. There are conjectures that this could be a retaliation in response to the large-scaled attack of the Union…”

“Triserpent Sect?” This phrase that was full of meaning immediately got him to make a mental association.

“Isolate all information about the Triserpent Sect!” Leylin commanded. With the keyword found, the A.I. Chip’s search went more quickly. Almost instantly, information relating to the Triserpent Sect was projected in front of him.

Through reading this information, Leylin gained a deeper understanding of this organisation.

The Triserpent Sect, which was also called the Triserpent Resistance Army, was an up-and-coming organisation, and its development was rapid. With the goal of overthrowing the rule of the Atlan Union, their operations were unpredictable and very much supported by the lower class commoners.

It was said that there were three heads of the Triserpent Sect, and they were terribly powerful, the Atlan Union’s attempts at cornering and annihilating them were to no avail.

However, days ago, the Atlan Union had suddenly announced that they had achieved victory while trying to eliminate the Triserpent Sect. Not only had they destroyed many of its branches, they had even killed the head.

The news of rebellion that Leylin had seen was retaliation launched by the Triserpent Sect.

“Triserpent Sect? Interesting! Is it really the three dukes, or is this bait?” Leylin touched his chin, but it was obvious that in the Atlan Union, there were clues of the location of the two Morning Star dukes!

For this reason, Leylin had to go there no matter what.

‘I keep having this feeling that the Atlan Union is very suspicious.’ Leylin touched his chin and sank deep into thought.

The three dukes had no grudge against the Atlan Union. Why would they suddenly attack them? Unless… They had made some astounding discovery in the Atlan Union!

‘Come to think of it, Jupiter’s Lightning found this world first. It would be strange if they did not painstakingly manage it. Hence, if the ones working behind the scenes in the Atlan Union were Jupiter’s Lightning, that would explain everything…’

Leylin wondered as explored different possible solutions.

Compared to the Divineflame Empire that was against all foreigners and full of fire elementals, the Atlan Union formed of the Emberwing race similar to humans were easier to manipulate.

On top of that, their strength was only second to the Divineflame Empire in Blazing Crown, and was more suited to the needs of the Morning Star Magi of Jupiter’s Lightning.

However, while this made sense logically, Leylin believed things could not be so simple. The same intuition that had helped him obtain astonishing harvests during dangerous moments was blaring sirens at him.

‘No matter what it is, I need to go the Atlan Union! As for the Triserpent Sect, we’ll see…’ Leylin sighed.

Boiling lava and fiery red light formed the only luster of the Lava World. And yet, even under this dazzling redness, life was growing stubbornly.

This was a grassland, and little steel trees similar to the one Leylin had seen before and filled the area, along with vegetation whose leaves had jagged edges. A few slender channels of lava could be seen every once in a while, flowing past like little streams in the grasslands. Yet, they could not harm the area at all.

These plants that were like grass that had their roots firmly and deeply in the ground, even boring into the lava and absorbing its energy for their growth.

The stubbornness for life had Leylin feeling surprised.

“Uncle Ley! Why do you like watching this iron-thread grass?” A very fair girl cloaked in read darted over, the sparse red feathers covering her forehead bouncing up and down.

This girl was no different from an ordinary human child, if one disregarded the feathers on her forehead and on the back of her hand.

This was the Emberwing race. In the Lava World, besides fire elemental life forms, they were the largest racial group, and formed the largest group in the Atlan Union.

“I just like them for their resilience!” Leylin chuckled as he handed over a large piece of meat to her. “Take this! I’m afraid we’ll have to part here.”

“Uncle Ley, are you leaving?” The little girl sucked on her finger, looking reluctant.

Though they had met on the road, the powerful aura of this clansman even had her father in awe. Based on her father’s guesses, this Mister Ley must be at least an Earth rank working hard to temper oneself and fervently hoping to advance to a higher realm.

“Brother Ley, are you already leaving?” Not long after, another large man of the Emberwing race rushed over. He had obviously just heard the news, and looked anxious.

Leylin now had a few fine red feathers on his forehead. This was the appearance of the Emberwing race.

In the Atlan Union, it was much too eye-catching if he were to continue pretending to be of the winged race.

“Yes! Working hard in this world can’t stimulate my progress anymore. Hence, I’ve decided to join the army! Perhaps competing against those evil fire elementals of the Divineflame Empire will help me advance to a higher level!”

Leylin’s expression was callous, “Besides, I’ve had a dream since I was young. I wanted to punish those flame bastards with my iron fist… Just in time for me to steel my skills in the upcoming battle at the Death Grand Canyon Battle!”

“D… Death Grand Canyon!” The large man’s eyeballs protruded. That was the frontlines of the battle between the Atlan Union and Divineflame Empire. That was also where the most casualties were.

“You…” The large man only moved his lips, but seeing the resolute look on Leylin’s face, he did not say more.

“My good brother, help me kill a few more fire elementals!” The large man could only pat Leylin’s shoulders as if wishing him luck, and he watched Leylin’s figure disappear into the horizon…

“Hah… I’ve finally arrived…” Leylin saw the outline of the Emberwing race in the distance, and let out a long breath.

The moment he had obtained intel on the Triserpent Sect, he had immediately set off and hurried here in secret.

However, as the Lava World was much too big, and Woking City was located in a very remote area, he had expended much time and effort to reach this place.

As for the large man and family of Emberwing race, they were only a few companions he had joined out of loneliness on the way here.

“Compared to the Magus World, many Exemplary ranks join the army directly in the Lava World and hold high rankings. If I want to obtain any information or intel, that would be the most convenient place.”

Chapter 550: Testing and Passing

Compared to the Magi of the Magus World who liked to work behind the scenes, the strong in the Lava World were more willing to take the stage and take control of the organisations.

The kingships of large-scaled kingdoms were taken up by Star ranks. In that case, it was understandable for there to be a large number of Exemplaries in the higher ups of the Atlan Union’s army.

Furthermore, the army was the quickest place to advance in status, especially during wartime. As long as one was capable, had outstanding results, and nobody obstructed them, people were usually promoted rapidly. This was a method that was much better than others, and also the way that Leylin liked the best.

“But… There’s so much hardship in being a soldier. I don’t want to be trampled on…” Leylin’s eyes swivelled around as he had an idea.

Days later, in a special building within the city.

“Are you here to apply for the Special Task Force? Come with me!” A female Emberwing race member said. She was dressed in a military uniform and was expressionless, yet looked to be formidable. She carried a stack of documents and forms and turned to leave, leaving Leylin and the rest with a view of her elegant back.

“This doll is really…” A burly man beside Leylin began to complain.

“How callous. I like it…” Another pale young man’s eyes glowed green, leaving Leylin speechless.

Those with Leylin were all of the Emberwing race. However, what made them distinct from the rest of their clansmen, was the obvious energy undulations from their bodies.

Since this world had Exemplaries, it was obvious that they had special treatment and missions. Things like the Special Task Force were formed for this reason.

With enough strength, Emberwing clansmen were allowed to be selected into the Special Task Force. Not only would their positions be high, they had the best treatment in the army.

Leylin wanted to sneak in, and he obviously formed a fake identity and signed up successfully.

What Leylin cared about was that the Special Task Force often needed to deal with riots that had to do with Exemplaries. As long as he was there, he would definitely bump into the Triserpent Sect.

For this reason, he was in no hurry at all. He would swing in and sneak into the Special Task Force and hide away there while gathering more information.

After all, he was not quite sure about the background of the Triserpent Sect, and he needed to remain cautious.

If this was a trap and he still charged right in, wouldn’t he be seeking death?

Leylin and the young male Emberwing looked just as nervous and excited as the rest while they followed the female soldier to a large square.

A middle-aged soldier in silver armour was already waiting there, his expression grim.

“We’re beginning the test now! Who’s first?” The middle-aged instructor’s voice was so loud that everyone’s eardrums seemed to have gone numb.

“Me!” That pale young man seemed to be too anxious to show off and darted to the front.

“Fine. Use all your strength and attack the black obelisk ahead!” The military instructor stepped aside and revealed a giant black crystal before everyone.

“Hah!” The young man took a deep breath, and a layer of fire-red light was emitted from his body. Streams of air were dispelled as dust filled the air.

*Rumble!* He threw a punch, and it landed on the black crystal. While it did not budge the slightest, a dim layer of red light appeared on the surface.

Red light filled the obelisk with some difficulty, and fine rings appeared on the surface.

A total of five red rings appeared, before completely disappearing. Upon seeing this, a look of satisfaction flashed by the young man’s expression.

“Mm! Fifth level of Emberwing Technique. Exemplary status. Pass!” The officer nodded, with no surprise in his expression.

“Next!” His voice was icy-cold, causing the young man’s original complacency to disappear.

“Me!” The one who went up was plump, and similarly used Emberwing Technique. However, only three ringed runes appeared on the obelisk.

“Third level of Emberwing Technique. Fail!”

The officer’s voice was callous, and two soldiers immediately went forward and dragged him out.

“Ah… Wait! Give me another chance, I can definitely…” From a distance, the sounds of his wails and pleas could be heard, causing great fear amongst the crowd in the square.

“Next!” The officer’s expression remained cold as he continued.

One young man after another went up, and most passed the test, though there were a few who failed. The officer was ruthless as he commanded the soldiers to chase them out.

Leylin watched this scene coolly from below.

Emberwing Technique! He had heard of it before, and knew that it was used by the Emberwing race. It could be said to be found everywhere, and practically everyone knew it.

There was nothing special about levels one to three of Emberwing Technique, and was similar to the breathing techniques of the Magus World. It could increase one’s vitality and endurance slightly, with some tolerance towards fire elements.

Once one got to the fourth level of Emberwing Technique, it would be similar to a meditation technique and allow the Emberwing clansmen to have a rapid increase in strength.

The fourth and fifth level was the strength of an Exemplary rank, while six and seven meant Earth rank. Eight and nine were considerably powerful existences and were comparable to the Sky rank. Once one advanced to the tenth level, of which there had been no precedent in history, that was the door to the Star realm!

Though the fundamental parts of Emberwing Technique could be found everywhere, the fourth and fifth levels were kept somewhat secret, and were considered the essence of the race. As for the next few levels, they were kept secure, and could only be passed on in a few places. The reason why so many young people wanted to enter the Special Task Force was probably because they wanted information on the later levels of the technique.

As for the tenth level, that was something only the family of the head of Atlan Union possessed. Most had never even heard of it.

A grave, burly, middle-aged Emberwing clansman went forward. Extending a scarlet palm, six fire rings immediately appeared on the obelisk, and even the officer couldn’t help but give the man a second look, “Sixth level of Emberwing Technique. Earth rank. Pass!”

“How amazing! It’s someone at level 6, the Earth rank!”

“These sorts of people can survive anywhere. What is he doing here?”

“It must be for the information regarding the eighth and ninth level of the technique! It’s only passed on in the army…” The appearance of what was the best results till now immediately gave rise to loud discussions in the queue.

The man from before stood expressionlessly aside in answer to the looks of curiosity or reverence, and the officer couldn’t help but have an expression of approval.

“Next!” The officer yelled again, eyes scanning through the crowd that was beginning to thin.

‘I’m afraid that this burly man is the one with the best results in this batch. It’s not a bad harvest! At least one is passable!’ The officer was stuck in this train of thought, but then he saw another slender clansman stand up.

“Hm?” Though this above average looking man seemed frail, the officer’s eyes brightened as he lapsed into thought.

‘This little guy doesn’t seem to be simple!’

Leylin obviously cared little about what the officer thought. In actuality, he was now performing research and gathering information on the path of Emberwing Technique.

‘Interesting. Interesting! At the beginning, it’s Knight training, and after that, there seems to be content infused with some conscient runes…’

He was interested in such techniques.

“But I need to get through this!” Leylin shook his head at the ruckus in the crowd due to his being in a daze for too long.

A Morning Star Magus’ point mass was a minute dot that could contain the terrifying strength of a Morning Star without leaking any energy. With the A.I. Chip’s help, there was no issue with simulating the energy belonging to Emberwing technique.

‘It’s a pity… The strongest person here is only the officer, who is at the Sky rank with the eighth level of Emberwing Technique. The next few levels, as well as that of the Star rank, can’t be obtained as of yet!’

Leylin slowly extended his palm. Yet, it seemed like a layer of melting flame came to life, spreading across its surface. This immediately silenced the crowd.

“Hah!” Leylin controlled his strength, looking as if he was attacking with all he had.

*Rumble!* The entire obelisk began to tremble as bright fiery runes appeared one after another.

One, two, three… The light from bright flames were dazzling, and spread till there were seven on the obelisk. There even seemed to be half a ring extra.

The officer’s eyes shone and he immediately asked, “Seventh level of Emberwing Technique. Peak Earth rank! Very good. What’s your name?”

“My name is ‘Ley’, my lord!” Leylin performed a military salute, something the officer immediately found pleasing.

At this moment, the silent crowd suddenly became boisterous, hearts filled with jealousy that could not be suppressed while observing Leylin’s handsome face.

As long as this young man did not die in battle, he would become the rising star of the Special Task Force, or even the entire union!

“Hm?” At this moment, Leylin acutely felt a gaze land on his back.

“It’s the large man from before at the sixth level. This feeling of jealousy and hostility? Though it’s normal, why is there killing intent?”

The corner of Leylin’s lips rose in a cold smile. An enemy of this level was too boring.

When all those who had failed cleared out, the officer stood before Leylin and the rest, voice booming.

“Welcome to the Special Task Force! I am your officer, Schiker. You’ll soon find that the Special Task Force is the best place to be. As long as you complete your missions, we can give you techniques, money, status or land…”

It had to be said that the officer was silver-tongued. In a short amount of time, he had incited the hot-bloodedness of the youths.

Leylin’s expression was also one of excitement, though he found this all ridiculous on the inside.

“Now, follow me to participate in your first mission!”

Powerful undulations were emitted from Schiker’s body. Only then did the members realise that their officer was actually at the Sky rank!

Chapter 551: Mobius

Different from ordinary troops, this elite group formed of Exemplaries needed to start on missions right away.

The Atlan Union had spent much manpower and physical resources on supporting the Special Task Force, and they were naturally not to be underestimated. However, this method of mentoring through fighting had resulted in the dissatisfaction of some members.

Of course, with Sky rank Schiker around suppressing them, it was as if nothing had happened.

“Hi, Ley! I’m Mies. This is our first time on the battlefield, how are you feeling? Nervous?”

The pale young man who had been the first for the testing leaned towards him, looking to fawn on him.

“Alright,” Leylin answered indifferently, and then pointed towards the burly man who had mastered the sixth level of Fireplume. “What’s his name?”

“Him? He’s Loke, and rumours have it that he was an expert at being a mercenary. Look at that pretentious display, as if all eyes are on him…”

Mies played the role of a lackey very well as he immediately stood in line, his instinct now to help his boss beat down the number two.

“Oh!” Leylin said lightly, and did not continue inquiring.

As fresh recruits, they had gotten a set of new clothes that were very pliable, and could even protect against high temperatures and ordinary knife slashes. As far as this world’s treasures went, they were alright.

“Look at these clothes, how chic!” Mies looked at the completely black uniform, and could not help but be infatuated with it as he arranged his collar.

Watching him act so foolishly, Leylin had little to say, “We’re on a mission. Focus!”

Upon hearing this, Mies froze for a moment as he continued to move quickly. Immediately afterwards, he looked in the direction of Schiker guiltily. Seeing that the officer hadn’t been focusing in their direction, he relaxed and heaved a sigh of relief.

After the excitement, Mies calmed down. He looked uneasy, his slight nervousness apparent as he looked towards Leylin, “Ley, what kind of mission do you think we will be assigned to?”

In his eyes, this comrade was exceptionally mysterious, and had a calm that most lacked. Even just staying by his side gave him a feeling of security.

“Whatever it is, it won’t be easy,” Leylin spoke dully.

In actuality, he was guessing that the mission was a test for the recruits. There was no better proof than real battles. Through intense fights, the weak would fail and be eliminated, while the strong would survive and gain even more resources. This was the ruthless order of nature.

Leylin guessed that this operation might be tailored just for them. Were it not so, the difficulty would be too high. Most of the members, maybe even the entire squad, would be wiped out.

The Atlan had enough strength and backing. That was enough to attract numerous willing participants, and there was no fear of the lack of manpower.

‘But… Am I going to bump into the Triserpent Sect on the first mission?’ A trace of doubt streaked through Leylin’s mind.

He had yet to gain enough information and knew little of how things stood with the Triserpent Sect. It was not a good idea to make contact with them recklessly.

Thankfully, Schiker, who was standing in front, began to speak coldly, and dispelled Leylin’s doubts, “Our mission this time is to eliminate an extremely evil, bloody sect, a branch of the Mobius Organisation. Kill all members!”

They were now far away from the barracks and city, and had come to an open, desolate area. Large amounts of red lava reflected an orange splendour that even dyed the horizon crimson.

With the bonus from Fireplume, these Special Task Force members all maintained a vigorous physical strength, and were still in good condition even after running across a long distance.

“Mobius Organisation?” Mies immediately cried out in surprise, “That disgusting sect that likes blood sacrifices and dismemberment?”

“A disgusting sect that likes blood sacrifices and dismemberment?” Leylin’s brows furrowed, seeming having heard the large Emberwing man he had befriended previously speak.

The sect seemed to be very secretive, and the higher-ups held enormous strength. There were rumours that it was being spread even in the Divineflame Empire, and could not be destroyed.

Of course, with their extreme methods, they weren’t that welcome.

“That Mobius Organisation?” “Heavens! I hear that they’re insane. To avenge one of their bishops, they massacred a city…”

The members began to discuss this softly, the sounds of endless whispers mixing together.

Seeing this, red light emitted from Schiker’s face. “Silence!” he shouted as tremendous sound waves covered the region. If not for having sensed a sound-proofing barrier being set up just prior, Leylin would have assumed that Schiker was a spy, intentionally notifying the Mobius Organisation.

“We’re soldiers. It is our duty to obey orders. Isn’t it just a Mobius Organisation? What are you afraid of? Don’t forget, you’re now Special Task Force members. The moment you disobey an order, I’ll immediately execute you. Even if you can escape, you’ll have to deal with being the target of a kill order from the union!”

Schiker’s words were eerily cold, and with the powerful forcefield undulations of a Sky rank, the original tendency towards disorder was wiped out.

“Do you want to betray the union?” Schiker’s dark words immediately had the Special Task Force members grow resolute as they answered in unison, “No, definitely not!”

“Good! These are the warriors our union needs!” Schiker seemed satisfied. “The organisation has only a few Earth ranks in charge. What does that count for? After succeeding, just the rewards alone are enough for you to spend for quite a few months! You might even accumulate points towards becoming nobility… Now, we’ll allocate tasks…”

“Hm?!” While Schiker was immersed in his unceasing narrations, he had failed to realise the interesting change in Leylin’s expression.

With a sweep of his soul force, the concealed undulations and even a full view of the structure below was presented in front of Leylin, and he laughed.

‘Looks like the union received relevant intelligence and know the military strength inside the stronghold like the back of their hands. Based on Schiker’s plans, our side should have had a large chance of success, but it’s a pity…’

With a scan of his soul force, Leylin found that there were quite a few Earth rank priests in the Mobius Organisations. On top of that, there even a few bishops wearing red religious attire, emitting the terrifying undulations of Sky ranks.

‘This is obviously a trap, though I don’t know if this is aimed specifically at Schiker. Whatever it is, he’s in trouble…’

Leylin’s expression held traces of pity.

“Good. This is the overall plan. Move!” Schiker obviously knew nothing of Leylin’s thoughts right now. On the contrary, he wanted to watch how Leylin, Loke and the rest performed and grade them.

*Rumble!* Along with a giant explosion, the barren land that was initially empty blew up, revealing a large building with a number of floors.

What first appeared was a glorious distorted black sculpture. The lines were simple and crude, and yet they gave Leylin a demonic impression.

Under the sculpture were many decorative designs that gave it a style similar of that of an altar. There were limbs and livers from living beings on it, and the blood had not dried yet. The fresh blood kept dripping and filling the spell formation.

The process of a sacrifice had obviously been interrupted, and a few low-ranked worshippers let loose roars of ire.

“Leave none alive. Crush them!” Schiker howled.

He didn’t actually need to yell. The Special Task Force members had long since seen red and pounced forward, boiling hot rays flickering on their bodies. Fireplume activated, giving them immense support.

*Pu!* A palm filled with flames extracted itself from the body of a worshipper, and the accompanying flames burnt this vicious-looking worshipper to ashes. “You must all die!”

Loke’s chilly voice swept through, voice spreading, and Schiker nodded unceasingly while watching in secret.

Meanwhile, Mies might seem cowardly, yet seemed to have had his thirst for blood kindled, especially after seeing his side winning all engagements. Many members were in high spirits as they went deeper in.

“What is this Ley doing?”

Schiker nodded in satisfaction, but when his eyes were on Leylin, his face scrunched up in dissatisfaction.

Leylin, who he’d thought should rush to the frontlines, was wandering around within the group. Even when he did make a move, it looked like he was cowering and seemed listless, falling behind Loke by a large margin in terms of his kill count.

“Hm? That’s not right. His way of moving forward implies he’s having reservations about something. Has he discovered something?”

Schiker instantly became cool-headed, going through Leylin’s actions and the information he had gotten previously. As he saw his troops continuously heading in after their victories, his pupils shrank as he realised that his members had lost their formation.

“Crap. Come back!”

Schiker shouted loudly, but it was much too late.

*Boom! Boom! Boom!* Large amounts of sparks exploded, forming a heat wave that wiped out most of the Special Task Force members. Even with the protection of Fireplume, the high temperature surpassed their limits caused them to turn into charred corpses.

“Keke, Schiker, we meet again!”

A few figures wrapped in light stood before Schiker, accompanied by warriors and worshippers, donning garments of their sect.

“Sky rank! Two Sky ranks!” Mies, who was lucky to have survived, watched the two tall figures in the air and cried out in pain and despair.

“It’s you… So it was a trap.” Schiker remained collected.

“Yes. This is a trap specifically to deal with you! What happened fifteen years ago can be settled properly now!” The two bishops in red clothing held hatred in their eyes.

Chapter 556: Orders Given

“What mission is it?” Leylin took the document that was labelled ‘top secret’ on the cover, and unconsciously furrowed his brows.

　　

“The union has ordered that our Special Task Force is to attack the Triserpent Sect and Mobius Organisation within the territory of the state. I am the person in charge of the eastern region!”

　　

Schiker’s voice was that of a hardened war veteran.　　

　　

“Your squadron is in charge of a few strongholds of the Triserpent Sect that have been discovered recently. I will personally take care of the Mobius Organisation’s side!”

　　

It was obvious that their trap had thoroughly enraged Schiker. Now, he wanted to exact revenge properly!　　

　　

“The Triserpent Sect?” A look of interest appeared on Leylin’s face, though he was sighing inside.

　　

His intention in coming to the Atlan Union was to obtain some information regarding the Triserpent Sect, but so many things had happened, especially with the appearance of the firasource stone. That one resource had dispelled all other thoughts.

　　

However, just when he was hoping to continue concealing himself, this matter had suddenly cropped up, and it just so happened that he was involved. This left him not knowing whether to laugh or cry.

　　

“The order this time was personally signed by the head of the state. The garrisons from all regions will coordinate with our operation. In other words, once we succeed, we will appear in front of the head immediately. Chances like these are hard to come by!”

Schiker seemed to be reminding him.　　

　

“Understood.” Leylin saluted, his back ramrod straight, though he began making some guesses. It seemed that Schiker had an unusual relationship with the union head, to the point that he could obtain the position of the person in charge of such a vital operation. He must have a very powerful backing, no wonder that Loke wanted to get close to him no matter what.　　

　　

“Good, you may leave. Get Loke to come in!” Schiker nodded in satisfaction.　　

　　

“Yes!” Leylin saluted and left. Every movement was like a textbook example and seasoned as a soldier. Schiker nodded inside after seeing this.　　

　

“Captain Loke, the instructor is calling you!”　　

　　

After walking out, Leylin found that Loke was already waiting aside. Compared to before, there was more calm and steadfastness on his expression, and he had ‘unwittingly’ broken through the sixth level and reached the seventh level of Fireplume. He could now be considered an Earth rank.　　

Of course, this was all a facade. Leylin believed he was at least at the Sky rank, but he had somehow snuck in for some unknown reason and gained Schiker’s trust.　　

　　

In the operation this time, Leylin was in charge of dealing with the Triserpent Sect, while Loke was to follow Schiker and was in charge of the matters of the Mobius Organisation. Just this point made it clear to Leylin that Schiker trusted Loke more.　　

　

In the Special Task Force, there had long since been rumours spreading that Ley and Loke were Schiker’s left and right-hand men, and Schiker himself did not deny this directly.　　

　

‘It’s a pity… When you find out the two subordinates you’d thought were your helpers were actually enemies sneaking in as spies, I wonder what expression you’d have? Whatever it is, I’m sure it’ll be amusing!’ Leylin touched his chin, a smile on his face as he ruminated.　　

　

“Leader Ley, is there anything else?” Loke observed Leylin who was acting in this manner. For some reason, he felt a chill in his heart, and seemed to have a bad premonition.　　

“Oh, nothing much. I was just thinking about the scene from our previous mission. Quick, get in!” Leylin patted Loke on the shoulder, and calmly sauntered away.

　

Loke kept drawing back and stared at Leylin’s back. Though he seemed to be sending Leylin off respectfully, there was a strange glint that flashed in his eyes.　　

　

“Soon… things will be different…”　

　　

A flicker of jealousy and hatred appeared in Loke’s eyes. Though both Leylin and he were captains, one was a Sky rank while the other was only at the Earth rank. That naturally gave rise to criticism.

　　

Though Loke was considerably powerful and was on good terms with Schiker, he seemed to be a level below Leylin in many aspects.

　　

He might not seem bothered on the surface, but that was because he was trying to be conceal himself. He wasn’t preparing for a life in the Union anyway, but he still somehow felt strange.　

　　

Of course, this was hidden well, and even the person closest to him had not realised it.

　　

“Loke, what are you waiting for?” Schiker’s dissatisfied voice travelled from within the room. Loke was startled and immediately returned his expression to the original honesty with a trace of shrewdness and admiration, nodding and bowing as he entered the office. “Reporting in!”

……　　

　

Back in his residence, Leylin was carefully browsing over some information in the documents. Only after some time did he put it down and sigh.　　

　　

The information within was so detailed that it was excessive. They even knew the strength of the leaders there, and it seemed that the Atlan Union definitely had hidden some spies and the like inside.

　

“The Triserpent Sect will probably suffer heavy losses this time…”　　

　

Leylin stroked his chin. He still could not confirm if the Triserpent Sect was an organisation formed by the three Giant Kemoyin Serpent Dukes, and he was not prepared to make a move.

　　

They were a few branches and strongholds anyway. Nothing would be missed even if everyone died, and with this, he could even gain a higher standing and more trust from the Union. That would make it convenient to pry into the secrets of the firasource stone!

　

With this thought, the light in Leylin’s eyes gradually dimmed, a bone-chilling iciness within. 　　

“B…Boss… Wha- What’s going on…”　　

　　

Mies chose this moment to push the door open and met Leylin’s gaze. Instantly, he collapsed, cold sweat pouring, and was left stuttering.　　

　　

“It’s nothing. Our official mission has been handed down. Take a look!”　　

　

Leylin chuckled, and it was as if all that ice had melted with the smile. Warm sunlight shone down, and Mies was no longer limp on the ground, and could struggle to take a hold the document.

　

However, while looking through it, his hands were still trembling slightly. Mies swore that he’d never have imagined that when Boss Ley’s expression was grim, it would be so frightening!　　

　　

That bone-piercing chilliness was something he had never experienced before. Swearing in the name of the honour of the Emberwings, he never wanted to meet that sort of gaze ever again. Heavens! He now felt that even the sweltering heat outside was more comfortable than staying in this room.　　

　　

“How is it? Have you finished looking through it? Tell me your thoughts!” Seeing Mies in this state, Leylin smiled gently and crossed his arms, body half leaning on the chair as he appeared to be at ease.

　

“This… Since it’s an order from the headquarters and the head of state, we can only obey. However, the members of our squadron don’t have enough strength, and I’m afraid we will need to mobilise and coordinate with the garrison!”　

Mies was no fool to have been able to survive up to this point. With some slight reflection, things immediately became clear to him, and he even had a contingency plan in mind already.

　

But… Mies stealthily peeked at Leylin, who was expressionless, and decided that before he could understand the man’s thoughts it was best not to speak his mind.

　　

That bit of bloodthirst earlier had frightened him.　　

　

“Mm, very good! I’ll leave contacting the local garrison to you. Don’t disappoint me!”　　

　　

Unexpectedly, Leylin did not ask about his plans and instead gave him a task.　　

　　

Though Leylin did not explicitly state the consequences of not completing the task, Mies could somewhat guess that it was something he absolutely did not want to bear.

　

“Understood, Captain!” As a long-term habit, while Leylin was issuing the command, Mies subconsciously stuck out his chest and saluted, expression full of respect.　　

　　

Ever since he had entered Leylin’s unit, he was completely convinced by Leylin and understood how he worked. It was consistently simple and crude, and he did not allow for retorts. Mies was naturally tactful.

“Mm, send down the order that I want our unit to assemble!” Leylin waved his arms, and Mies immediately escaped as if he was faced with a huge enemy.　　

　　

Though Leylin was usually very easy-going, to the point that Mies could get benefits like stealing some cool air here, the Leylin in missions was very resolute about killing. He was not going to make things bad for himself now.

　

After sending down the order, their unit assembled quickly.　　

　

On a field, Leylin wore military attire and walked past the orderly line, looking satisfied.

The Lava World was a world with Exemplaries. Their individual abilities far surpassed their collective strength, which was why this group was very small, with only ten or so members. However, every single one of them was at or above the fifth level of Fuming Wings, meaning they were at the peak of the Exemplary rank. He had three Earth ranks, and all had been forced to submission by him in missions. This was unthinkable in the eyes of many people.　

After all, Earth ranks were considered top-rated strengths even in the Atlan Union. They could take on important roles in the corps, so how could they be the subordinates of a little captain?

　

However, Leylin had done it, and many were in awe.　　

　

In reality, Leylin’s methods were simple. He had achieved victory with strength, and forcefully suppressed them.

　　

Even so, he had not intentionally taken in these three. They were an unexpected harvest.　　

　　

For him, Earth Ranks were comparable to rank 1 or 2 Magi or Warlocks in the Magus World. He could kill a large number of those who possessed this level of strength with just a breath, and he did not even need to spend much energy on it.

Even Sky ranks, who were comparable to rank 3 Magi, were nothing much.　　

　

The ones able to affect Leylin were Star ranks, who were of a similar strength! The attention of a Morning Star would forever be focused on enemies of the same level!　　

　

“Based on the intel, the commanders of the few Atlan military districts are all Star ranks! Rumours have it that the head of the union far exceeds the Star rank, and could be at rank 5, the Radiant Moon Realm…”

　

Learn touched his chin, a look of anticipation flashing in his eyes…

Chapter 557: Lava Base

“I really want to try my hand at fighting an enemy of this level of strength…” A fierce desire for battle burned in Leylin’s eyes, but was quickly withdrawn.

Though he was looking forward to the Radiant Moon Realm, he was no fool. Power at rank 5 was still far from him as he was now. Before he himself became a rank 5 Warlock, he was not going to fight with any Radiant Moon Magus, no matter who they were.

Leylin currently had his arms behind his back and after inspecting these members, he shouted, “Everyone, the head has issued our newest mission, which is an order for elimination! With us the Special Task Force taking the lead, the garrison troops will coordinate with us to uproot the Triserpent Sect strongholds that are throughout the Atlan Union!”

“Long live Atlan!” Many members yelled together, an agitated flush on their cheeks.

Compared to those troops formed with regular people, they were mostly people who were enlisted in a hurry and had not experienced much hardships so it was expected if they had unrealistic delusions. Furthermore, this time, it was clear that union was serious, and since the head had issued the command himself, it meant multiple opportunities to perform meritorious deeds.

And those meritorious deeds would net them higher level techniques, large amounts of information, and even the status and glory of nobility quite easily. How would they not be riled up?

“Good!” Leylin obviously knew what these people were thinking; On the contrary, he was no saint. Hence, he did not destroy their hopes right now.

“There are a total of fifteen strongholds in the eastern region that belong to the Triserpent Sect. I will now hand down the assignments…”

In actuality, Leylin had not even told them how to choose their targets. In his perspective, only he and the three Earth ranks were mildly useful in his group.

The others would probably only be useful running errands outside, or providing moral support.

It didn’t matter, since they were only destroying the branches of the Tri-serpent Sect, and the most powerful people there would probably be only at the Sky rank.

……

Within a large desert, boiling-hot temperatures caused slight distortions in the sky. Heat waves surged, causing the scenery in the distance to seem blurred.

“One of the branches of the Triserpent Sect is here! General Gilfah, your mission is to seal off this region and not let any suspicious characters escape. Any questions?”

In a simply constructed tent, Leylin pointed at a large map on the table and spoke to a white-haired Emberwing.

This Emberwing was obviously not young, and even his mottled red feathers were falling down. However, the tenacity was as strong as ever. What had Leylin raising his eyebrows in surprise was that this old man was a Sky rank.

“No problem!” Gilfah nodded matter-of-factly. “I will order the army to surround the area. Even a bug will not be able to escape!”

This high-ranking officer by the name of Gilfah was in charge of this region. He had been contacted by Mies.

While he had control over the troops by order of the head, Leylin had gotten this general’s support after displaying his strength.

“I hope you can destroy this nest in one go. A lot of disappearances in my jurisdiction are related to it,” The general brought up.

“I understand. Let’s go!” Leylin nodded and left the camp, suddenly waving his arms.

*Rumble!* His body turning into a tornado, he charged into the depths of the desert with a few similarly powerful pillars of light.

“This stronghold of the Triserpent Sect is really covert. If not for the vast network of spies controlled by the union, it would have been unlikely that I’d find this place…” Light flickered in Leylin’s eyes.

The Atlan Union was much too vast. Even if he had his bloodline and soul fire crystal and searched from city to city or even ran through the outskirts, it would still take several decades to cover the country. Even then, he could end up not even finding a trace of the Triserpent Sect.

They had long since been chased by the union, and their actions had always been secretive. Leylin had no confidence that he would coincidentally bump into them.

With the map, however, all the branches of the Triserpent Sect were bared before Leylin. There was no difficulty in finding them now.

“But… Did the three dukes really create the Triserpent Sect?” A giant, fire-red lake had appeared before Leylin’s eyes. At the heart of it, flames were vaguely seen. Based on the intel, the branch of the Triserpent Sect was under the lava lake.

Soul force surged through the lava and the desert to scan below, and it resulted in a marvellous expression on Leylin’s face.

“This…” With his soul force, Leylin could clearly see the many experiments in the laboratories of the Triserpent Sect branch, as well as the modified Emberwings.

“Bloodline modification experiments?” As a Warlock himself, he was no stranger to this, and could even be said to be a subject matter expert.

With just a look, he could find many traces of what the Magus World, even the Ouroboros Clan, were used to operative procedures.

“Could it be… that the Triserpent Sect really is an organisation set up by the three dukes?” Leylin’s eyes flashed, a crimson crystal already appearing his hands, two threads of pale soul flames twining around each other.

“No reaction… The two dukes aren’t here.” Leylin shook his head.

Though the range of bloodline and soul sensing was already quite vast, it was still too small in comparison to the whole Atlan Union, let alone the entire Lava World.

“Attack!” Thoughts whirling in his mind, Leylin unhesitatingly gave the order. A gigantic phantom phoenix made of fire appeared behind him. Bathed in pure golden flames, it was as if the real ancient phoenix had been reborn!

This was the pinnacle of the eighth level of Fireplume. Seeing this display, nobody would believe it even if Leylin himself admitted to not being an Emberwing.

The point mass of a Morning Star was incomparably tiny, and massive strength could be held within this tiny point. It would not cause any clashes with other energies.

Leylin had the A.I. Chip to analyse and perform simulations for him. In reality, he had secretly already practised up to the peak of the ninth level of Fireplume. In other words, the limit of rank 3!

However, as he lacked the training technique for the tenth level, he had been unable to progress further. Even if the A.I. Chip could simulate it, too much time would be spent on it and Leylin had thus lost his patience.

Hence, he had focused on Schiker. He was sure that with Schiker’s status, it was very possible for him to have access to the tenth level of Fireplume!

To Leylin’s knowledge, there were ten levels to Fireplume. The first three were for regular people, but the fourth and fifth, it would begin to touch on exemplary strength. The sixth and seventh were comparable to rank 1 and 2 Magi, while the eighth and ninth meant being able to battle rank 3 Magi! As long as he entered the tenth level, he would be a Star rank, which was comparable to a Morning Star Magus in the Magus World!

Leylin did not have much interest in the first nine levels of the technique, and was only invested in the tenth level.

After advancing to Morning Star, it meant that he had already chosen a path for himself. While Leylin had no plans of giving it up, other paths to power still had a lot of useful experience to give him.

Fireplume was one of the most advanced techniques among those of foreign origin. It could combine both physical and spiritual aspects, and this train of thought was a breath of fresh air for him.

If he could obtain the tenth level of Fireplume and gain clarity on the Emberwings’ path and system, it would definitely be of much use to him.

“Come out!” Leylin shouted, and an ear-piercing explosion sounded behind him, like a high-spirited phoenix cry filled with heat and excitement.

Amidst the cry, Leylin abruptly made his move. The flames that filled the sky were as splendid as the wings of a phoenix as they swept through the ground and shaved a layer of soil off the earth.

The ground kept trembling, and rocks and dirt were scattered everywhere. As if a geyser of water, the lava from the lake shot upwards as its surface emptied out, revealing a giant secret base underneath.

Many members of the Triserpent Sect raised their heads. Upon seeing the dazzling phantom phoenix, they yelled in alarm, “It’s Atlan’s Special Task Force! Those black leather dogs have caught up to us.”

The members of the Special Task Force were usually ruthless in their methods, possessed extraordinary power and dressed in black leather uniforms. That had netted them this title.

“Aren’t you wearing black robes too? What about it?” Leylin, who was in mid-air, grew speechless as he observed the followers who wore black, wide robes with an image of three black snakes intertwining on the surface.

While he was quibbling, a few streaks of powerful undulations rose, and two black-clothed people who were obviously the leaders blocked his way, dressed in luxurious robes. The sounds of members of the Triserpent Sect howling could be heard from within the stronghold.

“Take care of that trash as soon as possible!” Leylin’s brows furrowed. He could not sense any special aura from these two black-clothed people.

If they were higher-ups within the Tri-serpent Sect and had made contact with Morning Star, there should be some radiation residue or the like on their bodies, but there were no traces at all on these two leaders. This led to Leylin’s disappointment.

“Understood, leader!” A few streaks of red flames shot out, and Leylin’s Earth ranks immediately began their massacre, doing as they liked amongst the ordinary followers.

Crimson flames flashed, turning the region into a sea of fire.

Facing this attack that was at the Earth rank, these ordinary disciples were mowed down like grass. Under the prowess of the Exemplaries that he led, no matter how much battle intent the ordinary followers had, it all proved futile. That was the main reason why Leylin had brought a small team of only ten or so people, and dared to forcefully attack the enemy’s large-scaled base!

Chapter 559: Tingling Senses

There were many rebellious organisations in the Atlan Union, as well as various sects. However, the union leader had only chosen to act against the Triserpent Sect and Mobius Organisations, which led Leylin to make a mental association.

If the Triserpent Sect was targeted because of its three foreign Morning Star Warlocks, what about the Mobius Organisation? What did they have?

A trace of a smile appeared about Leylin’s lips. “Interesting! It’s getting increasingly interesting!”

He abruptly turned back and shouted, “All members, assemble…”

As Leylin had very few subordinates, he could act swiftly and decisively, bringing his unit to the Wox City Schiker had spoken of the very next afternoon.

After entering the city, Leylin sensed that the level of security was much higher than before. Even Leylin and the others were checked over once before being allowed entry. Uneasiness seemed to permeate the air.

‘Could the Mobius Organisation have caused a huge ruckus? Curious!’ Leylin touched his chin as he arrived at the area Schiker had spoken of, which was also the current station of the Special Task Force.

“Ley!” Loke welcomed him, pleasantly surprised. “It’s great that you could come so quickly!”

“What’s going on?” Leylin’s brows furrowed in feigned concern.

“We might have found the Mobius Organisation’s headquarters. The attack that Instructor led was met with a violent counterattack from the other side. It’s best that you personally take a look…”

Loke smiled wryly as he got out of the way. There was a gloom between his brows that would not disappear easily. It was so well-feigned that Leylin cheered for him on the inside. It was rare to find actors of this calibre.

As he opened the door and found Schiker inside, Leylin displayed an expression of ‘alarm’. “Instructor, how did you…”

The Schiker in front of him now was in a pitiful state, wrapped up to the point that he seemed like a mummy. His right arm was hung in front of his chest.

“Ley, you did well!” Seeing the worry on Leylin’s face, Schiker looked gratified, “You only took a day to get here…”

“It’s my honour to serve my lord!” Leylin looked devoted. After all, the other party had connections in the capital, and was his best route to getting firasource stones. He could not give him up so easily.

“What exactly happened?” Leylin clenched his fists, sparks emitting from his body.

“This level… It means your Fireplume is about to break through to the ninth level, entering the peak Sky rank…” Schiker watched Leylin, eyes full of an unspeakable radiance. “In terms of training, you’ll probably surpass me soon enough…”

“Not at all! It’s all thanks to Instructor’s nurture!” Leylin bowed slightly to show his respect.

“Mm! We underestimated our opponent this time. I’d assumed it was an ordinary branch of the enemy, but never could I have expected that we’d found their headquarters…”

Leylin listened closely. Schiker, with Loke and the rest as well as the support he garnered from the army, should have been able to complete the operation of destroying the Mobius Organisation smoothly. However, while wiping out one of the branches nearby, they’d found quite a few red-clothed bishops!

Schiker, who had realised he had found a big opportunity, was obviously excited as he gathered quite a few Sky rank generals and prepared to eliminate these bishops at one go.

However, when the time came for the actual attack, Schiker found out he had completely wrong.

There had been a mistake in his calculations. This wasn’t some branch of the Mobius Organisation, but their headquarters!

They had astounding harvests under the joint effort of the Sky ranks at first, and had even seized much of the resources the Mobius Organisation had stocked up on. Suddenly, Schiker was unwilling to say more, a hint of fear appearing on his expression.

This expression immediately alarmed Leylin. For the fearless Schiker to become this way, the matter could not be simple.

“I’ve gathered you only so that you can take over the next operations of the Special Task Force, especially since I’m in this state!” Schiker raised his arm and laughed bitterly.

“As for the issues there, there will be people coming in from the capital to take care of it. Don’t worry!”

Leylin came out, still baffled, and went to look for Loke. Under the questioning of this new ‘superior’, Loke narrated all the parts Schiker had failed to explain clearly.

As it turned out, while transporting the resources back, Schiker and the rest had been met with an ambush, resulting in total annihilation. Even the resources had been lost, and a few Sky rank generals had perished on the spot. Only Schiker had somehow managed to survive.

“Oh? How many people were there?” Leylin had some conjectures, and asked curiously.

“Ju– Just one, but he was more terrifying than thousands of troops and horses, because… that was a Star rank!”

Loke’s voice was low, as if afraid to alarm anyone. There was an obvious hint of joy in the fact that he was weak and useless in a battle between Sky ranks, and had thus not participated in that operation. Otherwise, he’d be dead right now.

“A Star rank?!” Leylin seemed to breathe in sharply, although his mind was actually working quickly.

Star ranks were the most powerful members of the Lava World. They were on the same level as Morning Star Magi of the Magus World, and were absolutely certain of their cultivation path. They were existences who had already generated a core.

Every single one of these existences was celebrated. Their achievements would be written in history books or even as legends, passed down for eternity.

Facing such an expert, Sky ranks would only be courting death unless there were other Star ranks suppressing them.

If Schiker had met one, it meant he had incredibly bad luck.

‘On top of that…’ Leylin touched his chin, deep in thought, ‘Schiker’s backing must be quite firm for even a Morning Star Magus to have qualms about killing him and leave him alive!’

Leylin, who was also a Morning Star, naturally knew the terror of rank 4s. For Morning Star Magi, Sky ranks were just like slightly large ants.

The generals, who were also at the Sky rank, had all died, leaving only Schiker behind. Leylin did not think that this Morning Star Magus had a good heart and let Schiker go. It was very likely that the real reason was because he feared the person backing Schiker.

‘Looks like Schiker’s background is very mysterious! I’ll need to pay more attention and take advantage of that!’ Leylin decided resolutely.

“That’s the basic situation… With the motivation from this event, many branches of the Mobius Organisation that had begun to disperse seem to be congregating again…”

Loke shrugged his shoulders, the wry smile not diminishing at all, “But we only need to push through during this period of time. The Northern Duke will reach this place soon, and when that happens, we can…”

‘Just continue acting!’ Leylin rolled his eyes inside, while he looked to be in favour of his words.

“The Northern Duke? That’s a famous Star rank of the Union! With him around, the Mobius Organisation won’t be able to settle down and have a peaceful time!” he exclaimed in admiration.

At the same time, he now understood the reason for Schiker’s listless look. Since someone with a higher status was taking over, his own position was dispensable, and his achievements would be wrested away from him.

Though the Northern Duke might not think much of these merits, Schiker would not want to accept charity from others. Leylin knew very well what type of person he was, and he was not one to admit defeat.

“In that case, I should return and quickly take over the defence of the Special Task Force, preparing for the counterattack!”

Leylin and Loke hastily bid farewell.

Leylin did not like this idea. The Mobius Organisation had Star ranks, as well as many helpers and followers. After noticing something, they would definitely retreat, and by the time that Northern Duke reached, he would only see an empty nest.

However, all this was none of Leylin’s business. What he focused on was the resources that had been stolen by the mysterious Star rank.

“To be able to get a Star rank dispatched after them, these resources must be especially precious. There might even be firasource stones inside…” Leylin’s eyes flashed. He was in dire need of these stones, but he did not have that many points to exchange them. Since the proper way wasn’t working, he would need to think of other methods.

Not long after Loke left, Leylin’s expression changed.

He came to his room and took out the crimson gemstone from before.

Rays of brilliance were twinkling, the two threads of pale flames beginning to increase in intensity at the middle.

Seeing this, a smile showed on Leylin’s face, “They’ve come together…”

……

At the bottom of the lava not far from the city, in a secret space that had been opened. Two figures were facing each other, sitting cross-legged.

All of a sudden, a bald male with no eyebrows or a beard opened his eyes, eyes full of doubt, “I felt a trace of my soul flames! Which Warlock has arrived here?”

“I had the same feeling!” Opposite him was a young girl in blood-red robes. Her eyes were strange vertical pupils that would make people shudder in fear.

“Is this a trap?” Gilbert muttered to himself and asked slowly.

“It doesn’t seem like it, unless the Ouroboros Clan was completely breached and Freya and the rest have all died.” Blood Duchess Emma was very confident in the loyalty of her students.

“Then… Have the reinforcements from the Warlock Union arrived?” Excitement appeared in Gilbert’s tone.

“Hmph! If they were reliable, we wouldn’t be in this situation!” In contrast, Emma’s retort showed that she did not have a good impression of the Warlock Union.

Chapter 560: Meeting

“It’s not for us to decide anyway, since they’ve already taken the initiative to come here!”

Crimson flames flashed on Emma’s body as she appeared in mid-air, Gilbert right behind her. Eventually, the two came to a stop, standing side by side.

“The soul flames are closing in very quickly, and the other party’s aura is very powerful! It’s a Morning Star, but… This blood line undulation… How is it possible…” Gilbert turned to Emma in disbelief, only to be met with Emma’s eyes filled with similar astonishment and suspicion.

From the incoming person, they felt the purest Kemoyin bloodline aura. But how was that possible?

There had always only been three Morning Star Warlocks in the Ouroboros Clan.

‘Did the First Elder come back to life?’ An idea rose in Gilbert’s mind, but was quickly extinguished. He had personally seen the death of the First Elder, and his point mass had even returned to the astral plane.

From the thickness of the bloodline, the purity of the other party’s Kemoyin bloodline was even above that of themselves, even that of the First Elder!

“Who is it?” Gilbert and Emma watched the red rays that were shooting over from the distance, filled with curiosity.

*Sou!* The light rays dissipated, revealing the appearance of a handsome young man.

A bright smile on his face, and he rushed to bow towards Gilbert. “Mentor… I’ve arrived!”

In the next moment, Gilbert and Emma’s mouths were just as wide, their eyeballs almost popping out. “Leylin? How’s that possible?”

……

A good while later, while Gilbert and Emma seemed to have accepted Leylin’s promotion to Morning Star as reality, there was still a shock that could not be concealed in their eyes.

“… This is how it happened. I advanced to Morning Star just when Phosphorescence Swamp was about to be breached, and then killed Demon Hunter Cyril. The allied forces withdrew, and both sides are restraining themselves. The situation has now stabilised…”

Leylin gave a brief overview of what he had experienced in the Magus World. Of course, anything that touched upon his secrets, such as the A.I. Chip, the Lamia fingerbone and all that, was obviously hidden and not discussed. Gilbert and Emma had not asked either.

Of those who had reached the realm of Morning Star, who did not have their own secrets? Even the two of them had many fortuitous meetings while at rank 3, and received inheritances from ruins and the like, which had allowed them to thankfully advance to rank 4.

“In that case… That guy, Cyril, is really dead…” Emma’s eyes were filled with astonishment as she sized up Leylin. Compared to her own age, Leylin was much too young right now.

However, it was this adolescent Warlock who had caused Demon Hunter Cyril’s fall?

Emma couldn’t help but recall Cyril’s terrifying demonic spells, as well as his power and abundant experience. Her opinion of this young man raised immensely.

“Alright! Well then… Are the two of you willing to return to the Magus World now?” Leylin took off the silver-white necklace on his neck that was emanating the rays of stars. Gilbert and Emma’s breaths immediately became heavier.

This was the projection of the coordinates of Leylin’s astral gate. It could open the astral gate and allow them to return to the Ouroboros Clan.

However, Gilbert and Emma exchanged a wry smile, and did not speak. Instead, the area turned strangely silent.

“I understand. It seems like Your Graces still have very important things to do in the Lava World!” Leylin laughed, not minding the least.

“Yes!” In the end, it was Emma who spoke up. “Leylin, you’re a Morning Star just like us, so you don’t have to call us ‘Your Grace’. Just call us by our names…”

“Alright, my Lords!” Leylin looked solemn as he began to make guesses. “Is it because of the firasource stones?”

The moment the words left his mouth, Leylin noticed the change in Gilbert’s expression, while Emma cried out in alarm.

“You’ve actually found out!”

“Of course! It’s a treasure that can strengthen the soul and even the point mass. Any Morning Star would go crazy over it!” Leylin nodded as he admitted.

“Alright. In that case, we don’t have to keep hiding it from you like before.” Emma immediately threw away all hesitation, “Although Jupiter’s Lightning had duped us, we were much stronger than they had anticipated. This was especially so in another world, where their Radiant Moon could not intrude. While we did suffer a bit, we managed to break out, and while searching for the road back we found out about the firasource stones.”

Emma sounded emotional, “How can we let go of this treasure that can amplify soul force? We three Morning Star Warlocks thus led the way and took in a few oppressed races within the Atlan Union, creating the organisation, the Triserpent Sect. On the surface, we want to overthrow the government of Atlan, but in reality, we prioritise gathering firasource stones!”

Leylin nodded. In this meeting, he had found that the two Dukes’ soul undulations were obviously much more powerful than in the Magus World. It seemed to be the effect from the firasource stones!

“Then… where’s the First Elder?” Leylin asked, and the atmosphere immediately became gloomy. A long while later, Gilbert spoke, his voice hoarse.

“There are many powerful beings in the Lava World. At the peak are a few who have a strength similar to Radiant Moon Magi. At the beginning, with the three of us working together, everything went smoothly, and we even seized quite a lot of firasource stones. However, the organisation Jupiter’s Lightning set up here was obviously much larger, and even had relations with the higher ups in Atlan. The head of their union was one who had trained up to the thirteenth level of the Fireplume technique, which was unheard of in history. He was a peak Radiant Moon Magus! Under his assault along with many other Magi, the First Elder fell… while trying to protect us…”

Though Gilbert explained it in a simplified manner, Leylin could tell how desperate that battle had been. He could keenly tell that Gilbert had concealed some things.

Whatever it was, he would never believe the First Elder was so selfless, but Gilbert and Emma had not asked why Leylin had not come here right after the battle and instead done so only now. Leylin thus would not make his opinion known.

“This means Mentor and Madam Emma are preparing to stay here for a period of time and conspire to obtain more firasource stones? In that case, we can collaborate!” Leylin touched his chin. He held the same thoughts as these two Morning Star Warlocks. With two Morning Star helpers, he had more confidence.

“That’s great. With you joining us, Leylin, our strength will increase by a large amount, and we will even have a way to retreat!” Emma and Gilbert exchanged a glance, the elation obvious in their eyes.

It looked like they had been planning to cause a huge ruckus before leaving this world.

Leylin could not help but feel his scalp tingle. The unrestrained attacks of three Morning Star Warlocks would definitely throw the entire Atlan Union into chaos.

However, this was none of his business. As long as he could obtain enough firasource stones, he didn’t mind pushing the union into the abyss, or breaking it into smithereens.

Leylin patted his head, suddenly remembering something as he spoke. “Right! I’m lying low in the Special Task Force in Atlan for now. In order to obtain their trust, I destroyed a few of Triserpent Sect’s strongholds…”

“It doesn’t matter. Those are just the surrounding organisations. We can just create a few more soon. To really obtain their full trust, it doesn’t matter even if we hand over the whole Triserpent Sect.”

Gilbert waved his arms, not minding the least.

“In actuality, we’ve also been keeping a low profile in the Atlan Union and even obtained titles. Most of the intel regarding the Triserpent Sect was intentionally divulged by us!” Emma laughed, a layer of sparkling red feathers appearing on her body.

“The Emberwings and Fireplume,” Leylin chuckled. Morning Star Warlocks were all grandmasters at remodelling bloodlines. With Emma and Gilbert’s experience, passing off an identity as an Emberwing was way too easy.

On top of that, these two were ruthless and had even sold away their organisation just to obtain trust. That was probably how they gained their titles, and why they did not mind Leylin’s actions.

Leylin was rather speechless at that, feeling like he still needed to learn much more from his seniors in these dark areas. If the followers of the Triserpent Sect found out they had been betrayed by their leaders, they would probably just break down.

Leylin could not help but begin to pity them.

“Do you have any intel?” Leylin asked. These two Warlocks had been laying low here for longer than he had, and definitely knew more secrets.

“Of course!” Gilbert laughed proudly.

“Based on our sources, there is only one place where the firasource stones are being generated, and that’s the capital of the Atlan Union— Tylasus! It only comes from the head himself, which means the source is being controlled by him. There are very few reserves outside!”

“The head who is at the thirteenth level of Fireplume, the peak of Radiant Moon?” Leylin sighed lightly, knowing things were going to get troublesome.

Three Morning Stars cooperating was still not enough to snatch something from this opponent.

That was not all. Fighting in another world, foreign beings like them obviously had a disadvantage compared to the people of this land. The World’s Will itself would also have a bias and help its own people, and even if a peak Radiant Moon were to head over, they might not be able to deal with this opponent.

“Gilbert and I have already set up a plan. We’re planning to sneak into Tylasus two months later, on the Holy Solar Day. You’re just in time!” Emma exclaimed.

Leylin touched his chin. Holy Solar Day was a very important festival of the Emberwings. During that time, the head would have to make a speech, participate in the feast and whatnot. There were more than enough opportunities to sneak into his residence.

Chapter 562: Leaking Intel

To Mies’ knowledge, Star ranks were the most powerful existences in the Lava World.

He, who had not seen much in the world, was not aware there was an even more powerful realm after the Star rank.

However, just one Star rank was enough to cause their leader, Schiker, to be heavily injured, and Sky ranked experts to die in large numbers. If another one had appeared? Mies didn’t even want to consider that.

“Has his Grace, the Northern Duke, arrived?” he guessed.

Well aware of all that was going on and actually the main offender himself, Leylin had a serious expression, “I’m afraid not! I’ll need to see the instructor!”

On the way, Leylin met Loke again. However, the man seemed to have much on his shoulders, and he could not tell if this was real or a pretence.

“Reporting in!” Leylin and Loke shouted outside the door.

“Come in!” Schiker’s slightly weary voice sounded from within. After entering the room, Leylin’s nose twitched, the smell of disinfectant and ointment filling his nostrils.

Schiker was still looking like a mummy, but looked to be in a better mental state. He could now perform simple actions.

“Did you feel those undulations too?” Schiker asked with his eyes unfocused, watching a gigantic white tree whose light yellow flowers were blossoming.

The undulations from a Star rank battle were as dazzling and bright as a torch in the dark night. Most likely, all the Earth ranks in a 500km radius around them had sensed it at as well. Leylin and Loke nodded.

“Sigh… Looks like one more powerful person has appeared apart from the previous Morning Star… The situation does not look good. Ley, send down the directive. Our Special Task Force is to wait for orders. Do not act recklessly!”

“I know!” Leylin apprehensively did as he was asked, but seemed hesitant.

“What is it?” Schiker asked. Seeing Leylin this way, he found it funny.

“Actually, instructor, I actually went into the battlefield in secret…” Leylin mumbled.

“What…” Schiker’s mouth went wide, as if he had just seen a rare beast.

Just a single stray wave from a Star rank battle could easily cause serious injuries or even death to Sky ranks. And this fearless fool had actually rushed in?

It was not only Schiker. Loke who was at the side was also stunned, feeling like he had to refamiliarize himself with this ‘Ley’.

“Hehe…” Leylin touched his head, looking embarrassed.

“I heard about what happened to Instructor and went to take a look and search for trails of that Star rank. It was in preparation for the arrival of His Grace, the Northern Duke…” With Leylin’s hot-headed displays in the past, this was a very plausible situation. Hence, Schiker merely nodded, not doubting anything at all.

“You…” Schiker had no idea what to say. “He must have thought little of a Sky ranked kid like you. On top of that, you must have had enough luck to come back safely. If not, we’d only be seeing your corpse now. No, we wouldn’t even have seen your corpse…”

“Your courage is really one of a kind…” Schiker nodded. “Well then, what did you see?”

“This is the report I prepared. Sir, take a look!”

Leylin immediately produced a sketch with two faces on it. The first sketch was someone Schiker did not recognise, because it was a portrait Leylin had drawn of nobody in particular. The other image, however, had Schiker’s eyes turning red, his throat letting loose a roar, “It’s him! He’s the one who attacked me!”

“Quick! Tell me everything you saw!” Schiker’s remaining arm held Leylin’s tightly, eyes hopeful.

“Alright. I…”

Leylin narrated the story he had come up with previously. All of it was the truth, though he took himself out of the equation.

“In that case, the Star rank who attacked me was defeated, and you remember which direction he fled in? You did well!”

The ruthlessness was apparent in Schiker’s eyes. He could sense that this could be his only chance at taking revenge.

*Thud!* A stack of documents fell to the ground, and Loke who was at the side cried out in surprise.

“What’s wrong?” Leylin watched Loke, who had panicked, and found the situation hilarious as he went forward and asked in concern.

“N-Nothing. I was just shocked!” Concealing the panic and anxiety well, Loke regained his previous demeanour.

“Oh, is that so.” Leylin nodded. He could now confirm that Loke was most likely a spy sent in from the Mobius Organisation, and his superior might very well be Collins.

He obviously knew where Collins was hiding, because he had done something to Collins’ body. Only Leylin, who had the A.I. Chip, was able to place an imprint that would determine Collins’ location without arousing suspicion.

Of course, he wouldn’t be so stupid as to reveal he had placed some symbol on the other party’s body. He just needed to point in a direction, and with this important clue, finding Collins was a simple matter with the entire Atlan Union working on it.

“Calm down, calm down!” Schiker stood and began to pace around the room. His face was flushed as he cursed.

After standing straight for a long while, Schiker lay back down, disappointed.

“No! Even a heavily injured Star rank isn’t someone we can just walk up to!” After calculating the power he had at hand, Schiker announced that he was giving up. Only his tightly-clenched fists signified unwillingness and desire for revenge.

“Sir, are we going to let him off like this?” Leylin seemed to be extremely impulsive as he yelled.

“Yes! Instructor, we can’t just let them off like this!” Loke relaxed inside, but shouted along as well.

“I know, but…” Schiker smiled bitterly.

“There’s no ‘but’s!” A resolute voice sounded from outside, and the door was pushed open. A tall, sturdy Emberwing walk in, dressed in military uniform. “Schiker, I will help you take your revenge.”

An intense aura took over the room, and the atmosphere grew as heavy as lead.

“Thank you so much, Uncle Martin!” Schiker’s eyes turned, looking ready to cry. This was the first time Leylin and Loke had seen such an expression on him, and their eyes grew wide as they watched on in surprise. When would they see Schiker, who had gained repute for his tenacity, having such an expression?

If not for pinching himself firmly, Loke would think he was dreaming.

Compared to Loke, Leylin was more focused on the energy undulations. “Fireplume, the tenth level of Fireplume! He must be the special commissioner, the Star rank Northern Duke!”

This was the first time Leylin had seen an Emberwing at the Star realm. He did not dare let down his guard and hid his point mass and soul energy completely and leaving only Fireplume operating outside.

“You must be Ley, right? Not bad! You’re brave! If you ever go to the Thunderoll Legion, remember to look for me!”

Martin extended a large hand that was like steel and patted Leylin’s shoulders, eyes full of praise. “Now, bring me to the place where they battled…”

A surging bloodlust was present in his eyes.

“Understood, sir!” Leylin sounded excited as he yelled, though he was actually giving a long sigh inside. “Luckily, he didn’t see through my pretence. Looks like a high-levelled Fireplume and the concealed strength of my point mass is enough for me to get away with this situation even in front of a Star rank Emberwing…”

Having ascertained this, Leylin now had more confidence in sneaking into the Atlan capital, Tylasus.

“Let’s go!” Fiery-red flames lit up, and Martin and Leylin left before Loke could come back to himself.

“In-Instructor, he’s…” Loke was tongue-tied.

“Haha, he’s the Northern Duke. A Star rank who once killed 18 fire elemental commanders in the Death Grand Canyon!”

A flush appeared on Schiker’s face from his elation; he was extremely excited.

“I heard from Father that even among Star ranks, Uncle Martin is still the best. The other party is now injured, and if Uncle Martin finds him, he definitely won’t be able to escape!”

He ferociously punched forward, hope and carefreeness in his expression, “My revenge will be taken quickly…”

Schiker went on and on excitedly, not noticing the hint of concern in Loke’s eyes.

……

Days later, a piece of shocking news spread through the eastern region of the Atlan Union. There were even indicators that this news would be spread to other countries. A patriarch of the Mobius Organisation, who was a terrifying being at the Star rank, had been killed by the union’s Northern Duke, Martin!

In that instant, the Northern Duke Martin’s reputation spread throughout the eastern region, causing many rebelling organisations to be panic-stricken. However, few knew that Leylin and two others had been adding fuel to the flames.

The fall of a Star rank was a huge blow to the Mobius Organisation. Ever since Collins’ death, the progress of the purging operation in the eastern region was lightning quick.

The squadron that Leylin led showed no mercy as they uprooted all organisations and strongholds that had anything to do with the Mobius Organisation. Such a fierce method instantly netted a favourable evaluation from Schiker, and with the intel from before, Leylin sensed that Schiker now treated him as a trusted aide.

As for Loke? That kid had been restless nowadays, and was not as enthusiastic in his missions. This had resulted in Schiker’s dissatisfaction. Of course, Leylin knew the reason, but he would not make it known.

A month had passed by in a flash after the large-scaled purging missions were over. The most magnificent and important festival of the Emberwings was now fast approaching — Holy Solar Festival!

Chapter 563: Formal Visit

A fleet of vehicles slowly drove out of Wox City. Leylin turned to look at the city, a ruminating smile about his lips.

　　

The Atlan Union’s operation had dealt a huge blow to both the Mobius Organisation and the Triserpent Sect.

　　

As he had found the opponent’s headquarters and killed a Star rank, the eastern line that Schiker was in charge of was instantly rewarded by the leader. Now, they were heading back to the headquarters of the Atlan Union to have their merits evaluated after giving their reports.　　

　　

Within another vehicle, Schiker’s injuries had pretty much healed and he watched Martin, deep in thought and sitting upright. He restrained himself for a while, before he could not help himself and asked, “Uncle Martin, what are you thinking about?”　　

　　

“Oh, it’s nothing.” Martin seemed to recover from his daze and looked tired.　　

　　

“I’m letting my imagination run wild in my old age,” he laughed, mocking himself. “The opponent this time is from another world. I keep having a feeling that if not for his being injured, I might just have…”　　

　　

“Hss…” Schiker sucked in deeply, “Someone as powerful as Uncle Martin! How about the person who injured him?”　　

　　

“Exactly! The mysterious person who exchanged blows with him is a giant threat, but no matter how hard I tried to find them, I couldn’t find any traces…” Martin rubbed his brows.　　

　

What worried him more was that with his intuition as a Star rank, he had a feeling that something big was going to happen at the Holy Solar Festival. However, there seemed to be a veil that he could not see through.

　　

“With the head around, who else could create trouble? I’m thinking too much into this…” Martin chuckled, and closed his eyes to get more rest, not realising there was someone watching him from the outside.

　　

“Tsk tsk… Tenth level of Fireplume! I really want to use him as a guinea pig and do some research…” Leylin withdrew his gaze.　　

　　

Martin was obviously an existence that had broken through to the Star rank, and in Leylin’s eyes, was like a specimen with very high research value.　　

　　

If he were to make a move on the sly, he had a very good chance of taking him down and obtaining the secret of the tenth level of Fireplume.

　　

However, for the greater benefits, Leylin restrained himself.　　

　　

Besides, even regular contact throughout the day was enough for the A.I. Chip to gather data on the energy undulations and forcefield of the Emberwing, speeding up the simulation of the tenth level.

……　　

　　

The sacred land of the Emberwings that was also the capital of the Atlan Union— Tylasus City appeared before Leylin.

　　

As the Holy Solar Festival was fast approaching, the whole city was in a state of merriment, with multicoloured streamers everywhere.　　

　　

In Leylin’s eyes, Tylasus City was not that vast, but since it was constructed on cliffs and precipices, it gave one the feeling of it being a boundless city in the sky.　　

　　

Red floating feathery cotton-like items floated down into the city like snow.

　　

Schiker and Martin parted ways at the entrance to the city, and brought Leylin and Loke to another area.

　　

Passing through a large square and a commemoratory forest full of large stone sculptures, Schiker arrived at a building as large and as majestic as a palace, the whole body made of some sort of white jade.　　

　

“This is the leader’s residence?” Loke’s voice trembled, as if extremely emotional. Leylin, however, shot him a discreet glance. This spy from the Mobius Organisation, which was also Jupiter’s Lightning, was probably targeting this place. That excitement was probably not feigned.

　　

Leylin, on the contrary, had a change in expression when looking over this residence, as a trace of solemness appeared in his eyes.

　

In his line of sight, there were powerful energy lights all over the residence, as well as many probing spells and the like. This was a normal sight.　　

　　

However, there seemed to be a terrifying feeling emanating from within the residence. This aura was scalding hot and dense, where the radiation from powerful fire elemental particles was felt.

　　

A humming sound pervaded the area as the world seemed to come to a standstill in Leylin’s eyes. Everything was monochrome, and there were distortions in the lines of the building. Eye-piercing red lights constantly leaked out to form an ancient fire phoenix that faced the sky and gave a long cry.　　

　　

*Chirp!* This fire phoenix was almost alive, eyes filled with wit as it glanced in Leylin’s direction.

　　

Surprised, Leylin immediately curbed all the undulations from his body, where his soul force holed up within his point mass.

　

A great heat wave swept past, and red rays of light flashed in Leylin’s eyes, causing him to momentarily be dazed.　　

　　

“What’s wrong, Ley?” Schiker immediately noticed him acting oddly and turned around, looking concerned.

　　

After all that had happened, he now treated Leylin as his trusted aide, and even depended on him more than Loke. They had a very good relationship.　　

　　

“Oh, it’s nothing. I was just thinking about how we’re going to see the magnificent leader of the state, so I was somehow lost in thought!” Leylin still looked slightly distracted but had obviously regained his senses. It seemed that only Schiker had seen him in that state.　　

　　

“Haha!” Schiker patted Leylin in understanding, causing a trace of jealousy to arise in Loke’s expression.　　

　　

“Lord Schiker!” The guards at both sides of the residence saluted with their bodies straight, not hindering Leylin and his group. It was obvious that they had known of Schiker’s identity beforehand.　　

　　

“Instructor, so you’re the son of the leader! It’s truly an honour to be able to serve you…” Loke entered the resistance, so stirred up that he seemed about to spit foam.

　

In order to get these two talents to submit more wholeheartedly, Schiker had revealed his identity as the leader’s son on the way to Tylasus.　　

　

In actuality, while he’d assumed that his identity was kept secret, Loke and Leylin had long since found out. However, they obviously appeared to be shocked, and were only one step short of grovelling at Schiker’s feet.　　

　　

“I’m going to bring you to see Father. Remember to be cautious with your words!”　　

　　

There was no excitement on Schiker’s expression, and his expression instead turning darker. This evidently had to do with his status as the illegitimate child, and Leylin and Loke naturally did not say more.

　

There was a second wall after they entered the residence. Schiker did not enter directly, but instead brought Leylin and Loke to another area similar to a duty room.　

　　

Leylin glanced at the inscriptions beside the room. There was a line of small wording written in black on a red base: Military Office.

　　

‘Could this be the Atlan Union leader’s personal force?’ Leylin could sense the Emberwing undulations from outside the place.

　　

He found that the auras of all the soldiers inside the office were immensely powerful, and none were below the eighth level of Fireplume. He could feel powerful crimson flames in a few other directions, causing his Fireplume at the peak of the ninth level to turn somewhat sluggish.

　　

‘Star ranks! Perhaps only the leader of the Atlan Union will be able to order Star ranks around. He’s probably a rank 5 Magus…’ Leylin wondered.

“I am Schiker, bringing two of my subordinates to see the leader. I’ve made an appointment,” Schiker spoke to a staff member at the military office, passing an emblem-like item over.

　

The staff member had a stern expression. From the undulations from the ninth level of Fireplume, he was also a peak Sky rank.

　

Taking Schiker’s emblem, he placed it on a piece of apparatus and scanned it.

　　

*Beep!* The screen on the apparatus leapt up, and showed information on Schiker’s appearance and some other basic details.　　

　

He stood up, performing a military salute, “Officer Schiker, you can bring two subordinates inside.”

　　

“Thanks” Ever since Schiker entered the residence, he had spoken sparingly, to the point that every single word was as precious as gold. Leylin and Loke struggled to suppress the excitement in their hearts and followed behind him as a military official led the way.

　　

‘A.I. Chip! Record information on the structure, as well as powerful energy responses. Whether it’s heat, electrons, radiation or chemical reactions, record everything!’ Leylin was inwardly communicating with the A.I. Chip, making the most of his time and creating a topographic map of this residence.　　

　　

‘The moment those two Kemoyin dukes found out about my status, they immediately threw this job at me while they relaxed. Sigh…’ Leylin rolled his eyes inside, but knew that they had already prepared this operation for a long time. Coming in mid-way of their plans meant he had lucked out, so he did not take this to heart.　　

　　

‘Firasource stones… This soul treasure is only distributed from the residence of the leader. There’s definitely something wrong!’ A glint flashed in Leylin’s eyes and withdrew again as he lowered his head and followed the official in front. They passed through several sentries and corners one after another. These security measures were all shown on the surface, and there were probably many more in the unknown.　　

　

In actuality, Leylin disapproved of these measures. For the leader, they were probably a burden, and at crucial moments, only his rank 5 strength could suppress everything.

　　

However, this was the anguish of a person occupying the top seat. Even if it was impractical, it was needed for a person befitting his status.　　

　

“His Highness, the leader, is inside. You have half an hour!” The official brought Leylin and the others before a large red door and gave a deep bow before retreating.　　

　　

Schiker took in a deep breath and held the brass handle of the door, “Father!”

　　

“Come in!” The voice was gentle, yet held within an irrefutable intent. Even the air seemed to distort, obstructing the usual operation of rules and physics.

　

‘There’s a rank 5 inside, but I have the A.I. Chip, as well as Fireplume at the peak of the ninth level as a cover. That’s enough to conceal my original strength!’

　　

Leylin, who had faith in his strength, followed him in.

Chapter 564: Infiltration

Leylin was clear that this was a huge test for him.　　

　　

If his disguise did not get through the leader of the Emberwings, everything was over. He could forget gaining his trust and the entire plan would have to be revised.　　

　　

Hence, he had to go through with this, but it wasn’t as if he was entirely unprepared.　　

　　

At least, the two Giant Kemoyin Serpent Dukes had stealthily entered as well and were constantly on the watch outside the residence. If the leader noticed anything, Leylin would immediately use his Kemoyin Serpent Transformation and attack. With three Morning Star Warlocks together, it would probably be enough to escape.　　

　　

After all, the three Kemoyin Elders from before had the record of fighting evenly with a rank 5 Radiant Moon Magus. Though the most powerful First Elder had already fallen, Leylin believed he was no less powerful than him.

　　

With three Giant Kemoyin Warlocks working together, it was enough for them to escape even if they could not win. That was what the three of them had counted on before daring to draw up this plan.　　

　　

“A.I. Chip!” Leylin called out in a low voice.　　

　

[Beep! Beginning to conceal energy undulations.]

The A.I. Chip intoned loyally, causing the aura on Leylin’s body to become more obvious as if he was a pure Emberwing.

　　

The hidden strength of the point mass of a Morning Star, the secret technique to hide bloodlines as well as the support of the A.I. Chip gave Leylin the confidence that he could get away with all this under the rank 5’s nose!

　

Taking a deep breath, Leylin followed Schiker into the room, bowing to the figure at the middle.

　　

This was a large study room. Simple armour, oil paintings and the like filled it with a history that changed the atmosphere. What surprised Leylin was the feeling that a domain had automatically been created in the study room.　　

　　

This was not the domain of Morning Star, but a special space that had been formed due to the long period of time it had existed.

　

“Schiker, you’re here!” The head’s voice was gentle as he watched Schiker and the rest enter.

　　

“Father!” Schiker called out after he went through a thousand different expressions.

　

“It’s been hard on you, get up. Are these your two subordinates? Excellent!” When the sound fell, Leylin felt his heart squeeze, and entire self get nervous. Immediately after, he felt something like a boiling hot gaze sweep at his body, causing him to tremble.

　

When the gaze was on his body, his point mass shuddered, as it his soul force defences was being forced to the surface, but Leylin firmly stopped it.　　

　

Meanwhile, his Fireplume, which had reached the peak of the ninth level, formed a giant energy tide that kept the point mass within. Terrifying flame energy began to revolve spontaneously, resisting the spying from outside.　　

　

“Hm?” The head made a light sound of surprise. “You must be Ley, right? Raise your head.”

　　

Though the voice was gentle, it held the hint of an irrefutable command. Almost at the very moment the voice was heard, Leylin raised his head like it was a conditioned reflex.　　

　　

Following that, he saw a handsome young man with red hair and eyebrows, looks slightly similar to that of Schiker. He wore a loose white robe, and his eyes seemed to hold… praise, within them?

“Pretty good strength, and a pure flame energy.” The red-haired young man nodded, and turned in the other direction.

　

Loke’s body shivered, but the head said nothing. It was no surprise either, though. Just a soldier at the seventh level of the fire feathered technique was not enough to attract the leader’s notice.　　

　　

“I’ve already looked through your achievements in detail. I hope you will continue to work hard in the future and protect our Union…” The handsome head encouraged them and waved his arms.

　　

Leylin and Loke immediately retreated with expressions of reverence.　　

　　

*Thud!* The door to the room closed, leaving only Schiker and the head inside. The head’s aura changed once more, and his expression while watching Schiker turned emotional, “It’s been hard on you these past few years!”　　

　

“It’s service for the union!” Schiker had a taut expression while speaking, but his clenched fists displayed the dissatisfaction in his heart right now.　　

　

“Forget it. I know you care nothing for using my name and working, so I’ll let things move according to the usual procedure. Your contributions are enough for you to be promoted to be an admiral. Make some preparations, you will work at the Tylasus garrison!”

　

The leader’s voice was gentle.

　　

“Understood!” Schiker answered coldly. Seeing this expression, the leader’s brows furrowed slightly.

　　

“One more thing. There’s something off about your two subordinates, Ley and Loke.”

　

“What’s wrong? I don’t need to say more about Ley’s loyalty, and as for Loke, he’s a descendant of the Eiffel family…”

　　

The muscles on Schiker’s face tensed. He cared quite a lot for these two subordinates.

　　

“There’s not a large issue with Ley. He’s long since broken through to the ninth level of the fire feathered technique, but he’s been concealing it and only revealing the strength of level eight. It’s probably on purpose,” the red-haired head commented.

“He must have a pretty high potential to reach this level at such a young age, and you can definitely consider roping him in. His intentions are too complex… Give him the tenth level of Fireplume later, I’m sure he’ll definitely be even more loyal to you after that…”

　　

“So he’s already reached level nine?” Schiker ducked his head, slightly ashamed. From his point of view, Leylin had probably hidden his strength because Schiker had yet to advance himself. He did not want to pressure his superior.　　

　　

He raised his head to look at his father, the number one genius of the Emberwings, and could not help but let his head hang down, defeated. He did not seem to have inherited even an ounce of talent from his father, and no matter how hard he worked, he still could not measure up to those geniuses. This was why he had been discouraged and left Tylasus City.

　

“I understand.” Schiker huffed out a long breath and nodded.　　

　　

The head’s next words caused Schiker’s brows to raise. “Loke, however, is a very serious problem.”

　　

“His appearance is a pretence. I’m afraid the real Loke has already died, and the one in front of you is of another race!”

　

“Another race?” Schiker cried out in alarm.　　

　　

“Yes! I can’t tell if he’s from the Triserpent Sect or Mobius Organisation, but he probably has his eyes on the Holy Solar Festival.” A sneer appeared about the leader’s lips.

　

“I’ll seize him immediately!” Schiker got up, understanding the situation. His heart was filled with fury from the betrayal.　　

　　

Never had he expected that Loke— the man who usually worked hard, was responsible, and very much to his tastes— was a spy from the enemy. The shame from not realising this hovered in his mind.　

　

The leader stopped Schiker, “There’s no hurry. They’re just a few bugs, what do they matter? What you need to do now is…”　　

……　　

　　

After leaving the residence, Leylin bade Loke farewell and found an inn to stay in.　　

　　

Though the Special Task Force members had a station in Tylasus City with many unoccupied rooms and better facilities, Leylin was obviously not going to choose to stay there. He would perhaps go there later, but for now, it was better to find a place that would not attract attention.　

　　

After sending the maid away, Leylin locked the door, and the light in the room dimmed.　　

　　

“How is it? Are things going well?” Two translucent figures emerged from the dark corners of the room. They were Gilbert and Emma.　　

　　

“Is this place safe? Make sure it’s secure!” Leylin’s brows furrowed.

　

Emma replied, “Don’t worry. We’ve long since set up a concealing spell formations and boundaries. Even the staff and guests of the inn have been \hypnotised, and we’ve also used some spiritual force pressure…”

　　

Leylin did not ask more and began to narrate the happenings of the day slowly, “Things are going well on my end. I’ve obtained part of the map of the building, and even met the leader successfully…”

　　

“So he didn’t suspect you? Tsk tsk! So that leader is a pretty boy!” Emma giggled.　　

　

“Probably not, but he did notice my faked Fireplume, something I intentional revealed,” Leylin laughed. He had long since gotten used to how these female Warlocks jumped from subject to subject so suddenly.　　

　　

“How powerful is he?” Gilbert’s focus on his power more than his appearance was only expected. They had exchanged blows with the leader before, but wanted to know Leylin’s opinion.　　

　　

“I can’t tell…” Leylin looked absent-minded, as if he was recalling the scene from the meeting. “But I can confirm that his soul strength is very powerful. It’s probably the strongest out of all the Radiant Moons I’ve seen!” 　　

　　

“He is the best of another world. He’s trained up to the thirteenth level of Fireplume, so he’s probably not any weaker than Radiant Moon Magi with level 5 meditation techniques in the Magus World. Not to mention he’s been using firasource stones and supplementing his soul…”　　

Gilbert sighed, recalling the scene when he had fought with their opponent, and his body involuntarily trembled.　　

　　

“In our operation this time, we’ll try our best not to make contact with him, and all should be fine…”

　　

Leylin’s heart sank but he continued and asked Emma, “How’s your preparation going?”　　

　　

“It’s smooth-sailing. Hehe… From now, you need to call us Viscount Flower and Earl Violet…” Emma giggled. It looked like she was doing well.

　　

Leylin was rather speechless. The Atlan Union had actually let outsiders do so well that they became earls. He had no idea how Emma had gotten through the nobility examination.　　

“Also, we’ve found traces of activity of several Jupiter’s Lightning Morning Stars in Tylasus!”　　

　　

Gilbert’s other piece of information immediately had Leylin’s attention, “Are they here to take revenge on us?” he asked as he touched his chin. After all, Collins was slain by them.

　　

Gilbert shook his head. “I’m afraid not. Their target should be the same as ours.”

　　

“Is that so? Then the difficulty of our operation should increase by a large amount. Of course, things might also become more convenient for us…” Leylin’s eyes glinted profoundly.

Chapter 565: Fire Phoenix

Leylin walked out of the inn, with the hypnotised boss and attendants left behind.

After he left, these people would forget his appearance and him having been there at all, and would not even doubt their memories. This was a spiritual force intent planted deep in their minds.

He had learnt this technique from the Spirit Circle Warlock, Paul.

He returned to the station to find Schiker waiting for him, having come in secret. After a lengthy conversation with him, Leylin was left wanting to both laugh and cry as he looked at the item on the table.

This was a little book with a fiery-red cover. Within was the information on the tenth level of the fire feathered technique!

Schiker had come over just to give him this. The tenth level of Fireplume that had been on Leylin’s mind had landed in his possession quite easily.

“I don’t know how to react…” Leylin commanded the A.I. Chip to destroy the book after recording the thing down. “But it looks like he has gotten rid of all suspicion towards me…”

On top of that, the item he had been desiring had landed in his palms. Leylin was in a pretty good mood.

[Beep! Recording of tenth level of Fireplume complete. Beginning analysis…]

The A.I. Chip’s voice sounded, and Leylin carefully looked through the contents in his memory bank.

Compared to the ninth level, the tenth touched on the Morning Star Realm, and was a path that focused on strength. Given that this had the unique characteristics of a foreign world, Leylin believed it would have very high research value.

Many ancient Magi were all-embracing, incorporating these paths from other worlds into their own systems to advance. By making use of others’ strengths to make up for their own weak points, they had been able to achieve the splendour of the ancient era. And Leylin, too, wanted to do the same!

“The tenth level of Fireplume!” Leylin’s expression gradually became solemn.

The more he watched on, the more he felt that the person who had created this technique had a talent that was off the charts. This was definitely a powerful technique that could contend against many other top-grade meditation techniques!

As the A.I. Chip’s analysis progressed, Leylin’s aura gradually changed.

Within his body, the boiling hot energy from the ninth level of Fireplume gradually purified and turned transparent, emanating a frightening might.

Large amounts of fire elemental crystals appeared, and even seemed to turn into a whirlpool.

*Skreee* A high-pitched phoenix cry sounded by Leylin’s ear. It felt as if his spiritual and soul force had made a connection with some unique existence!

At the bottom of an abyssal starry river, a giant, terrifying beast with a body that spanned several worlds suddenly opened its eyes, gazing at Leylin coldly.

“Could this be the legendary ancient fire phoenix? With this aura, it’s probably the king or even primogenitor of fire phoenixes!”

Leylin knew very well that even if what he saw was merely a phantom, such an ancient existence was mysterious and difficult to fathom. It could perhaps even use its phantom to display its strength.

The rage in the phoenix’s eyes caused Leylin to feel a biting cold.

‘Crap, it’s realised that I’ve been wearing a disguise!’ A thought flashed in Leylin’s mind, and immediately after he sensed a tremendous crimson current flooding towards him.

*Rumble!* The sound of shattering was heard in Leylin’s lower abdomen, and he immediately turned pale, spitting out a mouthful of blood. His expression, however, was that of rejoicement.

“Luckily, I’ve already condensed my point mass!” Leylin could still feel fear as he looked into his body.

His point mass, which had already turned silent, had suddenly appeared when Fireplume was writhing, ready to break through to the tenth level. That had shaken the crimson energy essence that had gathered and broken the process of the advancement to the tenth level of Fireplume, the Star rank. For this reason, Leylin had been pulled out of that dream-like fantasy, or else the consequences would be dire.

“That fire phoenix that was like a world itself… Could it be the ancient lord of phoenixes?”

Leylin recalled that terrifying giant fire phoenix. In his mind, it could only be compared with existences such as the Snake Dowager, Trial’s Eye, and a few others.

“It looks like Fireplume and the fire phoenix have a relationship, and the tenth level of Fireplume requires connecting with the fire phoenix, and even withstanding the corruptive power radiating from it. Of course, the Emberwings would call that power an additional boost”

The true body of the tremendous fire phoenix was obviously not here, but with sacrificial rites, or other techniques absorbing some sort of energy, disseminating power was a method used by many existences to traverse worlds.

If not for Leylin having already reached Morning Star and having his own path, forcefully interrupting the advancement of Fireplume might have immediately caused his death at its hands!

‘So Fireplume at the Morning Star rank is a path of sacrifice! By offering sacrifices up to the ancient fire phoenix or even changing one’s bloodline, one will ultimately become part of its family…’ Leylin touched his chin. These methods were similar to the belief in various gods, but was still different. Gods focused on quantity, while the path of sacrifice was passed on on a large scale, but then focused only on the elites. It was more like a chosen community of its own.

Leylin’s expression grew grim, as he thought of something, ‘These methods, this feeling of being suppressed…it’s very similar to the rule of the Snake Dowager…’

“A.I. Chip, begin modification of Fireplume. Moderate the force of point mass and simulate fusion of the two, eliminating the possibility of being controlled via sacrifice…”

Since he would attract attention from the fire phoenix after reaching the higher levels of Fireplume, Leylin obviously would not persist. However, he was rather interested in modifying the technique and fusing it into the Magus World system.

In the ancient era, these thoughts had been proven countless times to be workable. On top of that, the element he had the second most affinity with was the fire element, and in this area he had a natural advantage.

This led to an even more insane thought.

‘Since all this has to do with the bloodline, meditation techniques and controlling cultivation pathways, I can probably make use of this Fireplume and find ways to deal with the Snake Dowager…’

Leylin’s eyes turned darker. He was unwilling to serve beneath anyone, and while he had not gained the attention of the Snake Dowager yet, he could not tolerate the idea of being manipulated. He was already preparing for the day that will eventually come.

Whether it was attempting to break through bloodline shackles or abandoning the bloodline restraints from meditation techniques, it was all for this cause.

‘Where is the fun in having immortality at the peak yet being under the oppression of another?’ A trace of profound thought flashed in Leylin’s eyes.

[Beep! Beginning fusion simulation, mobilising 80% of task resources. Tenth level of Fireplume, meditation technique Kemoyin’s Pupil… Estimated time: 16 days, 14 hours, 34 minutes and 56 seconds…]

The A.I. Chip loyally intoned.

After Leylin had entered the Morning Star realm, its calculations and simulation techniques had been reinforced, and the time limit set was now precise to the second. This was a rare occurrence while simulating techniques in the past.

“16 days? It will be completed right before the Holy Solar Festival. That’s not bad!” Leylin touched his chin, rather satisfied with this outcome.

……

In the residence of the leader, at the deepest part underground.

Boiling heatwaves of hot lava expanded and withdrew, but were unable to advance due to an isolated maroon spell formation.

Within the maroon spell formation, there were many crowded buildings that formed a large number of private rooms.

In one of them, the leader, with his red brows and hair and young looks, was now meeting the gaze of another black figure in a mirror on the ground.

The figure in the mirror donned loose, majestic Magus robes, with a moon rune on his forehead. Those eyes were now filled with fury.

Zegna’s voice was low. “Scarlet Eye! You obviously knew that the Mobius Organisation was mine, and yet you still made a move? On top of that, there’s the fall of Collins as well. You need to take responsibility for it…”

The leader of the Atlan Union, Scarlet Eye, snorted. “When we last communicated, I reiterated many times that the Atlan Union is my territory, and I won’t let any outsiders spy on us, particularly Magi from other worlds. You seem to have forgotten that, my friend.”

Zegna, who was in the mirror, sighed lightly as if finding this a pity. He obviously knew what was taboo to the other party, but how could he have a large world right there but not do anything about it?

“But a Morning Star from our end has fallen! Do you know how much resources we would need to compensate that?” Zegna’s voice became sharp.

“Based on the intel from my subordinates, he was already seriously injured and on the verge of perishing when we found him. Those three enemies of yours had attacked him…” There was a hint of schadenfreude in Scarlet Eye’s voice.

Zegna’s voice was stilted, and he was slightly regretful.

When he had used this world and set a trap, he had been absolutely confident in taking care of the three dukes. That was why he had not minded the leaking of this world’s coordinates. However, he had grossly underestimated his opponents’ abilities, and they had used quite a few bloodline treasures to break free from their trap forcefully and descended down to this world. That had made things very troublesome for him.

If he could turn back time, he would probably not do the same thing.

“Besides… you have not kept to your word. Trading between us needs to be halted for a period of time…” Scarlet Eye tossed him a heavyweight bomb.

“No!” Zegna immediately cried out, and instantly saw the mocking smile on the other person.

He lowered his head unwillingly, but said little more. The other party did not mind losing the support of his technology, but he could not let go of the firasource stones. That was his only hope at having a glimpse into the Breaking Dawn throne!

Hence, he had no choice but to duck his head and gentle his tone. “Revered leader, I’m afraid we both have to take some responsibility, but this shouldn’t affect our friendship…”

“That’s right, my friend! As a cost of you violating the promise between us first, you will need to halve the price of the secondary element balancing spell formation you promised the last time!”

“Alright!” Zegna was practically gritting his teeth as he agreed.

When the communication was closed off, he stood up while roaring. The black throne under him continuously creaked, terrifying air waves dissipating in all directions.

“I’ll definitely kill that Scarlet Eye someday and roast his soul above my Magus Tower for ten thousand years!”

Chapter 566: Shadowing

A Morning Star Magus would not dare face the wrath of a Radiant Moon.

Outside the elegant palace, a few Morning Star Magi looked at each other and kept their distance, leaving the low-level servants hugging their heads and trembling at the side.

A reckless energy wave swept across the area near the throne, and soon there was not a single living thing in the area.

“Rage is the natural enemy of all Magi! Don’t tell me, you’re a bloodline Warlock as well?” A soothing gentle laugh sounded in the air like a clear spring, mocking at Zegna.

Shockingly, upon hearing the voice, Zegna calmed a little. Besides slightly heavy breathing, he showed no significant difference from before the contact.

“You are right! But soon or later I’m going to wipe out the bloodline of those damn Kemoyin Warlocks!”

Zegna returned to his throne, and the moon on his forehead glowed with bright light, brightening up the entire palace.

“In your current state, you might not be able to deal with Scarlet Eye even if you use a large amount of firasource stones to increase your soul force. Unless you can lure him out of the Lava World, or find a way to eliminate the resistance of the world’s will…” The woman said in a cold voice.

“You’re still pestering me to use that?” Zegna replied in the same tone.

“Yes! I am the most experienced in the tests of secondary clones. I can reduce the percentage of error such that it’s lower than one out of a million, and the best method for you to go to Lava World…”

The female voice seemed to analyse the situation in a very composed manner, sounding very charming.

“If you want to use rank 5 strength in the Lava World, this is the only way. Furthermore, you won’t be detected as an enemy by the foreign world through some cleansing of the mind of the clone.”

Zegna fell into complete silence upon hearing the last sentence. A foreign world’s will was the biggest hindrance to any Magus, and once it worked to support that world’s inhabitant, even a Radiant Moon would not dare to defy its terrifying power.

Perhaps, only those who were at the peak of the Breaking Dawn Realm would have the power to destroy the world’s will.

Zegna’s face turned solemn and gloomy all of a sudden. “Pass down my order. All Magi of Jupiter’s Thunder are to return and assist in the preparation of a pathway to the Lava World. All proposals and backups are to be effective immediately. Let’s give Scarlet Eye’s Holy Solar Festival a big gift!”

Zegna’s voice lowered gradually as his facial expression turned malevolent.

In the Lava World, Leylin had not noticed any of this. He had reached the head’s place with Loke And Schiker.

“You guys are really lucky. I was transferred to the central garrison. Since you lot were from the Special Task Force, I recommended all of you to enter the Martial Officer Department of the head.”

Schiker was wearing the uniform of an Emberwing general as he brought the rest to the Martial Officer Department.

“I am truly honoured and thankful for your recommendation!” Both Leylin and Loke showed gratitude towards Schiker.

With them being allocated here, they would hold high positions wherever they went in the future. It was also obvious that they would have the benefit of getting closer to the head.

As for Leylin and Loke, they both had unspeakable secrets, so the main reason why they got close to Schiker was to use him as a stepping stone towards the head. Since that dream of theirs had come true, they were both thrilled.

“Good! So long as you know I mean well!” Schiker patted Leylin’s shoulder. He did not wish to spare a second glance at Loke, but he still gave Loke a smile as he recalled his father’s words.

“It’s different here, completely unlike being in the Special Task Force. You have to be extra careful. Once you violate law and order, I won’t be able to help you… ”

While Schiker was giving them reminders, he walked them into a small office, “This is Bowens, and he’ll be in charge of you in the future.”

A blond-haired middle-aged man in the office got off from his seat and came up to welcome them when he saw Schiker. He seemed to be rather easy going, “Haha, Schiker! You haven’t been here in quite some time. So these are the ones? Don’t worry, I’ll take good care of them.”

But Leylin and Loke dared not ignore him. Not only would Bowens be their superior in future, his aura was somewhat similar to the Duke they had encountered previously.

This new superior of Leylin’s was also an impressive elite, a Morning Star Magus that had already reached level 10 of Fireplume.

‘This familiar aura! He was one of the elite Morning Star Magi I sensed earlier!’

The red progress bar was currently already halfway full. The A.I. Chip had already begun to smoothly merge the essence of the tenth level of Fireplume into his Morning Star point mass, which would greatly increase his power.power.

‘I’m not sure how the modified tenth level of Fireplume will be… How will it compare to these true Emberwing elites? I can’t wait to find out…’ Leylin curled his lips in a subtle movement, showing great interest.

Bowens was totally oblivious to the decision of his new subordinate, who was planning on getting rid of him after completing the new Fireplume. He instead found this Ley quite genial and amiable, instantly growing fond of him.

“There are specific duty rooms and bedrooms in the Martial Officer Department, you guys cannot stay in the Special Task Force anymore, you have to move in from now on. You do have any missions yet, I want you two to join the night patrol team and attend trainings during the daytime for now, any questions? ”

After Schiker had left, Bowens turned and looked at them, his tone was less courteous, his aura full of dignity.

“Yes, Sir!” Leylin and Loke bowed together.

Night arrived.

“Something is just not right…” Leylin straightened up his body, feeling good that everyone had their individual bedrooms despite the limited area.

“Schiker has always treated us as his trusted aides… Now that he’s going to the central garrison, why didn’t he bring us with him?”

Leylin rugged his chin, “Even though being in the Martial Officer Department means to have a very promising future, it is also considered as being his father’s bodyguards. It’s unlikely that he put both of us in here, unless… someone got exposed…”

Leylin had full confidence in himself, but Loke could not even fool him much less a rank 5 elite.

“Now it seems that they’re not as cautious about me anymore, even sending me the tenth level of Fireplume. However, I’m obviously here under observation. It seems like they don’t trust me unconditionally yet…”

“As for Loke, he’s basically bait. They’re ready to net the entire organisation behind him…”

Leylin grew more assured of his assumptions as he thought it through. Suddenly, a red light glowed from the ring on his finger.

Leylin was shocked for a second, but then he lifted a map written on pale yellow parchment from the top of the table.

A little black dot was moving slowly on the map.

“I knew you couldn’t wait, but I never expected you to be this impatient.” Leylin smiled and laid down.

A thin black string drifted swiftly out of his body and emerged from the darkness.

Hidden in the shadows, Leylin made use of his fine manipulation and the perception of the A.I. Chip, carefully avoiding numerous sentry devices and traps in the leader’s area as he followed the other party.

That person was holding onto a black pearl, which had helped him get through many detection formations and the like. It seemed to be recording something.

‘Collecting information, eh? It seems like Jupiter’s Lightning wants to get rid of the leader of Atlan too…’

Leylin smiled, discovering the other figure who had also secretly followed after Loke. He shook his head and hid himself further.

He was here in his real body, while inside the room was a mere shadow puppet. Still, with the A.I. Chip’s abilities, it was not a problem for the puppet to cover his absence for a short period of time.

‘This fellow didn’t even realise he was being followed. He only has himself to blame…’

Since Leylin already knew that this was a setup, he wanted to return to his bedroom, and hence he hid in silence.

Just when he was about to leave, a horrifying ferocious energy wave fluctuation in the air caused his body to come to a violent stop.

‘What’s this fluctuation?’

He raised his head, gazing at the sky nearby, ‘Morning Star Arcane Art? No, not that! It’s more like another path to power. It seems like magic, but it’s actually a combination of fire elemental spell formations, not an Arcane Art.’

Together with strong fluctuations, a point of scarlet fire lit up the sky. The heavens rumbled as if they contained muffled thunder.

A rain of lava dripped down, spreading over a vast range and almost covering up the entirety of the head’s residence.

‘He dares to attack this place directly?’ Leylin felt at a loss for words, unsure as to how he should praise that person’s bravery.

The ghastly lava rain had wrapped up the entire place, every single drop containing a power of over a thousand degrees. If they were allowed to hit the ground, all the officers except the head and a few elite Star ranks would die, and the whole place would be razed to the ground. The leader would turn into a huge laughingstock.

“Stop!” “How dare you!!”

A few ferocious and reckless voices sounded around the whole place, and dazzling energy light pillars shot up forming into a light shield that covered the whole place within.

“Kekeke! How many can you save?” A quirky voice sounded in the midst of sky, followed by a huge amount of lava rain, it extended fiercely, covering the entire city of Tylasus.

A drop of the lava rain could kill all the normal citizens easily. Were this to happen before the Holy Solar Festival, the head of the union would land in deep trouble.

Thus, Leylin judged that that person would surely take action.

“Screeee!”

Just then, a ferocious bird, huge scarlet body complemented with a stunning tail that was covered by flames flew out of the residence, the high-pitched whistle of a phoenix sounding out…

Chapter 567: Gaia’s Disc

*Skree!* The gigantic bird of fire dashed out of the building. It opened up its wings in a flash of light, and glorious flames shot out from its body as it enlarged in the blink of an eye. Its humongous wings closed, wrapping up the entire city of Tylasus.

The drops of lava with over a thousand degrees of power fell onto its wings, being absorbed by the flames.

When the lava storm passed, the city had emerged unscathed.

A bright light flashed across Leylin’s eyes as he looked at the scene, ‘Such a transformation is very similar to that of an ancient Warlock. It looks like the body of this Emberwing Morning Star has the bloodline of the fire phoenix.’

Warlocks were always fond of high-level bloodlines. As for the fire phoenix, Leylin had already seen its incredible power when he’d been trapped in the illusion previously. It was likely at least as strong as the Snake Dowager.

This bloodline posed an irresistible attraction to Warlocks even if it was diluted through sacrifices and projections.

‘Before we launch our plan, I should try to get some of the bloodline of a Morning Star Emberwing. It would be even better if I manage to get it from their leader, Scarlet Eye.’

Just as Leylin’s eyes brightened, the phoenix soared down from the clouds in the sky, revealing several gigantic, hundred meter long silhouettes made of flames.

The fire elementals were the most powerful living beings in the Lava World, and the most populous. They did not have blood or flesh, and instead had bodies covered in fuming flames and rocks. Their eyes were like deathly white flames that arose from the very soul.

“Divineflame Empire! It seems like you lot didn’t learn your lesson at Death Grand Canyon!” Scarlet Eye’s voice boomed across the sky, and the humongous wings wrapped up the giant fire elementals, flinging them away.

Its body rumbled as explosions erupted all over it, but it did not seem bothered at all.

By the time the phoenix vanished, half the flames in the sky had subsided. Leylin widened his eyes.

‘They even have such a method? Are there still people undercover in the leader’s residence? And does that mean this was a ploy to lure the tiger out of its den?’

Hidden in front of him was Loke. He sighed in relief and pulled out a circular disk as he saw the phoenix leave.

On the surface of this disk were weird runes with countless interconnected crimson lines that formed a vertical pupil.

‘Haven’t I seen something like this before?’ Puzzlement crossed his eyes as he immediately checked with the A.I. Chip’s database. The answer showed up within a second. ‘A copy of Gaia’s Disc? Such a technique actually exists…’

Loke stopped at an empty ground in the building. He placed the replica on the ground as he showed a tinge of excitement.

*Ssshh!* The very moment the disc touched the ground, a large amount of sand split apart like it was a stream, revealing a pitch dark tunnel that led underground.

“Here it is! Now I’m at the weakest part of the entire building. Together with the power of Gaia’s Disc…” Loke’s eyes grew impassioned. He had endured a lot of humiliation during this mission, and now he could finally succeed in his task!

‘That was good cooperation, but I’m afraid it won’t be of help.’ Leylin saw the agitated Loke enter the underground tunnel, soon to be followed by a gloomy Bowens. This was the superior they had just met that day.

It seemed like Loke’s luck was at an end.

However, Leylin had one more doubt, ‘Since they wanted to coordinate between the inside and outside, why don’t they just send a Morning Star Magus in, isn’t that much simpler? They already sent so many just to attract attention, one more wouldn’t be too hard…’

He did not think much of it since that was a question that wouldn’t see an answer soon. Instead, he followed the two and entered just as the tunnel closed up…

*Boom!* Schiker entered Leylin’s room.

“Instructor!” ‘Leylin’ got up from the bed, bowing even with blurry sight.

Schiker first looked around with a cautious gaze, and he looked relieved that Leylin was still around. Soon, he reprimanded the boy, “You’re still asleep under such circumstances?”

“Master Bowens and so many of his colleagues are around right now. If they can’t solve the problem, what can I do? I might as well just continue sleeping…”

‘Leylin’ threw his hands up, seemingly helpless. With the support of the A.I. Chip, every action of this puppet was a perfect copy of Leylin’s behaviour, even its character was flawless. Forget Schiker, even Gilbert was unlikely to be able to notice the difference.

“You…” Schiker was dumbfounded, but the waves in his heart secretly calmed down…

Inside the underground tunnel, Leylin followed closely after Bowens. He had weakened his breath to the maximum, and not a single energy wave fluctuation broke out. Additionally, Bowens seemed to have put his full focus on Loke, and he did not realise he was being shadowed.

“Gaia’s Disc was used by the Hero Moncordol of the Emberwings’ legend to lift open the stratum, it is also the powerful weapon which slew the demon king Falsace; this can easily crack open a huge underground tunnel even if it’s just a replica.”

Loke’s voice trembled in agitation, “The organisation possessed such a precious weapon that let me avoid triggering numerous traps. Truly, this is…”

As he reached the bottom, blood vessels popped out from under Loke’s skin, his aura growing berserk.

“The final layer of defence!” Loke was frantic in excitement as he saw a crimson defensive membrane.

He suddenly attacked, and a huge amount of fire exploded forth from his hands, rushing into the spell formation.

Crackling sounds rang out as the spell formation shook. A terrifying wave of energy was returned in counter, and surged through Loke’s body. His skin peeled off, revealing the flames burning within.

Loke’s body had been completely shredded by the formation’s counterattack, revealing a two-meter tall fire elemental, composed of flames and rocks.

The flame surged in all directions, and Loke’s aura rose to the pinnacle of the Sky rank, the equivalent of a peak rank 3 in the Magus World.

‘Hmmm? Loke is a fire elemental?’

Leylin was rather surprised. He had always thought that Loke was an undercover agent of the Mobius Organisation, Jupiter’s Lightning’s operations here, but now it seemed like he did not know the length of it. Jupiter’s Lightning had also approached the Divineflame Empire, and had signed some terms of agreement with each other.

After recovering his original appearance, Loke marched up to the scarlet spell formation.

A dot of a golden flame shot out of his body, burning a round opening in the spell formation’s light shield.

Loke turned into a ball of flames, entering from that tiny opening in the spell formation and soon returning to his normal form.

“Hahahaha… All of Scarlet Eye’s treasures and secrets are mine for the taking!” As Loke laughed, he explored the chamber. His flaming legs left a black burn mark with every step he took.

He seemed rather familiar with this area, running straight towards the chamber in the centre.

The gigantic chamber was spacious, with nothing around except a large spell formation. Strings of runes interlocked with the energy circuit. It was so refined that a Magus would go dizzy simply by staring at it for a length of time.

In the middle of the formation was a weak red light, it’s energy as it flickered causing Leylin’s heart to palpitate.

‘This aura is so familiar… Yes, the firasource stones! Wait… it’s a living creature?’ The A.I. Chip had made a judgement that threw Leylin into confusion.

“Found it!” Loke celebrated in his excitement. He took out a big black key, walking towards the spell formation.

Just then, a membrane of light blocked his path of return, the surging wave of energy sweeping him onto the ground in an instant.

The gigantic fire elemental fell flat to the ground with a thud, causing the chamber to shake a little.

“What happened? Doesn’t this place just have a single defensive layer?” Loke touched his head, puzzled.

“Obviously it is used to guard against people like you.” Bowens sneered, exiting stealth and walking out from the dark.

“B–Master Bowens?” Loke was totally taken aback.

“Hmm! The leader knew long ago that there was something wrong with you. It seems you hid quite a lot from us.”

The fuming lava hand dropped onto the ground, and the black key was snatched from his hands.

“You are a very important captive. The leader and Schiker will take great interest in you.” Bowens spoke coldly as the flame on his hands turned into ropes which tied Loke up.

Loke could not fight back against the power of a Star rank. Rather, he was so flabbergasted that he did not even struggle or otherwise resist.

While both of them were unaware of their surroundings, Leylin snuck close to the membrane of light. The A.I. Chip scanned the formation, revealing the entry condition, [Aura of level 10 Fireplume required for access.]

Watching Loke being taken away by Bowens, Leylin followed them out of the basement. He recalled the shadow puppet after returning to his bedroom.

He had lots of questions, ‘What was that red orb in the middle of the spell formation? Bowens settled Loke so quickly, and obviously he wasn’t used as bait. Was it merely for Gaia’s Disc and that black bronze key?’

Chapter 568: Holy Solar Day

“Gilbert, Emma; the tides have turned. The Mobius Organisation might be colluding with the Divineflame Empire. Be very careful!”

Unable to come up with anything even after a long time, Leylin specially informed Gilbert and Emma about the situation. He then returned immediately to the leader’s residence. His actions were not in the least bit unusual.

Yesterday, Scarlet Eye had returned to the mansion right after Leylin followed Bowens out, making Leylin secretly heave a sigh of relief.

If he had chosen to take action then, it was likely that even after he tackled Bowens, he would have bumped into Scarlet Eye who was rushing back. That would have spelt trouble.

Furthermore, he didn’t want to make a move before understanding the situation.

“Officer Schiker! Where’s Loke? Why haven’t I seen him around recently?” Leylin questioned ‘curiously’. Upon the mention of this name, Schiker’s facial muscles twitched, and he was silent for a long while before he spoke. “He has been assigned to a top-secret mission, and will be away for some time!”

“I see!” Leylin seemed to have gained some understanding. He moved closer to Schiker and asked, “Instructor, about that night… what happened in the end?”

“What else? The leader emerged victorious of course! He struck two of the masters from the other party who were at the Star rank. He took one of them prisoner, and the foreign affairs department will negotiate with the Divineflame Empire!” A look of admiration flashed across Schiker’s eyes, but Leylin’s heart sank.

‘They paid such a high price, yet ended up with nothing. Those people from the Divineflame Empire definitely will not take things lying down. Furthermore, the trap they set previously that caused the loss of the combat abilities of the Morning Stars was not very wise. What is the truth behind all of this?’

Combining that line of thought with the intelligence given by Emma and Gilbert in the past two days, Leylin suddenly felt as though the future was shrouded in a dense fog.

‘I’m afraid I’ll have to modify my previous plan. This Holy Solar Day will not pass in peace. Divineflame Empire, Jupiter’s Thunder, and even the Ouroboros Clan will take action. When that time comes, this place will be plunged into chaos…

‘Well, at least there’s this to look forward to!’ Leylin saw that the progress bar on the A.I. Chip was quickly filling up, and couldn’t help but smile.

The tenth level of Fireplume was the gateway to the Star rank. Leylin’s energy had already been condensed to form a point mass, and if these two systems could be fused successfully the formidable power produced would definitely not just be additive. There would be a horrifying qualitative change in him, amplifying his powers to a great extent.

Additionally, Leylin had long since used up all the firasource stones he had earned from Collins, something that caused his soul force to improve by leaps and bounds. His strength after all this would surely give many enemies a surprise.

His eyes glowed crimson as the corners of his lips rose to form a wicked smile.

The bloodline of the apex predator, the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, was pressing him to slaughter! He wanted to destroy everything, to bring it all to flaming ruin!

The emotional instability that was common to bloodline Warlocks had begun to act up. After he advanced to the Morning Star realm, the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s soul had fused with Leylin’s own, causing him to inherit these violent moods. These were no longer an external thing, but instead part of his own nature.

Once such an illness acted up, it would have a far-reaching effect on the Warlock’s personality.

Previously, Leylin had always made a conscious effort to restrain himself, preventing his feelings from eroding his character away. Now that war was upon them, he was facing unprecedented pressure, and some strange emotions managed to worm their way out…

No matter what others thought, time was still ticking by. Finally, the day of the Emberwings’ festival— the Holy Solar Day— had arrived.

During his recent trips, Leylin saw the streets and markets starting to bustle with activity. Many teenage Emberwings now went against the taboo, playing on the road. The atmosphere was filled with clamour.

The various district representatives from the Atlan Union and the other tourists who came on their own accord arrived at Tylasus City one by one. The place was packed to the brim, even overcrowded, resulting in multiple cases of breaches in public security. Even Leylin, a martial officer from the Military Office, had to step in at times, something more than evident of how thin the security had been stretched.

According to the information given by Gilbert and Emma in private, many of the elites from the Mobius organisation and Triserpent Sect had also snuck into Tylasus City. They were the ones who stirred up trouble here, making the place chaotic.

Additionally, the arch-enemy of the Atlan Union, the Divineflame Empire, had also sent a large team of ambassadors, causing more trouble.

“It just seems like things will get relatively more troublesome!” Leylin lamented. He donned the dashing uniform of a military official, and stood tall and straight. He and his colleagues lined along both sides, while Scarlet Eye stood in front of a huge fitting room mirror, adjusting the butterfly-shaped necktie on his collar.

“Your Highness! Your schedule for today is as follows: first up will be the parliament lecture, followed by welcoming the envoy from the Divineflame Empire. The banquet in the afternoon…” Standing next to Scarlet Eye were a few secretaries with pen and paper in hand, chattering away. There were also a few maids who were tidying up the creases on the coattails of his dinner suit.

Schiker, Bowens and the others were also dressed neatly and stood at the side. Outside the window, lots of fireworks and gun salutes could be seen. Colourful confetti filled the sky, and the place was filled with a festive atmosphere.

“Alright! I have my own plans for today’s matters!” Scarlet Eye furrowed his brows and waved his hand, sending away the secretaries who were still chattering endlessly.

“Schiker, you shall accompany me today.” These words seemed to move the leader’s son to tears.

Seeing his odd mix of being both moved and apprehensive, Leylin felt at a loss for words.

‘The private life of this state leader is quite confusing. His previous marriage did not produce a heir, and now that he only has Schiker, his illegitimate child, does he hope for him to inherit his political legacy and even become the next leader of the union?’

If the other officials knew that Leylin was silently cursing their almighty leader, they might have come together to tear him apart, and the outcome wouldn’t be pleasant.

“Let’s go!” After quite some time, Scarlet Eye finished his preparations and took the lead as he mounted a chariot that was drawn by numerous scarlet birds. Schiker followed closely behind.

Bowens walked behind everyone. He suddenly glanced at Leylin and commanded, “Ley, you come too!”

“But… The duty of a humble servant is to stay behind and guard the residence!” Leylin appeared to be hesitating, but he was secretly cursing in his heart.

His duty for today was to stand guard at the residence. This was perfectly normal as he lacked the proper qualifications, and thus could not show his face at the parliament. However, this was what he wanted. After all, the places that Scarlet Eye would go to today would not be tranquil, and there would not be any advantages from following him out. How would that be more enjoyable than being able to hide in the residence and unearth treasures the minute he discovered that something was off?

What did he stand to gain from going out with Scarlet Eye anyway? That one casual sentence from Bowens disrupted his plans for the day.

Leylin felt a little gloomy as he looked at Bowens. Maybe Bowens sensed that something was amiss, or maybe he just found Leylin an eyesore, but he had been causing a lot of trouble for Leylin on the sly.

“ .. Yes, Sir!” To the others, it seemed that Leylin only hesitated for a while before agreeing immediately in a loud voice, ecstasy spreading across his face. This made many of the officials who were staying behind envy him, yet they did not know that Leylin was secretly rolling his eyes.

Bowens was his superior after all, and Leylin could not do much even if he disagreed.

Leylin stood at the back of the fleet and reflected, ‘Might as well! When the moment comes, I’ll join Gilbert and Emma directly. Once something is amiss, we will immediately activate the coordinates and return. I don’t believe that Scarlet Eye will give chase and follow us back to the Magus World.’

Gilbert and Emma had first found their way into the ranks of feudal nobility through a small noble family by disguise and strength. They then wantonly betrayed the secrets of the Triserpent Sect against their interests, and attained the positions of Earl and Viscount, allowing them to attend today’s celebration.

If the three Giant Kemoyin Warlocks were together, even Scarlet Eye would find it hard to capture them successfully, so there was at least some form of assurance in terms of safety.

‘Bowens, however, has to be killed! He better not run into me today, or else…’ Leylin lowered his head slightly, hiding the brutal crimson radiance in his pupils.

Leylin kept Scarlet Eye company at the parliament while listening to an illogical and boring speech. Afterwards, he tagged along with the leader of the state and the other major ministers as they proceeded to the plaza where people pledged oaths and celebrated their victories. They were preparing to welcome the emissary from the Divineflame Empire.

Positioned behind Scarlet Eye were the delegates from several major districts, as well as a large number of high-ranking officials and influential ministers.

*Boom! Boom!*

it was as though there was an earthquake. Fire flashed in the distance, and Leylin noticed the arrival of copious amounts of fire elementals.

These fire elementals existed in various sizes, and some were not even humanoid. There were quite a number of beasts, bodies constituted of flames and lava, burning at temperatures that could scorch anything.

Although they moved as a delegation, they left two long burn tracks on the ground. The temperature of the entire plaza started to rise steadily.

It was fortunate that most of the Emberwings practised Fireplume. The high-ranking officials and nobility present in the plaza had all mastered at least three levels of the technique, and thus didn’t find it hard to bear.

Creatures that were able to survive in the Lava World had a powerful resistance towards high temperatures.

The officials who were specially put in charge of diplomacy appeared, and engaged in a series of complicated rites and etiquette, something so boring that Leylin yawned multiple times in succession.

Regardless of as a scientist in his previous life or a Magus now, he did not have an ounce of interest in such rituals.

In contrast, he was more willing to perform a few more experiments in his laboratory, or expound upon a few hypotheses, or even meditate!

This was a common understanding between an overwhelming majority of Magi in the Magus World.

In the Lava World, the circumstances were evidently different. As compared to Magi who were much like researchers, the Emberwings who studied Fireplume were more similar to knights. They had a great thirst for the secular benefits of various territories.

The Magi of the Magus World often withdrew to the second line of duty, and manipulated the countries from behind the scenes. Those who held authority in the Lava World, however, were different. They liked to handle things personally, and preferred to take control of the entire system in the foreground.

Chapter 569: The Opening

Leylin obviously did not think that everything done in the Magus World was right, but he did not approve of the methods in Lava World because they were too time-consuming.

Of course, that might have to do with him being a Magus, since he consciously wanted to protect his own interests.

“Greetings to the Atlan Union Leader. I am Saka, the envoy of the Divineflame Empire!”

Walking ahead of the diplomatic mission was a flaming giant who was over ten metres tall, looking like a fire demon from myths. Him bowing down to a tiny Emberwing seemed rather laughable, but nobody would actually dare to do so.

Scarlet Eye merely stood there like an eternal mountain, a sky which people could only look up to.

“Also… Our empire seriously condemns the leader, Scarlet Eye, for killing one of our personnel without reason.” Saka’s next words caused the atmosphere to turn chilly.

“Condemn?” Scarlet Eye chuckled lightly. “Anything else?”

“The leader has to take responsibility for this matter, apologise and resign! If not, the Holy Solar Festival that is a celebration for the Emberwings will mark the beginning of a war between us!”

“What?” There was a clamour amongst the audience, and even Leylin’s pupils shrunk. Never had he imagined that the Divineflame Empire’s purpose in coming here was to declare war!

Scarlet Eye’s personality was quite open. Was it possible to get him to apologise and resign?

When those words exited the envoy’s mouth, Leylin felt a chill down his spine, as if a vicious ancient beast was staring him down. This was the imposing aura that the strong unwittingly gave off, filled with a sense of danger.

“Is that so?” Scarlet Eye narrowed his eyes, and the fire elemental giant opposite him took quite a few steps back. The terrifying energy emitting from his body reached the Morning Star realm.

This member of the diplomatic mission was actually a Star rank, and that was not all. A few of the other fire elementals behind him had an abrupt change in their physiques, their bodies emanating powerful energy undulations.

“With just a few Star ranks? That’s hardly enough!” Scarlet Eye’s half-closed eyes opened slightly, as if he was stating a fact.

However, all the Emberwings knew that their leader was already at the brink of fury.

“How could we inconvenience the leader to make a move against them? Uncle Bowens!” Schiker was so frustrated that he had flushed red, suddenly standing up.

“The Military Office does not permit anyone humiliating our leader!” Bowens stood up, crimson energy covering his entire body. With a wave of his hand, military officials charged out and surrounded the diplomatic mission.

Seeing Bowens taking the initiative, Scarlet Eye’s brows lifted. “Bowens, you should first…”

At this moment, he suddenly turned his gaze north-west. *Rumble!* An immense blast sounded from that area.

The earth swished along like a metal plank that floated on water, drifting up and down. Giant waves rippled, and a large number of cracks appeared, spewing crimson lava and scorching flames.

It was as if there was a large flame demon underground. The cracks that formed were like a spiderweb that extended in the direction of Tylasus City.

The moment these cracks closed in, the tremendous mountain that the city stood on would completely sink, and the city itself would not be spared.

“Haha… Scarlet Eye, do you feel touched that this emperor came to congratulate you personally?” The earth split open, and a large arm that could cover the sky emerged from within, filled with flames and red lava.

Scarlet Eye’s expression was the most stern it had ever been. “Archibald…”

Accompanying the large hand was the frightening suppression of power at rank 5, causing the many Emberwings to feel suffocated.

‘A rank 5! Could this be the Divineflame Empire’s emperor?’

Leylin took a few steps backwards, making use of the shadows from a few buildings to hide. Amidst the terror caused by rank 5 might, his little actions remained undiscovered.

Scarlet Eye’s expression was somewhat dark. He knew that if the other party’s attack was successful, the entirety of Tylasus City would suffer great losses, and many high-ranked officials and nobles would die. Hence, he had no choice but to make a move!

A high-pitched cry appeared as a phoenix abruptly appeared in the sky, brilliant flames surrounding its body as its scarlet wings collided with the arm.

*Boom!* The earth and sky seemed to disappear in that instant, and everyone fell into a daze. When their eyes could finally see again, they saw the giant fire phoenix that Scarlet Eye had turned into circling a flame giant that seemed able to support the skies. The two battled further into the distance, but the residual energy undulations still inspired fear.

“Go!” Bowens’ expression was grim as he cried out. Flames with energy at the Star rank blazed on his body.

*Swish!* The military officials seemed to act on a conditioned reflex as they headed straight for the diplomatic mission from the Divineflame Empire, with some soldiers and nobles following behind.

Among the Emberwings of the Atlan Union, true nobles trained up to at least the eighth level of Fireplume, the Sky rank. None of them was weak. There were even a few Star rank experts keeping watch, but not revealing their strength.

However, the diplomatic mission of the Divineflame Empire was not a pushover either. There were a few fire elementals who had already broken through the Star rank, and in that instant the two sides had reached a deadlock. Flames and lava flew everywhere, destroying the square where pledges of peace and victory were to be made beyond recognition.

Leylin hid under a gigantic sculpture of the founder of the country. The people nearby had yet to realise there was a military official breaking away from the formation and escaping.

At this moment, the sound of Gilbert’s questioning voice sounded in his ear, “What should we do?”

Leylin transmitted back calmly, “Watch the changes in the situation, but don’t make a move. Only the fire elementals of the Divineflame Empire have appeared, but there isn’t news of the Mobius Organisation which Jupiter’s Lightning controls.”

He had a feeling that this situation probably had more to it than met the eye. Scarlet Eye was not someone so shallow, and wouldn’t have made no preparations. Hence, there could very well be a dramatic change in this situation later on.

In this spectacle, three Morning Star Warlocks like them were not considered top strengths, and definitely needed to conceal themselves and wait for a chance to go in for the kill.

‘Besides…’ Leylin looked at the screen that showed the A.I. Chip’s status.

The bar that signified the progress of fusing Fireplume’s concepts with his point mass had reached 99.9%. Only a tiny bit was left.

A large amount of energy from Fireplume condensed within his body, but this time it was being contaminated by great amounts of darkness elemental energy particles. The energy turned darker than its original scarlet red, now tending towards black.

His point mass, as well as the nebula surrounding it had appeared as well, beginning to take in large amounts of the dark red energy from the modified Fireplume, constantly condensing and assimilating it.

With the point mass’ purification, the energy of Emberwing had become richer. At the same time, its colour grew increasingly darker, giving it a sinister feeling.

“Ley, what are you doing?” All of a sudden, a stern yell and a piercing gaze swept towards Leylin’s location.

Bowens’ gaze now could practically kill Leylin, “What are you doing? Trying to desert the army?”

‘Damn it, why did he set his sights on me?’ Leylin walked out, speechless. Seeing the quick changes in Schiker’s eyes, he knew he could not explain this half-heartedly, or he would be attacked.

“Bowens is getting increasingly annoying!” Leylin took in a deep breath, Fireplume at the peak of the ninth level exploding from his body, like a dazzling meteor streaking through the skies.

“Our people have already acted according to plan. All that’s left depends on you!”

A distance away from the square, in a residential building. The original owner had long since disappeared. The walls were filled with red runes, revealing a maroon luster. Some of the blood had yet to dry, and droplets of it were still dripping down, causing long blood-red lines to form on them.

Within this building, a few people dressed in black robes were watching the scene in the square from afar through the window.

The fire elemental delegation acted immediately and began to fight many military officials and nobles. Such an act caused chaos among the spectating commoners.

The attacks from the fire elementals were ruthless. If lava brushed across a commoner’s body, it would reduce them to ashes in an instant. On top of that, the military officials and the nobles of the union didn’t really bother themselves with protecting them. As a result, a huge number of the people watching died, resulting in great casualties. The mix of piercing screams and feeble cries for help were filled with the taste of horror.

Many commoners of the union were wailing, pushing everyone else as they tried to leave the blazing hell that was the square. This resulted in the chaos intensifying, leading to more innocent deaths.

“Hehe… Resent us! Cry out! These souls filled with hatred and fresh blood are the best nourishment for our spell formation…” An aged voice sounded from within the mantle of a black robe.

“Don’t worry, my friend. Us of the Mobius Organisation always trade fairly!” The old man’s voice was as piercing as an owl’s screech, and would cause goosebumps on anyone who listened to him. Yet, the fire elemental opposite him did not seem to mind.

“The chaos we’re creating can only last for a while longer. You’ll need to make a move quickly!”

“Alright, alright!” the old man cackled, touching a dark green metal bracelet, “How’s the set-up on your end?”

White noise sounded from the bracelet, followed by the voice of a middle-aged man, “Enough flesh and blood have been gathered. It’s just difficult to obtain vengeful spirits full of resentment. Only 80% of the charging process has been completed.”

“That’s enough!” The old man laughed coldly. “On my command, begin!”

Chapter 575: Breakthrough in Fusion

Flames flashed, and Scarlet Eye’s figure appeared once more. Now, however, his face was filled with fury and his aura was unstable.

He glared at the storm of fire that had burst forth and immediately turned back, his palms opening up a spatial passageway like drawing apart a curtain. He immediately re-entered the Lava World.

*Rumble!* Tens of seconds later, black lightning and a large rock smashed into the firestorm, revealing the miserable figures of Zegna and Archibald.

*Woosh!* Cracks spread across the rock like spiderwebs, and large fragments began to fall off.

At the end of it all, Archibald’s body was much smaller than before, and could even be called ‘pocket-sized.’

Zegna was in an even more pitiful state. Not only were their traces of burn wounds all over his body, even a great portion of his hair had been burned off.

“Haha! After this, the injuries on Scarlet Eye’s body will probably take at least a hundred years to recover!” Archibald was unusually carefree as he burst into laughter.

He then glanced at Zegna, “So? Should we chase after him?”

“Forgive me, Your Highness! This body of mine probably won’t be able to take the intensity of the next battle!” Zegna laughed wryly.

“Then forget it. The losses the Atlan Union suffered this time should be enough to give them a headache for a long while.”

Archibald laughed, “My Divineflame Empire should have been the victor in the power struggles, but with Scarlet Eye being an Emberwing, we can’t let our guards down…”

“I believe that with your guidance, the fire elementals will remain the leaders of the Lava World!” Zegna had a smile on his face.

Reputation and nice words meant nothing to him. As long as there were enough benefits, calling the other party the leader of the Lava World was not an issue.

“Haha…” Even so, that was enough for Archibald to laugh heartily.

“Alright, based on our previous agreement…” Zegna wanted to continue on, but his expression immediately changed. “Damn it! Bowens and the rest are such trash!” he cursed, turning into a streak of black lightning and disappearing in that instant.

“Hehe… interesting!” Large flames appeared under Archibald’s feet, lifting and moving him forward as he followed.

Though he had joined hands with Zegna, he had never let down his guard against this guest from another world.

……

Underground, next to the giant spell formation. Leylin had met with a crisis as well.

The barrier that Scarlet Eye had set up had actually been a trap. The moment it made contact with an external force, it had immediately shown the image of the Emberwing himself, and unleashed an attack.

This was the terrifying attack of a Radiant Moon! It could seriously injure if not kill even the current Leylin.

‘Schiker’s bloodline can’t be fake, and my Fireplume shouldn’t be a problem either. Is it Bowens?’ Leylin quickly shot Bowens a glance, but found him equally panicked, evidently not expecting this situation.

“Despicable thieves, die!” Scarlet Eye’s figure roared, hair and eyebrows seemingly beginning to burn up. Tremendous, fierce flames formed a blazing phoenix that charged towards Leylin’s groups.

As if this phantom had a will of its own, its first target was the traitor, Bowens.

“AAAH!” In the face of the suppression from a rank 5, Bowens’ Fireplume energy was destroyed quickly despite his desperate attempts at saving himself. He cried out miserably as he burst into flames. In one move, Bowens of Jupiter’s Lightning had died at the phantom’s hands.

After taking care of the traitor, the phantom looked straight at Leylin and the other two. Leylin seemed to have become the primary target.

Goosebumps appeared on Leylin’s body.

‘Is there no other way but to undergo Kemoyin Serpent Transformation with the other two? If we do that, the entirety of this underground room will be destroyed!’ In a short period, a variety of thoughts passed in Leylin’s mind, and he gave up on this plan.

“I can only use Fireplume to fight it out.’ A glint appeared in Leylin’s eyes as he made up his mind.

[Beep! Simulation of Fireplume at 100%. Mission complete.]

The A.I. Chip’s prompt sounded out.

The A.I. Chip’s progress in fusing Fireplume’s energy with his point mass had already reached 99.9% completion before. Scanning Bowens’ version of Fireplume was enough for it to take that last step.

“Oh!” Leylin’s expression changed, Fireplume energy turning black as it was absorbed by his point mass.

His point mass buzzed as it shook vigorously, rotating at a high speed. Powerful energy undulations were emitted from it.

The nebula surrounding the point mass had increased in area by half a fold before it slowed down and stopped.

The tenth level of Fireplume had been modified to fuse with his point mass. This result was not just an addition of one plus one. Furthermore, this was a perfect fusion, not the bastardised version that Bowens had created. The amplification of power was even greater than Leylin had expected.

[Beep! Fireplume modification complete, point mass is being upgraded. Host body…]

The A.I. Chip’s voice was intermittent, but Leylin had no plans of listening carefully.

He felt power overflowing in his body, and facing the incoming rank 5 attack he made his move without hesitation.

After the modification, the energy of Fireplume was driven by the force of a Morning Star’s point mass. The resulting power was terrifying.

*Crackle!* Devilish black flames appeared around Leylin, forming a phoenix wreathed in black fire.

The phoenix cried out, and this screech brought with an aura of devilish power.

“Modified obscure tenth level of Fireplume— Soaring Demonic Phoenix!” Leylin spread his arms like a soaring phoenix, slashing towards the phantom Scarlet Eye with grace.

*Chirp!* Melodic phoenix cries were heard, and the blackfire phoenix streaked across the horizon to welcome the phantom.

Confronting this blackfire phoenix, Scarlet Eye’s face was tinted with confusion, even fear. The earth rumbled as black and gold flames intertwined, creating a shockwave that spread throughout the area.

Following that, the black flames actually began to devour the other side, becoming even more exuberant as time passed. Soon enough, it had exterminated the other party’s phoenix and even drowned out Scarlet Eye’s figure.

‘This modified Fireplume is this good at absorbing other Fireplume energy as fuel and fusing with it?’ Seeing Scarlet Eye’s phantom struggling amidst the black flames and gradually disappearing, even Leylin himself was shocked, and he was the creator!

He felt that with the A.I. Chip balancing and fusing the essence of Fireplume into his point mass, the power of this already formidable technique had been furthered and reached a horrifying degree of power.

It was a pity that the A.I. Chip was unique to him, and only he could train in this Dark Fireplume version.

“What… What just happened?” Gilbert and Emma were dazed. What had they just seen? Leylin had wiped out the phantom of a rank 5 Magus in just one move?

That was a full-out attack from a rank 5! In that moment, Gilbert and Emma felt as if they were dreaming.

It took a while before Gilbert spoke. “Ley–Leylin, did you break through to rank 5?”

“No, I just made some progress in Fireplume…” Leylin answered truthfully. Though the fusion of Fireplume energy with his point mass had immense benefits, it had not allowed him to cross over into the Radiant Moon realm. If this had been an attack by a phantom of Zegna instead, it wouldn’t have been nearly as easy.

His easy dispatchment of the Scarlet Eye phantom was most likely to do with the modified Fireplume.

“I have a intensified feeling,” Leylin raised his arms and watched the demonic black flames, “that these mutated black flames are the bane of all traditional Fireplume energy.”

“Whatever it is, we need to leave after getting the firasource stones! It’s a pity we lost Bowens.” Gilbert watched the flames piteously. A bright point mass was received by starlight and floated into the astral plane.

Not caring about Bowens, Leylin pointed his hands at the flame shield. “Open!” The membrane began to be burned down by black demonic flames.

No, it was not burning. It was being corroded! The top-grade flames from Scarlet Eye’s Fireplume were corroded by the modified flames from Dark Fireplume, gradually revealing a giant hole.

“Let’s go.” Leylin and the other two arrived before a complicated spell formation.

Emma touched the runes on the ground, looking solemn. “Spatial binding runes. Dormant sacrificial runes and life absorption runes as well! This spell formation is probably used to extract the life force of some being.”

“Could that lifeform be at the centre…” Leylin immediately focused his gaze on the red light at the heart of the spell formation. It was weak, flickering like a candle in the wind. And yet, it somehow survived with all tenacity.

‘The energy undulations are similar to those of firasource stones! I can somewhat guess what it is!’ Recalling the sorrow he had felt before, Leylin sighed and produced the black copper key he had obtained from Bowens.

The large black copper key rose into the air and projected a large number of complex data and light rays.

The spell formation on the ground began to activate, and the sound of a key clicking was heard continuously.

At the same time, the runes on the ground were unsealed one by one, revealing a giant cage.

*Rumble!* Scalding red light filled the entire room, and the cage in the middle opened up to reveal a scarlet egg.

Chapter 577: Terrifying Battle

The Northern Duke had never expected that the kid Ley, who he had once met and had a good impression of, was actually of another race!

Furthermore, the Dark Fireplume that Leylin used gave him a sense of fear. Perhaps if not for his dignity and resolution as a soldier and someone with power, he might have fled.

This was especially true since he did not seem to be losing against his most revered leader. Instead… he was winning?

“Great Mother Phoenix! Could I be dreaming? Please help me wake up as soon as possible.” While the Northern Duke’s will was strong, even he was beginning to find this situation absurd.

“Phoenix egg!” At this moment, two other powerful auras descended. Zegna observed the giant red egg at the middle of the battlefield, unable to conceal his desire.

Archibald could not stand it either. This was the peak of all fire elemental beings!

“It’s mine! The phoenix can only exist in our Divineflame Empire for all eternity!” he roared in rage, and the earth began to shake. He charged forward, large hands grabbing towards the large scarlet egg.

*Swish!* Zegna was even faster than him as he turned into a streak of black lightning, heading right for it.

“So this is the source of the firasource stones. This phoenix egg must be mine! With it, I’ll be able to advance to rank 6…”

“Go away!” A black wall of flames obstructed Zegna’s path, the boiling temperature causing him to subconsciously slow his steps.

“Warlock Leylin! A mere Morning Star dares stop me? Aren’t you afraid I’ll eliminate your Ouroboros Clan? Give me the phoenix egg right now, and I guarantee your Ouroboros Clan shall be greatly rewarded!” Zegna’s expression was sinister.

What answered him, however, was a wave of fire that covered the skies.

“Soaring Demonic Phoenix!” A large phantom of a blackfire phoenix sent Zegna flying. Black flames constantly devoured the radiation energy from their opponent, causing him even more serious harm.

“Hmph! A gravely injured clone still dares say such things to me. Do you have a screw loose?” Leylin snorted. Noticing Scarlet Eye and Archibald fighting. He could not help but turn back.

With him shielding them, the undulations from the battle did not spread to this side, and the arrangements of Gilbert and Emma weren’t interrupted. A door came into existence, one wreathed in starlight.

“There’s not much time left, I need to finish this quickly. The black flames on Leylin’s body gradually weakened, and substituting them were four horrifying rings of blood coloured light.

The energy rings that signified his innate spells flashed one after another and gradually fused, forming a terrifying spell— the Morning Star Arcane Art, Kemoyin Serpent Transformation!

*Rumble!* An ancient vicious beast appeared in Tylasus City, one that was thousands of metres long. Just its descent alone caused the destruction of a great amount of architecture. Even if Scarlet Eye could hold onto his position today, he would have to relocate his capital.

The Giant Kemoyin Serpent hissed, a terrifying aura emanating from its body. Regular Star ranks could not help but tremble in fear.

These low-ranked beings all shared the common fear that came from being placed in front of a top level predator.

Compared to his previous times, Leylin’s current Giant Kemoyin Serpent transformation at the peak of Morning Star was vastly different. Not only was it much larger in size, there were now more red patterns on the scales, with darkness and fire elemental particles surrounding the body and forming a mist around it.

“A Giant Kemoyin Serpent of this size…” Even as Morning Star Kemoyin Warlocks themselves, Gilbert and Emma were stunned by Leylin’s Morning Star Arcane Art.

“How did this kid get so large? It’s about three times the size of my transformation…”

Gilbert sized up the body of Leylin’s transformation that spanned hundreds and thousands of metres, absolutely astonished. It was obvious that he was envious as well. Even amongst the bodies of real ancient Kemoyin Serpents, Leylin was definitely the king.

“I’m afraid… Leylin can be considered the strongest Kemoyin Warlock in history!” Emma sighed.

“Eye of Petrification” Two amber pupils that were like stars stared hard at Zegna who was flying backwards.

“Crap!” Before Zegna could react, his magic equipment had already exploded, and a layer of petrified skin appeared on his face as his movements ground to a halt. A petrification cast by an ancient Giant Kemoyin Serpent would affect even Radiant Moon Magi.

*Boom!* With a flick of its tail, the Giant Kemoyin Serpent struck the petrified Zegna. The earth shook wildly, and many buildings collapsed. Cracks spread in the shape of a web.

*Boom!* The petrified Zegna exploded, being obliterated into dust that flew around in the air. A huge pit was formed in the ground.

In front of the enhanced Giant Kemoyin Serpent, the clone of a Radiant Moon Magus had died just like that.

“Let’s take care of him first, or it’ll do us no good!” Scarlet Eye roared as he stopped his fight with Archibald upon witnessing this scene. Archibald halted his movements as well, fear evident on his face.

*Hss!* Leylin obviously would not let two rank 5 Magi attack him together. He took the initiative and spewed out a few large black flame blades.

*Boom!* The giant flame blades did not move in Scarlet Eye’s direction, but instead, headed towards the phoenix egg in the middle of the battlefield.

*Boom! Boom! Boom!* In the midst of immensely powerful explosions, the giant scarlet egg had cracked apart into countless fragments. Under the disbelieving gases of everyone else, a boiling heat spread in all directions.

“HOW DARE HE… How could he do that?” Scarlet Eye almost vomited blood in his fury. Never had he expected Leylin to destroy such a precious treasure.

However, he unconsciously headed towards the remains. Archibald did the same, and really, all the other Star ranks had the same thought.

This way, the recently formed forces against Leylin was dispersed.

Leylin was obviously unwilling to damage such a treasure, but he saw the big picture and knew that it was very difficult to leave safely with all their enemies watching. It was even more impossible to get the phoenix egg.

Though this treasure was precious, Leylin could still make the decision when met with issues of his own safety. Besides, he could take advantage of such a chaotic situation.

*Hsss!* The Giant Kemoyin Serpent charged around violently, and the Star ranks were forced away. They could only stare wide-eyed at its defensive scales. Leylin did not hesitate as he swallowed the remaining third of the egg into his belly, pulling back until he was in front of Gilbert and Emma. He had returned to his human form.

“Let’s go!” Leylin shouted.

“Let’s go!” Gilbert and Emma knew they had to leave no matter how unwilling they were. After all this chaos and contest was over, they would immediately be sieged by the entirety of the Lava World, and while they were reluctant they immediately made their decision.

The gigantic door of light expanded and swallowed the three of them, dissipating with grace.

*Boom!* The moment after that door disappeared, a streaking flame turned that region into a sea of fire. Atop this sea of fire was Scarlet Eye’s body, but now his eyes were bloodshot.

“Damn it, damn it, DAMN IT!” He looked at the sparkling, beautiful red gemstone in his hands that was emanating warmth. After the phoenix’s egg had been smashed apart, it had turned into this state.

He had not obtained even a quarter of the gains. Everything had been taken by Archibald and the other Star ranks.

Even if they were Star rank Emberwings, it was impossible to make them return something they had taken.

“AAAH…” Scarlet Eye, who had suffered massive losses, began to cry out hysterically…

……

Jupiter’s Lightning headquarters, Magus World.

At the same time, Zegna was shouting as well.

Black lightning flashed and wrecked the palace, turning it to ash.

“LEYLIN! I won’t let you off!” Zegna could feel his heart bleeding. That was a phoenix egg! If he’d obtained that, he could have immediately advanced to become a Breaking Dawn Monarch! Now, however, all his dreams were ruined.

First, his secondary clone had been killed, “LEYLIN! I won’t let you off!” His secondary clone had been killed by Leylin, so he had no chance to contest for the fragments of the egg. In that sense, he’d gotten no returns for all the work he’d put in.

Even the surviving Morning Stars of Jupiter’s Lightning had been fortunate enough to get part of the fragments, and they would definitely not give it to him unless there was a trade of equivalent value. However, where would he go to find something comparable to a treasure like the phoenix’s egg?

If he used violence, he would force all the Morning Stars away.

“Ah… AAH…” After thinking for a long while, Zegna’s face contorted as he roared, “Leylin, Leylin, Leylin. I won’t let you get away with this, I swear!”

“Impulse is the devil’s emissary!” The mysterious female voice sounded once more.

“It’s all your fault. If my main body had gone over, how would my secondary clone have been killed?” Zegna thundered.

“Hehe… Can your true body go over?” The female voice asked, and Zegna immediately became quiet.

“I taught you the method of making a secondary clone without any compensation, and even told you about my experiences. This is how you repay me?” The female’s voice turned cold.

“Alright! Forgive me for that. Tha kid made me lose my calm.”

Chapter 579: Contend

If not for Leylin’s appearance, the Ouroboros Clan would probably have been annihilated in the attack by the allied forces.　　

　　

Even if Leylin showed off his terrifying battle might and talent, and used various methods to get the other side to withdraw their troops, all the land and resources that had been occupied would not be taken back easily.　　

　　

Leylin had merely been a newly-advanced Morning Star then. How could he request a territory as large as that of the other three Morning Star Warlocks? If they were to be attacked again, he would not be able to suppress it alone.

　　

The amount of strength he possessed dictated the treatment he could command. Leylin was very clear on this fact. Now, with the return of the two dukes and the rise of his battle power, Leylin felt that he had enough under his belt to request this.

　　

As for whether this would offend Jupiter’s Lightning… Hadn’t Leylin already done so in the past? Since he had completely offended them, doing anything more wasn’t a huge issue.

　　

“Mm! The Black River Domain used to be one of the territories of the Ouroboros Clan, and it being occupied by some other organisation is an insult to us Bloodline Warlocks!” Philip stood up, looking indignant, “I’ll definitely tell the union!”

　　

Seeing him acting this way, Paul and the other Warlock rolled their eyes inwardly but did not retort against him. Rather, they were in favour of that decision.

　　

Those territories had initially belonged to the Ouroboros Clan, and they were merely recovering them. In addition, they would at most show their support verbally and not actually act, unless the Ouroboros Clan was willing to make more compromises for their benefits.　　

However, Leylin was only requesting that they be witnesses, and was not planning on having them act.　　

　

Not considering his current strength, just Gilbert and Emma working together would be enough to handle this.　　

Hearing that Leylin had intentions of reclaiming their old land, the Crystal Phase Warlocks around did not speak, but they were very emotional.　　

　　

The allied forces still occupied their lands and ruled their people. That was the ultimate humiliation!

The fact that the battle had come all the way to the headquarters and they had almost completely been uprooted was still fresh, and was deeply carved into the minds of these Warlocks. With these seeds of hatred planted, they were stirred up on hearing that Leylin was going to lead them to enact their vengeance.

　　

Seeing this, Leylin nodded.　　

　　

The reason for this expansion was to increase the size of the pie so as to avert dissent. With three Morning Stars now in the Ouroboros Clan, the resources of the area they controlled were not enough to divide amongst all of them, leave alone the rest of the people under them.

　　

Furthermore, by leading them to take revenge, Leylin’s reputation would reach an unprecedented level, which would make it more convenient for him to take control of the organisation.

　　

This was an open conspiracy. Even if Gilbert and Emma could tell, they would not be able to say much.

　　

Having agreed on the time, Philip and the others took their leaves, and even Freya and other high-ranked Warlocks left automatically. Only Leylin and the other two were left.

“Are you going to declare war on Jupiter’s Lightning now? Didn’t you say to maintain the current state?” Emma asked worriedly.　　

　　

“When I said to maintain the current state, I meant our current state of preparing for battle!” Leylin laughed grimly, a tyrannical aura emanating from his body. “Besides, Jupiter’s Lightning is probably too busy with their own matters…”　　

　　

“Oh? How is that?” Gilbert was interested. He was always elated when there were methods to trim Jupiter Lightning’s strength. From Leylin’s perspective, this was a deeply embedded enmity.

“When I went to the Lava World, I asked the rank 5 ‘Golden Lion’ Warlock, Lord Wayde, to help hold up Zegna. He accidentally let a rank 5 clone go, but the main body did not descend. For that reason, I’m going to hold to our agreement!”

　　

“What agreement?” Gilbert and Emma exchanged a glance. Ever since they had known Leylin, they had never seen this kid at a disadvantage before. There must definitely be some deep meaning for him to do this.　　

　

“He helped me hold Zegna back, so in return, I will give them the coordinates to the Lava World!” Leylin laughed. “Just now, Wayde received my message…”　　

　　

“What?” Gilbert and Emma stood up abruptly, “That’s a world! Do you know what you’ve done?”

　　

A large alternative world meant unprecedented benefits. Just the strength systems and paths to power they had were extremely helpful for Magi, and could help them progress rapidly.　　

　　

Not considering other matters, those Breaking Dawn Monarchs had taken over entire large worlds before advancing. The fact that Leylin had obtained such benefits was also proof of the value of a world.

　

Hence, organisations would guard these coordinates with the highest security. If not for Zegna being absolutely confident and having been bewitched by somebody else, he would not use these coordinates to trap the three Kemoyin dukes.

　

A world that had not been exploited yet was very attractive. It was not as if the three Kemoyin dukes didn’t have their suspicions, but they still fell into the trap. The fact was that the benefits were immense, to the point that it affected their rationality!

　　

Of course, it was Zegna who had lost everything. Not only had he gained nothing, he had also suffered greatly.

　　

Now, Leylin was giving such a huge secret away? Emma and Gilbert could not comprehend this.

　　

After all, in their eyes, only they and Jupiter’s Lightning knew of the Lava World’s coordinates. At this point, it was best to keep this secret to their death and when the time was right, they could destroy Jupiter’s Lightning and completely take over the Lava World!

　　

“You guys…” Leylin shook his head helplessly, “How could another world be so easy to take control of? Besides, there are numerous rank 5s there, as well as Jupiter’s Lightning eyeing this strength.”　　

　　

“What we need the most now is not another world, but enough time to rest and regain our strength.”

　　

“Wayde is part of our Warlock Union. By luring him there, Jupiter’s Lightning will definitely launch an intense battle for control of the Lava World. That will give us ample time for developments.” Leylin spoke frankly and assuredly, tone full of confidence and eyes emanating an incomparable vigour.　　

　　

“There are rank 5s on both ends. How could the Lava World be so easily taken over? In this period of time, it’s enough for us to take advantage of the chaos and gain benefits!”

　

“On top of that, once we obtain more strength, it’s not like we can’t forcefully retrieve the Lava World from the other party’s hands!”

　　

Not only did Leylin make the final decision, he even presented a pretty picture for Emma and Gilbert.

　　

“If you say that…” Gilbert and Emma looked each other in the eye begrudgingly.　　

　

Seeing them acting this way, Leylin was laughing inside.　　

　　

He obviously didn’t care much for the Lava World, because he’d already gotten the most benefits from there. Not only had he obtained the mutated Fireplume and caused his Morning Star point mass to grow to the limits, he’d even gotten a third of the essence from the phoenix egg.　　

　　

These were basically the greatest treasures of the Lava World, and Leylin was obviously satisfied with his gains.

　　

After the matter with the Holy Solar Festival, he had offended the heads of the two largest organisations in the Lava World, Scarlet Eye and Archibald, and it could only be resolved by the death of a party.

　　

Just the knowledge that he had obtained fragments of the phoenix’s egg would be enough to cause the strong ones within the Lava World to hunger after his gains.

　　

The reason Leylin had handed over the coordinates to the Lava World was because he had considered this as well. With Wayde in control, he could still hold onto what he had. Besides, he’d already handed the coordinates over already. If Wayde or others wanted some? It was simple, they could go to the Lava World themselves and contend with each other for it!

　　

“That Zegna from Jupiter’s Lightning is probably coughing up blood right now, given that I threw these coordinates away.” Leylin stroked his chin, a malicious grin about his lips.　　

……　　

He sent the two dukes away after their discussion. Following that was a conversation with Freya over dinner before Leylin finally returned to his Morning Star Magus Tower.

The place was as towering as always, full of archaism and grandeur. As he entered the tower, the intelligent tower genie flew out, “Master!”

“Hmm. Show me all the recent records, as well as the current state of operation of the Magus Tower,” Leylin commanded.　　

　　

“In the time that master has been away, the astral gate has been operating at the lowest energy level. Astral stone storage has been completely used up. Magus Tower is now running on minimal energy required. 3.78% of the Host’s health is injured. Supplies-wise, ….”

　　

The tower genie was expressionless and began to send in the reports methodically. It was extremely meticulous, as if he was the most thorough of butlers.

“Keke… I’ve practically used up all the astral stones I’ve accumulated as well as the power source of the Magus Tower.” Leylin sighed, feeling his heart ache.

　

“But in comparison to such a huge harvest, this investment is very worth it. The profits were immense! Of course, that’s because I have the A.I. Chip and can unearth the resources of foreign worlds to the highest degree.”

　　

Back in his study room, Eternal Flames emitted heated light. Seated behind the study table, he began to compare his gains.

　　

“I’ve successfully met my goal and brought the two Kemoyin dukes back. The Ouroboros Clan’s strength has risen rapidly, and just this alone means that I’ve gotten more than I invested.”

　　

Leylin’s eyes were twinkling as he spread out a black notebook on the table and began to scribble on it.

　　

“In terms of resources, there’s the essence of the phoenix egg. That is definitely a world-class treasure. Not only can it accelerate progress in Fireplume, it’s remarkably useful for a Magus’ soul and point mass. The resources that I especially collected from the Emberwings can also be considered to be abundant!”

Chapter 582: Retrieving Land

Every Magus possessed knowledge and wisdom that far surpassed that of ordinary men. How could any such person knowingly provoke a rank 5?

There were only two ways that such a thing would happen. They were either absolutely confident in victory, or had a trump card that guaranteed them their lives.

Though this Morning Star couldn’t guess what trump card Leylin and the rest had, he could tell that the situation today was not in his favour.

“Alright! Give me five minutes, and I’ll order all my Magi to withdraw. I’ll leave Greenflame City to you,” he relented, albeit grudgingly.

The city and territory were all small matters to him. His Magi were what truly mattered, and he did not hesitate to make this choice even if he was unwilling.

“There’s no need for that. Whatever the Ouroboros Clan lost, we will retrieve it with our own strength.” Gilbert shook his head and rejected the other party’s suggestion.

“Also, even if it’s you, whoever dares offend our Ouroboros Clan will need to pay the price,” Leylin added from the core of the group of Warlocks.

“What?” The enemy Morning Star Magus was enraged. “The nerve! You dare threaten me?”

He had been infuriated. Morning Star Magi lorded over the central continent. With their Morning Star Arcane Arts, they had trump cards capable of taking their opponents down with them, and they’d thus developed a pride rooted in the belief that they were unrivalled.

He acknowledged that he had been defeated, and taking the initiative and withdrawing was already giving his opponent face. However, the Warlocks of the Ouroboros Clan wanted him to pay a price?

“Lunatics! You bunch of Kemoyin Warlocks are all lunatics!” The Morning Star’s expression turned frosty.

If he knew of Leylin’s previous battle achievements, he wouldn’t dare say things like this.

Now, however, the Magus was determined to teach Leylin a lesson, and terrifying elemental energy gathered on his body as rings of light formed one after the other.

“Morning Star Arcane Art!” Paul and the others exclaimed in shock.

“That’s right… Since you don’t know what’s good for you, then let this area be completely destroyed!” The Morning Star Magus yelled maniacally. If a Morning Star were to disregard everything, the Ouroboros Clan’s territory would be ruined.

“Stand down. Let me do this.”

Unexpectedly, the Warlocks opposing him had not withdrawn from his threats. Instead, Leylin had stepped out.

“A mere newly-advanced Morning Star is going to stop me?” This Morning Star suddenly had the urge to laugh.

Soon enough, though, this smile turned stiff.

*Hsssss!*” Along with large amounts of demonic black flames, the giant phantom of a serpent appeared behind Leylin’s back. This large serpent was quite similar to the Giant Kemoyin Serpent of the Ouroboros Clan, but there were red patterns on the scales and large amounts of black flames twining around its body. It was as if it was wreathed in a layer of flaming armour.

A forcefield even more terrifying than those of ancient rank 4 beings spread out, covering him.

*Crack!* The rings of light broke, and the energy of this Morning Star Magus’ point mass began to seep out and enter the black flames.

“Wha– What monster is this?!” The Morning Star Magus’ expression changed, regret filling his mind. He now knew that this newly-advanced Morning Star was the most terrifying of this group of Warlocks!

“Hssss!” The huge serpent snarled and devoured the Morning Star…

*Rumble!* Air shook and created shockwaves. Gilbert, Emma and the rest shot glances at each other and began to stabilise the space around them.

*Whoosh!* A moment later, a blue figure escaped from the giant phantom serpent, making a strange sound as he fled pitifully.

Leylin stood quietly where he was, not even a wrinkle in his clothes or a strand of stray hair jutting out. He did not proceed to give chase.

“Why did you let him go?” Gilbert and Emma asked. They knew it was intentional on Leylin’s part, after all they had personally seen his prowess.

“Our goal right now is to regain our territory. Now isn’t the time to start wars with others. Battles between Morning Stars would attract the attention of Breaking Dawn Monarchs.”

Leylin shook his head, “Besides, the injuries to his body will take a few hundred years to heal. There’s no need to take notice of him in the future!”

It had to be said that Leylin was very meticulous in some matters. Gilbert and Emma looked to give him their approval.

“Ley– Leylin, you’re so amazing? Goodnes! That was a Morning Star!” Philip was gaping. He had to admit that what he had seen today was just too amazing, and something rarely seen even in his long life.

Leylin could actually forcefully suppress a Magus by interrupting them while they were performing their Morning Star Arcane Art. He had even gravely injured his opponent, and was confident in killing them!

This was not a strength that belonged to rank 4s. It was the might that only great rank 5 Magi possessed!

“Leylin, Your Grace. Have you advanced to rank 5 already?” Paul asked a question that Gilbert and Emma wanted to enquire about as well.

“Of course not!” Leylin shook his head, but that only gave Paul the feeling that he was enigmatic and unmeasurable.

“Alright! Since the Morning Star has already been chased off, Greenflame City shall return to the arms of our Ouroboros Clan!”

Gilbert said a few words to a secret imprint, and soon enough troops formed of multiple high-ranked Warlocks arrived at the place.

Having already been attacked by a rank 4 spell and seeing their Morning Star flee in defeat, the high-ranked Magi of the enemy had no plans of fighting on. Teleportation portals flashed and people flew away as they fled.

Greenflame City returned to the Warlocks’ control in less than an hour.

“I remember that this place once belonged to the Mair Family, right?” Emma spoke, implying something.

“Yes! As the Mair Family did not guard their territory properly, I suggest we reduce their land and take Greenflame City, giving it to other bloodline nobility!” Gilbert immediately spoke.

This was a reshuffling of power. With Leylin’s powerful, abrupt rise, as well as the fall of the original First Elder, there were definitely conflicts of interest when it came to the allocation of benefits. The war was a perfect excuse to make changes to this.

Leylin stood silently at the side, not seeming to have any intentions of seizing power. However, even outsiders like Paul and Philip could tell that most of the territories that were being reclaimed would definitely be placed under Leylin’s Farlier Family and Freya’s Blood Serpent Family.

After the war, the Blood Serpent and Farlier Families would immediately rise in power. There was no doubt about that.

“Alright, let’s get to the next area!” Once all affairs at Greenflame City were taken care of, a few Warlocks immediately continued on a new journey.

With Leylin along with Gilbert and Emma as support, the organisations that relied on Jupiter’s Lightning and had merely one or two Morning Star Magi were swept through.

While Philip and Paul did not do anything, just their presence represented the stance of the Warlock Union. Even Rank 5 Magi had to reconsider the consequences.

Hence, the frontlines were pushed forward smoothly. In less than a month, all the land that had been occupied had returned to the high-ranked Warlocks of the Ouroboros Clan. Of course, there were naturally changes when it came to allocation, but no Warlock dared complain.

“Hah… Onyx Castle! I’m back!”

Leylin stood above Onyx Castle in his territory, and was speechless.

The Magus Tower not far away had long since been overturned by the Oakheart family. Of course, they had immediately compensated Leylin with a brand new Morning Star Magus Tower.

The Onyx Castle below had obviously been destroyed and reconstructed. That must have been the Oakheart Family trying to curry favour with him since they were already here.

“Are you very familiar with the Azure Mountain King? The moment you arrived, he immediately withdrew his troops, and even looked impatient in doing it!”

“I just have something on him, so we’re temporary allies.” Leylin shook his head and chuckled.

“Temporary?” Emma observed Leylin’s profound smile, suddenly feeling like the breeze in the skies was slightly chilly. She began to mourn for the Oakheart Family.

“News has come in that the Green Snake Marshes have been taken back. Our Ouroboros Clan has now regained all its past territory!” Gilbert’s figure appeared by Leylin side, a sigh in his tone. “What should we do next?”

“Nothing. Just work on consolidating our original territories.”

Leylin knew when to stop. Though he did not know if it was his existence or the intimidation of the Warlock Union, Jupiter’s Lightning had displayed a high degree of tolerance towards the Ouroboros Clan’s recent activities, and practically did not interfere at all. This was also why Leylin and the rest had been able to reclaim their territories so quickly.

Of course, Leylin did not believe that they were afraid of him or the union.

Zegna probably had something more important to focus on, which was why he was temporarily enduring his activities. As long as he killed Leylin, the Ouroboros Clan would quickly fall apart even if they took up half of the central continent.

Leylin always had his guard up against this Radiant Moon.

“The Ouroboros Clan has completely expelled our organisations and restored their territories!”

“In the Lava World, Wayde has brought a group of high-ranked Warlocks and is going around annihilating the Mobius Organisation!”

“Damn it, Damn it, DAMN IT! Leylin, Wayde… One day, I’ll bury your skulls under my palace’s steps, and have your souls wailing within the flames of my lights…”

Zegna’s eyes were bloodshot as he sent the reporting Morning Star Magus away. Recently, all that was being delivered to him was bad news.

Wayde had actually gotten the coordinates to the Lava World, bringing a whole group and vying for territory with him. His previous actions had lost him his friendship with Scarlet Eye, and Archibald had become hostile with him after this matter as well.

While Zegna was in terrible shape worrying over these, Leylin had meanwhile reclaimed all the territory that had once belonged to the Ouroboros Clan!

Chapter 584: Giant Dragon Potion

“Leylin!” Gilbert and Emma had come over while Leylin was deep in thought. Their eyes were twinkling with joy.

　　

“What’s this? You’ve acquired an interest in body tempering?” Emma had immediately made the connection after glancing at the mess of materials on the table.

　

“Mm. My soul has strengthened too much recently, and my physical body hasn’t been able to keep up.” Leylin nodded. This wasn’t any information worth hiding after all.

　

“Seriously,” Gilbert sat down speechlessly, “Us bloodline Warlocks have the advantage of increased vitality due to our inheritance of ancient genes. We’re ahead of Magi in this field, and normally we only have to worry about how to increase our soul force. There are practically no other people in your situation!”

　　

Leylin’s monstrous growth rate was something Gilbert found difficult to digest.

　　

Leylin laughed, and asked the two dukes some other questions about body tempering. However, both of them knew even less than he did, and could hardly give him any useful information.

　　

In the end, Leylin could only ask, “How much do you know about Sky City?”

　　

“What?!” “Don’t tell me you’re going there!?” Both Warlocks stood up in shock.

　

“Why? What’s the matter?” Leylin asked with a smile.

　　

The Endowing Scepter kept in Sky City was a treasure that only Virtuous Sky Sages could come in contact with, and it had the ability to increase his physique by two levels without any side effects. To the present Leylin, that was a huge temptation.

　

Two levels was roughly twenty points of vitality. With the additional ten points from the Giant Dragon Potion, his vitality would grow very close to a hundred points. The remainder could be increased slowly through Fireplume or Multilimb Strength.

　

Therefore, if he couldn’t find other methods to substitute for it, he had to go through with this.

　　

After a moment of silence Emma spoke. “Leylin… Even though the Monarch of the Skies hasn’t targeted Warlocks before, you know the situation with our Warlock Union…”

　

Due to unknown reasons, bloodline Warlocks had been rejected and were treated as enemies by the regular Magi of the central continent. They had even reached the verge of extinction. Despite the tremendous efforts of the few Radiant Moon Warlocks, most Warlocks still felt quite unsafe. This was why the Morning Star Area had come up.

　　

If the Monarchs hadn’t given the suppression of Warlocks their tacit approval, this would have been impossible.

　

In Emma’s eyes, Leylin was an up-and-coming talent who she had high expectations for, even someone who she considered a son-in-law. She naturally wouldn’t want Leylin to leave and expose himself to danger.

　　

“Mentor Gilbert, what do you think?” Leylin could only laugh wryly inside, his eyes focusing on Gilbert.

　　

“Let’s not talk about the Monarch of the Skies. Sky City is a holy land for Magi in the central continent, and is considered the Palace of Truth. Countless top-grade masters, artisans and scholars gather there, calling it the cradle of knowledge. In terms of innovations and advancements in spells, rapid progress is made every single day!”

　　

Gilbert scratched his bald head, recalling some fond memories from the past as his eyes shimmered.

　　

“If you hadn’t already become a Morning Star Warlock and the pillar that’s propping up our Ouroboros Clan, my very first recommendation would be to go to Sky City if you intend to travel across the continent!”

　

“If this is the case, I’m even more interested in going there!” Leylin stroked his chin, yearning evident in his expression.

　　

“Alright then, but you have to be extra careful. It’s best to hide your true identity.” Gilbert and Emma smiled wryly at each other. They knew Leylin well enough. He was the stubborn type, and now that he had already made his own decision, he would not change his mind easily. He just wanted to listen to their suggestions.

“I know!” Leylin crossed his arms, leaning slightly forward.　　

　　

“Well then, is there any reason for you to come all the way here now?”　

　

“Oh yes, of course! We’d even forgotten about that!” Gilbert slapped his forehead. He passed Leylin a recording crystal.　　

“After a month of hard fighting, we have finally regained all our territory. This is the new map we’ve drawn out.”

Leylin sent his soul force into the crystal, and immediately perceived a giant map. Different colours were used to divide the regions that belonged to the different bloodline nobles.　　

Compared to the previous map, there was not much of a change on the whole, but much of the nobles’ territories had been greatly modified.

Primely, the territory that belonged to the nobles under the previous First Elder’s wings had been greatly reduced, reallocated instead to the Blood Serpent Family and more significantly the Farlier Family.

‘On the whole, both the dukes’ rights and benefits remain the same as before, while I get a hold of the territory and resources that originally belonged to the First Elder?’ Leylin pondered over this in his mind, though on the surface, just nodded, “I think this is fine! Let’s go with this redistributed map!”　　

Only after Leylin agreed to this redistribution did Gilbert and Emma feel as if a weight had been lifted off their shoulders. After all, Leylin was far too crucial to the Ouroboros Clan, and if he was dissatisfied with the distribution and left the clan they would be in deep trouble.

Leylin laughed and shook his head as he saw both of these ‘senior’ Morning Star Warlocks in fear and trepidation before him.

“Master! I’ve captured a third batch of Kobold Warlocks, and placed them in the binding room.” Tanasha bowed to Leylin as she reported. This Magus who was currently wearing a black dress had afforded him even more respect since his advancement, She had become very cautious with her work as well. At Leylin’s command, she had captured large numbers of Kobold Warlocks in the blink of an eye.　

“Mm, good job!” Leylin knew exactly what she wanted.

He laid lazily on the couch, waving his right hand slightly. A demonic dark flame formed on her forehead, leaving behind a distinct brand in the shape of a black snake.

*Hss! Hss!* Surrounding the snake were hazy flames. The snake looked as if it was alive, about to break through the thin membrane of skin at any moment,

“Master!” Tanasha knelt down in trepidation. She could feel terrifying power from the mark, enough to crush her into powder!

“This is my secret imprint, and is representative of me. I’ve also stored within a one-time attack from my own hands. Normal Morning Stars won’t be able to withstand it….” Leylin closed his eyes slightly as he spoke slowly. In the meanwhile, Tanasha was thrilled by his words.　　

“I’d once promised you at Quicksand Castle that once I was strong enough, and not afraid of retaliation, I would grant you your vengeance.” Indeed, this was the reason that Tanasha had chosen to serve under him.

“Yes, Master! It’s just that I never thought this time would come so soon…” Tanasha sounded a little unsteady. Leylin’s rate of advancement was far beyond her expectations.　　

“The family that you are going to take revenge on has no Morning Star. I have also talked to their backing organisation, and they won’t get in your way. You should be able to handle everything. The secret imprint I’ve left on you is your last resort!”

“Thank you, Master!” Tanasha’s choked as she sobbed, her eyes red as the memories of her being harmed and chased after came up. It was still extremely vivid in her mind, how she’d even have to hide in the wilderness to survive.

“Go!” Leylin waved his hand, and Tanasha exited respectfully.

After exiting the Magus Tower, Tanasha felt the secret imprint on her forehead, especially the immense power within it, and her eyes glinted with strength. “How have you been, Dove? I will be back soon…”　　

Most would think Tanasha and this Dove were very good friends from her words, but they would be frightened upon looking at the terrifying expression on her face.　　

“Deeply buried hatred that hasn’t dissipated over time. It’s instead fermented and grown…” After Tanasha left, Leylin stood up slowly, and announced something that sounded like a prophecy.

He had a feeling that Tanasha’s trip back would be accompanied by a great amount of bloodshed and pain. The misery of being forced to leave home and the experience of hiding for survival was enough to turn Tanasha into a terrifying goddess of vengeance.

But the history between them didn’t matter to him. No matter what had happened, Leylin would surely side with Tanasha, and for a very simple reason. He had no relationship with the other party, whereas Tanasha was his subordinate.

Leylin had always favoured people of his own. He followed his own set of rules, and would definitely side with his own people if they were engaged in conflict with outsiders. Were Freya to fight his subordinates, for example, he would support her. But in case the two of them fell out, he would choose to protect his own benefits.

His personal benefits was in the core of his set of rules. The closer an external circle of benefits was to the centre, the more priority it received.

As for fairness? Justice? To things like that…Haha.

“Tower genie! Begin the modulation of Kobold Warlocks based on the bloodline operation sequence I had entered earlier on!”

Take now for instance. Leylin’s interests were in conflict with those of the Kobolds, so he would not hesitate to sacrifice them.

[Beep! First stage of modulation beginning, increase in activity of bloodline…]

The tower genie’s voice sounded. Meanwhile, sounds of mournful cries could be heard from the multiple cages under the Magus Tower…　　

After days of experiments, Leylin held a purplish red bloodline potion in a test tube, his face filled with satisfaction, “Even though there were some failures in between, the Giant Dragon Potion is finally ready!”

Chapter 585: Vitality and Formation

Leylin had tremendous achievements in Potioneering, to the extent that he’d even surpassed the realm of Grandmasters, reaching a higher level.

Even though the Giant Dragon Potion was rare and difficult to make even during ancient times, it was only a matter of trial and error for Leylin.

Even these few failures were not due to his technique, but because experiments were prone to failure themselves.

“Since the Giant Dragon Potion is done, I can begin now!”

Leylin took a glance at the surroundings. It was a huge public square located in the Morning Star Magus Tower, created with the help of the tower genie. On the ground were complex designs and magic runes, and even vicious totem images.

Surrounding the entire spell formation were four gigantic pillars, every single stone pillar the thickness of three men combined. Above them was something like a huge hollow tunnel, it seemed to be split open by sharp weapons, full of a wild ancient aura.

[Hades’ Blood Sacrifice spell formation, progress 99.9999%]

the A. I. Chip responded after scanning through.

“Hades’ spell formation, what an affinity between us!” Leylin laughed.

Hades was one of the most terrifying dark Magi of ancient myth. His level of dark magic was said to be unreachable, and rumour had it that he had even completely grasped the rules of death. He possessed eternal youth, and was full of desire for flesh and souls.

But of course, Hades was nothing more than a super powerful dark Magus in the eyes of Leylin and other Magi, and some even looked up to Hades as a motivational target and tried to surpass him.

When Leylin was trying to advance to rank 2, he had made use of the opponent’s spell formation to harvest spirits.

Of course, the current blood spell formation was a few levels higher than the one back then, it could even absorb the sacrificial offerings’ bloodlines by force in order to increase the Morning Star Magus’s vitality.

Leylin took a look at his current status:

[Leylin Farlier, Rank 4 Bloodline Warlock: Giant Kemoyin Serpent (complete form) Strength: 50, Agility: 45, Vitality: 65, Spiritual Force: 956.8, Magic Power: 956 (magic power in synchronisation with spiritual force) Soul Force: ???]

“I have more than enough spiritual force, but vitality is so hard to increase!” Leylin smiled wryly. This was the side effect for his sudden, huge advancements recently.

Moreover, if his vitality still could not reach 100, it would be a huge problem once the Multilimb seal was broken.

“Begin!” Leylin’s eyes shimmered with crimson light.

*Crack! Crack!* Under the manipulation of the tower genie, the entire square started shaking, and grieved howls could be heard from a near distance.

That was the mourning of the strengthened Kobold Warlocks. After the bloodline extraction, these creatures were being treated as waste material and processed by Leylin

Waves of a terrifying aura rose continuously within the spell formation. Once the mourning of the Kobolds weakened, the whole spell formation started to change.

The four gigantic stone pillars surrounding the square began to shake. From the tunnel up above, a huge amount of sticky liquid that was blood red in colour dripped down. Mixed in were white objects that looked like crushed bones.

The red liquid first filled the pillars to the brink, before it slowly spilled out like blood flowing in veins, causing the pillars to turn crimson.

The liquid flowed all the way down, finally reaching the runes of the spell formation.

The concentrated blood red liquid filled the runes in order. The entire process was full of a certain solemnity, and the stagnant atmosphere was stifling.

The spell formation kicked into action, and an enormous layer of crimson light shot up from the runes.

Under the attraction of the crimson light rays, the vacant void above the spell formation was broken. Light took on the form of symbols seen in sacrificial rites, as it began to radiate waves of summoning.

*Awooooo…*The phantom of a monstrous two-headed wolf hovered in the sky above the spell formation, howling ferociously. Greed filled its green eyes as saliva dripped down its jaws.

‘I’ve never seen such a summoning technique before, is it a summoning from a foreign world or from a different time and space?’ Leylin‘s eyes flashed blue. He had ordered the A.I. Chip to record the scene down into his database for future use.

*Awooooo…* The two-headed wolf did not start to feast on the pulp of flesh, bones and blood immediately. Instead, it turned to Leylin, a ferocious look in its eyes as it glared at him as if he was one of the offerings.

‘It has a certain level of intelligence? Could it be a clone of Hades?’ Leylin stroked his chin, started as he sized up this two-headed wolf. This carefree behaviour of Leylin greatly irritated the phantom as it howled and aimed to pounce onto Leylin.

*Sssssii* A malevolent phantom of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, this one with crimson scales, appeared behind Leylin and bared its jaws at the wolf.

A magnificent aura emanated from the Kemoyin Serpent, causing the wolf to waver.

“The summoning of a creature from another world is indeed troublesome!” Leylin snorted, started to activate a spell.

*Rumble!* Eye piercing white flashes of lightning struck the phantom, causing it to howl as it lost some of its dark form.

After the lightning passed, each of the two wolf heads now had a collar on, with spikes that faced the neck.

The two-headed wolf was threatened by the spikes, and dared not rebel. It then dashed into the crimson light before starting to feast on the flesh hungrily. The formation grew silent except for the bone-chilling munching noises.

After a few minutes, the flesh and light inside the spell formation were both devoured by the two-headed wolf. It then roared to the sky, the sound waves travelling far and wide as it howled loudly.

The spell formation started to warp once more under these terrifying howls.

Starlight shone down through the Magus Tower, revealing the image of a bright moon.

Under the howls of the wolf, the moon gradually turned red before it stretched into the sides and formed the shape of a human eye.

An icy gaze swept across, causing Leylin to shudder in fear. He felt as if he had called upon a disaster and his body tensed up. ‘This pressuring aura must surely belong to a high levelled Magus!’

Leylin inhaled deeply. Fortunately, the crimson eye did not fix its gaze on him. Instead, it only spared him a short glance and focused on the two-headed wolf.

An eerie scene formed as the two-headed wolf howled continuously under the gaze of the crimson moon-eye.

*Pop!* The sound of a bubble bursting was followed by a crisp explosive sound, and the phenomenal sights in the area disappeared without a trace.

The two-headed wolf, the full moon and the starlight suddenly seemed to be an illusion, and a tinge of purple light twirled around the spell formation.

[Conscient of greed from a foreign world has been attracted, summoning of ancient Hades phantom is complete!]

A notification from the A. I. Chip sounded, reminding Leylin that what he had seen just now was not a hallucination.

“Phew…what a weird spell formation! Hades, the king of the ancient dark Magi, is truly a powerful elite!” Leylin let out a long breath and stepped into the spell formation.

*Boom* The rumbling of the formation acted like a signal, and a huge amount of purple light converged on Leylin as it entered his body.

“Argh!” Leylin let out a stuffy groan and started to spasm.

After the purple light rays entered his body, they started wriggling like earthworms. This feeling was indescribable; if not for his superb vitality and great endurance, he would have passed out or even died due to the pain!

“The Giant Dragon Potion!” Leylin kept himself composed, using the purplish red medicine which he had long since prepared in his hand.

*Pow!* There seemed to be a chemical reaction when the potion entered his stomach, and the amount of pain increased tenfold.

Leylin’s vision turned pitch black, but he managed to persevere through it with his strong will.

[Beep! Host is undergoing Hades’ sacrificial rites! Muscle fiber strengthening in process.]

[Beep! Host is absorbing quintessential materials, vitality increased.]

[Beep! Giant Dragon Potion has taken effect. Radiation is creating the best environment for absorption.]

The notifications from the A. I. Chip sounded continuously.

After the last wave of pain had passed, Leylin felt a stream of boiling heat gushing all over his body.

[Beep! Host vitality increasing, currently at 66.7! 67.5! 68.3! 69.9!]

The value showing Leylin’s vitality kept on increasing in the A. I. Chip’s database, and surpassed 70 within a split second before continuing on.

71! 72! 73! 74! 74.5!

In almost an instant, the number had rocketed up by ten. It only stopped upon reaching 74.9.

Leylin straightened his body after the effects of the potion passed, and crackling sounds rang throughout it.

[Host data changed, readjusting!]

Leylin took a look at his stats and discovered a huge change in them.

[Leylin Farlier, Rank 4 Bloodline Warlock: Kemoyin’s Serpent (complete form) Strength: 50 Agility: 45 Vitality: 74.9 Spiritual Force: 956.8 Magic Power: 956(Magic power in synchronisation with spiritual force) Soul force:???]

“Hmm! Vitality had increased by 9.9 units! Pretty close to the estimated data from the A. I. Chip!” Leylin nodded in satisfaction.

Right now, he had reached a monstrous value in terms of his vitality.

Chapter 588: Floating City

The multiple bolts of lightning twined together, converging into a giant lightning serpent. There even seemed to be a hologram behind it, as it faced the unwanted guest that had just entered its lightning zone.

*Bzz Bzz!* Sparks flew madly on the surface of the Colossal Serpent, and the original defensive layer began to deform, seemingly unable to endure further.

“Emergency alert? The strength of each lightning bolt is above 300 degrees?” Leylin touched his chin.

An attack strength of 300 degrees was rare even amongst rank 3 Magi. Even Crystal Phase Magi would find it difficult to take on the combination of the lightning storm and the atmosphere.

Other than Morning Star Magi, perhaps only a fleet of tens of rank 3 Magi could gain entry using the airship’s defences augmented by a continuous supply of magic crystals and potions.

This had caused tickets into Sky City to become immensely expensive, enough to make official Magi go broke.

‘If not for caring little for this meagre source of income, Morning Star Magi could earn quite a lot of money if they took charge of these airships!’ Leylin thought indifferently.

Of course, Morning Star Magi were exceedingly rich and cared little for such a meagre profit. In addition, their arrogance would not allow them to do something like this.

Leylin was not staying idle right now. A terrifying soul force emanated from this body, wrapping the Colossal Serpent within it.

*Buzz!* With the support of soul force, the Colossal Serpent’s defensive membrane immediately stabilised and was now reinforced with another thick layer. It was now like a solid black crystal.

The deck of the Colossal Serpent, that had been shuddering all this while, was now as solid as a mountain.

That was not all. Tiny black flames clung to the energy defence. The lightning could not even reach the Colossal Serpent itself and was instead absorbed by these flames. In fact, the Colossal Serpent’s energy reserves grew rapidly.

The black flames seemed to form a pathway in the air, not allowing any lightning to strike in its path.

The Colossal Serpent was then free to move as it liked, the lightning no longer daring to attack.

“Oh?” Leylin scanned an area and chuckled. The Colossal Serpent turned into a black streak as he quickly left.

“Hah…” A long while after the Colossal Serpent disappeared, the clouds dissipated to reveal an elemental sprite whose lower body was covered by a spiral of unlimited lightning elemental particles.

“What a terrifying human!” Only now did it dare mutter to itself, a tremble in its voice, “He’d long since found me! Just his gaze alone was paralysing… Even the earlier Morning Stars haven’t given me this feeling, could he be a great Radiant Moon Magus?”

This lightning elemental sprite with a body of lightning energy particles shuddered as it looked in the direction Leylin had departed, eyes full of fear…

*Boom!* The black clouds parted as a similarly black streak flew across the skies, with black flames trailing behind as it left a magnificent path in the air.

“Hah… So this is Sky City, the airborne holy land of the Magi!” Leylin observed a large floating city from the deck in amazement.

This city was constructed on a hemispherical island. The city itself was massive, glowing with light from all types of spells. Once in a while, a few ant-like black dots would move in the distance horizon. With Leylin’s sight, he could tell that they were no ants, but magic airships that were bigger than even the most gigantic cruises in his previous world.

In comparison to the floating city, these large airships appeared to be tiny.

“And to think I still knew that Sky City was afloat. Pictures and words can’t describe the mind-blowing nature of this view.” As the Colossal Serpent approached it, the city seemed to grow even larger. A faint golden light rose from the heart of the city, seeming to create a holy radiance in the sky.

“Peace and harmony! What a beautiful city!” Even Leylin could not help but sing its praises right now.

[Beep! The Colossal Serpent has received a communication request.]

the A.I. Chip sounded. The floating city had obviously discovered the communication devices on Leylin’s personal airship.

‘As expected of something from the Fallor Family, they’d tampered with the airship!’ Leylin’s eyes flashed coldly. While he had known of this, he had allowed it because it made communications easier, which did not go past his bottom line.

Leylin had intentionally used the Colossal Serpent to come here. If he were to sneak in alone, who would discover him?

Through the communications channel, a polite and humble voice was heard. “Airship number DKGW1394! Distinguished Duke Farlier, welcome to Sky City! Please follow our guiding airship and park at the private port we’ve allocated!”

“Mm!” Leylin agreed, and the Colossal Serpent began to slow down while following the mentioned route before it stopped.

Meanwhile, in the command room somewhere in Sky City, things were in chaos!

“Morning Star undulations detected! Determined to be at Four Stars!”

“No issues with the Colossal Serpent. Kemoyin Duke Farlier is confirmed to be inside.” Information was flashed through red warning lights and many staff members gaped at the gigantic airship. The figures working the deck felt faint.

“A Morning Star has come to visit us. Why were we not notified earlier?” A burly middle-aged man shouted as he barged in after bursting through the door. He looked panicked as he snarled, “Do you know who he is? He’s the most powerful Kemoyin Warlock in history, the one who killed Demon Hunter Cyril. It’s Duke Leylin Farlier! If this kind of person flares up at us for how we receive him, we’re finished!”

Immediately after, he looked at the red warning alarm and couldn’t help but hold his head in his hands, feeling the desire to end his life there and then. “Four Star undulations? The upper-tier of Morning Star? Gods, just let me die!”

Morning Star Magi were a rarity in the central continent, and there were naturally no clear methods of classifying them. They were normally classified based on their reputation and battle achievements among others.

As the holy land of Magi, Sky City was the most advanced research centre in the central continent. It had independently come up with a standard to measure the strength of a Morning Star.

They had divided Morning Stars into five levels represented by five Stars, with a One Star Magus being the weakest. A grade of Four Stars was already at the upper tier of Morning Stars, while Five Stars was the peak!

Of course, since Leylin had intentionally hidden some of his strength, their detection was not accurate.

However, even Four Stars was already terrifying. Most of the Morning Stars were around One to Three Stars. Morning Stars at Four Stars or above were absolutely powerful, and even Radiant Moons would be apprehensive when up against them.

Sky City might be called the holy land of Magi, but there were few Morning Stars of this calibre among their ranks.

People like them in charge of the ports could not afford to offend him. Even if they were exposed to the radiations on his body, there would be massive casualties here!

“We’ve already sent out the signal and requested that he stop at the personal dock. He’s accepted our guidance airship, and is probably here with kind intentions…”

A golden-haired young man produced a handkerchief and wiped away the cold sweat on his forehead. “What we need to do now is to report this news to the Sage Committee, and then all of us should welcome him!”

“Oh, yes, yes! You’re right. Quick, report it in!” While the Sage Committee which controlled Sky City had their own methods of detection, as their subordinates, they had to do their utmost as well.

The burly man from before looked like he had just woken up as he snarled, “What are you standing there like that for? Report it in, and follow me to welcome him!”

“No need for that.” A white-gold flash appeared in the control room.

“Lord Boffel!” The staff of the control room immediately bowed to the man.

“He comes with good intentions and doesn’t want to act ostentatiously. I’ll see to him myself. Go back to your posts and forget about this!” The white-gold light spoke and diverged into many rays of light.

“Good, good! With our Morning Star taking over, anything that happens next isn’t our problem!” The burly man sighed, hands behind his back as he left the control room.

The other members in the control room looked relieved as they sat back down. The young man who had reported this earlier continued to work diligently, concealing the envy and feverish look in his eyes.

*Boom!* The Colossal Serpent steadily descended atop a lawn with a large rune on it, not flipping up any dust.

“Is it Lord Leylin? Welcome!” Due to the urgent message just now, there was no staff member around. A young man with platinum hair and wings of light similar to the wings of angels stood under the elevating platform of the airship.

“I am Leylin Farlier. You are…?” The door opened and Leylin walked out, looking friendly.

Though Gilbert had suggested that he sneak in and conceal his identity, Leylin wanted the title of a Virtuous Sky Sage in Sky City, and he would need to make contact with the Endowing Scepter. He would definitely be interrogated thoroughly and would even attract the attention of the Monarch of the Skies. How could he conceal himself?

Hence, Leylin had chosen to step forward without any tricks. The title of a Virtuous Sky Sage from Sky City was an honour open to all Magi of the central continent, and large numbers of scholars would be attracted here. It was not shameful in any way that he wanted to obtain this.

Chapter 591: Great Library

“Let’s go! Leylin watched Weyers as he left and brought Yuro with him. He had yet to arrive at his intended destination, which was the Great Library. To him, whatever just happened was like a circus act and nothing more.

When Leylin’s figure had disappeared as well, the remaining Magi present immediately got up, their faces full of grime.

Being affected by the battle out of nowhere and being suppressed by a Morning Star domain for a long time had now left them in a pitiful state.

Afterwards, the officials who had arrived slowly began to tidy up the roads and calculated the losses. Everything was methodical and thorough.

“Gill!” back in the office, Weyers’ voice was low. The arrogance from before had completely vanished.

“Master!” A black shadow silently surfaced from the floor.

“Investigate this! Who’s responsible for the incident at the Floating Feather Avenue? Who was it that did this on my watch?” Weyers’ voice was frigid as he spoke in a discerning manner.

“Understood!” The black figure answered and withdrew noiselessly.

Once Weyers was alone in the room, he frowned. He began to sift through the memories of the day’s events, and a cold smirk appeared on his lips. “Trying to use me as cannon fodder, eh? Good! Very good!”

How many among those who had reached the Morning Star realm were fools? No matter how young he looked, even if he seemed like a child, Weyers had lived for almost a hundred years. It was clear to him what had happened.

Provoking a Morning Star Magus just for some false reputation? He would not do anything so stupid. Even if his backing could take on the backlash, pointless actions should be avoided if possible.

“That Warlock Leylin from today was quite interesting. Like me, he’s being bound by some pointless reputation.” Through the events that had occurred that day, Weyers had formed a favourable impression of Leylin.

He was currently enraged at the person who had set up this situation. “Perhaps I’ve been keeping a low profile for too long, and some people have begun to think I’m an easy target…” he muttered to himself after a long period of silence. The temperature dropped as his voice sounded, and the place turned into an icy wonderland…

Of course, Leylin was not aware of any of this. After Weyers had left, he had arrived at the Great Library under Yuro’s guidance.

“Truth is my calling!” “The pursuit of knowledge is the foundation of all strength.”

Leylin was currently observing a large number of statues in a seemingly boundless palace. They were proportionate, and so detailed one could differentiate the strands of hair on their bodies. It made them seem lifelike.

The pedestals under these statues held information like their time periods, maxims, achievements and the like.

Leylin turned his attention to the time period of the central statue after reading its maxim. “Illesme. Year 1327–?”

“Just a birth date, and no death date. Could he have lived for over five thousand years?’ Leylin stared at this statue in astonishment. He saw a kindly old man there, a spotless white beard floating in front of his chest. A pair of wise eyes hid behind circular rimmed glasses.

“This is the Great Sage, Lord Illesme. He was the first generation ruler of Sky City and is a Breaking Dawn Magus. While his whereabouts are currently unknown, many still believe that he is alive, and is perhaps risking his life exploring foreign worlds…” Yuro was full of admiration as she made the introduction.

“Mm!” Leylin had seen some information regarding this Great Sage, but those were all mixed in with legends and rumours. None had been as specific as the base of the statue.

He circled the forest of statues with interest, finding that only Morning Star Magi and above were allowed here. They were scholars who had made significant contributions to Sky City or the Magus World.

There was a small number of Magi who were like Illesme, with only a birth but no death date.

This meant there was a good possibility of them still being alive, perhaps stuck in foreign worlds or ancient spell formations. However, if they were to appear as a group, the strength they possessed was enough for the entire central continent to tremble.

“Without the contributions of the past sages, there would not be the Magi of today!”

Leylin looked solemn as he bowed to the many statues, “I, Leylin Farlier, shall complete all your unfinished work, and resolve all regrets!”

Of course, he could only say this inside his mind. If Yuro heard it, things would be slightly troublesome.

Though the continent was full of ambitious Magi, there were few as egotistical as Leylin.

After they paid their respects, Yuro brought Leylin to the entrance of what seemed like a greek temple. “My Lord, here is the entrance to the Great Library. The collection here in the Sky City is open to all Magi with no restrictions.”

What surprised Leylin was that the entrance to the library had no doors, nor were there any guards. Everyone could move about freely.

A comfortable warm glow from eternal light spells filled the area.

Magi would pass by Leylin every once in a while, but while there were quite a few of them, they were generally very quiet.

Yuro spoke in a low voice by Leylin’s ear. “The Great Library is set up above a gigantic spell formation and is being managed by a sentient spirit genie. It’s in charge of all management, and while there aren’t any guards stationed here, there has never been an incident thus far!”

“There’s never been an incident here?” Leylin nodded. This meant that on top of the basic effects of repelling dust, moisture and flames, the gigantic spell formation also possessed an exceedingly more powerful defensive ability.

“Yes! Rumour has it that the defensive spell formation of the Great Library can even confine a Morning Star…” She was apprehensive while she spoke, peeking at Leylin while afraid he would grow angry. However, Leylin remained calm, and Yuro could not tell if he was happy or annoyed.

“Not bad! My expectation on the information here has risen further now!”

With the spirit genie managing the area, every single corner of the library was probably being monitored. With the ability to suppress even Morning Stars and the Magi of Sky City being ready to provide support very quickly if anything were to happen, there seemed to be an impenetrable defence. There was obviously a vast amount of information.

There was a large bright hall past the entrance that could hold over a thousand people without becoming crowded. At the middle were hundreds of tables, and what looked like terminals.

“The Great Library is separated into seven levels. The first three are open to all Magi, and you can browse through once you pay a certain number of magic crystals. The information and documents at the fourth level and above are kept very confidential, and one can only browse through them using information points.”

Leylin stood aside, watching a Magus operating the system. After inserting pure magic crystals into the terminal and using spiritual force to interface with it, he took out a blank crystal ball at the opening of another device. Large amounts of information was transmitted, instantly filling the crystal ball up with information.

“Transmission of data, as well as a backup!” Leylin shouted in surprise. Thankfully, the terminal could not directly send information to the Magus’ memory, or Leylin would be worried that something like the A.I. Chip existed in this world.

“Yes! As long as it’s information that the spirit genie has a backup of, it can be duplicated using the terminal. Of course, there is a required fee.”

Some information was stored in certain special materials, and it could only be presented in that specific format. For example, there were some books that the spirit genie was unable to make a duplicate of, and required that one read using the physical copy.

Leylin now had so many magic crystals that he cared little for them. He asked Yuro, “How do I obtain information points?”

“There are two methods. One is to complete missions by the Sage Committee. The second is to furnish the spirit genie’s inner library with information it still does not possess. One will be awarded information points based on the value of the added information.”

Yuro laughed wryly, “But I don’t recommend the second method. This could have been possible in the early days, but with the addition by generations of Magi, there’s very little information that the Great Library has yet to obtain…”

After hearing how the library operated, Leylin was quiet for a long while and took a deep breath. “How bold!” he exclaimed. Even the first three levels being made public showed how bold they were.

The system of information points conversion also allowed the library to become more abundant in information, and by this point, it had accumulated a vast trove of knowledge.

Such a huge amassment of information had allowed Sky City to withstand the test of time. Considering it one of the strongest organisations in the central continent was not even a stretch.

Yuro brought Leylin to a terminal. After paying the magic crystals, she passed a white crystal card to Leylin. “This is a blank crystal card. Every newcomer here will obtain one!

“You may choose to seal it with your spiritual force, or you can leave it open. However, you will then need to keep your crystal card properly, or else anyone can choose to use it!”

With a sweep of Leylin’s soul force, the library card began to emit a black luster. He placed the card in a small depression, and the terminal’s screen instantly brightened.

A few lines in a familiar script appeared on it and gave him a few choices.

Leylin did not try to skim through the table of contents, but instead chose to obtain information points through providing data.

Though Yuro mentioned that the database was already quite complete, Leylin was confident. His A.I. Chip had a lot of information regarding the Lava World! The Great Library couldn’t have information from foreign worlds, could it?

Chapter 592: Shocking Accumulation

[Beep! Spiritual force data connection detected, proceed with transmission?]

The A.I. Chip intoned.

Although Leylin had placed a crystal ball on the transmission port of the terminal, he was actually mobilizing his A.I. Chip for it instead.

“Try this first!” Leylin selected a piece of information regarding the one-horned clan of the Lava World and uploaded it.

“Serial number ZXC678 has chosen to contribute information. Processing…” A progress bar suddenly appeared on the terminal screen.

As the progress bar reached completion, it was replaced with new content.

“Helix Tree composite image: 89% complete! Initial inventory: 40% complete! Effectiveness: 51%! Initializing fusion of data… Helix Tree composite image: 91% complete! Your contribution has been evaluated and you will be awarded 26 information points!”

*Whoosh!* A golden light flashed, and the number 26 appeared in a new row on Leylin’s library card.

He drew a sharp breath. ‘It even contains knowledge from such a remote place as the Lava World, even if it’s flawed…’

After a moment of thought, though, he came to a realisation, “The ancient Magus World was in control of a great number of other worlds. Sky City obtained a portion of the ancient world’s database, so it’s no strange matter that it contains some pieces of flawed content!”

After that one attempt, Leylin had to restrain his excitement. “I’ll be living here from now, so don’t disturb me unnecessarily,” he instructed Yuro. Soon after, he left the dumbfounded maid alone and buried his head into the sea of knowledge.

The huge library in Sky City could be said to have everything. Its information was not limited to that about the central continent; there was data about other worlds as well.

Further in from the data terminals and the hall was the gigantic library that resembled a palace. Some sort of technique had been employed to expand the space within. At a glimpse, one would see bookshelves as massive as mountains, all so densely packed and numerous that there seemed to be no end.

Leylin was now standing at the foot of a bookshelf that was tens of metres tall. The giant wooden ladder brought him in front of a row of little black catalogues as per his wish.

“Mm! Raphael’s Poetic Saga!” Leylin nodded, his eyes glistening.

“The many ancient myths and legends actually contain a large amount of intelligence, it’s just that those who recorded these accounts have beautified and romanticised them. Thus, we have to separate the wheat from the chaff in order to obtain the most accurate information. Raphael was a famous poet in ancient times, yet he also had a hidden identity as a Magus. Therefore, all the accounts that he recorded have high research value…” Leylin muttered to himself as his eyes glistened. He fingered through the numerous volume numbers of a series of books and stopped when he reached volume 239.

When he tried to pull out the book, the robotic voice of the spirit genie rang in his mind, “Beep! You are requesting to read Raphael’s Poetic Saga, Volume 239. Fee is 2 information points. Do you wish to proceed?”

“Yes!” With a motion of Leylin’s soul force, 2 information points were automatically deducted from his library card. The energy that had been protecting Raphael’s Poetic Saga also disappeared suddenly, allowing Leylin to remove the book easily from the shelf.

He clicked his tongue. “Although I know that library books of grade 3 and above are very expensive, even these mere historical records have such exorbitant costs…”

Leylin shook his head. The wooden ladder, as though a living creature, automatically transported him onto the ground.

Leylin was now in the fifth storey of the library, which was much quieter than the previous levels he had been to. There was practically no one there, and beside the tens of bookshelves, there would always be a small area where Magi could peruse the books.

Leylin found a random chair and sat down as he began to flip open the jet black cover of Raphael’s Poetic Saga.

“I have come…. I can see…”

The pages of the book were a dazzling flame-like red. The words, especially, were like fire sprites, jumping around the pages.

‘A.I. Chip, record this!’ Leylin commanded inwardly.

[Assignment established, beginning scan! Beep! Raphael’s Poetic Saga, Volume 239 discovered. Supplementing Raphael’s Poetic Saga in the history folder!]

The robotic voice of the A.I. Chip sounded. Seconds later, the entirety of Raphael’s Poetic Saga had been recorded.

“I’ve been searching high and low for this portion of Raphael’s Poetic Saga, and was lacking just these few volumes. Who would have thought that this huge library would actually contain the full set! Now that it has been supplemented…”

An expression of satisfaction surfaced across Leylin’s face. As a bonus, he had discovered the shortcomings of the spirit genie and the data terminal.

Through data transmission, the spirit genie could only fully engrave low grade data records into crystals. However, Magi would still have to obtain the knowledge within them through studying them, unlike the A.I. Chip which was able to directly transmit information to one’s memory.

Comparing the time consumed by the two methods, the disparity was rather frightening. This further proved that the A.I. Chip’s operational and analytical abilities were far better than that of the spirit genie.

Moreover, content that was at grade 3 and above were mostly engraved using the Magus’ own energy. The materials the books were made of were also very special. The spirit genie was unable to duplicate such information, and thus Magi had to come down personally to study the content from the physical book itself.

“Even so, this huge library is still rather overwhelming!” As compared to his previous database, the amount of information in the entire library was seemingly like a vast ocean—boundless. It was incomparably enriching. Leylin felt like a person who was nearly dying from thirst being thrown into a freshwater lake all of a sudden. He absorbed all the content as though his life depended on it, and never stepped a foot out of the place.

The same went for the A.I. Chip. As its database grew with even more detailed and complex subjects, its technical ability was supplemented unceasingly.

The copious amount of information in here formed a foundation for all disciplines of magic scholarship.

Leylin had a premonition that the numerous resources he had amassed this time would result in a relatively drastic upgrade for the A.I. Chip. After this upgrade, he would definitely reap harvests that he would not have even dreamed of before!

[Beep! Supplementation of foundational information complete. Refreshing and restarting system, estimated time: 2 hours, 34 minutes and 13 seconds!]

The A.I. Chip prompted, startling Leylin.

“It actually grew to such an extent? What surprises will be the renewed database bring me?” This was a happy occasion, and Leylin’s face almost lit up with delight.

“Indeed, I made the right choice to come to Sky City. Even if not for the Endowing Scepter, I just had to make this trip.”

Although there was loads of information in the huge library, Leylin felt that content that was grade 3 and below were the most important. This was because he possessed a near unlimited amount of magic crystals, and coupled with the data terminal the convenience of information transmission was unparalleled. In just a short span of time, the foundational information that could be duplicated by the spirit genie had all been backed up into the A.I. Chip.

As for more advanced content that was above grade 3, Leylin had tossed out all his information to the spirit genie—as long as it was eligible for conversion and would not attract any trouble, of course. This allowed him to exchange his data for a monumental amount of information points. He then specifically searched for topics that Warlocks and the A.I. Chip lacked information on before commanding the A.I. Chip to scan and record it.

With the A.I. Chip, a large amount of academic content could be derived from just the foundational information alone. No matter how high the grade, the content could still be deduced.

After all, now that he already had a great foundation, all that was left was to perform derivations that would consume copious amounts of operational energy.

Leylin used his information points to directly access the content that the A.I. Chip did not have the ability to derive, thus completing his database.

In this manner, within the short span of a month or so, he had already recorded roughly all of the content in the huge library.

One must know that even Radiant Moons, Breaking Dawns and other Magi or scholars who grew up in Sky City wouldn’t be able to remember so much. The excessive accumulated information would have conflicting information, causing the Magus to forget some things. They would have to constantly refresh their memory.

With their standards, being able to remember all the grade 1 and 2 information would mean that one was an absolute genius. Leylin, however, had exceeded them by leaps and bounds. He’d accumulated a lifetime of information!

If others knew about his terrifying rate of progress, Leylin would definitely attract a lot of trouble. Thus, he could only be secretly satisfied with himself, not revealing anything.

“When the A.I. Chip is done refreshing, I’m afraid that I will be worthy of being called the most learned person throughout the entire central continent, and will be knowledgeable about even the research done in other worlds…”

Leylin had now thoroughly understood the meaning of the phrase “knowledge is power!”

While his further studies did not increase his strength by a single bit, the underlying effect on his foundation was truly terrifying.

“This is just right! The information points are mostly spent, so I might as well use up all of the remaining ones as well!

Leylin fished out his library card, the thin lines of golden numbers immensely glaring. They couldn’t be compared to the single long line of numbers on his card previously. The astronomical number of information points had only lasted him a month or so.

*Crash!* Opposite Leylin’s desk, a female Magus raised her head and peered over her book curiously, gazing at Leylin’s back. A pair of spectacles with thick lenses was perched on the bridge of her nose, and her hair was tied in two braids.

She had been paying attention to this strange Magus in front of her for a long time now.

He didn’t seem to lack information points, which could be seen from how he often referred to thick stacks of resources. Even if she worked all day and night for a month without rest, she wouldn’t be able to earn the amount of information points required for such information.

After selecting his resources, he didn’t read the information carefully, but instead flipped through it briefly before casually casting it aside. This made her heart ache.

Library resources that were grade 3 and above were only for private browsing in the reading room. They couldn’t be brought out of the library or exchanged with others. Under the supervision of the spirit genie, there were no loopholes.

Thus, this female Magus could only drool with envy at the mountains of resources Leylin had acquired with his information points, and couldn’t do a single thing about it.

Without the scanning abilities of the A.I. Chip, Leylin could only depend on reading the resources himself to obtain knowledge. Thus, he chose a book on how to optimise one’s vitality, and laid back in his chair as he slowly started to read.

The eternal light spell was adjusted by the spirit genie, gently tuning the light rays for a better reading experience. Time ticked by along with the rustling sound of the pages turning.

‘This odd Magus is finally acting normal!’ The female Magus secretly nodded, then continued to immerse herself in her books. Time was precious, and she could not afford to waste any of it.

Chapter 593: Soul Profiling

[Beep! Database has been refreshed. Update completed.]

After Leylin had flipped through about half of the book in his hands, the A.I. Chip which had gone silent for a while suddenly sounded out.

“Good! Let’s see if there are any differences in the upgraded A.I. Chip!” His attention immediately wandered from the book, and he focused on his A.I. Chip.

[Beep! Database on soul force is complete. Beginning collection of host’s data, recalculating.]

The first prompt that the A.I. Chip gave had Leylin elated.

“So soul force has finally been enumerated…” He had been at a loss due to the A.I. Chip’s inability to enumerate soul force for a very long time. All this while, he had collected a lot of information on the soul, and performed many experiments and thought of numerous conjectures. However, all that had not been able to complete the database on the soul.

Now, the A.I. Chip had completely deduced this information.

“Show me my current stats!” Leylin immediately commanded.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 4 Warlock. Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent (complete form). Strength: 50, Agility: 45, Vitality: 74.9, Spiritual Force: 956.8, Magic Power: 956 (magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force). Soul force: 96 (Five Star)]

The A.I. Chip intoned.

“96 soul force? What does ‘five star’ mean?” Leylin asked.

Soon after, a passage of information was shown by the A.I. Chip,

[The star rating is a method that the Sky City has come up with to evaluate Morning Stars, based on organisms in the astral plane. Newly-advanced Morning Stars are at one star, while the peak is at five stars…]

“I see. What beings are used as the standard?” Leylin wasn’t that interested in this star system. Instead, he was rather tempted to perform research on the organisms that had been set to be the standards for Morning Star Magi.

[The organisms that have been set as the standard are the beings of the astral plane— the Heavenly Astral Race! At birth, they possess strength at the Morning Star realm, and it’s unknown how powerful they can become. The race was wiped out during ancient times. The Magi of Sky City obtained some of the data from ancient times, which is how it became the standard when it came to evaluating strength!]

“Heavenly Astral Race? Beings from the astral plane? Morning Stars at birth?!”

This piece of information had Leylin completely stunned. Never did he expect there to be dwellers in a place like the astral plane, and they were even so powerful that they had Morning Star strength right from birth.

If compared to the Heavenly Astral Race, Giant Kemoyin Serpents could only cry. Their end point was this race’s beginning! There was no way to begin to compare them since they weren’t even on the same level.

“Even such gifted creatures went extinct. Looks like the events during the ancient times were unfathomable…” Leylin sighed deeply.

[Acquired information on a standard individual of the Heavenly Astral Race. Change standards?]

Leylin’s current system of measurement used the standards from his previous world, which was why the numbers in each attribute seemed to be so phenomenally high, especially since they were calculated with regular humans in mind. If he used the standard criteria of the Heavenly Astral Race, his stats would immediately drop sharply.

Compared to before, with the standard strength of a regular person at 1, this was now compared with the terrifying strength of a Heavenly Astral Race at 1. There would obviously be a marked difference in quantity.

‘Changing the measurement units? Let’s try!’ Leylin touched his chin. “Display it!”

[Beep!]

A blue light flashed, and the numbers immediately changed before Leylin.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 4 Warlock. Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent (complete form). Strength: 1.5, Agility: 1.2, Vitality: 2.7, Spiritual force: 4.3 Soul force: 4.3 (Five Star)]

Seeing the numbers that had decreased drastically, Leylin was rendered speechless.

‘In other words, my strength and agility are only slightly higher than a Heavenly Astral Race at Morning Star. My vitality is twice that of theirs, while my spiritual and soul force are more than four times greater. All in all, I can take on two or three of them at once?’

This comparison had stunned Leylin. He was now considered to be at the apex amongst Morning Stars in the central continent. He could even rival a Radiant Moon, and yet he was only slightly stronger than a child of the Heavenly Astral Race?

This was quite a blow to his ego.

“Forget it! Show the numbers according to the units from before. At the very least, the smaller the base numbers, the higher the precision!” Leylin stroked his chin, ‘When the numbers in all aspects increase by a large amount, I’ll then begin using the units of the Heavenly Astral Race. That’s better!’

With a flicker from the A.I. Chip, all his data reverted to the original.

[Display host’s soul diagram?]

At this moment, the A.I. Chip showed another prompt.

“Of course!” Leylin did not hesitate at all. After the soul force database was completed, his grasp on soul force was even greater, and he could do things that would have been very difficult before.

One of these included the structural diagram of his soul.

*Bzz!* A diagram that had been magnified countless times was projected in front of Leylin’s eyes.

His soul, which was also the truesoul of a Morning Star, was protected within the point mass. The point mass’ terrifying density and strength was the last defensive layer protecting a Morning Star’s truesoul.

There were few Magi who could clearly observe their own truesouls within their point mass, and make appropriate changes to train the soul. In fact, there were practically none.

With the help of the A.I. Chip, he could finally pass through this barrier.

In the diagram, Leylin’s truesoul was like a tiny star, emanating bright rays of light, with a tinge of crimson within. It was as if a crimson Giant Kemoyin Serpent was cruising inside the thing.

[Beep! Host’s soul composition is loose and not dense enough. Suggestion…]

Through the diagram and the A.I. Chip’s analysis, Leylin’s issues when training the soul were made apparent, and the A.I. Chip gave concrete suggestions.

If other Morning Star Magi were to know of this, they’d want to commit suicide out of envy.

When had the mysteries of the soul ever been displayed before Magi?

‘It was probably because of the hasty infusion of Fireplume.’ Leylin stroked his chin, ‘Luckily, I can still salvage the situation through the improved meditation technique.’

Every three ranks in training as a Magus was a major hurdle. The first to third focused on training spiritual force, and the fourth to sixth on the soul. If problems with the soul were not resolved now, there would be huge issues during his future advancements.

However, this was not the end of the surprises that the A.I. Chip had to offer.

[Beep! To generate a conjecture of Radiant Moon soul and compare it to a diagram?]

The A.I. Chip asked robotically,

“Yes!” Leylin obviously chose that option.

Afterwards, beside his soul diagram, a few other similar ones appeared, marking out the initial, middle, and late stages of Radiant Moon.

In the diagram, the difference between Morning Stars and Radiant Moons was made obvious. The soul of a Morning Star was similar to a star, dazzling and condensed, but a Radiant Moon who had just advanced had a soul that was tens of times larger than that of a Morning Star, forming a large and full sphere.

In other words, it resembled the moon.

As for the Radiant Moon stages, those who had just advanced had souls which only emanated bright rays from a small portion of its full area. The rest of the moon was dim, forming a crescent. It was like a new moon being blocked by the sun.

Magi at the middle stage of Radiant Moon had half their soul emanating clear rays, like a half moon. Peak Radiant Moon Magi had light that was dazzling and transparent, like a full moon.

“Name these stages New Moon, Half Moon and Full Moon!” Leylin did not hesitate to label these Radiant Moon stages.

Of course, his soul was now merely a star and was a large distance away from reaching Radiant Moon.

‘There were mistakes in my previous conjectures. Zegna was probably merely a New Moon, while Scarlet Eye was at most a Half Moon. He had yet to achieve the peak, Full Moon!’

Leylin’s eyes suddenly flashed with understanding. He had not obtained the twelfth and thirteenth levels of Fireplume, so it was plausible that the fourteenth level could still be at the Radiant Moon realm, and was representative of the soul reaching Full Moon.

‘In that case, the road from rank 4 to rank 5 has completely unravelled in front of me!’ Leylin looked ecstatic. The third and fourth ranks had a very large disparity between them, with spiritual force upgrading to soul force. There was another huge gap between rank six and seven, with soul force upgrading to the manifestation and wielding of Laws. Hence, all these gaps were immense and usually caused tremendous changes.

Advancing from rank 3 to 6, one’s training was mostly on the soul, because it was the level of one’s soul that signified one’s strength.

“First is Morning Star, where the soul becomes a tiny star, with power from one star up to five. Next are the New Moon, Half Moon and Full Moon phases at the Radiant Moon realm!”

The path through Morning Star and Radiant Moon were completely presented before Leylin.

‘That’s basically it. Of course, there might be some odd geniuses at the apex who break through these boundaries, but in general, that’s how this is divided.

‘This upgrade was definitely worth it! Even just the completion of the soul force database alone would have been enough, not to mention the rest.’

An expression of elation rose on Leylin’s face as he could not hold himself back and burst into laughter.

“My Lord!” At this moment, Yuro’s voice travelled over. It was very low, and she was obviously afraid of disturbing the other scholars.

“Mm?” Leylin turned back and saw Boffel behind her.

“Haha! So Your Grace has been staying in the library all this while. Such a thirst for knowledge is definitely admirable, but the Sage Appraisal is about to begin. Besides, the Monarch of Skies would like to meet Your Grace…”

Boffel had on an amiable smile, while the female Magus beside him looked rather flabbergasted.

Chapter 594: Stuart

‘Boffel? Could it be the ‘Divine Luminescent Wing’? And calling him ‘Your Grace’? Isn’t that a title used in ancient times for Morning Stars? And the Monarch of the Skies? Oh, goodness. Could this Magus be a Morning Star as well?’

The female Magus who had a pair of thick glasses on peeked at Leylin, feeling like he was as unfathomable as the mountains and the seas. She could not help but lower her head, feeling ashamed at her previous conjectures.

Boffel did not spare her a glance. Since violence could not be employed in the library, the usage of Morning Star domains was restricted. She could hear some of what they were saying, but since this was an honest conversation there was nothing to be hidden anyway.

“Oh, my apologies. The information here is just so abundant that I forgot about the time!” Leylin stood up, looking apologetic.

“Anyone who disturbs a Magus immersed in the ocean of knowledge should have their souls scorched in the flames of the ninth hell. Why would I mind?” Boffel had a very witty way of speech, and Leylin immediately formed a better impression of him.

Boffel was not at all surprised about Leylin staying in the library all day. Many scholarly Magi would treat the Great Library as their home upon reaching Sky City for the first time. There were people who stayed within from a few months to even decades, and if not for having too little information points, they would even stay there for their whole lives! Compared to these people, Leylin had only been there for a month, which was very normal. Boffel felt that he seemed to have too many information points, but then again, considering he had just returned from a foreign world, he must have gained large amounts of knowledge from it, so this was understandable.

“Alright. I shall head there now.”

Leylin placed the book back in its original position. He had reaped a great harvest this time, and the Great Library currently did not have anything especially useful to him. Besides, the Monarch of the Skies had summoned him, and it was best that he tidy himself up. This was a necessary part of etiquette.

“And you, earnest young lady!” Leylin shot a glance at the female Magus who only wished she could hide behind her book.

“Your Grace, Boffel, and this… your Grace. Please forgive me for my offensive behaviour!” Cold sweat was already dripping from the female Magus’ forehead.

Though Sky City was a peaceful area that paid attention to the law, Morning Stars always had privileges. The moment Leylin or Boffel found her an eye sore, she would wind up in a pitiful state even if they didn’t act themselves.

“Haha… don’t be afraid! I want to thank you for accompanying me while I studied for this past month. Treat this as a gift!”

Leylin laughed, and the library card in his hands flew out. Scanning the female Magus’ library card, he transferred his remaining information points to her.

The Great Library now held little meaning for Leylin, which was why there was no point in having these information points with him.

“This…” Though Leylin felt that the number of information points left was pitifully low, to the point that it had almost hit zero, this was still a gigantic amount for the female Magus! She immediately cried out in surprise.

By the time she had recovered from her shock and wanted to thank Leylin, she found that they had long since left.

“Your Grace’s act of providing financial aid to other Magi is truly admirable!” Boffel could not understand Leylin’s actions, since the information on him showed that Leylin was not someone so charitable.

“Hehe… I’m just in a good mood!” Leylin chuckled.

This explanation rendered Boffel completely at ease. Warlocks were truly a group of Magi who were very emotional. In such good moods from the benefits from the library, they could indeed reward any low-ranking Magi as they wished. This unusual situation lost all strangeness when Warlocks were involved.

Boffel did not pay much attention to Leylin’s momentary act of kindness, and instead brought to attention some things to take note of when meeting the Monarch of the Skies.

“I don’t get it…” Leylin immediately asked Boffel, “I’m merely a Morning Star. Why would the Monarch of the Skies want to see me?”

The other party was a Breaking Dawn Magus with influence all over the central continent. He had complete control of the airship networks, and possessed a foreign world of his own that had been completely taken over. The Morning Stars and Radiant Moons under him were innumerable.

This sort of person should, by right, be far superior to him. Why was there the sudden desire to meet Leylin?

Leylin had once had the idea of making a trade with the coordinates of the Lava World, but he’d never once expressed these thoughts.

‘Something’s suspicious…’ Leylin stroked his chin and immediately, Jupiter’s Lightning came to mind. It could not be helped. He had few enemies in the central continent, and Zegna was the only one of them could influence the organisation behind Sky City.

‘I was just worried you wouldn’t come!’ A smirk appeared about Leylin’s lips.

The heart of Sky City was a large-scale floating garden, forming the ‘floating’ landscape that gave the title of the floating city.

This garden— the Drifting Garden— was the heart of Sky CIty’s power. It was also the temporary imperial residence of His Majesty, the Monarch of the Skies.

“This is Boffel. Step aside.” Boffel flew all the way to the Drifting Garden with Leylin in tow. The Warlock had tidied up and was now dressed in formal attire.

The deeper into Sky City one went, the more the instances of probing and detection, to the point that Leylin’s expression changed slightly. If not for Boffel guiding him, it would have been inconvenient for him to sneak into the Drifting Garden without being detected.

Looking down from the edges of the Drifting Garden, one could see all the sights of Sky City. It left one’s heart free and unfettered.

Further in was a cobbled lane. On both sides of the path were Devil Fungi Taro, Heavenly Intoxicating Nectar, and large amounts of other precious plants that Leylin did not even know the names of. They were numerous, and all in full bloom. If not for the A.I. Chip detecting powerful shackling runes there, Leylin would have had plans of taking a bunch.

“After walking through this area, we will arrive at His Majesty’s residing quarters. I can only accompany you up to this point.” Boffel laughed as he spoke, “His Majesty is a very amiable person, and he’ll definitely…”

“Boffel, you seem to have brought someone new here. That’s against the rules!” Another voice sounded, and Leylin especially went stiff, feeling like he was being stared at by a poisonous snake.

“You!” He raised his head, seeing what looked to be a kindly old Magus approaching them.

“Lord Stuart! This is Duke Leylin Farlier of the Ouroboros Clan, here to meet His Majesty.” Boffel bowed. At the same time, he introduced the person to Leylin in a quiet voice, “This is Lord Stuart, a Radiant Moon Magus. Since His Majesty is often absent, he is usually in charge of managing Sky City…”

“So it’s Lord Stuart!” Leylin bowed, neither too enthusiastic nor too cold. His sensitive soul immediately found a trace of ill intent directed at him. In that case, he wouldn’t bother being too cordial.

“Hm?!” Such an attitude rapidly increased the distaste that Stuart already had. He did not hold back and began to criticise Leylin. “As expected, it’s a little chap with no manners. Is it really alright for this kind of person to meet with His Majesty?”

“Lord Stuart, Leylin is a treasured guest of our Sky City.” Boffel coughed and answered with a warning. Stuart’s attitude was obviously biased, and he could not watch further.

“Your Highness, Stuart, you are in no position to judge whether I have any manners!” Leylin retorted without restraint.

This immediately left Boffel dumbfounded. This was a Radiant Moon, a great rank 5 Magus! In Sky City, he had tens of thousands of subordinates under him, and yet, Leylin was not giving him any face?

In actuality, if the other party was merely a little arrogant, Leylin did not mind humbling himself and treating him the way he did Weyers. However, Stuart was obviously here to create trouble, finding Leylin an eyesore before even meeting him. No matter how much Leylin tried to endure this, he would only be humiliated, and all for nothing. There was therefore no reason to be courteous.

“Good! I’ll teach you some manners right now!” Hearing Leylin’s tone, Stuart was evidently exasperated. Never did he expect a Morning Star like Leylin to speak to him in such a manner!

*Rumble!* Formless soul force was like a raging sea as it gushed towards Leylin.

He had intentionally controlled the might of the spell, such that it affected only this small area. With Stuart’s control, he was confident that he could keep the battlefield within the area and not alarm anyone else.

Boffel could only laugh wryly. While he did agree that Stuart had gone too far, he only stood aside.

“Hmph! Is a rank 5 so fantastic?” Leylin sneered, his soul force that had reached five stars surging forth.

The gigantic phantom of a Giant Kemoyin Serpent with scarlet lines on it appeared behind him, hissing at Stuart.

“Hss!” The ferocious soul tide formed a gigantic black snake, colliding fiercely with Stuart’s soul force.

“Hm?!” Stuart’s eyes widened, not expecting to have difficulties in dealing with Leylin. ‘Five star soul force? Didn’t the intel say four stars?’

Crackling sounds rang out as the two bouts of soul force cancelled each other after the collision. The forces that went astray caused an explosion.

*Pak! Pak! Pak!* The sounds of countless runic chains breaking could be heard. The concealing spell formations that Stuart had previously set up were completely broken through!

“Urgh!” Leylin staggered backwards, face completely red.

Stuart, on the other hand, stood completely still as he stared at Leylin expressionlessly, not intending to pursue this fight.

The strength of this Morning Star before him had exceeded his expectations, and he was a five star Warlock! It would take a large amount of time and energy to take him down.

What was even worse was that this would not be hidden from His Majesty, and Stuart’s expression turned dark.

Chapter 597: Hot on the Heels

“Rescanning. Confirmed to be a Morning Star Magus!” As the spirit genie’s voice rang out, the person in charge was silenced. One instance could be considered a glitch, but what if it happened a second or third time?

He watched the figure on the screen in disbelief, “What level is he at? Display his star grade!”

The screen quickly changed, “Target is Leylin Farlier. Saved data: Four Stars.”

“What a joke! Rescan him.” He was practically yelling at this point.

*Swish!* An energy bar appeared, and the four star level was filled almost instantly. The meter arrived at five stars.

“So it’s a peak Morning Star. It’s no wonder that he can contend with Lord Stuart. But don’t worry, he can’t hold on for long…”

He sighed suddenly, but immediately after, the monitoring staff pulled him to look at the screen once more. In that moment, he practically turned to stone.

On the screen, the meter filled up even the five star grade, and then burst through it!

The screen glitched out and was restarted. The spirit genie then gave another evaluation.

“A Morning Star at the Six Star grade! It’s a monster, a monster!” He collapsed feebly onto his chair.

“My Lord! What do we do?” The staff watched the man in charge, hesitating to speak.

“What else can we do? Activate the most powerful defences and ensure that their battle won’t affect any other regions. We can’t handle the other matters…” The man’s eyes rolled back as he lost consciousness.

Weyers was on the battlefield, and he slowly gained more clarity on Leylin’s strength.

“This level of strength…” Weyers watched the giant phantom of a serpent soaring through the sky as it let loose terrifying sounds. He had become slightly dazed, “This is definitely stronger than a Five Star. Is he a legendary Six Star Morning Star?”

There were only five normal ranks for Morning Stars. However, history always produced frightening geniuses that defied common sense. This was the Six Star grade! A Morning Star who could match up to a Radiant Moon!

“He’s actually reached this level?” Weyers clutched his fists tightly, thinking about his pride at breaking through to Four Stars, and he suddenly flushed red. He wanted to find a place to hide in.

*Swish! Swish!* Large numbers of elites rushed over, looking solemn and preparing for death.

Platinum flames flashed, and Weyers stood in their way, “I’ll take over here. Step back for now.”

Though he was envious, he still had to abide by their agreement. Weyers watched these guards and the Morning Star that arrived behind them in a lofty manner, and offered his greetings…

*Boom!* A tremendous energy tornado split open, and a blackened Stuart was ruthlessly sent flying as he arrived beside Weyers.

Leylin threw the Morning Star Magus to the ground, the black gas already completely removed from him.

“It’s a Magus from Jupiter’s Lightning!” “The spirit undulations are correct as well. I’ve seen him once before, and those can’t be hidden!”

Many Morning Stars looked at each other.

“Everyone can see that Lord Leylin was merely attacking the Magus from the opposing organisation, Jupiter’s Lightning. Based on the decree of the Monarch of the Skies, our Sky City is to maintain a neutral stance,” Weyers stood up and spoke righteously.

Many Morning Star Magi exchanged glances, and watched Leylin who did not back down despite his injuries. In the distance, Stuart looked exasperated as he maintained his silence.

Leylin and Weyers glanced at each other, grinning. The outcome had been decided.

Information about this huge battle in Sky City spread like a storm.

The Warlock Leylin took on a Radiant Moon Magus by himself, only suffering light injuries to capture a Morning Star Magus from the other party. His name spread far and wide, and Stuart had been delegated to a supporting role.

The commotion grew further and further, dwarfing that over the Sage Appraisal.

Now, Weyers watched on as a black airship left Sky City from a private port. A strange expression was on his face.

The person leaving was naturally Leylin. Though he had successfully taken care of the Magus from Jupiter’s Lightning and humiliated Stuart, he had completely ruffled the feathers of Sky City.

After all, he had ruthlessly attacked on of their esteemed elders in their own territory! If not for Weyers helping him control the situation, the Magi of Sky City might have just declared war against him.

Weyers obviously did not go uncompensated for his help. They had discussed that part beforehand, which was the only reason Leylin was cocky enough to rush to the frontlines.

Even then, knowing that he was garnering too much attention, Leylin did not dare stay in Sky City much longer. He accepted Weyers’ proposal and went through unofficial channels to be baptised by the Endowing Scepter, keeping a low profile along the way. With his vitality increased by about 20 points, he secretly left the area, not participating in the appraisal.

As long as he obtained the profits, Leylin did not particularly care for such a title, and he tossed the conversation he’d had with the Monarch of the Skies to the back of his mind.

Leylin looked at his stats.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 4 Warlock. Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent (complete form). Strength: 50, Agility: 45, Vitality: 94.9, Spiritual Force: 956.8, Magic Power: 956(Magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force). Soul Force: 96 (Five Stars)]

“My vitality increased by 20 points, which means my body is pretty much adapted to the increased soul force now. The Endowing Scepter was truly essential!”

Leylin couldn’t help but mumble to himself as he recalled the scepter.

He had realised during the baptism that the Endowing Scepter was the energy core of Sky City. If it was attacked, the entire city would fall to the ground, leading to a horrifying disaster.

The Endowing Scepter was not an actual scepter, but instead a gigantic energy reaction furnace. Its refined looped structure was something Leylin admired, and he had the impulse to steal it and study it.

Leylin suddenly came back to himself, a slight smile about his lips. “It’s about time they caught up to me.”

*Rumble!* Immense energy undulations swept through the area, and the Colossal Serpent vanished in a puff of smoke. Leylin, who had been prepared, merely stood in mid-air while staring at Stuart who had suddenly appeared ahead of him.

Within Sky City, Weyers watched the direction Leylin had left in, and muttered to himself, “Though I agreed to help you take on the pressure from Sky City, you’ll need to deal with Stuart’s retaliation yourself!”

His gaze was full of complicated feelings, “Leylin, I admit that you’re the biggest genius I’ve seen, to the point that you can tussle with a rank 5. However, the disparity between ranks is not something one can step across so easily…”

In the battle before, Leylin had successfully captured the Morning Star Magus alive, but he had also paid the price of getting injured. Meanwhile, Stuart had been covered in dirt, but he had no real injuries.

Now that he was away from Sky City, it was hard to tell the outcome if he was was caught.

The most likely outcome was that, after an intense battle, Stuart would end up with serious injuries and Leylin would wind up dead.

Insanity flashed in Weyers’ eyes, “There needs only be one true genius, and that will be me!”

“Is he gone?” Flames flickered, and a Magus stood beside Weyers that looked similar to him. The Radiant Moon energy he gave off was even more terrifying than Stuart’s.

He glanced at Weyers with a look of encouragement, “You did well this time! With Stuart dejected, our organisation can now make ourselves known in Sky City!”

“Leylin’s already gone. I’ve also received news that Stuart has followed him!” Weyers’ voice held a trace of laughter. Weyers daring to oppose Stuart was not because he was a fool, but because someone else was backing him.

“Weyers, do you know why His Majesty, the Monarch of the Skies, promised not to interfere in the battle between the Ouroboros Clan and Jupiter’s Lightning? A Radiant Moon isn’t nearly enough for His Majesty to do this…”

The Radiant Moon looked serious as he spoke.

“Could it be…” Weyers’ expression changed.

“Leylin, you can’t run this time. I will return the humiliation you gave me today tenfold! No, a hundredfold!” Stuart’s voice was distorted, and his expression vicious.

Though Leylin was powerful, his total strength could still not match up to his own. This was what he had depended on when he chased after Leylin. Besides, he had help today, and could absolutely kill Leylin here!

Meanwhile, Jupiter’s Lightning headquarters, in a Magus Tower.

“Is it all prepared? It’s about to begin!”

Observing the bubbling Pond of Lamentation, Zegna’s expression fluctuated as a female voice was heard.

“This will consume 21% of the Pond of Lamentation’s energy reserves, and might even affect your transformation! Have you thought it through properly?”

“I’ve thought it through enough. Do it!” Zegna’s voice was low.

“Alright! Give me a portion of the control rights…”

Mysterious, complicated incantations sounded in the secret room, and multiple black masks arose, disappearing into the void.

“Hm?” Leylin, who was facing Stuart, had a change in expression.

Large numbers of black masks suddenly surrounded his body, sticking onto his face.

[Beep! Host has been inflicted with a curse. Vitality and soul force have weakened!]

the A.I. Chip’s voice transmitted.

“A curse? And it’s a long-distance ancient curse?” Leylin’s pupils shrank.

“Haha… You’re fated to die here. I will extract your soul and torture you for a thousand years!” Stuart laughed madly before he charged forth.

A terrifying rank 5 spell formed a snarling black monster that opened its large, ferocious mouth in Leylin’s direction.

“Scarlet Earring!” Red light flashed from Leylin’s ears, and a crescent-shaped blade of scarlet light slashed out…

Chapter 598: Usage

The scarlet crescent of light slashed through the sky. The humongous black monster howled in grief as it disintegrated into black vapour and dispersed.

From the black vapour came Stuart’s voice, full of fear, “A piece of high-grade magic equipment! You actually have a piece of high-grade magic equipment!”

He looked at the crimson earring hanging on Leylin’s ear, his eyes filled with restraining fear and insatiable greed, “I’ll kill you! All of this will be mine!”

‘A.I. Chip, begin resisting the radiation from the curse, and find the source!’ Leylin looked solemn as he secretly gave the command. If it was in the past, such an ancient curse would be highly troublesome to deal with, but with the vast amount of information from the Great Library as his trump card, and the A.I. Chip’s ability to successfully quantify soul force, he had formed a decent database, allowing him to resist.

The same went for the Scarlet Earring. Before he thoroughly understood its origin and functions, he didn’t dare to use it much. However, he had managed to find the history of and a detailed introduction to the Scarlet Earring in the Great Library, including operational instructions. This naturally allowed this piece of high-grade magic equipment to be put to full use.

Most of the magic equipment circulating around the central continent was low-grade. Middle-grade magic equipment was rare, and high-grade magic equipment would make even Radian Moons green with envy!

His ability to use the Scarlet Earring had boosted Leylin’s strength tremendously in one go, especially against things such as suppressive curses like now.

[Beep! Task established, begin projection of soul interference. Searching for source of curse!]

The A.I. Chip immediately intoned.

A layer of light yellow light was emitted from Leylin’s body, while the numerous black masks rushed up like moths to the flame.

‘A curse way beyond my expectations! And with such horrifying crippling abilities! It must’ve been cast by a Radiant Moon. I’m 90% sure Zegna is behind this. Who would’ve thought that he had talent in the field of curses…’

An icy glare flashed in Leylin’s eyes. Even he could not deploy such an ancient curse, especially if it was a technique that involved crossing space. This even exceeded the boundaries of what a rank 5 could do!

‘Or maybe… Someone is helping him? An even stronger Magus at that?’ This idea had Leylin face turning darker. Not only did he have to fight against two rank 5 Magi who had joined forces, he had to pay even more attention to as mysterious high-ranking Magus who was spying on him.

“I really underestimated you previously!” Seeing that the black masks attacking Leylin from all sides were decreasing in number, Stuart unexpectedly did not continue attacking him, but instead started to gasp.

‘He actually has a method to resist the ancient curse. He may be at the peak of a Morning Star formally, but his strength is comparable to that of a Radiant Moon Magus! And he even possesses a piece of high-grade magic equipment! If I had known all this earlier, I wouldn’t have taken action even if Zegna multiplied his remuneration by tenfold!’

No matter how he felt, Stuart was a Magus after all. After his rage had subsided, he regained his senses and grew rational.

However, Leylin had a rather bad feeling about Stuart’s calm and straightforward manner of speaking.

“What a pity… Since the seeds of hatred have already been planted, I will not allow them to take root and germinate!” Stuart looked at Leylin with a profound look in his eyes, “If I cannot make you fall today, the day you advance to rank 5 will be judgement day for me! Even the Monarch of the Skies will not be able to save me…”

Leylin was silent, and didn’t say much. Indeed, his enemy understood him best. Once he had sufficient strength in the future, he would definitely return for revenge and even eliminate him completely. He was not the only one who thought of this, as Stuart had as well. Neither of them tried to conceal it.

“So you must die here today, lest I be destroyed and return to the astral plane!” Stuart was resolute. Bizarre undulations appeared on his body, and the rings of light representing his five innate spells flickered into existence behind him. Even spacetime seemed to have been frozen at that moment.

“A Radiant Moon Arcane Art?!” Leylin’s expression was extremely solemn.

Morning Stars, powered by their point masses, could combine their four innate spells to produce the Morning Star Arcane Art, and Radiant Moons could do the same with their five. This terrifying fusion of powers was strong enough to cause massive destruction even at rank 4; how strong, then, would it be at rank 5?

Leylin had never seen a Radiant Moon Arcane Art before, but it was evident that the entirety of Sky City would be hard pressed to survive Stuart’s attack.

If not, he would have long used his Radiant Moon Arcane Art when he was humiliated then. He wouldn’t have been so afraid of the Monarch of the Skies and forced himself to endure for so long before finally taking action now!

This place was rather far from Sky City. Even if the undulations spread to the Sky City, its defence mechanisms and the Magi inside would be able to handle it. Thus, Stuart could go all out without any qualms!

At this moment, Leylin seemed to have seen Stuart’s truesoul through his point mass! His soul was sparkling with the frigid, dazzling radiance of a crescent moon!

‘The superposition of innate spells to form a Morning Star Arcane Art does not result in a simple additive effect. With the introduction of a fifth, rank 5 innate spell, the formidability of a Radiant Moon Arcane Art is definitely exponentially greater. It should be at least ten times as strong, if not more!’

Leylin stared at the fused rings of light behind Stuart, fear rising within him. They were rippling with a bright radiance that seemed like it could destroy the world in one sweep!

“Stuart has really firmed his resolve. He actually dared to show his Radiant Moon Arcane Art in the main world!” Leylin sighed deeply and didn’t go on the offensive directly. While Stuart was casting the Arcane Art, a frightening protective mechanism had automatically formed around him. If he attacked now, he might have to face the dreadful wrath of the Radiant Moon Arcane Art directly!

‘The disparity between our powers is too large. Such a formidable strength is enough to cause my fall!’ Leylin’s face flushed red. ‘The only way now is to….’

He slowly took off the white glove on his left hand, revealing an imprint in the form of a sun that was surrounded by black flames.

[Beep! Curse procedure found. Initializing tracking mode. Source confirmed.]

At this instant, the A.I. Chip brought him a piece of good news.

“Might as well settle them together then!” Leylin’s eyes glistened as he rushed towards Stuart…

Sky City.

“What does that mean? Didn’t Leylin obtain an agreement of neutrality from the Monarch of the Skies in exchange for the coordinates of the Lava World and his outstanding strength that could match a Radiant Moon’s?” Weyers gazed at his elder, puzzled.

The Radiant Moon Magus, however, shook his head. Weyers could even detect a bitter smile at the corners of his lips, much to his astonishment.

This elder of his was relatively strong among the Radiant Moon Magi, so why would he have such an expression? Could it be that Leylin’s strength had already grown to the extent that even he felt helpless?

Weyers shook his head firmly, as though trying to expel this thought from his brain. He didn’t consider that the more he did this, the deeper this conjecture took root in his mind.

*Rumble!* Horrifying vibrations were transmitted over, accompanied by dazzling white light.

“This is… a Morning Star Arcane Art? No! An energy undulation more terrifying than a Morning Star Art… Could it be Leylin?” Weyers lifted his head, gazing at the bright flames in the distance with a glint in his eyes.

“Stuart could not control himself in the end!” The Radiant Moon Magus sighed deeply, then said to Weyers, “You’re lucky to be able to witness a Radiant Moon Arcane Art in the main world; and even other, greater things!”

“Greater things?” Weyers was rather confused, but soon after his mouth dropped agape in shock.

What did he see? A sun! An existence from ancient times, a boundless sun that was incomparably vast! It suddenly eclipsed the radiance of the Radiant Moon Arcane Art.

The degree of heat and undulations of heat waves emitted by it struck terror in his heart. Weyers knew that even a thread of those flames was sufficient to seriously injure or even kill him!

Under the rays coming from this sun, the white radiance of the Radiant Moon Arcane Art popped like a bubble. The corona had grown enormous and still continued to expand, quickly spreading to the outskirts of Sky City.

*Boom! Boom! Boom!* Numerous defensive spell formations shattered one by one. Terrifying golden-red heat rays intruded into the place, and it was as though the sky had disintegrated and the sun had fallen. Many buildings collapsed as the entirety of Sky City descended into chaos.

“Ah…” Weyers’ jaw hung open. He had never imagined that Sky City, which had always been incomparably stable and never experienced a single tremor, would waver like a small sailboat in the stormy seas under such a horrifying attack, facing destruction and death at any moment.

Under the dreadful might of a rank 6 spell, even Sky City, the most academic progress in the entire central continent, was on the verge of collapse!

The humongous floating city wobbled violently in the storm of pure gold flames, seemingly about to fall apart any moment!

“This cannot do! We must escape as quickly as possible, and be far away from the range of this spell. This is utterly terrible…” Weyers murmured to himself.

Just as his defence mechanism could hold no longer, a hand landed on Weyers’ back, stabilising him instantly.

“Don’t panic! We still have our lord! The Monarch of the Skies will not sit still and allow the fall of Sky City!”

The words of the Radiant Moon Magus seemed to have a strong reassuring effect, allowing Weyers to recover from his previous state. Still, the shock in his pupils did not fade for a long time.

“That spell… Is it… No! That’s no longer a spell! It’s the law! The law of fire!” Weyers had never acted like this before. Never had he felt that he was so immensely insignificant and powerless. The disparity between him and Leylin was huge.

*Chirp!* Spotless white feathers floated down like snowflakes, accompanied by pleasing chirps. They firmly wrapped around the entire city, blocking out the flames.

With the assistance of this strange force, Sky City started to regain its stability.

“It’s the Monarch of the Skies! He has made a move!” The Radiant Moon Magus gasped.

The numerous Magi in the Sky City kowtowed devoutly in the direction of the Drifting Garden, expressing their gratitude to the monarch for saving their lives.

Chapter 606: Arctic Underground

*Chik chik!* The foraging Icy Jade Scorpion saw Leylin, and immediately lifted its two giant claws. The stinger of the large beast swayed as it positioned itself, ready to attack.

“Good timing!” Leylin laughed at the sight, and a fiery shadow appeared on the back of the Icy Jade Scorpion.

*Chik chik!* The scorpion tried to struggle, but a palm with a terrifying energy and intent covered its head.

The intent in the palm immediately smashed apart all resistance, and the large Icy Jade Scorpion crouched down. From this person’s body, it seemed to feel a familiar and amiable energy that belonged to an emperor.

“Let’s go!” Leylin commanded, and the Icy Jade Scorpion immediately stood up, carrying Leylin on its back and running ahead…

In the frosty world of ice, a green figure carried a black dot on its back as it moved forward at an extreme speed.

It had to be said that in this underground version of the Icy World, Icy Jade Scorpions were very useful tools for transportation. Not only did they have a high tolerance for icy radiation, their limbs were like hooks, every step digging holes in the steel-like icy ground. It did not slip at all.

The large Icy Jade Scorpion was intimidating and could avoid a lot of little inconveniences. At the very least, regular beings of the world of ice would not dare provoke it.

“Here! This is the limits of the map Celine gave me before.”

*Thud!* A large green figure jumped up and fell on the ground, its pincers sweeping across and opening a hole in the wall, revealing deep pathways inside that had obviously been altered with time.

Watching them Leylin’s eyes filled with pity. At that time, he had brazenly captured a bunch of Icy Jade Scorpions to treat the emotional instability stemming from his bloodline.

‘The icy radiation has been strengthened, and the Icy Jade Scorpions have mutated. I wonder if there’s anything now that can heal the emotional instability at Morning Star?’ Leylin thought as he touched his skin. Then, he had only used a peak rank 1 Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor to suppress his emotional instability until he became a Morning Star.

Now, even the regular Icy Jade Scorpions had strength equivalent to a rank 2 Magus, so the Icy Breath of a rank 3 elite or emperor would definitely be effective at dealing with the emotional instability of Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks at the Morning Star realm.

This was especially true for Leylin. The A.I. Chip managed to deduce that the Icy Breath of an Icy Jade Scorpion was very suitable for his Warlock physique, and therefore he would have no more issues in that aspect.

‘After I extract the bloodline of the female bronze giant, the world of ice underground will probably collapse due to losing the icy radiation. I should capture an Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor.

‘Of course, things don’t need to be so complicated! The bloodline of the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor comes from the Scorpion Man, and as long as I obtain his remains, the effects will definitely be better than from regular emperors. Perhaps it could solve the issue permanently…’

“Let’s go!”

The laboratory was completely empty. When Leylin left previously, he had brought everything inside with him. Now, he was only here to determine the coordinates.

After a brief moment recalling it, Leylin patted the head if the Icy Jade Scorpion under him.

*Chik chik…* The large Icy Jade Scorpion whined as it brought Leylin into the depths of the world of ice.

This place was out of the bounds of the map he possessed and had many dead ends filled with unknown mysteries. Of course, there was also danger!

*Whoosh…* The chilly gale howled as it accompanied the Icy Jade Scorpion deeper in, the surrounding temperatures lowering continuously. The ferocious icy radiation became even more violent.

A green luster began to form on the shell of the Icy Jade Scorpion; even it was starting to find it difficult to withstand the temperature.

The tremendous darkness completely shrouded the region, and only the green light from the Icy Jade Scorpion’s body could light up the path ahead.

Pairs of large eyes were filled with bloodthirst and greed as they appeared around Leylin like flames hidden in the night.

*Chik chik…* The large Icy Jade Scorpion did not really want to move forward anymore. It was merely a rank 2 creature, and while it was considered powerful in Twilight Zone, it was nothing in the world of ice that was deep within.

Any of the creatures shrouded in the darkness could capture and kill it easily. Normally, the Icy Jade Scorpion would scurry away in retreat, but right now it was quite confident. It was not alone now, and its owner possessed a terrifying power!

“Rank 2 and 3 creatures?” Leylin, who was sitting on the Icy Jade Scorpion’s back, suddenly laughed.

Though these creatures didn’t seem like much to him, they would definitely be a disaster for the Twilight Zone if they ever left the Icy Cave.

Rank 2 Magi were already considered powerful in Twilight Zone, while rank 3s were rulers. If they were to see the world of ice, this miniature version of the Icy World, their eyes would probably fall out of their sockets.

“Even Celine probably doesn’t know how dangerous the interior of the Icy Cave is.” Leylin shook his head, the void behind him distorting and exerting a terrifying pressure. The phantom of a terrifying snake that was tens of thousands of metres long came into view, producing loud snarls.

Winds surged, bringing with them the might of an ancient being at the top of the food chain as they spread in all directions.

The spying eyes were immediately filled with fear, and the sounds of footsteps and bumping sounded. Large numbers of eyes quickly retreated, bloody battles occurring in the darkness just for the escape route. Explosions and shrieks of horror sounded everywhere.

No matter how intense these battles were, none of the icy creatures dared take another glimpse in Leylin’s direction.

“You useless thing!” Leylin was annoyed at the incompetence of the Icy Jade Scorpion under him. It had lain on the ground the moment the Giant Kemoyin Serpent figure appeared, and would not get up no matter how he shouted at it.

*Hss…* The large Kemoyin Serpent phantom lowered its head and looked at the little green thing that could pass between the gaps in its teeth. It opened its mouth threateningly, revealing a crimson tongue and fierce teeth that were like little hills.

*Chik chik! Chik chik!* The Icy Jade Scorpion that had been lying on the ground suddenly got up, and began to run like lightning.

Strong winds constantly blew at Leylin’s ears, and he didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. “This scorpion is really…”

Explosions boomed as a large amount of icy rocks flew into the sky. A layer of ice broke from the top, and a large scorpion that was carrying a black figure jumped through the hole and landed firmly on the ground.

“Hah… Here!” Leylin led the Icy Jade Scorpion to higher ground, looking over the surroundings.

This was a world of ice! Ice and snow covered the place, leading the ground to sparkle. Even the hills and rivers were made of ice! The vegetation that was spread around the area was covered with frost as well. Flowers bloomed and trees bore fruit, all with a terrifying chill.

Things that looked like ribbons hung from large trees, with eyeballs that looked like longans on them, emitting a blue lustre.

‘This scene is so similar to the Icy World in the Scorpion Man’s memories!’ Leylin touched his chin, and a powerful soul force scanned over a large area.

The beings within hundreds of kilometers seemed to have met their natural predator. Whether it was the mountainous icy monsters or the tiny snowflake bugs, everything fell to the ground, trembling.

After a long moment, Leylin opened his eyes once more.

“Just from what I’m able to see, this place is already more than a tenth of the size of Twilight Zone. Could this be the second layer to the subterranean world?” There was naturally more than just one layer underneath the Magus World. It was rumoured that there were seven layers that the ancient Magi had taken over, and the further one went the more dangerous it was. There were even existences like Matriarch of the Abyss.

Of course, the resources there were more plentiful as well. They could be called places where risk met reward.

Twilight Zone was merely in the first layer, and it was quite a normal place. It was only a region which was isolated from the external world.

‘No, that’s not right! The distance is far too small, it can’t be the second layer. It should be in the empty space between the first two layers instead…’ Leylin stroked his chin.

‘When the Scorpion Man fell through the spatial rifts that popped up during that ancient battle, he was transported here. The continuous radiation from the blood of the female bronze giant had transformed this area until it grew similar to the Icy World. It even included the formation of a large number of creatures of the ice.’

Leylin’s expression turned solemn. Existences like these that had stepped across the two-thirds of realms and entered rank 7 were the most troublesome, as they had grasped laws.

Just a droplet of fresh blood from the original body had such a powerful effect. How powerful would the original body have been?

“With such a large area, I wouldn’t find it strange even if I found icy beings of the Morning Star level…” Leylin sighed. The Morning Star realm was a threshold, and if there were Morning Star icy beings here, the difficulty in exploring this place would increase severalfold.

To be direct, if Leylin had come here when he was rank 3, he would definitely have died. Even after he’d advanced to Morning Star, he might not have been able to completely unravel the mysteries of the Icy World.

Of course, Leylin was no longer the same as before. He had improved through his excursions to both the Lava World and Sky City. His true strength now far surpassed the Morning Star realm, and he could even rival Radiant Moons!

Hence, after entering the Icy World, he could use his soul force and probe the area without fear of inadvertently alerting any enemy. Power was enough to pulverise all conspiracies.

‘From the reaction to my soul force just now, the life undulations from here are the strongest!’ Leylin patted the Icy Jade Scorpion that was now seated, and it immediately budged. Jade green limbs began to move with rhythm, each step carrying them a good distance as it crawled in the direction Leylin pointed.

Chapter 609: Arwen

“Found it! It’s there!” The moment Leylin defeated the Arctic Knight, a hint of happiness emerged on Arwen’s face. He’d been waiting in the castle at the core of this world of ice the whole time.

He pulled out a few pieces of black crystal from his arms, among which one had already cracked quite obviously.

“It’s the canyon area that Rose is in charge of!” After discovering the target, Arwen’s entire person blurred into a phantom as he shot towards the canyon area.

Of course, he’d never hoped that his subordinates would capture a Morning Star; that would just be a joke. Those he’d sent out this time would serve as nothing more than a warning.

Once they came into contact with that Morning Star, Arwen who was in control of their spirit sources would know immediately.

Hence, that Duchess Rose from before was just cannon fodder in his eyes.

Arwen who was far away had an indifferent and emotionless expression. In a battle between Morning Stars, it was in fact very extraordinary that Duchess Rose ended up being cannon fodder.

At the same time, in canyon area within the hill village of the Arctic Tribe, Leylin looked at Yamos speechlessly as the creature crawled and knelt at his feet, both hands clinging to his boots.

“My Lord! The Arctic Queen is the most evil of demons! She greedily exploited our Arctic Tribe’s resources, and even asked our matured members to become blood sacrifices… She has brought us great suffering and tears of blood. We beg you, Sire must help us with our vengeance! Defeat the Arctic Queen…”

Yamos was over two metres tall, veritably a small giant. For such a creature to kneel before him and cry so hard left Leylin at a loss for words.

The chief of the snow elves, Amos, was also apologising with tears in his eyes, complaining about the Arctic Queen’s evil deeds simultaneously.

“Actually, other than a regular tribute and having your matured members become blood sacrifices, it seems as if this Arctic Queen hasn’t committed any evil?”

Yamos was clearly just one person, but there were different thoughts from two different brains buzzing beside Leylin’s ears continuously, making him feel a little fed up.

However, he still endured it by force of will in order to obtain the information, all the while plotting something in his heart.

The situation in the world of ice also grew clearer to him. From Yamos’ introduction, he learned that the place was very vast, with many tribes scattered across it. They were all being ruled by someone called the Arctic Queen.

This queen seldom appeared in public, and it could be said that she had almost never shown her face before.

All the affairs were handled by her butler, Arwen. The man possessed a formidable strength. The tribes that had been exploited and oppressed had allied together in several crusades but had easily been defeated by him. After a few bloodbaths, there was no one else in this miniature Icy World who dared to go against the Arctic Queen’s regime.

Leylin felt like the tribute this Arctic Queen demanded was still quite mild. It was only her demand for blood sacrifices that was terrifyingly huge.

There were almost no adults other than the chief in the Arctic Tribe. Based on Yamos’ accusations, they had either fled or were sent to the castle to be used as blood sacrifices.

‘It seems like the Scorpion Man’s remains and the female bronze giant’s bloodline are definitely related to the Arctic Queen. They may even be right in her castle!’ Leylin stroked his chin, thinking of something, ‘All these blood sacrifices, could it be…’

His eyes sparkled, and soon after he suddenly lifted his head and looked into the distant sky.

A small black dot grew larger and larger, pressing down like a small mountain. The approaching figure was that of an icy creature who was half human, half scorpion. His upper body was dressed in a butler’s suit, the bloodshot eyes leaving a deep impression.

“It’s Arwen! Oh God, Sir Arwen has come personally!” Yamos burst out at a shocking speed, and with a whoosh it arrived at the platform where Yamos had arrived and knelt down. Emotional tears flowed down from all four eyes.

“Sir Arwen, you’re finally here! This criminal has committed a grave mistake, we need you to judge him! Yamos is your loyal servant—”

Before Yamos could finish speaking, a faint blue light enveloped it in a moment, turning it into an ice sculpture.

A web of cracks emerged on this sculpture, covering it up entirely before it shattered into pieces. It sounded like a glass cup had fallen to the ground.

Yamos, along with the ice sculpture, had turned into dust. Faced with such strength, even the Arctic Tribe’s innate ability of symbiosis was rendered completely ineffective.

“Greetings, foreign Morning Star!” After killing Yamos, Arwen pulled out a clean, white handkerchief and wiped his palms, greeting Leylin as if he was an unconcerned person.

“Hello, powerhouse of the world of ice!” Leylin bowed.

Arwen’s form was slightly similar to the Scorpion Man he had previously seen. However, there were also major differences. His figure was smaller and did not carry the fierce aura that came with the bloodline of an ancient creature. Having the Giant Kemoyin Serpent Bloodline himself, Leylin could easily identify it.

But seeing how he had shown up here, and also his appearance, he was related to the Scorpion Man.

“I represent my master, the Arctic Queen, in inviting you to her castle. I wonder if Sir is willing to accept her invitation?” Arwen bowed humbly.

“I’ve admired the Arctic Queen for a long time. But what if I refuse?” A mocking smile emerged at the corners of Leylin’s lips.

“That would be a great pity!” Arwen shook his head, as if he was feeling sorry for Leylin’s irrationality.

A blood-red light shot out of his eyes in a flash. As if the entire earth was shaken, thunder roared and his entire body jumped into motion from his stationary state, coming before Leylin as if he had broken through the boundaries of time and space,

*Swoosh!* A long and translucent dark green needle rushed towards Leylin, a bright, dazzling radiance at its tip.

A tail was attached to the long needle. It was the tail section of a scorpion!

However, Leylin already knew about the Scorpion Man’s strong body from the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor’s memories. How would he let Arwen get his way?

A small round shield emerged to block the stinger almost the same moment it rushed forth, blocking the unavoidable strike. Giant Kemoyin Serpents moved around on the shield’s surface, hissing on occasion.

The dark green needle broke through the center of the bloodline shield with a snip, arriving in front of Leylin.

“Kemoyin’s Scales!” Instantaneously, the innate defence emerged on the surface of Leylin’s body. After his vitality surpassed 100, this rank 1 innate spell seemed to have undergone an intriguing change. Not only was there an additional layer of blazing stripes on the scales, they had even grown dazzling.

*Ka-cha!* A small white dot emerged on the black scales and Leylin’s figure retreated. At the same time, the red crescent of light from his earring swept across Arwen’s chest. Dazzling sparks flew out as it collided with a translucent icy armour that suddenly appeared.

“High-grade magic artifact?” Arwen looked at the huge crack on his chestplate as a trace of apprehension appeared on his face. Large amounts of white, icy fog solidified, mending the damage to the armour.

‘There are no weaknesses to exploit in a Morning Star!’

The confrontation just now had occurred very quickly, and was very dangerous. Although the spells that Morning Star Magi took most pride in were not used, the mere confrontation in strength and vitality created a lingering fear in Leylin.

Arwen’s previous attack was very strange. If not for his vitality breaking past 100 and the addition of his bloodline, an attack at such close quarters would have probably injured him severely.

‘Morning Stars from a foreign place may not excel in magical abilities! Hence there’s a need to pay attention to all aspects!’ After opening up some distance between them, Leylin directed a cold gaze at Arwen.

“You’re the first person who was able to escape my ‘Breath of Doom’!” Arwen looked at his own stinger, his face seeming a little regretful yet gratified.

“Damn you! In this world of ice, is there another Morning Star apart from you and your queen?” Leylin secretly rolled his eyes.

Because the outside world did not have any icy radiation, it was very rare for Arwen to go out even after he advanced to Morning Star. In face, because he had to protect the Arctic Queen, he probably even rarely left the castle. He used Morning Star strength to bully the aboriginals of the world of ice, yet he still had the nerve to act like an expert.

Although he felt a little speechless, Leylin still looked at his opponent carefully. Arwen would rank as a Four Star Morning Star according to Sky City’s rankings. If his body’s special abilities were included, his strength would probably even reach Five Stars.

A certain amount of effort would be needed to take down such an enemy.

A splendid starry sky suddenly emerged behind Leylin, illuminating a sea of blood. Facing Arwen, Leylin emitted his own Morning Star domain. His terrifying pull on bloodlines attracted Arwen’s own, making his face flush slightly red.

With him being a Warlock with an ancient bloodline who had also received that bloodline’s legacy, Leylin’s Morning Star domain was naturally connected to it.

“So this is the Morning Star domain of a Magus… In our world of ice, we call it the ‘Power Aura’ or ‘Vitality’s Forcefield’!” A realm of ice emerged behind Arwen as he spoke, offsetting Leylin’s Morning Star domain.

The two huge domains collided, making even the void vibrate. The illusory walls shattered, creating the feeling as if the world being destroyed.

However, Arwen’s icy realm was evidently suppressed by Leylin’s domain, causing his expression to change.

“Did you know the most terrifying thing about us Magi is still our spells?” Leylin’s smile made Arwen’s hair stand on end…

Chapter 612: Arctic Queen

A black shooting star streaked across the horizon, its magnificence amplified under the translucent icy sky.

Leylin was sending out a thread of soul force every once in a while, scanning the energies of the surrounding beings.

‘It seems like Arwen’s fall caused some sort of chain reaction.’ As far as he could see, the various regions in this world of ice had been disturbed at least on some level. Many of the intellectual icy beings, such as the Arctic Tribe, and even the ice leopards and the frost dragons were beginning to rebel against the Arctic Queen’s rule.

‘It’s understandable though. The other races never could stand being under her rule anyway. Since she’s fallen, a frenzied rebellion is only to be expected,’ Leylin thought as he touched his pouch. Extracting the Icy Breath to treat his emotional stability was not the only thing he’d done. He hadn’t wasted any part of the body, not even his bloodline. It was all currently stored in his pouch.

There were still many survivors who had seen Leylin defeat Arwen, and news had spread quickly. Without the suppression of a Morning Star, the rebellion of these various races was not surprising.

‘But the Arctic Queen has been in power for so many years… It doesn’t make sense for everything to fall apart so bad so quickly…’ Leylin’s eyes twinkled with a distinct light. Even with Arwen’s death, the Arctic Queen’s guards should not have been defeated so quickly. It was like the headquarters had been destroyed with no clear commands given.

At this point, Leylin suddenly had a thought, ‘Could there be something wrong at the Arctic Queen’s palace?’

That was all he managed to think of. The shooting star that was Leylin whizzed faster into the horizon, only leaving behind after-images in the sky.

Even rank 3 creatures could only crouch on the ground, unable to move after seeing Leylin hurtling past. They were terrified by his speed and prowess…

The castle of ice was located at the heart of this world, and when Leylin came here he found that the vicinity of the place had gone up in smoke.

The many suppressed races had formed an alliance, gathering troops at the centre of the icy plains.

The few remaining guards were led by Arctic Knights as they used the terrain of the great valley at their stronghold to fight back, but it was a losing battle. It looked like this alliance would be able to enter the castle in no time at all.

‘Keke… With Arwen’s death, the entire castle’s defence is rendered useless!’ Watching the bustling camp of the allied forces, a smirk rose about Leylin’s lips, ‘When they breach the walls of the palace and, instead of victory, see the Arctic Queen who’s even more terrifying than Arwen, what kind of expression will they have?’

Leylin’s eyes did not stop on the battlefield, and instead switched to the castle.

There were a few loyal guards and the like who wanted to stop him, but they were no match for him at all. They were not even able to hold him back for a few seconds.

What Leylin found strange was that the closer he got to the castle, the weaker the resistance grew. The moment he arrived on top of the place, the guards only dared to look at him from afar, not advancing. It was as if there was some kind of terrifying danger within the castle.

‘This is the place? There’s no life force in here at all, only some kind of absorptive force…’ Leylin hovered above the castle of ice and observed its magnificence, though his eyes only held solemness.

The icy radiation had peaked here, and the concentration was hundreds, even thousands of times greater than in the outer world. It was constantly changing and growing, distorting continuously.

“Those below Morning Star probably won’t be able to survive here…” The radiation was far too powerful, to the point that no ordinary beings could handle it; it had become a life-threatening poison!

However, what astonished Leylin was not the concentration of the radiation, but the mysterious absorptive force coming from the ground.

The area under this castle of ice was like a terrifying black hole to his senses, continuously absorbing the life force of everything on the ground. On top of that, it was expanding without end.

A thick layer of white, icy powder had formed on the ground, left behind by some unlucky fighters.

Blue light shot out from Leylin’s eyes, and he cried out involuntarily. “No! It’s not their life force that’s being absorbed… It’s the frost energy and the icy nature of their bloodlines…”

Suddenly, as if having sensed Leylin’s arrival, the entire surface of the castle began to quiver.

That vague scent and aura Leylin had sensed began to awaken, its strength increasing.

“Ugh…” The mumble of a female voice resounded above the icy castle.

Large amounts of winds and snow gathered, forming the statue of a female giant.

The woman had a crown on her head, a dignified pair of freezing eyes under slender eyelashes. She extended her arms towards the distant battle.

*Rumble!* Terrifying blue pillars of light emerged from the ground, and seemed to break through into the heavens, releasing endless ripples of energy.

The eyes of those who had been embroiled in the bloody battle were suddenly filled with confusion and regret.

“All hail the Queen!” “All hail the Queen!” “All hail the Queen!”

A guard was the first to toss away his lance and shield, running towards the danger zone that he’d avoided as if it was a den of scorpions and snakes, looking extremely enthusiastic.

His legs were frozen as a blue light emerged from them and travelled underground. They then cracked off.

The guard did not notice at all. Even when his two legs were torn off, he still tried to get to the castle on his hands, the injury clotted with a layer of frost.

The frost continued to expand, covering the entirety of the guard. Traces of blue light were absorbed by the ground, causing his life force to weaken continuously.

He was zealous unto death, as if the Arctic Queen was his goddess to whom he was willing to sacrifice his everything.

‘This is even more terrifying than an illusion. Even his soul isn’t his own anymore…’ Leylin sighed from high in the sky, watching everything apathetically.

It was not just the guards. Even the opposing allied forces threw their weapons away, showing the same fanaticism after one glance at the female giant. They rushed towards the castle as well.

Countless icy statues formed and then broke down, forming a thick layer of white powder on the ground. Yet, even that did not prevent them from surging forth, wave upon wave.

Blue light was emitted from Leylin’s eyes, and great amounts of information were stored in his database. With the A.I. Chip’s collection of statistical data, everything was presented before him.

‘The attraction of the bloodline? The icy radiation too had affected their behaviour!’ Leylin touched his chin. This was not a temporary control from illusory spells, but a terrifying effect that was formed over a long period of time. That was why the effects were so good, such that even rank 3 beings could not escape.

“Looks like this is a blood sacrifice…” Leylin suddenly guessed. Perhaps the Arctic Queen had herded the various races in this world like livestock. Every once in a while, they would be harvested after reaching maturity.

“If that’s so, the Arctic Queen is probably…” A flash of determination appeared in Leylin’s eyes, Morning Star radiation engulfing the area.

The void itself seemed to tremble, and the world instantly turned black and white.

The scope of the radiation continuously widened, and the few that had yet to enter the range of the castle suddenly showed looks of pain and suffering as they collapsed to the ground, their faces distorting. Even their internal organs swelled and ruptured.

Leylin had already reached the peak of Morning Star. He usually kept his radiation sealed, which was how he brought no harm to his surroundings wherever he went. Now, his suddenly unleashing it was difficult for the rank 3 beings to bear.

The sufferance was enough for these icy beings to regain their senses. They raised their heads, eyes full of terror as they stared hard at the floating Leylin and the female giant. Making some strange sounds, they escaped without turning back.

Even so, they’d come into contact with Leylin’s powerful radiation. There were a few rank 2s and 3s at the side who could still use their own strength to rid themselves of the contamination, but those weaker than that would probably die if they were contaminated. It was only a matter of time.

Before their lives were completely burnt through, they would still have to deal with bearing the pain from the contamination.

The disturbance seemed to spread further and further as more of these tribals regained their sanity. No matter what camp they were in, these life-and-death enemies all escaped pitifully, only wanting to get as far away as possible.

The female giant in the air suddenly turned back, her eyes focussing on Leylin. Coldness was laid bare in them, but Leylin met her gaze head on.

He hadn’t interfered at first because he needed to collect information and calculate the way the energy was used. Yet, once all was said and done, he wouldn’t be so stupid as to let his opponent grow in power.

The giant made of ice snarled, and a large icy tornado was formed at her fist, hurtling towards Leylin.

A gigantic Giant Kemoyin Serpent appeared at Leylin’s back. Compared to before, it was now even larger, and its eyes glowed with greater intelligence as it hissed at the giant.

*Boom!* Formless sound waves clashed with the tornado, and snow filled the sky.

Chapter 613: Illusion and Manipulation

“A mere clone wants to attack me?” Leylin sneered, the phantom Giant Kemoyin Serpent behind him rapidly shrinking. Its body was now more substantial, and its scales reflected a dazzling luster.

The Giant Kemoyin Serpent snarled, its tremendous tail whipping at the female giant like a mace.

*Boom!* The female giant’s body blew up, and snowflakes fluttered in the sky.

The aftershocks were transmitted to the castle below, and large cracks began to appear on the walls.

*Whoosh!* As the wind and snow calmed, the entire area turned strangely silent.

The white powder formed from the life energy and consumption of frost energy of the many icy races covered the ground. There were also the remains of armour and weapons, which made the area seem even more desolate.

Leylin heaved a long sigh, producing a test tube from his spatial pouch that was filled with a purple liquid.

The seal at the mouth of the test tube opened automatically and a liquid dripped down to the ground, spreading quickly.

Large amounts of white powder were dissolved by the potion, creating a gigantic pool of water. There were countless bubbles constantly being produced on the surface, and they instantly turned the surroundings of the castle into a purple swamp.

The purple swamp continued to expand, also showing signs of going deeper.

‘I’ve made calculations with the A.I. Chip and developed this potion from Arwen’s blood and flesh using his memories. Let’s hope this is effective.’ By this point, Leylin had guessed the origin of this Arctic Queen. Hence, he was currently feeling very serious, hoping that his conjecture was wrong.

However, what he had just seen had validated his suspicion.

Large amounts of purple bubbles were constantly produced, and the original castle of ice was beginning to be eaten into, the main body of the building slowly sinking down.

*Buzz!* A pure, powerful spiritual force extended and began to fuse with the surroundings.

Almost instantly, Leylin found himself in another wondrous environment.

The sky was no longer filled with ice, it wasn’t the crust of the earth. The moon sparkled in a starry sky, and below was a white continent that spread a vast ocean, as far as the eye could see.

Ice Mountain Wyverns, Chilly Giants and other creatures were roaring out, and most had surpassed the limits of Morning Star.

“This is… the real Icy World!” Leylin muttered to himself. He, who possessed some of the memories of the ancient Scorpion Man, was naturally somewhat familiar with this place.

“Yes. The real Icy World, my homeland! Foreign Magus, can you fulfil my wish of returning to my homeland?” The Arctic Queen spoke with a gentle tone as she appeared by his side. Looking somewhat similar to the giant from before, she had on a crown and platinum imperial robes.

“Arctic Queen?” Leylin’s pupils shrank as he scanned the surroundings. “Not a bad illusion!”

“The most beautiful of illusions is still not reality. Even the fake world of ice in reality does not measure up to a smidgen of the splendour of the real Icy World…” The Arctic Queen sighed, her tone so sorrowful Leylin couldn’t bear it. He wanted to speak up, helping her solve the issue.

“As long as you’re willing to help me, you shall be the sole emperor of the entire Icy World!” As if she had seen Leylin wavering, the Arctic Queen added a bargaining chip.

“Pretty good conditions! It’s a pity that I don’t see any sincerity in them at all. How can someone who uses illusory magic on potential allies be trusted to abide by their promises?” Leylin shook his head, his words causing the expression on the Arctic Queen’s face to change.

Blood-red flames came into being on Leylin’s hands. They crackled as they were shot to the Arctic Queen’s feet without hesitation, starting to burn her.

“You’ll regret this!” The Arctic Queen, who was now covered in flames, showed a wavering energy. Yet, she was like an expressionless paper doll as she spoke.

“If I agree to your conditions, I might regret it even more!” Leylin was still slightly fearful at this time. He’d believed that he had a very powerful resistance to illusory magic, and yet he had easily been pulled into the illusion that his opponent had created, and almost lost his senses.

If not for the A.I. Chip’s timely warning, as well as the many secret techniques of Spirit Warlocks he’d learnt from Paul, he might very well have died here.

After all, who would have thought that the ruler of the Icy World was proficient in illusory psychological hints?

“You’ll regret this!” “You’ll regret this!”

An icy female voice resounded in the illusion, causing his hair to stand.

Paper dolls that resembled the Arctic Queen sprang up one after another, the icy world collapsing with a rumble. Whether it was the stars in the sky, the continent, or the creatures upon it, everything turned into an Arctic Queen, giving Leylin a terrifying glare.

[Beep! Host’s brain is suffering from an unknown influence. Determined to be illusory magic,]

the A.I. Chip’s voice sounded.

“That’s obvious damn it, but my connection to the real world hasn’t been severed. If I die here, my main body outside will probably die as well…”

Morning Star energy rippled as traces of soul force lingered around the surface of Leylin’s body, giving him a few layers of protection.

Such a high-level illusion could render a Magus’ spiritual force useless. However, it could not restrict a Morning Star’s soul force, which still had a good effect.

However, this was the opponent’s home ground. If he used up all of his soul force, he would be in trouble.

“A.I. Chip, scan the structure of the illusion and search for the point of three-dimensional construct and Wors’ Space!” Leylin silently sent down the order.

The A.I. Chip did not have a good method of dealing with such a situation before, but now with the database on the soul, its ability at analysis had improved by leaps and bounds.

“You can’t escape!” Like the many galaxies in the universe, countless three-dimensional Arctic Queens were formed. These clones that looked like inverted images of the original held weapons in their hands, going on the offensive against him.

*Ting!* Soul force condensed to form a blood-red cross blade in Leylin’s hands.

Leylin quickly took a step forward, the cross blade blocking large numbers of icy blades that produced dazzling rays of light.

“Cross Slash!” A cross-shaped light flashed, and tens of paper dolls turned into fragments that filled the skies.

“It’s of no use. This is my spiritual world! No number of deaths will cause any exhaustion to me. How long do you think your soul force can last you?” The doll accompanying this icy voice was torn to shreds, but it then reformed into the Arctic Queen once more.

“Stop resisting when it doesn’t even matter. Together, we can—”

*Schlick!* Before the Arctic Queen could finish her words, her head was chopped off.

The flat head that was like a piece of paper fell to the ground, and continued to chatter on, “Your only choice is to serve me! Hand over your soul source and become my servant. This way, I might even let you off!”

*Rumble!* Red flames flashed and burnt the paper into ashes.

There was a cold smirk on Leylin’s face. “I’d be a fool to listen to your commands!”

“Kill him!” As if the Arctic Queen had been enraged, large numbers of two-dimensional paper clones pounced on him.

“Cross Slash!” Leylin’s expression was cool as he launched attack after attack, sending fragmented paper flying into the skies, filling it like butterflies. They even covered Leylin’s clothes, his weapon, and his hair.

“I told you, you can’t escape!” The paper on Leylin’s body became as heavy as lead, a few pieces joining to form the face of the Arctic Queen.

Leylin’s body grew sluggish as a blade swiped at his chest. The fine Kemoyin’s Scales unexpectedly could not hinder the blade at all, and a wound opened up on his chest, blood spurting out.

“I told you this is my mental world. Even if your defences are extremely powerful in the external world, I am the ruler here!” The paper doll standing in front of Leylin spoke slowly.

“Is that so?” Leylin’s face was pale, his body in the external world evidently receiving a real injury.

“If it’s true, wouldn’t you have killed me long ago? Why would you still be here spouting so much nonsense?”

“Nonsense?” The Arctic Queen’s brows lifted and raised her arms. Leylin had no idea which part of his speech had irritated her.

The number of illusory figures increased greatly, and in practically an instant the area was completely filled with paper dolls of various colours.

“Since you wish to die, let me fulfil your wish!” Countless Arctic Queens pounced forth.

At this moment, however, a slight smile appeared about Leylin’s lips. “Found it!”

He suddenly moved forward, soul force undulating at his body and gathering on the cross blade, resulting in rays of flaming light that seemed endless.

“Cross Slash!” The gleaming cross blade sliced at a point in the sky.

*Crack! Crack!* It was like a mirror being shattered, and numerous shivering, spotted lights that resembled tadpoles appeared behind it.

“No! Impossible! How did you find out?” The Arctic Queen’s voice became high-pitched and piercing.

“Haha…” Leylin laughed maniacally, ignoring the fury of the Arctic Queen behind him and rushed headfirst into the sea of tadpoles.

“A.I. Chip! Begin destruction based on the previous plan…” Countless black threads appeared in Leylin’s hands and quickly dispersed. Even more mirrors shattered.

*Bang!* A slight tremor was produced by Leylin’s body, and his eyes instantly focused. He glanced at the icy castle and purple swamp as well as the cut on his chest and sighed, “I’m finally out!”

*Chi chi…* At this moment, a furious, high-pitched sound was emitted from under the castle.

“The opponent’s illusory spells are too powerful. I need to leave for now!” Just now, Leylin had lucked out. Depending on the A.I. Chip’s ability to find the gaps in the illusion, he’d managed to escape. The next time, the situation would be different. Even if he could find the gaps again, successfully breaking through them was still an issue.

Leylin’s eyes flashed as he moved a long distance away in an instant.

Chapter 618: Rank 5 and the Snake Dowager

Gigantic and graceful, the phantom of a Kemoyin Serpent Emperor that held an elegance befitting a ruler appeared behind Leylin’s back. Large amounts of blood-coloured energy shrouded him. The serpent emperor snarled as a black hole appeared in front of it, sucking in the surrounding ice, earth, rocks, the remains and even the air.

　　

Once large amounts of materials disappeared into its mouth, Leylin felt a powerful life force begin to circulate within his body. His body buzzed as first the skeleton, then his internal organs, blood, flesh, and finally the skin was regenerated. With the help of a powerful life force, the injuries on his body recovered at a frightening rate.　

‘Could this be the rumoured devouring ability of the Kemoyin Serpent Emperor?’ Leylin had a thought.

Immediately after, he felt his arm go numb, and the limb that had been broken off began to regenerate. In just ten or so seconds, the grave injury was completely recovered.

　

This speed left even Leylin in shock. ‘With this rate of recovery, I can recover quickly even in a battle against a Radiant Moon. I could even endure a Morning Star Arcane Art with just my body, immediately restoring myself afterwards! If the devouring ability is already so terrifying, what about that of control?’ he wondered.

The information about the Kemoyin Serpent Emperor had been lost in ancient times, and a large portion of the information that was gathered had been derived by the A.I. Chip from his bloodline memories. It was rather small, but just looking at the description he could tell that his control over Kemoyin Warlocks was great. Great enough, in fact, that if he commanded a Morning Star Kemoyin Warlock to die, the other party would not be able to resist at all.

　

*Hss—* Though he had completely recovered, the Giant Kemoyin Serpent figure at Leylin’s back was still unsatisfied. It abruptly broke through the layer of soil and soared into the air.　　

　

A terrifying suction force appeared, and everything, be it living or otherwise, was dragged towards the black hole that had appeared in the serpent’s mouth.

　

The force spread out farther than even the bounds of the castle, radiating into the surroundings. Leylin could see several powerful creatures, many at the Crystal Phase, dragged from the sky by force as they disappeared into the black hole.

　　

Practically every being in this world of ice automatically bowed their heads in respect and fear, trembling bodies paralysed under the suppression of the Kemoyin Serpent Emperor.

　

The accumulated life force was enormous, eventually forming a cocoon that covered Leylin. The Kemoyin Serpent Emperor at Leylin’s back continued to snarl unceasingly, and only after almost devouring the entirety of the central icy plains did it pull back into the cocoon of light, satisfied.

　　

Leylin was undergoing a wondrous transformation within. Powerful bloodline energy fused with boundless life force, aiding Leylin in his bid to charge into rank 5.

　　

He was becoming a rank 5 Warlock, a Radiant Moon! There were likely no more than twenty Radiant Moons in the entire central continent, second only to the Breaking Dawn Monarchs. It was also precisely due to the Radiant Moons in the Union that bloodline Warlocks still survived to this day.

　　

On top of that, this event was even more significant for Leylin. He had finally moved past the bloodline shackles of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, and now had the wherewithal to try to become a rank 5.

　

“I already reached the peak of Morning Star after fusing Fireplume into my point mass, so I already meet the requirements for the advancement. And now that the bloodline and technique that were holding me back are solved…” Leylin chuckled lightly.

With the cooperation of the bloodline of the rank 5 Kemoyin Serpent Emperor, his advancement was smooth. The fifth level of Kemoyin’s Pupil that the A.I. Chip had just deduced began to operate slowly.　　

The point mass in his sea of consciousness buzzed as it revolved quickly, growing in density as the nebula surrounding it began another round of frantic expansion. Another layer of fine black runes emerged on top of it.

With the probing of the soul through the A.I. Chip, Leylin could see the truesoul located at the heart of the point mass beginning to evolve.　　

Probing through his A.I. Chip, Leylin saw his truesoul at the heart of his point mass breaking through its limits at the peak of Morning Star, expanding to form the shape of a moon. It was glittering with a fine radiance that filled it with a sense of perfection.

　　

Soul force was constantly poured in, causing the round moon to emanate a cool lustre. Once that was completed, his soul that was a size larger than that of normal Radiant Moon Magi had on it a layer of soul force that looked like a crescent moon that emitted an intense radiance.

　　

‘I don’t have enough soul force to fill my truesoul. In fact, I don’t even have enough to fill half the volume… It seems like I’m a New Moon…’ Leylin suddenly came to an understanding of how Radiant Moons trained.

　

Ranks 4 to 6 involved the training of soul force. Morning Stars were still fumbling around without direction; it was when one advanced to Radiant Moon that they began true training.

　

The soul, which was in the shape of a moon showed how much soul force one had with its radiance. Rank 5 Magi had to train and fill it up. The different amounts of fullness represented the different stages of New Moon, Half Moon, and Full Moon Magi.

[Beep! Host’s soul force has been strengthened. Chip upgrade commencing… Time to completion: 4m24s.]　　

　　

With the advancement of his soul, the A.I. Chip was undergoing its upgrade immediately as well, having been fused into it. Perhaps it was because it had already gained quite a bit from Sky City, the advancement this time was quite rapid. In less than five minutes, it had completed its upgrade and rebooted.

　　

The sounds of the A.I. Chip rang once more.

[Beep! Host’s Kemoyin’s Pupil meditation technique has reached the fifth level. Advancing to rank 5 Warlock!]　　

[Beep! Host has advanced to become a Radiant Moon Warlock. All statistics have been significantly strengthened, recalculating…]　　

　

The familiar robotic voice seemed to be accompanied with a changed interface, the screen projected in Leylin’s mind even more solid than before.

‘Looks like the A.I. Chip has undergone a huge transformation!’ Leylin touched his chin.

[Data collection complete. Display?]

 The A.I. Chip launched another prompt. Leylin nodded as he voiced his approval. The A.I Chip immediately projected the refreshed numbers before Leylin’s eyes.

[Leylin Farlier, Rank 5 Warlock. Bloodline: Kemoyin Serpent Emperor. Strength: 75, Agility: 61, Vitality: 137.5, Spiritual force: 1326.7, Magic power: 1326(Magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force). Soul force: 133 (New Moon)] 　

“It really deserves to be called the bloodline of the Kemoyin Emperor. The numbers were raised to such a huge extent!” Leylin’s expression was filled with glee. Not only had his spiritual force broken through 1000, his strength and agility which had not improved in a very long while had increased as well. His vitality had been raised by over 30 points, which was just terrifying!　　

　

“I never expected that the growth of Kemoyin Warlocks would only become more frightful with time!” Leylin read through his stats and could not help but sigh.　　

He felt the soul energy in his body that was as cool as water. It was soul force that had reached rank 5, and was of a higher quality than that at Morning Star, therefore having better effects. However, there was no elation in Leylin’s expression.　

“The issue of the bloodline shackles still has not been dealt with. I’ve only pushed it back by a rank, and this time there’s no such thing as raising the rank of my bloodline anymore!” Leylin gazed at the prompt at the bottom of the stats frame and turned grim.

　　

[Host’s Kemoyin bloodline has reached limits of genes. Unable to advance further.]

The A.I. Chip was plainly telling Leylin that after reaching the Kemoyin Serpent Emperor, he had reached the limits of his bloodline. At least Kemoyin Serpents had no way to advance to a higher realm.

　　

An ominous feeling, like his future path had been cut off, emerged in Leylin’s mind…

*BOOM!* The cocoon of light in the world of ice burst apart, revealing Leylin within.

“Whatever it is, I’ve finally attained my goal in coming to the subterranean world this time. I just didn’t expect the remains of the Scorpion Man to be burnt up along with my opponent. It’s slightly regretful that I didn’t manage to obtain the coordinates to the Icy World…” Leylin sighed ruefully, turning into a black figure that disappeared into the void.

The long majestic river that was the astral plane flowed on, many foreign worlds like the stars in the galaxy. They were a brightly coloured array, twinkling with varying lustres.

In one such world, full of flames and shadows, a boundless darkness formed a dense fog that completely covered the continent.

Numerous ancient, terrifying serpents grew and multiplied in this place, terrifying auras at Morning Star advancements appearing everywhere.

　

At the heart of the continent, the holy land of all snakes, Morning Star serpents could be seen everywhere. The closer one got to the centre, the more horrifying they became, as rank 5 and even ran 6 snakes flashed by on occasion.

In a gigantic spatial crack, a coiled ball of snake the size of a star revealed the alluring figure of the Snake Dowager. The moment Leylin reached rank 5, she opened a pair of misty eyes that seemed like water.

　　

“I’d never thought that today, after the end of the ancient era, an Emperor would awaken among the Kemoyin race!” The eyes of the Snake Dowager seemed to penetrate across multiple worlds and the astral plane, locking onto the Magus World and a young Warlock.

　

To her, a Morning Star was just a basic soldier. Rank 5s and 6s were worthy of attention, and such a thing as the Kemoyin Serpent Emperor that could control the Giant Kemoyin Serpents was even more worthy of interest.

“The power of destiny is guiding you here…” The life and death of multiple worlds flashed across her beautiful eyes. Two mandara flowers, one bright and one dark, bloomed in them before dissipating.

Destiny, seen through the eyes of the Snake Dowager!

Chapter 620: Of Curses and Dreams

Will walked out dejectedly. He had gained no further insight than Leylin’s encouragement. Other than that, he felt that this father whom he had never seen before was shrouded in a layer of dense fog.

“What’s wrong with Will?” Celine had instantly noticed this anomaly as she walked into Leylin’s villa carrying a silver plate.

“Freshly grounded coffee, personally made by me!” On the silver plate, white mist floated above the beige can and mug.

“Nothing much! Just a youth’s confusion!” Leylin smiled, held up a cup of coffee and said, “The taste is still as good as before!”

“You… How long are you going to be staying this time?” Celine bit her lips, watching Leylin with an evasive gaze. Compared to the previous time they met, Leylin now seemed like an ordinary man; there were no powerful energy waves being transmitted from his body anymore.

And yet, she knew that this was only a sign of Leylin becoming more powerful. It seemed like he had gained many things during his journey to the Icy Cave.

However, even if she’d known beforehand, Celine could only smile bitterly. One could only gain as much as their strength allowed them. Even if she knew about the existence of the world of ice before Leylin, any one of the giant icy creatures in there could kill her without even leaving her corpse behind.

And now, Celine keenly sensed that Leylin had already gained what he wanted, which was why Twilight Zone no longer attracted him. This discovery immediately made her uneasy.

“It may be quite some time, but it won’t be longer than a year!” Leylin took a sip of the rich and mellow coffee. However, the words he said caused Celine’s face to turn pale.

For a Magus, a year’s time was too short. Regardless of what was being done, it was not nearly enough. Even an experiment required a lot more time than this.

Seeing Celine’s unwilling expression, Leylin secretly sighed, but he did not say anything else. The entire Twilight Zone was just too barren. This place where even a rank 3 Magus could act like a tyrant and become a ruler was honestly too small. Only the larger central continent and the astral plane where there were endless profound mysteries were worthy of Leylin’s residence, allowing him to travel as much as he wanted in the future.

“In that case, can you let me follow you to the central continent?” Celine clenched her teeth.

“Of course you can, but I have to tell you a few things first!” Leylin looked at Celine with a profound expression in his pupils, “In the central continent, rank 2 Magi are merely like ants, their sheer number inconceivable. With your current strength, you will only be in the lowest rung of society there. Also, I already have a wife… Are you going to be willing to give up everything in Twilight Zone and leave with me?”

After hearing Leylin speak honestly about him already having a wife, Celine stumbled a few steps back, obviously not expecting it. And upon hearing that she had to give up the entirety of Twilight Zone, her expression darkened even further.

After a long silence, she finally made a decision. Smiling bitterly, she said, “Alright! I cannot give up on Mentor’s wish, nor on Twilight Zone. This is my home!”

Leylin smiled, “Perhaps I can make it up to you in other aspects! For example, didn’t you want my bloodline very badly before?”

This was a decision Leylin had made after long and careful deliberation. His current Kemoyin’s bloodline had already evolved to an extreme point, even reaching its genetic limits. There was no more room for improvement. Hence, the time was finally right to grow his family.

A rank 5 Warlock’s bloodline would be sufficient to form a terrifying power in a short period of time. With the restriction of the bloodline and his own ability as emperor to control all Giant Kemoyin Serpents, these bloodline descendants would become his most capable assistants in the future. Since he was prepared to grow the Farlier Family after his return, there was no harm in leaving another child behind in Twilight Zone.

“Really?” Celine’s eyes sparkled, and her face even flushed red with excitement. The terrifying innate abilities Leylin had displayed was proof enough that his descendants definitely wouldn’t turn out too bad. They might even inherit some powerful abilities from him. Such a bloodline was one that many female Magi sought, but few could obtain.

One Morning Star’s family always had a great chance of producing another among their ranks, much greater than that of other Magus clans. Perhaps one of her own descendants would be a strong Morning Star as well!

As she thought along this line, Celine’s breathing could not help but gradually get heavier.

Seeing Celine in such a state, Leylin could not help but burst out laughing. Although this woman had changed slightly, she was still that same old Celine in essence.

However, he did not hold much hope for her at all. Even if she was willing to give up everything in Twilight Zone and return to the central continent with him, she would at most be another good friend for Freya.

Furthermore, letting his bloodline grow in multiple places was also safer overall.

Leylin stroked his chin. His decision to grow his bloodline in many different places was certainly not about something as simple as expanding his influence.

Through his endless study on bloodline mutations and gene changing, he’d come to know that, with enough descendants, there was a chance that a genetic mutation would occur, allowing the individual’s strength to rise further than normal. Although such odds were small enough to be disregarded, there was always hope.

In fact, many Kemoyin Warlocks and other bloodline Warlocks practised this method. Whenever descendants of exceptionally rich bloodlines appeared, they would perceive it as fate’s blessing.

‘I have to go back once my Kemoyin Serpent Emperor bloodline has fully matured and I develop my Radiant Moon strength.’ Leylin’s pupils dimmed…

The boiling lava boomed endlessly. Many fiery dragons splashed about, and rocks shattered to expose a passageway that led upwards. A few black figures rushed out of the place directly.

“Damned Leylin and damned Twilight Zone! Chief, don’t you know that concentrated fire elemental particles are a great enemy for a female Magus’ skin? My maintenance charges for this mission are going to increase!” Carol pouted coquettishly, taking out a mirror and looking her skin over carefully.

However, the leader and the Magus called Eugene evidently did not care much.

“As long as this mission can be completed, no one would care even if you rested for a hundred years!” the leader snorted coldly. He ignored his subordinate’s complaints, much more interested in this territory.

“Tsk… This underground… the elemental particles are already so barren… It’s simply a desert for Magi!” On the other hand, Eugene also sighed while clicking his tongue, showing his disdain towards the barrenness of the Twilight Zone.

“Compared to the central continent, this place is indeed a desert. However, the darkness and earth elemental particle concentration is still passable, even if barely. Use spells of these two elements as much as possible to conserve your soul force…” The chief’s head tilted to one side, looking at Carol, “Carol, found the opponent yet?”

“Let me see…” Carol took out a transparent crystal ball. In the core of this ball was a black wisp of air that swayed back and forth. This was Leylin’s aura, collected from Mount Asura.

Although Leylin had covered his traces very carefully, as long as such Magi had the correct location and suitable spells, finding his tracks was only a matter of time.

A black stream of air emerged on Carol’s face. After pondering for a moment with her eyes closed, she pointed towards the north and spoke confidently. “He’s in that direction, I’m sure of it.”

“Good! Now that we’ve discovered the opponent’s position, won’t three Radiant Moons like us be able to deal with a simple Morning Star?” Eugene licked his lips, “That rascal made me run about outside for such a long time. I want him!”

This leader nodded, “We can. But the target is still as strong as a Radiant Moon himself, do not underestimate him. However, I have information that the target still has a weakness. Even if he has fighting strength at the Radiant Moon realm and powerful bloodline imprints, he is still a Morning Star at his core. The strength of his truesoul is limited to the peak of Morning Star. If we cast curses or attack the soul…”

“It’ll be very safe!” Carol nodded. “Just nice, there’s been some progress in my research on soul curses recently, just leave it to me!”

“The two of us will assist!” The leader looked at Eugene, and the latter agreed with a little reluctance, “Alright! You’re the leader. Whatever you say goes!” Evidently, he was a little depressed because he was unable to draw blood directly.

“Leylin! Hurry to school, you’re going to be late!” A foreign yet familiar voice echoed in his ears, making Leylin a little confused.

“Where is this? A.I. Chip?” Around him was a road, cherry blossom trees in full bloom on both sides. Blossoms drifted down to the street one after the other.

The ground was very clean, without any sorts of paper scraps. Leylin looked at his own hands, his skin that was milky white without much musculature was full of youth.

“…” There was no response from the A.I. Chip, causing Leylin to fall into a deep silence.

At this moment, a large chunk of memory entered his brain. “I’m Leylin! Innocent Saints High School, year 3 student! I also have an elder sister and a younger sister in my family, I’m supposed to go to the campus festival….”

“Why… Why do I feel like I’ve forgotten something important, and what is an A.I. Chip? Why did I remember it subconsciously?” Looking at the checkered shirt on his body and the student name tag on his chest, Leylin became quiet in an instant.

“Hey Leylin, what’s wrong with you?” A blonde haired student walked over, pulling Leylin’s arm along with him.

“Serway…” Leylin called out the student’s once he opened his mouth, which made him fall into greater confusion, ‘I need to calm down… Why do I know his name? Where exactly is this?’

“What are you waiting for? We won’t make it in time!” Serway stopped a taxi, shoving Leylin into it before following closely behind, “Driver, Innocent Saints High School!”

“Have you lost your mind? The famous singer, Carol has a concert at the campus festival today…”

Chapter 621: Carol

“Carol?” Leylin leaned back against the couch while feeling the familiar rumble of the engine, his mind fuzzy. ‘Seems to be a very famous singer, said to be the idol of teenagers in the Furze Federation… Also seems to be slightly related to me, but… I don’t remember anymore…’

Memories related to the other person immediately emerged in Leylin’s brain, ‘Only, why do I keep feeling that something’s wrong? This shouldn’t be my life… My life…’

Leylin stretched out his right hand and a word suddenly emerged in his brain: “Fire!” This was pronounced in the ancient Byron language, but tens of seconds passed and nothing happened.

“What’s wrong with you Leylin? Devising new words? Why haven’t I heard this before, is this German or Spanish?” Serway asked thoughtlessly as he looked at the scenery outside the window from time to time.

“Neither! I may have pronounced it wrongly…” Leylin’s face was slightly flushed, but his heart was stirring, ‘What happened just now, why did I have a premonition that something interesting would happen after reading that phone… No! Why do I remember this syllable?’

*Skrrrrr!* Following the sound of sudden brakes, the taxi stopped in front of a beautiful institution.

A large coniferous tree and a holly tree stood on both sides of a white marble statue. In front of the entrance was a banner— Innocent Saints 57th Campus Festival.

Below the banner, there was a row of tiny words written in black ink using felt-tip pens and spray paint — Welcoming the beautiful Miss Carol’s arrival. We will support you forever! A smiley face was even drawn after it, and Leylin felt like laughing upon seeing it.

“This lad is a student of Innocents Saints High School? Work hard…” The taxi driver waved his hand and disappeared into the road. Leylin secretly rolled his eyes at the hand that was stretched out of the car’s window.

After walking into the school, Leylin could see the bustle of a large crowd. Many teenage boys in shirts and teenage girls in dresses hovered around a colourful tent that was set up temporarily. From time to time, playful giggles also echoed from within. Colourful confetti fluttered gently while a sweet, symphonic music permeated the place.

“Brother! Why aren’t you moving? You were the last one we were missing!” A small girl came over and pulled Leylin by the hands, giving him a feeling of warmth.

Leylin fell into a trance for a moment as chunks of memories emerged one after the other in his mind. This young lady was his younger sister Gail, currently in year one. And yet, this familiar face seemed foreign as well, causing him to be somewhat dazed. “Aren’t I here now?” he said in reply.

“Let’s go! Let’s go!” Serway and Gail, one behind the other, brought Leylin to the side of a large open stage.

“Hurry and start work, oh Debugging Master!” Serway pushed Leylin to a mechanical platform that was filled with joysticks and buttons, taking out a huge heart shaped bouquet of roses from his back as if he was performing magic. He shifted his attention towards a tall girl in the dance team, a sight that caused Leylin to roll his eyes.

“What’s the matter? Is there a problem? Nooo! Miss Carol will be here soon!” Gail was looking at Leylin who stood looking silly in front of the debugging platform. Thinking that the machine malfunctioned or something, she couldn’t help but pace back and forth as a layer of tears appeared in her eyes.

Seeing Gail like that, Leylin secretly heaved a sigh of relief and came before the debugging platform, “Oh it’s fine, I was just thinking about something and my mind kind of wandered off…”

The moment he came in front of the platform, his hands moved to its surface, beginning to work subconsciously. Numerous lights lit up, and the curtains on the stage were slowly drawn back.

‘Okay! The joysticks and sliding platforms are all normal, just do it according to the previous procedure and it’ll be fine…’ Leylin rubbed his forehead, feeling that things had grown more unexpected. The knowledge of the debugging machine seemed to have been shoved into his brain all of a sudden, and although he felt extremely familiar with it fear began to rise in his heart.

“Yay! My brother is the best, you’re awesome!” Gail jumped in glee. Seeing her like that, along with the gentle and kind memory of his elder sister, Leylin suddenly felt that such a life… didn’t seem all that bad.

This thought seemed to have only come up for a moment, but it made his heart stir as if he discovered something incredible. Fragments of memories poured into his mind, as if he was watching some sort of movie.

He’d seen an ignorant and underdeveloped world that was filled with a mysterious force called magic. He seemed to have been exploring that place.

‘Hmm… Is this what I dreamt of last night? Maybe I can use it as an idea for a novel or something…’ Leylin stroked his chin, but he still had the nagging feeling that things weren’t so simple.

While Leylin had sunk into deep thought, a loud, deafening clamour sounded out. Many people rushed out to gather at the front of the stage in a flood, breaking his train of thought.

“Look! Sister Carol is here!” Gail shouted in excitement as well, squeezing forward on tiptoes.

“Isn’t she just a celebrity? Just you wait, I’ll get a few autographed photos and postcards for you later!” Leylin snorted.

“Of course you can take as many photos of her as you want, but the current scenario is different! I’m so excited…” Gail squeezed forward even more, but Leylin grew confused, “Wait, what do you mean I can take as many as I want, am I very close to her?”

But Gail had already disappeared into the crowd, making Leylin lose someone to question.

Carol slowly walked to the centre of the stage, accompanied by the hysterical shouts of the crowd. The many spotlights emitted a dazzling brilliance even in the day as colourful mist spread out and surrounded her.

“Carol!” “Carol!” “Carol!” “We love you!”

Numerous teenagers screamed at the top of their lungs, almost to the point that Leylin could not help but cover his ears, feeling as if his eardrums had been destroyed.

At the same time, his gaze shifted, attracted to the girl at the centre of the stage. Carol wore a magnificent costume that wasn’t the dazzling kind, with two plaits hanging down gently from her haid. Her face was so exquisite she looked like a doll.

“Thank you! I love you all too!” Carol looked at the fans below and smiled sweetly, causing many fanatical fans to cover her in another round of adulation.

Her voice was very airy, melding well with her personality to form a unique aura. Even a few words from her generated an extraordinary attraction.

“Next, let’s invite Miss Carol to perform her famous song for us — Flight!” Because of Carol’s presence, the two emcees were almost forgotten. Patiently waiting for their chance, they immediately announced the song.

“Okay! Start the background music!” Leylin wore his headphones, but Carol who was on the stage, made a signal to stop.

“Wait! I have another piece of news here for everyone,” Carol smiled, carrying a rare hint of excitement in her voice. “My trip to Innocent Saints’ campus this time was on my boyfriend’s invitation. Yes! I’m in love!”

The place instantly fell into a deathly silence. Carol, who was famous across the entirety of the Furze Federation and had always been lovely idol, was actually in love, and with a high school student?

This storm immediately petrified the surrounding audience. Soon after, a howl echoed, livening the atmosphere at the scene.

“What? No! Carol, you’re my goddess, how can you…” “Oh! No! How is that possible?” Many teenage boys clenched their chests in pain and collapsed. Leylin even felt like he could hear the sound of their glass hearts shattering.

But even more of the audience waved the fresh flowers, lightsticks and other items in their hands and said, “Carol, we support you!”

“Thank you!” Carol bowed at the audience below with reddened eyes, “I’d like to invite my boyfriend up to sing Flight with me! To commemorate this day…” Upon hearing this, many of the students looked at one another, as if they were trying to identify Carol’s boyfriend.

‘Wahaha… This Carol’s boyfriend is going to get unlucky!’ Leylin thought gloatingly.

“Then, aren’t you going to hurry up there?” Who knew since when, Serway and Gail had appeared beside Leylin again, pulling him onto the stage.

“Brother! Sister Carol has already mustered her courage like that, what are you still waiting for?” Gail tugged on Leylin’s sleeve, laughing like a small fox that had successfully stolen a chicken.

“Eh? What what? It’s me?” Leylin pointed at his own nose, “Carol’s boyfriend is me?” Suddenly, another memory appeared again.

“Leylin, remember our promise!” Wearing a pretty ribbon on her head, Carol pulled Leylin’s hand.

Only at this moment did Leylin recall. it seemed… As if… Should be… Roughly… Carol had actually been his neighbour for 3 years, and it was at that time that the two had embarked on a romantic relationship.

After being dragged onto the stage with Carol pulling his hand, facing the multiple spotlights and the fervent gazes of many geeks, Leylin’s face was still a little stiff.

“Are you serious? This scenario just isn’t right…” Leylin felt slightly dizzy. At this moment, the gentle background music started playing, and an angelic voice echoed from beside him.

Leylin looked slightly dazed as he watched this beautiful fairy-like girl beside him. Her voice was airy like no other, as clear as spring water. It seemed like even her spirit could cleanse him, it was extremely refreshing. This was especially true of her eyes. Those eyes were full of emotion as she sang, making it extremely difficult for him to part with her.

‘An affluent life, and the admiration of a celebrity, all this is so wonderful… What am I still waiting for?’ Leylin could not help but question himself.

But at the same time, the uneasiness in his heart grew stronger, a feeling that he would regret the wrong decision here for the rest of his life.

‘That’s right! My dreams, my goals, my original pursuits, what exactly are they?’ Leylin asked himself repeatedly.

Chapter 623: Trial and Destruction

A Magus created spells by using his spiritual force to draw the energy particles in the air. The current Leylin could cause a mysterious change with just a spoken rune syllable and the injection of spiritual force.

A ball of flames formed in front of Leylin and a huge wall of fire spread out, blocking the white light.

The figures that were armoured in black could only see a huge amount of flames appearing out of thin air to collide with the laser. The teen himself was still safe and sound.

*Plop!* An armoured man loosened his grip and dropped his laser gun. A peculiar scene such as this was still a first for them despite their years of war experience and the gory training they’d undergone.

“Mutants!” The leader cried.

“Mutants? Is this what your world calls people with mysterious powers?” Leylin laughed and placed his hands behind his back, sizing up his surroundings with a sense of nostalgia. ‘Is this a dream? Or a world generated from my memories? Though there are many similarities to my previous world, there are still quite a few differences…’

“Our target is her, you can leave!” The leader said in a low voice. Being one of the few higher-ups that knew of the existence of Mutants, how could he not be afraid of Leylin’s abilities?

“Scram!” But Leylin only looked at them apathetically as if he was looking at prey.

“You-” The leader’s face flushed with anger.

He pulled out a glimmering ring from his waist.

“Magnetic Hybrid Storm No. 2! This is specially created to counter weapons created by Mutants! If you are to leave now, we will treat it as nothing happened.”

“Hm, interesting!” The ring disappeared from the leader’s hand in an instant and showed up in Leylin’s.

“Spatial power? Or high-speed movement?” Cold sweat gathered on the leader’s forehead.

“How ignorant and stupid!” Leylin looked at them sympathetically and colour drained from the leader’s face.

This was a Mutant who allowed him no chance of resistance and who could snatch the weapon from his hand in seconds. Leylin was definitely someone beyond what he could handle, and it was highly possible for his whole team would die here!

“We have to leave quickly!” The leader shouted as a mini laser gun appeared in his hand. He aimed several fatal beams at Leylin.

*Pew!* All the laser rays were blocked by a golden curtain before flames burst forth.

The massive flames illuminated the surroundings with a fiery red glow, the last sight this leader would see before he left the world.

Carol stood rooted to the ground, suddenly realising that the Leylin in front of her was very much different from the Leylin she knew. He seemed a lot more confident and exuded a monstrous aura. Although she thought of things such as power and aura as a joke, she learnt then that there was true power in this world.

Just a mere flash of red light could turn those threatening enemies into ashes. If someone with such power wasn’t greater than the rest, who was?

“You are Carol, right?” In front of her stood the person she was familiar with speaking with a voice she was familiar with, but she couldn’t help but move back.

“Who are you? Don’t come near me! Where is Leylin?” Tears gathered in the girl’s eyes. She wanted to leave this person, but an invisible force brought her in front of him.

“Are you the focal point in this world?” Leylin smiled gently at her and began to say things that made her mind spin. “Through the allure of choices presented to me and tricking me into making decisions through emotions, my truesoul will forever be confined in this makeshift world huh?”

Carol knew the meaning of each individual word Leylin was saying but was confused at their intended meaning.

“Seems like someone’s been targeting me…” Leylin touched his chin, “A.I. Chip, how do I get out?”

[Beep! Host body affected by unknown radiation, truesoul at a loss.]

[Beep! Fog appeared in host’s sea of consciousness, affecting cognitive abilities. Beginning projection of guiding coordinates…]

The A.I. Chip’s reply came instantly this time, accompanied with numerous status updates.

The A.I. Chip was fused with leylin’s very soul. No matter where he went, his truesoul’s survival meant the A.I. Chip’s survival. Enemies stood a chance of intercepting this connection for a short while, but they couldn’t break it.

The A.I. Chip was continuously trying to awaken Leylin’s truesoul. This was also why he was so quick to see through the hazy world so quickly.

“A.I. Chip, begin scan. The target is this entire world.” Leylin commanded.

[Beep! Mission established, scan beginning…]

With the update after his advancement to Radiant Moon, the changes were not merely cosmetic. The Chip’s various functions had been updated as well.

[Scanning 3D structure! Instability detected! Absence of plane curves, concluded as unstable world!]

[Curse detected. Concluded as dream curse.]

The A.I. Chip responded quickly.

“As expected, someone dragged me into a trance with a curse… “ Leylin’s face slowly warped as he read through the data.

“In order to break out of this trance, we have to start from the ‘key’ of this world and then neutralise the counterattack!” Leylin came to Carol.

“W-What do you want? Don’t come near me!” Carol moved backwards in fear, but Leylin maintained his poker face and pointed a finger at her forehead.

*Boom!* The world shook, and Carol fell down.

Though she had yet to die, Leylin could feel the connection between her and some form of entity weakening.

“Carol is only a shell, the counterattack should be coming soon after I’m done dealing with the ‘key’!” Leylin said, floating in mid-air as the very space vibrated.

“Gail, look! That person over there, he looks like Leylin!” Serway’s jaw dropped.

“It, it really is him! Did he become a superhero?” Gail ruffled her hair and seemed to be a little dizzy. Had her useless brother been pretending all along, hiding a secret life as a superhero? Was he one of those who secretly guarding the world’s peace?

A piercing anti-aircraft alarm sounded, and violet light filled the entire city. A large number of UFOs surrounded the area, armoured men flying out from within. Complex energy circuits flashed from on their armours, that worn by the troops from before complete trash in comparison.

These people with peculiar energy undulations should’ve been the Mutants that the leader of those troops was talking about. They looked pretty advanced.

“UFOs… Is this the extraterrestrial colonisation fleet of the federation? God!” Many students and passersby started screaming on the ground. The few figures in front especially made them feel like they were suffocating just by looking at them.

Delusion and reality, illusion and mystery, things that only existed in conjectures, were all suddenly appearing front of everyone’s eyes, giving them a strong sense of intangibility.

A ray of blue light scanned over Leylin’s body, and the scanned data flashed across the glasses of the person leading the troop. It was like he instantly knew Leylin’s identity.

“Leylin, year 3 student of Innocent Saints High School… How dare you use your powers carelessly in public as a Mutant? Return with us to the headquarters to receive your punishment!”

“Well…” Leylin shook his head and sighed, “Why weren’t you here before when we were being attacked? And now you come over with such speed when everything’s solved? I protest!” The mocking tone in Leylin’s voice caused the person to furrow his brows. He decided to teach a good lesson to the arrogant young man in front of him.

“Who do you think you are? The headquarters only take actions against our own kind; humans are exempted. Prepare to be tried for your crimes!”

The troop leader waved his hand, and two figures ran towards Leylin.

“Hmm… As expected, weakness is a sin no matter what world you’re in.” Leylin sighed, and frenzied energy undulations burst forth from his body.

*Whoosh!* Huge clouds of smog wrapped around two Mutants. The sound of blood dripping was heard, and when the smog cleared, a few damaged bones and metal components fell down. The two people were nowhere to be seen.

*Boom!* The glasses of the leader’s eyes exploded, the scratches from the shrapnel forming blood red lines across his face. Yet, he didn’t seem to care at all, only glaring at Leylin as he muttered in disbelief, “Silvan-ranked! He is a Silvan-ranked Mutant!”

Many of them took a step back, as if realising they’d been surrounding a monster all this while.

Mutant of the Silvan-ranked is the highest of all the levels as of current times. They only existed in rumours, and were strong enough to cause energy probes to blow up!

The thought of going against someone of this standard made many of the troop members shudder.

“If the situation is as such, your Grace, shall we…” The leader clenched his teeth and walked forward, but Leylin did not want to waste any more time on them.

“What a group of clowns. The counter-measures of this world are weak, so weak that I’m disappointed!” A tiny black orb appeared on his finger, and he flicked it forward.

“You lot haven’t seen real strength! The pitch-black orb absorbed all light, causing space itself to collapse.

The terrifying turbulence enveloped all the UFOs and enemies.

Chapter 634: Reflection and Experimentation

After Jeffrey left Leylin’s castle, the sunny smile on Leylin’s face slowly crumbled, a brooding look taking its place. “A Warlock that has inherited a rank 6 bloodline? Interesting. Very interesting!”

Till now, the highest bloodlines he’d seen were those of the Sun’s Child which was rank 6, and the blood of the rank 7 bronze female giant who’d comprehended laws.

As for the fire phoenix, perhaps that wasn’t even a bloodline creature at all. Even though he possessed the egg, Leylin had no way to extract a bloodline from it.

The bloodline of the Sun’s Child had been completely exhausted after Leylin had created two bloodline imprints, and the bloodline of the bronze female giant had been a huge driving force in Leylin’s bloodline evolution. Not only were the quantities of blood in both cases meagre, neither had even come with a real body. After they were used up, they had disappeared.

Things would be different with a Warlock who had inherited a rank 6 bloodline. The fellow would have a complete body, and even if he were to lose some of his bloodline. This was different for a bloodline Warlock who had inherited the bloodline of a rank 6 creature, he could probably make up for it with the natural regeneration of blood by his body.

‘Based on what Jeffrey said, he has already become a Radiant Moon Warlock. The bloodline in his body meets my requirements as well, even if barely. However, if I want the best effects, I should wait till he advances to Breaking Dawn. When his bloodline force is at its best, I can reap the most perfect fruit…’ Leylin stroked his chin, his lips curving up.

Though Warlocks had the ability to regenerate blood, bloodlines were not quite as simple. Leylin believed that ancient bloodlines inherited by Warlocks could not be extracted without limit, as they had a close connection to their sources.

There was no issue if a small part of the bloodline was extracted, but if the other party was used as a blood bank, their bloodline would soon be exhausted. This would have the same effect even on ancient creatures.

Whatever it was, the bloodline of a rank 5 Warlock, especially that from a Warlock who had inherited his bloodline from an ancient Breaking Dawn Creature, was basically a moving treasure trove for Leylin. Forget purifying it or making imprints from it, just observing how a rank 6 bloodline interacted with the body would bring great benefits to his bloodline experiments.

But of course, the other party would definitely not let himself be treated as a guinea pig.

‘Forget that for now, I’ll decide on that after looking at his attitude. Right now, I need to think about the Blazing Flame Monarch.’ Leylin stood up and entered the astral laboratory.

Melinda had tried to entice him into dealing with the Blazing Flame Monarch together, stating that she knew of his weakness. In order to gain his trust, she’d even given him some information, and the A.I. Chip had tested its veracity. However, the most important bit was still in her possession, and there was nothing Leylin could do about that.

He obviously knew that she wouldn’t divulge key information until the time for the operation came. There was no other way about it. And since the other side would give him no more information, Leylin could only begin thinking of ways to increase his own strength. No matter what the situation was, he could not go wrong with that.

“In actuality, the best method is to hole myself up and then deal with the Flame Monarch after I reach Breaking Dawn!”

‘Truth be told, it’s best that I hole myself up and deal with the Blazing Flame Monarch only after I reach Breaking Dawn.’ Although Leylin thought this way, it was a pity that he had been attacked by the Monarch. He now knew that this was impossible.

Leylin could feel an obvious malicious desire from him. It told him the Monarch was intent on eliminating him. The only reason for the current silence was that the opponent needed to recover some strength. Once they reacted completely, the most terrifying of strengths would be brought to bear on Leylin like lightning.

‘Shit! When did I ever provoke them? Even if it was the previous time, he was the one who dispatched Magi to attack me!’ Leylin felt that he was being wronged, and was rather confused.

There was no reason for the Flame Monarch’s hatred towards him.

Of course, the Blazing Flame Monarch had always had a strange temper. Back then, if not for Offa and the other rank 5 Radiant Moon standing up to the leader of the Warlocks purge campaign in time, perhaps the central continent would not exist today.

After cursing the opponent a few times, Leylin found he could not do anything about it. He’d been walking as he delved into thought, and the A.I. Chip’s robotic voice sounded automatically the moment he walked through the laboratory.

[Beep! Host body has entered range of astral laboratory. Beginning sterilisation and disinfection. Beginning automatic sterilisation and disinfecting.]

Once the voice sounded, Leylin’s body was covered with a layer of black as fiery red light cleaned it top to bottom.

This was an essential procedure for interplanar experiments. With such complete measures that cleverly made use of magic, Leylin felt like this laboratory matched up to the high-end laboratories of his previous world, even surpassing them in some aspects.

Completing the sterilisation and having prepared his defences, Leylin arrived at the astral laboratory. He did not head for the astral gate straight away, and instead entered one of the binding rooms beside it.

Blue light rippled in a massive pool made not of water, but condensed lightning. Densely packed confinement and isolation runes separated it from the outside. This sort of strict defence was obviously prepared to confine a creature or material from the astral plane.

After he reached Radiant Moon, Leylin’s ability to explore the astral plane had improved greatly. With the additional help of the A.I. Chip, he’d obtained various harvests every time he activated his gate. Though he hadn’t yet found a foreign world with no World Will, he’d acquired quite a few scraps, even meeting a wanderer in the astral plane and making a few deals.

There were even a few astral beings who were unlucky enough to charge headfirst into Leylin’s side, arriving at this world through his gate. These beings eventually became Leylin’s spoils from his explorations and were all collected here.

Large numbers of confinement runes formed several separate frames at the bottom of the pool. Various strange items were placed within each. One of them was a creature similar to a black octopus with numerous illusory tentacles touching the edges of the frames, as if trying to probe something before being frightened back by the terrifying current.

*Wooh wooh…* Practically at the very moment Leylin arrived, the octopus quickly withdrew into a ball, as if Leylin was some horrifying demon.

“Looks like I was too rough with it…” Leylin laughed as he read through the records by the A.I. Chip.

[Spectral Octopus: Astral Being. Period Since Capture: 15 days, 9 hours. Currently in good condition, no distinct need to eat.]

The image that the A.I. Chip provided had numbers all over the different parts of the octopus, with some conjectures included. Everything about this spectral octopus was being shown to him.

“Training the soul is extremely troublesome. The method the ancients passed down is to constantly probe the astral plane, simulating and understanding its rules to allow one’s own soul to evolve…” Such a method took too much time and consumed a tremendous amount of astral stones. However, it was safe and effective.

The vast astral plane was truly boundless, and it encompassed all things. Experiencing the working of such a thing was very beneficial for a Magus’ truesoul.

Leylin, however, had the cheat that was the phoenix egg. He had no need for this. If not for his own vitality being unable to keep up and his fear of the issues that would arise due to a lack of coordination between the body and a rapidly strengthened soul, he would long since have broken through to the peak of Radiant Moon.

To him, interplanar experiments carried a whole different meaning. “I’ve already pushed the paths of a Warlock and Magus to the limits for now. If I need to strengthen myself quickly, the only ways left are in other worlds…”

Leylin’s eyes were calm. He who had the A.I. Chip constantly analysing things for him knew very clearly the paths of Warlocks and Magi. He understood that his strength had reached its peak until he could deal with the issue of body-soul balance, which was why he’d shifted his attention to the astral plane.

Since he had reached a bottleneck in his own path, it was a good idea to walk on others. Such a thing would definitely be beneficial to him.

On top of that, Leylin had never given up his search for the Purgatory World!

The attention from the Snake Dowager had given him a terrible premonition. He did not want to meet her when he was caught unprepared one day, and wished to solve this problem himself. Finding the coordinates to the Purgatory World was therefore of extreme importance.

The coordinates to the Purgatory World were something the Warlocks of the Ouroboros Clan yearned for, which was why after obtaining the information left behind by those Kemoyin Warlocks, Leylin’s progress in this area had increased rapidly.

Leylin, who had the innate ability of control due to his Kemoyin Serpent Emperor bloodline, naturally knew how terrifying a creature like the Snake Dowager was.

If possible, he obviously did not want to meet her now, but it was necessary to make some preparations for the future.

“I’ve been using so many astral stones without care, and I only got so much…”

Leylin gazed at the items in the restraining lightning pool, speechless, “It’s no wonder that Morning Star Magi spend so many resources to no avail. Things like this that rely on luck are too scary. This is my result with the aid of the A.I. Chip; other Magi won’t even have this much…”

Leylin’s astral stone consumption had reached a terrifying stage, and he’d even used up all the astral stones belonging to the Ouroboros Clan. If not for the Warlock Union replenishing his supply, he would’ve faced a problem with the energy for his future experiments.

Even then, he wasn’t lucky enough to have gathered many resources, and he was facing a net loss…

Chapter 635: Feather and Dream

“A trip to the astral plane is like a sea voyage during the era of exploration. Few people successfully found new continents, returning with gold. Most just ended up as skeletons buried deep under the sea.…” Leylin sighed.

He left the binding room and came before the astral gate, a grey feather appearing in his palm. This feather looked very ordinary, with nothing different about it, as if it was a regular feather from a bird.

However, Leylin knew how unordinary it was. The feather had been a gift from the owl which had come from the crack between reality and dreams.

“Dreamscape is in actuality another world of dreams. I wonder if I can make contact with it using the astral gate.”

Before this day, Leylin had already used the A.I. Chip to scan the feather multiple times, performing many experiments. However, he’d had no results.

The results showed that this was the most ordinary of feathers.

Now, with no other ideas, he decided to use it in an interplanar experiment, hoping to link to Dreamscape.

In the boundless astral plane, the two most powerful worlds he knew of were the Magus World and the World of Gods.

Of course, due to the ancient war, both of these worlds had been weakened, though the Magus World was now gradually regaining its former glory.

Dreamscape was the strangest and most mysterious world! Time and space were misleading and the place was filled with various indefinite laws.

Things that were obvious and followed common sense did not exist there. In other words, everything was topsy-turvy, and it was a world with no real laws.

Even the ancient Magus World had been taken aback when met with the invasion by Dreamscape. Of course, it was also due to this very instability that Dreamscape’s attack had started strong but sputtered out.

“Though it’s full of all sorts of strange things, that’s an opportunity for me!” Leylin’s eyes gleamed. Other worlds had existences that abided by objective laws. Personal growth required much time and energy there.

However, anything was possible in Dreamscape. If he wanted to obtain the most strength in the shortest amount of time, he would have to go in there and try his luck.

Of course, he had to be prepared to return with no benefits.

‘A.I. Chip!’ Leylin commanded inwardly. When he had entered, Leylin’s soul force had long since taken control of all the apparatus and energy sources here, and then handed it over to the A.I. Chip to manage.

Though Leylin had set up a spirit genie here, that was just a ruse. How could such low-levelled programs match up to his A.I. Chip?

[Beep! Energy source beginning preparations. Routes detected to be normal. Rate of wear and tear at 0.0017. Beginning connection with astral gate]

The A.I. Chip quickly intoned. Along with its robotic prompt, all the apparatus in the laboratory activated methodically. The rays of light and the sounds combined to form the most splendid of symphonies.

Under the control of the A.I. Chip, Leylin’s usage of everything in the laboratory was as fluent as him using his own arm.

[Astral gate has been engaged!]

In the laboratory, the stone gate emanating weak starlight rumbled, being covered by blue light in the form of flames.

Countless mysterious links were generated in the flames, and the void crumbled, revealing the shadows of innumerable unknown places.

A river of light was formed entirely out of blue stars that were the shadows of these foreign worlds, majestically surging into the darkness unknown.

“No matter how many times I see this, I can’t help but praise it…” Leylin murmured as a glint of fervour shone in his eyes. After his advance to the Radiant Moon realm, the form of this astral gate before his eyes had been changed as well, and his exploration of the astral plane had become more thorough.

A great, ancient aura was being transmitted from the astral gate, and Leylin immediately turned serious as he closed his eyes, sensing everything attentively.

Bits of blue starlight covered his body, and with the passage of time, the rays on it grew more solid, to the point that they resembled actual flames.

Within the point mass, the crescent that was his truesoul abruptly emanated clear rays of light. It seemed to have absorbed something from the astral plane, in the process becoming more pure and dazzling. His soul force that had been supplemented greatly by the phoenix egg seemed to be rinsed and purified as it completely stabilised.

“The mysteries of the astral plane, and its resonance with the soul…” Leylin’s eyes seemed different as he opened them, “I need a complete harmony between my soul and the rest of the world. Once I reach the realm of that fusion, the next step will be to synchronise my soul with the astral plane. No matter what path to power I use, at the end it still feels strangely familiar, like I’m coming back home…”

It was great that this experience strengthened his truesoul. However, when he glanced at the astral gate the elation on his face turned into a wry smile. The blue flames on the surface of the gate had shrunk to about half their original size, and part of the astral stones outside had lost their lustre, becoming fragmented.

Leylin froze before asking the A.I. Chip, “A.I. Chip! How long was I out of it for?”

[Beep! Host has been standing for 2h 34min 12s.]

The A.I. Chip answered faithfully.

“So much time has passed already…” Leylin shook his head and suddenly came to a realisation, “No wonder most of the energy from the astral stone reserves has been consumed…”

He now knew why Morning Star Magi did not use the astral gate to train their souls. There was no other reason than that it was too extravagant. Leylin had prepared a lot of astral stones for this experiment. He had merely been a little absorbed in feeling the aura for a short period of time, and this had happened.

If he were to be caught in a trance for a while longer, he might just use up all the astral stones here. The amount of astral stones here was something many Morning Star Magi took decades to earn, and would use over ten years.

Since the effort put in and the rewards were not proportional, it was understandable that this method had been discarded.

“Even Breaking Dawn Magi will find it painful to engage in such an extravagant method of training. Even they might not be able to keep up with the cost…” Leylin shook his head and produced the grey feather.

The soft feather fluttered and, following a breeze, slowly flew through the air towards the blue flames of the astral gate.

“What kind of world is Dreamscape? Is this attempt going to be useful?” Leylin seemed slightly nervous.

Using the feather as a coordinate and throwing it into the astral gate was something he did with no other option. Whether he succeeded or failed, the feather would completely disappear, which was why he was rather apprehensive.

*Pu!* The moment the edge of the grey feather made contact with the flames, there was a wondrous change. Large amounts of blue fire crawled onto its surface, and with a gentle sound they began to flash. The owl’s feather burned to ashes in the flames.

*Rumble!* As if gas had been poured onto them, the flames rose several metres high, being coloured a bright orange.

The whole stone gate began to shake, as if it had been linked to some immensely powerful existence.

‘Have I succeeded?’ “A.I. Chip!” Leylin called out lowly.

[Record of data from astral gate complete. Beginning search of coordinates…]

The A.I. Chip’s emotionless voice rang out, and the flames grew more intense.

The shadows of countless worlds came into view and quickly slipped away, flashing past in front of the astral gate allowing it a mere fleeting glance. Leylin, whose soul force was linked with the astral gate, seemed to see a very mysterious world.

On the exterior, numerous dream worlds formed a long starry river. The world itself was like a twisting hourglass, full of mystery and a feeling of asymmetry.

“Is this Dreamscape?” Leylin muttered.

However, this scene did not last for long. A piercing warning sounded.

[Warning! Warning! Astral gate undulations have grown unstable. Recommended action: Halt search!]

“Are you kidding? I’ve only just seen the edges of Dreamscape, and haven’t been able to deduce the coordinates…”

Leylin’s eyes were fixed on the scene in the astral gate as he muttered, “Faster. Faster!”

Cracks appeared on the surface of the astral gate, but the scenes behind were gaining more clarity. Leylin didn’t bother with the change as he took several steps forward.

*Rumble!* At this moment, however, the fissures on the gate expanded, forming large explosive ripples that swept Leylin within.

The virtual image of Dreamscape immediately disappeared. Amidst the explosion, Leylin’s roars could be heard, “No, damn it! I just needed a minute, or even half a minute! With that, I can completely determine the coordinates of Dreamscape!”

[Host’s laboratory has exploded. Handling using emergency plan number 3. In process of stabilising space. Allocating usage of rank 2 rune.]

The A.I. Chip’s robotic voice rang.

With its operation, groups of robotic puppets went ahead, coordinating with the spell formation and beginning to clean the rubble in the laboratory.

A neutralising water current that carried the piercing smell of disinfectant was sprinkled from the ceiling of the laboratory, drenching everything.

In just ten or so minutes, the rubble in the laboratory had been cleaned, and the radiation from the other world had been isolated.

At the heart of the explosion, Leylin stood expressionlessly, a black layer emerging on his body. He had not sustained any injuries in the explosion.

Chapter 636: Spatial Conversion

Leylin stared at the large pit in front of him absent-mindedly, hands still maintaining the position from when he had been casting the spell.

In front of him, all that was left of the astral gate were ruins. Terrifying electric currents and radiations were still present in some places, but with the A.I. Chip’s directions those, too, were quickly isolated and extinguished.

Though the explosion of the astral gate was dangerous, danger depended on the individual facing it as well. In the face of Leylin’s Kemoyin scales that had been strengthened to rank 5, the stray undulations from the explosion were nothing. Even the area around him was completely safe.

Even so, the destruction of the astral gate, as well as the loss of the coordinates, left Leylin’s heart aching.

The amount of astral stones needed to construct an astral gate again was negligible with the large organisation of the Warlock Union backing him, and amassing even more astral stones wouldn’t be a problem given some time. However, the loss of Dreamscape was a huge blow to him.

“Did I fail…” Leylin sighed, expelling the sorrow in his heart. When he raised his head once again, his eyes were now calm once more.

“If the coordinates of Dreamscape are gone, then so be it. I was expecting too much when I thought I could use the material from a strange creature and find the coordinates anyway. Furthermore, as I am now a foreign world is too powerful for me to explore…”

Leylin shook his head as he ordered, “A.I. Chip, tidy up the place!” He turned to leave the laboratory, but when he pulled the door open, Leylin’s pupils shrank.

“This place…” In front of him was a tremendous barren desert. Three strange suns shone in the skies, boiling heat waves everywhere. The friction between his shoes and the rocky yellow sand was audible.

Leylin looked up and around, finding the place completely desolate. At the base of a hill, he could see the broken tip of a building. The thing seemed to have toppled over an unknown amount of time ago, the signs of age extremely obvious on the surface.

‘A.I. Chip, begin scan!’ Leylin picked up a signboard that had landed near his feet. He could not read the words, but he felt a sense of familiarity from them. The black board did not feel too heavy in his hands and creaked with the slightest application of strength, as if ready to break into smithereens at any moment.

Blue light from the A.I. Chip scanned the thing, and it immediately came to a conclusion.

[Based on carbon 14 dating, estimated age: 21982 years, 11 months…]

“Over twenty thousand years ago?” Leylin stroked his chin and tossed the signboard. As soon as the thing hit the ground, it cracked apart into fragments, some bits even turning into powder.

“Where is this place?” Leylin raised his head, looking at the three strange suns that were still scorching the place.

Of the three, the one on the left was distorted, like a circle that had been twisted multiple times. The one in the middle was round, but there were numerous tentacles on the outside that made it seem rather horrifying. The one on the right? It was a complicated polygon, with its sunlight holding a different tint.

Leylin turned back, and found his astral plane laboratory still standing tall, its doors still open. However, the surface was visibly ageing.

Silver metal was being corroded and fell off. Very quickly, his brand new laboratory had aged to a state where he would have to abandon it.

“What’s going on? The metal on the surface of the laboratory is an alloy known for its resistance to corrosion…” Leylin’s eyes swept over the place, but he could not find anything in the vicinity that was related to his castle.

The situation now was as if he had brought his laboratory along and, as one entity, crossed over to another plane from the castle.

“Could this be Dreamscape? Or did the accident with the astral gate bring me to another world?” In that instant, all sorts of conjectures appeared in Leylin’s mind. He took a deep breath and re-entered the laboratory.

*Boom!* He closed the door.

“If it’s another foreign world, I’d definitely have felt like I was travelling through space, and from my experience, there’s only one world that can take me elsewhere without any warning— the Dreamscape!”

The phantom of a Kemoyin Serpent Emperor appeared behind Leylin’s back. Its amber pupils blinked open, scanning the area with vigilance.

“Bring it on!” Leylin opened the door once more as the Eternal Light spell shone ahead of him. There were many small roads around, connecting the laboratory with other constructions within the castle.

Leylin raised his head, the shattered sky unique to the Morning Star area entering his line of sight.

He glanced at the surface of the laboratory. The signs of ageing had long since disappeared, as if all he had witnessed was a mere illusion.

“Master!” With Leylin’s will, a few metallic puppets arrived before him.

The A.I. Chip confirmed their identities, leading Leylin to ascertain that he was truly in the castle in the Morning Star Area.

“Interesting!” Leylin’s eyes flashed with curiosity. He pondered over it for a moment and returned to the laboratory.

When the door was opened once more, the barren land and oddly-shaped suns appeared before him again.

Compared to before, however, there were some changes in the surroundings. Traces of yellowish-green weeds tenaciously grew from the seams of rocks, and the collapsed buildings were now covered with vines and seemed full of life.

There were even some small shrubs in the distance, growing with vigour.

“The life force here has grown richer, as if tens of millennia have passed…” Leylin narrowed his eyes. The three strange suns now shone with a green hue which he could not get used to.

Arriving back at where he’d tossed the signboard, Leylin found that the thing wasn’t in pieces anymore, and was instead at its original place. The cracks from before seemed to have faded to an extent. ‘A.I. Chip, test age.’

[Beep! Based on carbon 14 test, estimated age: 1328 years, 7 months…]

the chip quickly replied.

“The last test showed it was over twenty thousand years old, and it even broke apart on the spot…” Leylin stroked his chin, “Time is behaving strangely here… Only an unbelievable world like Dreamscape could be in such a situation…”

“But… The last time I came here, my soul had been caught in a trap, and this time I managed to enter with my body as well… Am I in someone else’s dream?”

“What is the boundary between dream and reality?”

The further he pondered, the more Leylin found that the secrets of Dreamscape were terrifying. However, there was not one riddle he could solve.

“There are even such strange changes. Is it a spacetime wormhole? Or perhaps some sort哦分garbled effect from Murphy’s Law?”

Seeing the vines climbing all over the laboratory, Leylin walked in and closed the door. Opening it once more, he found himself in the Morning Star area.

Leylin immediately ordered, “Categorise this area as a special first rank region! Seal the whole region, and move away all nearby constructions. Carve runes to protect it from radiation and contamination.”

The metallic puppets immediately got to work, startling Freya.

“What’s going on, darling?” Freya was currently in a loose nightgown, looking dazed.

Leylin went forward and pulled at Freya’s hand while consoling her, “Nothing, something just went wrong with an experiment, and the contamination from the radiation is growing more intense. It’s best you move out for a while, staying far away from the castle…”

While he didn’t really understand the current situation, that explosion in his astral laboratory had resulted in an even more mysterious change. It had now become a bridge between this place and Dreamscape.

One needed only enter to change what space it was connected to, something that immediately piqued Leylin’s curiosity.

He could now move between worlds without consuming any energy. If any Magus were to find out about this, they would go insane. Hence, using the excuse that an experiment had gone wrong and he was afraid that the contamination would leak, he was taking necessary emergency measures.

However, the reason for this situation still had Leylin befuddled.

‘Is it because of that owl feather? Or was it the explosion of the astral gate? Or did both those events somehow affect each other causing this mysterious change…’ he thought as he stroked his chin.

Whatever it was, this accident was a good thing. Not only had he obtained the coordinates to Dreamscape, but he’d also acquired a bridge between the two worlds.

“However, this can’t last forever,” Leylin recalled some spatial theory. The Magus World and Dreamscape were like two parallel sheets of paper, and his astral laboratory was a point between the two, the only link between them.

However, with how space worked, this point would eventually break. In other words, his laboratory would eventually lose its connection to Dreamscape.

“I need to speed up my exploration!” Leylin’s heart was burning. Dreamscape was the most mysterious of worlds, one that had even invaded the ancient Magus World.

It was an extraordinary place whose inhabitants lacked true bodies. Formed of the dreams of intellectual beings, it had a mystical strength.

If he could find the dreams of some ancient Magus that had comprehended laws and obtain his understanding, he would reap huge benefits. Basically, in front of Leylin was a gigantic treasure trove…

Chapter 639: Accident and Meeting

The sudden appearance of a half human statue, and the hairline cracks that could only be seen through Astral Vision… all this caused a chill in Leylin’s heart.

The things in Dreamscape were way too mysterious, but the attraction they held for Leylin was incomparable. Precisely because of this, Leylin who had all along been immersed in experiments had slightly neglected the extreme dangers contained there.

Leylin looked at the continuously enlarging cracks on the statue, and could not help but say with a deep voice, “Seal!”

*Ring!* A blood-red radiance emerged from underground, instantly transforming into a translucent cage. The runes he’d previously set up near the statue began to flicker as well. Suppressive energy waves gathered together, firmly sealing the half human statue within.

The range of cracking on the statue grew wider even as it was sealed off, all the cracks coming together to form a terrifying large mouth.

A wave of tiny black bugs wriggled out of the big mouth, each one the size of an ant. They crawled out of the statue layer after layer, covering the ground in a flash.

The concentration of the dark red dreamforce was amplified several times as it formed a dense whirlpool that rippled back and forth in the air.

‘Why is the dreamforce circulating so fast?’ This discovery dulled a lot of the joy from the experiment’s success. Leylin began reflecting on himself. With just one insignificant step in the study of Dreamscape, he had only pulled off a corner of the veil. He still needed to be wary of the unknown. The little bit of complacency that had appeared was immediately suppressed.

*Squeak!* Accompanied by a creepy screech and a fine gnawing sound, Leylin found to his horror that the binding runes were shattering apart one by one. Even the spell formation on the ground was terrifyingly being corroded.

The dark red dreamforce constantly darkened further, and its strange power even caused Leylin’s expression to change.

“Damn it! If I wait until tomorrow, I’ll use up all the isolation materials found today…” Leylin’s heart was very hateful, but he was helpless.

“Destroy!” He suddenly attacked, and a strange black flame swept across the room violently, completing drowning all the places the half-human statue had previously been.

The temperature of the entire laboratory rose to an extreme for a moment, before falling rapidly once more.

The original floor had melted due to the high temperature, hollowing out. At the bottom of this hole were all sorts of molten materials that mixed together and solidified again, forming colourful gem-like crystals.

*Creak!* Black spots started appearing on these crystals one by one.

Although the statue disappeared, those black bugs had impressively survived Leylin’s demonic flames.

‘They’re based off dreamforce, I need to solve the problem from its roots.’ Leylin’s eyes turned gloomy. He waved both hands, and the current experimental boards in the lightning pool flew out in a flash, exploding to form dust in the air. As if some power was bringing them together, they then formed a fine membrane, covering the area where the black bugs were.

“Isolate!” A great amount of lightning covered the membrane and formed an isolation layer similar to that of the previous experiment. Dark red dreamforce was isolated to the outside.

A large amount of dreamforce condensed, unexpectedly causing many holes in the membrane, causing it to crack under the attack.

‘Although the dreamforce can be isolated, it can also break through the latter. My last experiment only targeted an ordinary Dreamscape creature… So this kind of thing can happen when encountering something of a higher rank…’ Leylin’s pupils narrowed.

This meant that, if he encountered an even more powerful existence, this membrane he set up would likely be torn apart immediately.

Thinking over it once, that made sense as well. A rope net could catch small fish, but how could it catch a tiger shark in the ocean?

‘The priority is to completely eliminate all these hidden dangers before the opponent gains Dreamscape’s support!’ Determination flashed in Leylin’s eyes as the demonic flames burned once more.

This time, the black ants that lost dreamforce melted apart very quickly, turning into motes of black light and dissipating.

As if due to this event, the dreamforce outside the membrane grew richer, causing fine cracks to appear on the membrane. It would rupture at any time.

“Faster! Make it faster!” Leylin shouted deeply. Cold soul force merged, being injected into the flames.

The black flames immediately burned tenfold more vigorously, burning all of the black ants into ashes. And the instant when the last ant disappeared, the isolation membrane emitted a saddening cry, unable to bear the heavy load any longer as it shattered. The dreamforce had lost its target though, and it hovered for a while before dissipating automatically. It caused Leylin to let out a deep breath. He turned around.

All of a sudden, it was as if the half-human statue was pasted in front of his eyes, the huge cracked mouth seemingly ridiculing him! A terrifying gloomy breath was constantly emitted from the crack that was the huge mouth.

Leylin’s pupils narrowed as dense Kemoyin Scales emerged in an instant, New Moon soul force bursting forth from his truesoul to cover his body.

*Squeak!* The terrifying black ants emerged once more, covering Leylin’s entire body. His Magus robes, which were a magic artifact, did not even manage to block them for a moment, thousands of holes forming on it instantly.

The black ants covered Leylin’s body, and even the rank 5 Kemoyin Scales could not resist the opponent’s fangs. An intense pain was transmitted from his skin as countless nicks appeared on Leylin’s body.

*HSS—* Behind him, the phantom of a Kemoyin Serpent Emperor emerged, growling as a layer of black flames burned on Leylin’s body.

“Huff…” After the flames stopped burning, Leylin was momentarily taken aback. When he came back to his senses, all the black ants had disappeared.

However, fine black wounds were still densely packed on his body, making it seem a little horrifying.

“Is this the invasion of Dreamscape?” Leylin looked at the blue lightning pool, the hollow ground, and the scales that had automatically emerged on his body, heaving a deep sigh.

Dreamscape was a world where reality and virtuality were mixed, and all sorts of things could happen in there.

‘I’m afraid that with that sort of influx of dreamforce, this lab has already become a building of Dreamscape. Even the nature of the materials has changed…’ Such a situation was very similar to the process of a high-ranked Magus irradiating his castle on his own accord, only at a much deeper and more overbearing level.

‘A.I. Chip, raise the alert level once more. Forbid all entry other than my own!’ As he walked out of the laboratory, Leylin was slightly gloomy. The feeling of being shrouded in an illusion, as if he had been struck by magic but had not realised it, really left him uncomfortable.

Moreover, although dreamforce was not like magic, it could still affect reality. No matter what he experienced in dreams, it would all be reflected on his main body.

‘Dreamscape experiments are indeed full of dangers!’ Leylin sighed. Even the current him did not dare to live near this laboratory.

“Your Highness Leylin! You’re finally out?” Jeffrey’s voice was heard as Leylin walked out of the castle. This rank 5 protector of the Morning Star area had actually been waiting outside the castle without his knowledge.

“What’s the matter, Your Highness Jeffrey?” Leylin asked curiously. This was considered his personal territory, Jeffrey could not intrude on his own. It would be considered disrespectful to its owner.

“I tried to contact you several times, but there was some hindrance so I could only wait outside…” Jeffrey shrugged his shoulders with a bitter smile.

“I see. Forgive me, I was immersed in an experiment!” Leylin immediately apologised as an embarrassed look emerged on his face. The effect of the pollution and isolation of dreamforce was much more terrifying than other spells.

If a laboratory in such an environment was still able to receive communications from the outside world, that would truly be something fishy!

“What experiment are you performing? I heard that there was even an accident before, and the pollution caused by the leakage is very serious…” Jeffrey looked at the tightly guarded castle behind Leylin that had no signs of life, seeming curious.

Of course, the leakage due to an experiment was something Leylin had deliberately made up so he could tighten the vigilance in this place openly and seemingly righteously.

“Nothing much… Just the leakage from an interplanar experiment. Something seems to have escaped as well…” Leylin’s words were both true and false, showing the great improvement in his acting skills. Even without the A.I. Chip’s coordination, he was able to deceive an old sly fox like Jeffrey.

“It’s a cute, timid creature. In order to play hide and seek with it, I had no choice but to seal off the entire castle…” Leylin smiled.

“Oh!” Jeffrey nodded but did not pursue any further. Magi’s experimental information was definitely top secret, not to mention that both Leylin and himself were rank 5 warlocks of equal ranks. It would have been way too out of line.

“This Sir Leylin has not invited us in even now, isn’t he too rude?” At this moment, a Warlock standing beside Jeffrey spoke up indifferently, actually displaying slight hostility towards Leylin.

“Hm?!” Leylin was also shocked. Only now did he notice this figure beside Jeffrey. He was very handsome, his eyes containing an exuberance and vitality. His body’s aura was extremely abstruse, yet also very easily neglected.

Chapter 640: Bevis

“This is?” Leylin was on guard. This person was able to hide from his sense, which meant he was no ordinary fellow.

“Hehe… Let me introduce him to you, Leylin. This is the person I mentioned before. He’s Bevis, the last of the Radiant Moon Warlocks in our Warlock Union!”

Following Jeffrey’s introduction, Bevis proudly lifted his head slightly. “Archduke Leylin, you come out to meet your guests looking like this. Aren’t you violating etiquette?”

Leylin was stunned, and quickly looked at himself. Due to the mishap previously, his robe was now utterly tattered, and he did seem rather impolite.

“My apologies, that was my mistake! Please, come to Black Serpent Castle next door. It’s not far away, and my wife is there as well.” Leylin apologised sincerely, and directed them there while still in front of his castle. He did not intend to invite the both of them in to tour this castle.

According to Leylin’s plan, this area would be completely isolated and abandoned. After what happened today, he surely had doubts about the safety here.

The invasion of Dreamscape came as silent as the night, yet contained a vast amount of terror.

Even rank 5 Radiant Moon Warlocks might not be able to effectively protect themselves in the face of such an invasion.

Before having complete control over dreamforce and being able to defend himself, Leylin would maintain distance from this place. His safety wasn’t a joke.

Seeing that Leylin acknowledged his mistake and apologised so readily, Jeffrey’s smile became more gentle. After all, he didn’t want to see a divide between the military powers of his own organisation. As for Bevis, a trace of astonishment flashed in his eyes, but he concealed it well.

Leylin, who noticed all of this, sighed secretly, ‘This Bevis… he isn’t the haughty and brainless person he appears to be…’

Previously, Jeffrey had mentioned that there were a group of Warlocks that had the highest hopes of obtaining a throne, and Bevis was the last Warlock that did not appear back then. He’d always thought that this fellow was outside of the Morning Star area, but didn’t expect that he would actually appear right in front of him directly.

‘Is his ability to block me from probing also brought about by the rank 6 bloodline?’ Leylin carefully sized up this Warlock who possessed the bloodline of a rank 6 creature.

As he tried to probe him, a rich layer of bloodline energy that surrounded Bevis like a dense fog warded off any prying eyes.

Perhaps it was because of this ability that he was able to avoid the hostility of many Magi, and thereby grow to this stage.

‘A.I. Chip, is it possible to bypass this isolation layer from his bloodline energy?’ Leylin appeared to be talking cheerfully to the two Warlocks as they walked along, but he was actually commanding the A.I. Chip and making continuous attempts to gather information about this Warlock.

[Beep! It is necessary to break the protective layer to gather information about this Warlock. This will attract his attention. Continue with action?]

 the A.I. Chip swiftly intoned.

‘No!’ Leylin wouldn’t be so reckless of course, he didn’t want to be seen as an enemy.

‘Ancient bloodlines at rank 6 that possess concealment abilities are few and far between…’ Leylin stroked his chin and glanced at Jeffrey.

‘Jeffrey himself should have the bloodline of a rank 5 creature, an ancient bat. Bevis on the other hand… A Crystal Dragon? Or a Misty Fog Giant?’ The many possibilities surfaced at the bottom of Leylin’s heart. After the A.I. Chip made continuous comparisons, it finally narrowed it down to the two most probable bloodlines.

Bevis was of course,unaware that, within a short span of time, Leylin was already close to completely understanding him inside out. He was aloof throughout their journey, standing at the side while Leylin and Jeffrey conversed. He only occasionally interjected.

After connecting to Dreamscape, Leylin had constructed another Black Serpent Castle next to his original castle, and shifted Freya and the servants over.

The Morning Star area was extraordinary in that the land available was endlessly vast, hence Leylin effortlessly obtained ownership over a large amount of land. As for the construction of the castle, it was made simple with the assistance of spells and numerous giant adamantine puppets following his orders.

A short moment later, Leylin and the guests took their seats in the living room of the new castle. The maid served milk tea and some light refreshments. Freya came out to meet them for a while, but retreated soon after, leaving the space to the three Warlocks.

Leylin fiddled with the cup in his hands, and didn’t take the initiative to speak.

He hadn’t expected Jeffrey to bring Bevis here. However, since he already knew about the rank 6 bloodline, Jeffrey probably didn’t have anything to hide as well. Perhaps he brought Bevis over with the intention of resolving misunderstandings and to remove any grudges that Leylin might harbour.

After all, the Warlock Union had intentionally hidden Bevis’ existence for a long time. If not for Leylin’s discovery, they might have continued hiding him. He could sense how distanced their relationship was merely from their attitude.

Bevis’ attitude towards him was also worth pondering over…

Seeing Leylin behave in this manner, Jeffrey felt somewhat embarrassed. After all, they were in the wrong to begin with, and now could only smooth things over. “His Highness Leylin is the Warlock who has spent the shortest amount of time in advancing to Radiant Moon in the history of bloodline Warlocks. His innate talent is astonishing, and his future is limitless…”

“Hmph…” Bevis spoke coldly, “If not the fact that I sealed myself previously in order to conceal my bloodline, I wouldn’t have let this achievement go to someone else…”

Judging by the additional strength of a rank 6 bloodline, Bevis might just have been able to surpass Leylin’s record. Hence, it was very normal for him to have complaints, but Leylin felt that it wasn’t that ordinary.

‘Sounds like he seems to be… dissatisfied with me?’ Leylin glanced curiously at Bevis. Today should have been the first time they met, yet he was in a hurry to show off. What was he trying to do?

‘Could it be that the prophecy led him to feel like he was about to face some kind of crisis? Or perhaps it is purely because he’s a spoilt brat? Or even more likely, is he trying to make the other Warlocks declare their position through such an attitude?’ Leylin suddenly had a premonition that his existence would create problems for Bevis.

Bevis had always been thought of as the last hope of the Warlocks, and one could not imagine the extent to which he was valued. Leylin’s appearance at this moment was a forceful attack on his position.

He advanced to Radiant Moon faster than him, and was even younger than him. Even though there were bloodline shackles to consider, he had a history of creating miracles, and it was not as if there was no hope for him to break through them.

Furthermore, even though Leylin’s limit was rank 5, he was already a top figure among the Warlocks, and was worth investing in.

Thus, the entire Warlock Union was now more inclined to allocate some resources to him. Even though it was just a tiny portion, it was enough to arouse discontent and vigilance on Bevis’ end.

‘Afraid that my recent rising will affect your status?’ Having had an exceedingly rich experience with power struggles, Leylin immediately sniffed out that something was different.

Still, this possibility left him speechless. Sometimes it was easy to build animosity. Perhaps it was because of baseless conjectures, or maybe purely because Bevis found Leylin an eyesore.

“Your Highness Bevis’ bloodline is beyond me…” Leylin paused for a moment, then continued, “But as the hope of the Warlock Union, what Your Highness should do now is break through the boundaries of rank 6 as soon as possible, and become a Monarch so you can acquire a larger space for us Warlocks to live in.”

Since Bevis’ attitude was clear to him, there was nothing for Leylin to be courteous about, and he directly returned the ‘compliment’.

Leylin was proud of his age and experience, and this attitude instantly made Bevis turn red with anger. Leylin was practically instructing him like a child!

In fact, Bevis was doing pretty well. Leylin didn’t have to break through his barrier to find, with the help of the A.I. Chip, that he was already a Half Moon Radiant Moon. With the amplification of strength by his bloodline, he could probably match even Offa in battle, albeit with difficulty.

He would probably be ranked second in terms of strength within the Warlock Union.

Such was the terror of a rank 6 bloodline. Any ranks below rank 6 could be slowly cultivated and broken through with the strength of the bloodline. With such a huge asset on his side, it was perfectly fine for Bevis to have a slightly arrogant personality.

Besides, since he had always been taken good care of, he probably didn’t have much life experience to speak of. The emotions of rank 6 creatures were far more frightening, and would be a fatal weakness for him.

Hence, after hearing Leylin’s provocation, Bevis erupted without the slightest hesitation, “I am here today because I have something to say regarding Your Highness Leylin’s suggestion from before!”

“From before?” Leylin looked at Jeffrey, puzzled.

“Your Highness Leylin mentioned it previously. It’s about taking action against the powers of the Blazing Flame Monarch. Although I think it’s better that we do not take part, we should discuss it!” Jeffrey explained awkwardly.

“Your Highness Leylin, as a Radiant Moon in our Warlock Alliance, how can you enrage a rank 6 being such as the Blazing Flame Monarch because of your personal hatred, without a care about our interests as a whole? Even if it’s done in your name, this cannot do. Can you guarantee he won’t take out his anger on the other Warlocks?”

Bevis’ voice was very loud, and he appeared to speak forcefully and with justice.

“Personal hatred?” Leylin gave a light laugh. “The recent persecution of Warlocks nearly ended our legacy. It was quite recently that he dispatched assassins to end our excellent bloodlines. The numerous offences he’s made are mere personal grudges in your eyes, Your Highness? Don’t forget that you too are a Warlock of the Union!”

Having never experienced such mincing words before, Bevis was at a loss for words momentarily.

Chapter 643: Help and Discovery

Leylin was slightly disappointed after listening to Gillian’s story. It would be excessive of him to expect any good power system or training method from such a weak race.

　

‘However, they are the natives after all. There should be some valuable items or information…’ Leylin stroked his chin.　　

　

‘Furthermore, Dreamscape can’t be judged with common sense. Perhaps the next time I come, she’ll have turned into a terrifying existence. Of course the chances of that are so meagre they’re negligible, but even if she’s more likely to die instead there’s some hope…’

　　

“No… No… Don’t go…” Gillian seemed to be restless in her dreams, her hands clutching the blanket and her brows deeply furrowed. Her eyeballs were rolling around under her eyelids, and she looked miserable and pitiful.

“DON’T LEAVE ME… Hah… Hah, it was a dream…” She suddenly sat up, looking bewildered. It was only after she saw the bonfire blazing constantly that she huffed out a long breath.

　

“Nightmares?” Leylin laughed and pushed a piece of roast meat in front of her. Grease and roast meat combined to present the most tantalising of scents, one that caused Gillian to swallow.

　　

“This is… for me?” Gillian’s stomach growled, much to her embarrassment, but she still questioned in disbelief.

“Of course!” Leylin’s smile was very gentle. There had not been any unhappiness between them, and was giving her roast meat and bread considered a waste? This bit was nothing at all to Leylin, so he obviously wouldn’t mind being gentle and kind.

Experience told him that such a pretence was very effective in concealing him in an unfamiliar environment. On top of that, Leylin didn’t mind showing benevolence to stray cats and dogs.　　

　　

“Thank– Thank you!” Gillian spoke in a low voice, and immediately grabbed the meat and began to bite at it ravenously. Halfway through, she suddenly sounded like she was choked with emotion and began to sob.

　

“There’s no hurry, I still have a lot of food. Finish eating first, then I’ll bring you to your companions.” Leylin understood what she was feeling very well. He comforted her slowly, and the girl eventually calmed down.　　

　　

*Ka-cha!* Withered branches snapped when stepped on. Leylin and Gillian carefully skirted the theme park, pushing through the primitive forest.

　

“Those terrifying monsters never leave the scope of the node. As long as we don’t go there, there shouldn’t be any problems…” Gillian was wearing the hunting attire that Leylin had given her, her cleaned face revealing a vigorous spirit that made her seem pretty.

　　

“What’s truly scary in Dreamscape are the wanderers and masters! They can cause tempests to descend at any time, destroying homes and crops, resulting in massive casualties on our end…”　　

　　

Her voice became low. “If not for them looking down on us and treating us like ants, we would probably have all died long ago…”　　

At this point, she gazed at Leylin. From what she could remember, the methods Leylin used were very similar to those employed by the masters.

　

“No need to worry, I’m not anything like that. I’ve only just studied some other methods. Haven’t any of you met with other intellectual lifeforms and interacted with them before?” In front of Gillian, Leylin did not conceal his identity as a foreigner.

　　

“Yes! It’s not just in the forest, but even in the nodes. There are existences that we can communicate with, but they seldom appear. Normally it’s just monsters that only know how to kill.

　　

Gillian tilted her head as she thought it over, “I heard from Father that long, long ago, a giant castle appeared at a node. An old grandpa with a white beard lived inside, and he was like the masters with the ability to control lightning and fire. He even passed down methods to manipulate these powers to Uncle Morin…”

　

“Hm?” Leylin’s interest was aroused, for this sounded quite similar to a Magus, “And then?”

　　

“And then….” Gillian’s eyes grew dazed, “After grasping the tremendous power, he said he would take us away from the forest to see the outside world… and then, he disappeared… never to return…”

　　

“What a sad story… Oh, my apologies!” Leylin had nothing to say in response to that.　

　

“It’s nothing!” Gillian seemed rather strong, and after seeing a sign by the road, she even cheered excitedly, “We’re quite close to our camp!”

　　

*Whizz!* A bone arrow landed in front of Leylin, the arrow’s feathers still shaking.

　

“Who is it?” A deep voice sounded from the forest. Leylin laughed, not answering. He had actually noticed the other party long ago, but it was obviously better for Gillian to deal with him.　　

　

“Uncle Mark! It’s Gillian!” She happily yelled into the depths of the forest.　　

“Little Gillian!” The trees on the opposite end began to shake, revealing a middle-aged burly man with sideburns. This man, who was clothed in animal hide, spoke out, “I heard that you’d fallen into a node. I thought you’d died! Do you know how much I cried for you…”

　

“Uncle Mark!” Gillian went forward and hugged him tightly, “I’m sorry for making you worry! Here, let me introduce you. This is Mister Leylin who rescued me from the node!”

　　

Gillian pulled at Mark’s hands and dragged him before Leylin. Evidently, the lack of purple patterns on Leylin’s skin left the man on guard.

　

Leylin chuckled, not minding at all. It was fine as long as he found the place. After all, given his abilities, could the natives even block his attacks?

　

Of course, Leylin did not dare overstep his boundaries due to the mysteries of Dreamscape. It was best not to use violence when it could interfere with him obtaining any harvests.　

　

After all, this was a world filled with the unknown. The warped reality and complexities in here far exceeded his expectations.

　

Perhaps the next time he came here, these natives would have undergone a tremendous change. If he were to invest some effort here and strike up a good relationship with them, it would be worth it in the future.

　　

What happened next was obvious. After Leylin displayed his kind intent, and with Gillian’s vouching for him, Mark brought Leylin to their camp.

Leylin took a look around. This was evidently a temporary base, with many wooden piles that had been cut down and were yet to be tidied up in the surroundings.　　

　

At the back of the camp were traces of a large fire, as well as a small plot with vegetables and the like.

‘These farming methods are rather ancient.’ Leylin shook his head, but he knew this was inevitable. These natives could find the next time they woke up that their land had lost all fertility, turning into an arid desert, a forest, a river, or even a volcano. There was no need for more effort than this.

　

Such simplicity extended even to the buildings. A wooden house was made with a few trees put together. Many of the natives chose to rest out in the open or found a hole in a tree. Leylin felt that the tent he had brought along could be considered a palace compared to this.　　

　　

In the simple and crude wooden house, Leylin met Gillian’s father. He seemed like a haggard middle-aged man, hard work over a long period of time making him look as if he already had one foot in the grave.

　　

“Cough cough… thank you, guest from distant lands! Gillian is my everything. I really don’t know what I can do to show you my gratitude. There’s this food as well… this…”

　　

The middle-aged man surveyed the white bread, biscuits and other food piled in front of him, a flush rising on his face. Such first-rate food was something he could not normally enjoy.

　

“Please don’t mind it! Gillian is a very lovable girl. Nobody would want to watch her come in harm’s way!” Leylin smiled gently.　　

　　

“Please forgive my bluntness, but based on what Gillian has said, you… are a Magus?” The man coughed for a while before asking suddenly.　　

　　

“Yes!” Leylin’s astonishment was outweighed only by his curiosity, “Have you seen a Magus before? Where did you make contact with them?”　　

“Cough cough… It was Morin who told me this…” The flush on the middle-aged man became even more serious, to the point that Leylin sensed that the fires of his life were about to be extinguished.　　

　　

“Morin was once viewed favourably by a Magus and studied under him for a period of time. We were told many epic stories, but unfortunately…” Leylin had heard about what happened after from Gillian before.　　

“May I know if the node where the castle was still exists?” Leylin was rather curious about his kind.

“No. On a certain day, the entire castle and the node completely disappeared. If not for Morin spending the night elsewhere that day, I’m afraid…”

The man shook his head, and seemed to think of something. Shivering uncontrollably, he produced a portion of animal hide and respectfully placed it in front of Leylin.

　　

“This is what Morin left for me. Though I can’t understand it, it’s definitely got to do with the Magus. Take this gift as my thanks!”

　　

“This…” After taking the skin, Leylin’s pupils suddenly shrank.　　

　　

Atop the animal hide were some brown designs and runes. It was no wonder that the man couldn’t understand it; the real information was concealed by spiritual force within the hide.

　　

[Beep! Discovered data interface. Information being transmitted!]

The A.I. Chip’s voice was transmitted as well, and a look of glee appeared on Leylin’s face.　　

　　

‘I am Morin, what Mentor calls an inhabitant of Dreamscape. If you see this information, please treat my clan members well. What you will see next is the path that Mentor has come up with after spending decades studying my body — A Magus…’

The information on the animal hide gave rise to a look of elation on Leylin’s face.

Chapter 644: Exchange and Consternation

‘A Magus coincidentally chancing upon Dreamscape who was enchanted by the bizarre environment here and took in an inhabitant as his acolyte…’ Leylin secretly made a guess about what happened at that time.

‘To adapt to this environment, he even specifically targeted dreamforce and the acolyte’s vitality, developing some kind of customised meditation technique and spells…

‘And due to some external factors which could not be resisted, the castle of this Magus had turned into ashes overnight and that acolyte disappeared soon after…’

That should’ve been the gist of it. Leylin wasn’t all that interested in investigating the incident. As long as he gained information, this expedition into Dreamscape would be considered a success.

‘That Magus that was stranded here was at least a Breaking Dawn, and might even been a higher existence that comprehended laws…’ The more he studied the information on hand, the more Leylin grew to admire that Magus.

The A.I. Chip’s assistance was why he could make an analysis of dreamforce relatively effortlessly. However, other Magi did not have such convenience on hand, and this one had to have slowly worked out and perfected an energy system that suited Dreamscape using his own experiences.

To Leylin, obtaining this system of dreamforce was more important than anything else. The uses for it would aid him greatly.

“Thank you so much, this information is very important to me!” Leylin put away the animal skin with a cautious expression, interrupting the hesitant speech of the middle-aged man opposite him, “I have important matters and there’s always great danger beside me. I’m afraid I cannot take reciprocate your kindness enough. These two documents contain methods to obtain strength. I hope you will accept them!”

Light shone in Leylin’s hands and two rolled documents emerged. These were methods for the cultivation of knighthood and magic. Although each only contained a basic portion, that was already enough for these inhabitants.

The steps for cultivation were very easy to follow. Leylin even wrote it down in their language so that they could understand it.

“This… truly…” The middle-aged man looked to be taken back by surprise, but he still accepted the two gifts. After all, these things Leylin was giving him were way too important for his tribe.

This left Leylin slightly doubtful. Why hadn’t that Morin spread the power system when he obtained it? Once he mulled over it, he thought it might be because the Magus left him with strict orders at that time. Either way, he had already disappeared, and this would probably remain a riddle.

Leylin’s eyes sparkled upon seeing his gift being accepted, and he said with a smile. “I actually have more diverse types of food as well. I was thinking of a trade… are you interested?”

“Trade? Of what sort?” The middle-aged man was a little doubtful. What would this Magus from a world rich with products need?

“Various kinds of specimens, be they plants or animals. Also anything of unknown purpose. You can sell it all to me, and I’ll purchase them with food.” Leylin spoke without even blinking his eyes. He had many spatial artifacts with him anyway, and he’d grown into the habit of bringing piles of rations with him whenever he went out. As such, his supplies were extremely abundant. Moreover, even if there wasn’t enough, he would have to make a trip home at the worst.

With the rich resources in the Magus World, who would be afraid of a lack of food?

“Specimens? That Sir from last time asked for the same thing as well… Please rest assured, I will definitely fulfil this request of yours!” The middle-aged man patted his chest as he made the guarantee.

“Then I’ll be here waiting for good news.” Leylin smiled faintly. He was a single person, with only so much time and energy. Matters like gathering ordinary specimens were best left to the inhabitants.

Moreover, the animal skin they’d given him had inspired him greatly as well, giving him hope that there were even stranger things on their hands.

Food was abundant in the Magus World, but it was scarce here. This gave Leylin a bargaining chip, and for the sake of his benefits Leylin didn’t mind becoming an unscrupulous businessman. Compared to everything he had invested, those gains would only be insignificant.

Once this news was announced, the entirety of the temporary camp went wild.

Large amounts of plants, animal tissues, and even rocks were sent to Leylin. He welcomed it all; as long as it was a specimen he hadn’t seen before he would give them a portion of food for it. Because they lacked manpower, even Gillian and her father were hired specifically to do this work. To these inhabitants, Leylin was a fool who used precious food to exchange for these items.

Unfortunately for Leylin, this kind of opportunity to make unrestrained purchases was quite rare. Given that the value of all this food added up wasn’t even worth a few magic crystals, he was simply making a huge profit.

For now, both parties were very satisfied.

“Uncle Leylin, take a look look at this!” Gillian passed Leylin some bizarre flesh that looked like numerous eyeballs bound together, “I’ve never seen this thing before!”

“Hmm…” Leylin tried to analyse this bizarre material, a blue glow being emitted from his eyes.

[Detected unknown article, unable to scan!]

The A.I. Chip immediately responded.

“Where did you find this?” Leylin glanced at the inhabitant behind Gillian. It was a youth, the purple pattern on whose forehead formed an odd flower bud-like shape.

When Leylin’s gaze swept over him, the youth grew very tense, even beginning to stammer. “Near… Near the new node!”

“This is pretty good! You can get three pounds of black bread for it, or anything else of equal worth.” The youth immediately laughed when Leylin nodded. Something that he’d casually picked up already had such value, it was simply a giveaway.

Leylin casually took the item from Gillian’s hands and stowed it away. Truth be told, this bit of expense was nothing at all to him. Even if the items they handed over was worth nothing much to him, as long as Leylin hadn’t seen them before he would basically accept it.

With such a high rate of accumulation, it was a short period of time before Leylin effectively controlled the surrounding geological and botanical specimens.

Plenty of strange, unknown items were now in Leylin’s possession. Although most of it was junk, as long as even one bit had value he would profit.

“Uncle Leylin, the number of people is much smaller today!” Gillian came before Leylin, both eyes turning round and round. Her thoughts were indecipherable.

“That’s obvious of course. I already have the basic specimens with me, and specimens from distant areas require time to collect…” On the contrary, Leylin had already guessed this long ago. He had the A.I. Chip after all. As long as things were already stored in his database, he wouldn’t need a second copy.

“That… Uncle Leylin…” Gillian also had a hesitant look.

“I know what you want to say, little Gillian!” Leylin stroked Gillian’s head, “But it’s very dangerous beside Uncle, and also very troublesome. If you follow me, it’ll be a disturbance…”

Watching Gillian lower her head, Leylin comforted her again with a laugh, “Hasn’t your father found a batch of youths, preparing to pass down what I’ve taught him? You can go and learn as well…

“Also, I’m preparing to make a trip back home. I’ll come back in a few days. You can hoard all the items you receive for now, and I’ll bring even more food and supplies next time…” Leylin sent Gillian away and began checking the day’s gains.

After the botanical and mineral specimens were sterilised, they were numbered by the A.I. Chip and kept away properly under their own categories in his waist pouch.

The resources in the Warlock Union were very abundant, and a Radiant Moon like Leylin could deploy some of them as long as he didn’t touch the bottom line. He’d found himself a magic equipment pouch, whose capacity greatly exceeded his original storage pouch.

Even so, his food reserves were almost all used up. After all, he’d stored it with only himself in mind, and it was already a big thing for it to have lasted all this while.

‘In fact, if not for the restrictions on astral gates, trading with other worlds would be the best!’ Leylin’s eyes sparkled, and he sighed. ‘Trading, then colonisation, followed by complete dominance! Although other worlds have differences in power systems and other aspects, they still follow this principle. Of course, Dreamscape is different. This world is too strange, and any investment can cause us to lose everything…’

The next day, he bid farewell to Gillian and the inhabitants at the temporary camp. Loaded with specimens and strange items, Leylin embarked on a journey back home.

“Judging from the laboratory’s energy waves, this space-time-travel can still be supported for a period of time. I’ll have just enough time to get ahold of all the surrounding specimens and strange items littered throughout this camp!”

Leylin stroked his chin, “Moreover, that Gillian seemed to be leaning towards me. So long as I tempt her a little more, she will enter the Magus world willingly. At the same time, I could secretly capture some inhabitants, which would guarantee enough specimens in the future…”

The current Leylin was taking precautions in case he couldn’t use his astral lab anymore.

“However, no matter what, the Magus’ message on the animal skin is already a great harvest!” Leylin smiled in satisfaction.

[Warning! Warning! Astral laboratory under attack. Activating rank 1 runes, stored energy at 34.7%!]

At this moment, the A.I. Chip flashed a red warning, immediately making Leylin anxious.

Chapter 645: Spider and Breakage

After all, if the astral laboratory was destroyed, not only would he lose his channel to Dreamscape, he would be trapped here, forever.

‘‘Impossible! I set up a concealing technique and spell formation before leaving. I even left behind…’’

Leylin’s mind began to work rapidly. He was confident in his setup, but the warning from the A.I. Chip definitely wasn’t false.

‘Could it be some kind of unique creature that can see through my illusory spell formation? Or… is it demons?’ The possibility instantly turned Leylin gloomy. He suddenly sped up, coming to the area where his laboratory was…

But the scene that came into his vision made Leylin’s eyes widen gradually. “This…”

In his sight was a huge spider the size of a tall mountain, spitting out threads that wrapped up the entire laboratory.

The runes around the laboratory flickered continuously, rippling with a dazzling lustre. The defensive layer and spider web depleted each other.

On the spider’s abdomens were large numbers of patterns, coming together to form a distorted male face. A whimpering sound echoed from its wide open maw.

[Warning! Warning! Formation genie energy reserves at less than 10%, approaching critical value. Immediate countermeasures recommended!]

the A.I. Chip’s red warning window shot out again.

“Is it possible to scan the opponent?” Leylin quickly asked.

[Mission established, attempting to scan. Beginning to break through opponent’s force field.]

*Chik Chik!* Even as the A.I. Chip sounded out mechanically, the huge spider in mid-air seemed to be provoked by something. Its compound eyes turned, aiming directly at Leylin.

A forceful scan would release a feeling of a malicious invasion. It was likely to trigger the opponent’s hatred, something Leylin expected long ago.

The male face on the spider’s abdomen let out a sob, and terrifying sound waves swept past the area where Leylin was, tearing off the topsoil to reveal the thick bedrock.

Leylin had taken precautions the moment he commanded the A.I. Chip to scan. His body was covered in a layer of Kemoyin Scales, and a few blood-red shields emerged.

*Ka-cha!* *Ka-cha!* The blood-red shields and the sound waves came into contact, and it seemed to be unable to defend for much longer. Many cracks emerged on the surface of the shields, and they soon shattered.

The sound waves swept across Leylin, causing intense pain to be transmitted from his Kemoyin Scales.

“Argh… This power!” Weirdly enough, a hint of happiness emerged in Leylin’s eyes. At the very least, he could confirm through this attack that his opponent had not comprehended laws. The opponent was not a regulatory existence. This was more important than anything else.

If not, he could only have turned around and fled, abandoning the laboratory and wandering alone in Dreamscape.

[Beep! Target has resisted scanning, not all data has been obtained. Display what is available?]

the A.I. Chip asked mechanically.

Of course, Leylin assented unhesitantly. The A.I. Chip responded immediately, projecting a data panel with many incomplete fields before him.

[Beep! Unknown Creature. Power: 200+, Agility: 100+, Vitality: Not enough information, Spiritual Force: 2000+(estimate), Abilities: 1, Detection: Has a keen perceptivity towards the energy waves in its territory, 2, unknown… 3, unknown…]

‘That Detection ability should be why the opponent could discover the laboratory in spite of my meticulous concealment.’ Leylin sighed. He was reminded of the saying, ‘Man proposes, God disposes.’

He had observed this area for a long time. Only after ensuring that there weren’t any terrifying creatures did he go out to explore with peace of mind. He hadn’t expected that such a terrifying monster would be attracted when he was out.

‘The opponent is a rank 6 creature at most, there’s still a chance!’ Leylin’s figure twinkled endlessly as he dodged the snow-white spider web in mid-air. His thoughts were running endlessly.

Of course, the beings of Dreamscape did not follow the Magus World’s rankings. Because of the inherent uncertainty of dreamforce, their rankings were very vague.

But through the A.I. Chip’s detection and his own observations, Leylin could already confirm that the opponent was at least a rank 6 creature, ferocious and powerful/

‘These kinds of creatures all occupy their own territories normally. Why did it come out for no reason?’ Leylin immediately shook his head even as this thought came to mind, ‘I’m too foolish! This is Dreamscape, why would it follow such rules?’

Right at this moment, the abdomen of the spider in mid-air suddenly bloated as it let out a cry, expanding and lastly exploding! Large quantities of densely packed spiders fell from the sky like raindrops. A translucent thread at all their tails connected them to the main body.

An even finer radiance flashed across these closely packed threads.

Terrifying amounts of dreamforce condensed with a bang, converging on that man’s distorted face as he let out a horrifying growl in the sky. “kdalkgmalk!”

Terrifying dreamforce crashed down on Leylin’s body, causing the defensive suit to begin cracking inch by inch.

“So powerful! Is this the power of rank 6?” As Leylin mumbled, a blood-red radiance burst out from his body. The power from his point mass had concentrated to an extreme as it boosted a spell, resulting in a new transformation.

“Radiant Moon Arcane Art— Kemoyin Transformation!”

Along with a terrifying hiss, an enormous serpent over a hundred thousand metres long suddenly appeared in the sky. The large bones at the top of its head formed something like a crown, the smooth and elegant lines of its scales emitting the aura of nobility.

This was the ruler of the ancient Giant Kemoyin Serpents— the rank 5 Kemoyin Emperor!

*Whoosh!* A huge phantom flashed across the sky. The Kemoyin Emperor suddenly flung its tail out, which struck the face in the sky and caused it to explode. Mysterious petrifying light short from the amber pupils that were like Morning Stars.

Many of the tiny spiders were petrified right in mid-air, turning into rocks and falling down.

“Innate skill— Devour!” Along with Leylin’s soul force, the Kemoyin Emperor suddenly widened its serpent’s jaw and a big black hole formed faintly before him.

The spider web in the sky was directly broken, disappearing into the terrifying black hole with the surrounding rocks, branches, and even light itself.

“Get out!” Accompanying Leylin’s explosive shout, the enormous serpent suddenly crashed into the large spider in the sky.

With a mountain-cracking, space-shattering rumble, terrifying shockwaves of air swept out in all directions. The large spider that was hovering in front of the laboratory was struck some distance away.

*Chik chik!* This kind of attack obviously enraged the spider. With ear-piercing yells, a few blades of dark light suddenly burst forth, leaving deep scars on the Kemoyin Emperor’s body.

Large scales fell down as blood splashed in all directions. Yet, under the effect of the innate Devour skill, the serpent recovered very quickly.

A poof sounded as countless black streams of air gathered together, restoring Leylin’s true body. There was an unusual blush on his face as numerous black flames formed on his body making him resemble a demonic phoenix.

“Soaring Demonic Phoenix!” Together with an exalted phoenix cry, the blackfire phoenix tore open the layers of webbing that had wrapped around the laboratory and Leylin dashed inside.

“Go!” Various potions were thrown out from Leylin’s body, forming a terrifying combination spell. It mixed with attacks from the Scarlet Earring, and they drowned the enormous spider that was rushing over.

He did not even look at the outcome of that, suddenly closing the door of the laboratory.

*Bang!* When he opened it again, the surroundings of the laboratory had already transformed into the scene of an ancient castle.

“I’m back!” Leylin murmured. His expression suddenly changed and a great amount of dark red dreamforce shrouded his body, forming the phantom of a huge spider.

“Indeed. I still can’t resist the attack of a rank 6 creature…” He mumbled with a bitter smile on his face. Suddenly, his expression showed another drastic change.

*Rumble!* Glaring blue lightning bounced around the surroundings of the laboratory, even emerging in Dreamscape. A huge red spider spat out a large amount of thread from the other side that seemed to stretch across the void. With his Astral Vision, Leylin saw a large amount of thread twisting on top of the laboratory, aiming to drag it back into Dreamscape.

“No! If this goes on, no matter whether the laboratory is dragged over there or that thing gets access to the channel leading here, it isn’t going to be something I wish to see.” A rare look of hesitation emerged on Leylin’s face, but ultimately dissolved into resolution. “I need to break the connection!”

Leylin had studied this space-switching of the laboratory extensively. Although he hadn’t had many results, he’d still deduced how to stop this phenomenon.

Leylin’s right hand dropped a little powerlessly. “A.I. Chip, command the formation genie to activate self-destruct procedures!”

[Beep! Authority confirmed, enforcing command.]

Without human thoughts, the A.I. Chip only carried out his orders mechanically. As it sounded out, a slightly dark red gas emerged from the floor of the lab.

The dark red dreamforce grew more concentrated as it converged, eventually even forming a layer of dark red flames.

With a series of bangs, a great amount of webbing melted and broke apart. Even the laboratory itself began to melt slowly.

*Chik Chik Chi…* Leylin felt like he could hear the furious growls of the spider all the way from the distant Dreamscape.

The loud sound was originally very intense, but is soon softened as it gradually disappeared. The dark red flames then extinguished, leaving a big black hole where the laboratory had originally stood. It had disappeared without a trace.

Chapter 649: Fog Giant

“The Warlock Union isn’t the personal property of a single Warlock. It’s an alliance between all Warlocks, each of whom have their own wills and requirements for benefits,” Offa’s voice was icy, “Even when Bevis reaches Breaking Dawn, he still won’t have the authority to represent us all!”

Wayde and Jeffrey did not refute out of their desire to protect their own interests.

“Furthermore, Leylin wants to raid the Blazing Flame Monarch in his own name, and Bevis is trying all he can to stop this. In principle, neither of them are wrong. Hence, let’s give them a chance to sort it out among themselves. We’ll appear later to adjudicate. Isn’t that appropriate?” An intelligent glint flashed in Offa’s eyes. As the oldest and most powerful Radiant Moon Warlock, his might in the Warlock Union could not be underestimated.

“That’s true. They’re young people after all, they need to be hot-blooded sometimes!” Wayde exclaimed from the other side. Completely golden, he looked like a god of battle.

“But… Bevis is someone who can advance to Breaking Dawn. If some enmity arises between the two Warlocks because of what happens today, the future of the Warlocks of our union…” Jeffrey was slightly worried.

“Bevis has yet to attain Breaking Dawn. Besides, how are you so sure that he will be the one to become a rank 6 Warlock?”

“How can I not be sure? He has…” Jeffrey instinctively retorted, and then saw Offa’s expression that was somewhat like a smile but not quite. He immediately went mute, sinking into deep thought.

Though Offa kept saying he wanted to be impartial, one of the two involved was a Warlock with a rank 5 bloodline and the other a Warlock with a rank 6 bloodline. Letting the two fight out a personal battle was already unfair to some extent.

‘Perhaps Offa has great expectations of Leylin?’ Jeffrey suddenly understood this fact.

Seeing his look of sudden realisation, Offa nodded in gratification, “The prophecy didn’t indicate who it was that would reach Breaking Dawn. Although Bevis being the one is most probable, Leylin still had hope as well. Even you and I, as well as all the Warlocks limited to Morning Star, have a chance. That’s why we need to make some bets when we need to, that is how we can maintain our influence. Although we’re putting a lot of our hope on Bevis, we can’t reduce our support towards other Warlocks…”

“I understand!” Jeffrey nodded solemnly.

Offa beamed as he spoke, “Good. No matter who wins or loses, you just need to express goodwill to the loser and show our kindness…”

“Could it be that Your Highness thinks Leylin has a chance of winning?” Jeffrey gaped, “Not only has Bevis reached Half Moon, he has a rank 6 bloodline…”

“Hehe… Someone who can become a rank 5 Warlock with his own abilities isn’t a nobody!” Offa laughed, as if hinting at something. He pressed in closer, his eyeballs that were glazed over glinting with a strange light, “Leylin is someone who can create miracles. Nobody can tell the results of this fight, but whatever it is, it’s pointless to speculate further. Let’s watch!”

Hearing Offa say this, Jeffrey and Wayde watched the battlefield grimly.

Leylin had long since noticed the concealed Bevis with the A.I. Chip’s scans. The other Radiant Moon Warlocks weren’t around, something Leylin found strange.

‘Offa and the rest didn’t come with him to put pressure on me… Are they maintaining a neutral stance? Rather unexpected.’ Leylin’s eyes flashed with intelligence, ‘Their meaning is quite clear. If I don’t exceed Bevis, there’s nothing else to say, but if I achieve victory over him or breakthrough I can do as I like?”

‘Their placing their bets on both of us… What a bunch of sly old foxes indeed!’ Leylin lamented.

Immediately after, his gaze towards Bevis turned piteous. No matter how talented he was, he lacked experience. He evidently hadn’t pondered over this, and was still frustrated by the previous events.

“Aaah! Leylin Farlier, I won’t let you off. Come back with me obediently!” Bevis roared, a large fog surging from his body.

“Just as well. I’ll play with you as a warmup. Besides…” Leylin laughed, and large amounts of demonic black flames suddenly emerged from his body. High-pitched phoenix cries sounded from within.

All of a sudden, the flames flew into the sky, gathering to form a devilishly enchanting blackfire phoenix.

“Soaring Demonic Phoenix!” With the high-pitched buzzing of flames breaking through space, the arrogant phoenix spread its wings, spurring on immense tides of black flames. Space itself was melted down, and the fog that Bevis emitted was devoured and absorbed.

After acquiring the devouring ability of the Kemoyin Serpent Emperor, Leylin found that the same ability of his black flames had been upgraded as well, the two seemingly complementing each other well.

“Is that what you’re so confident in? A black phoenix? What kind of bloodline ability is that?” The vigorous fire energy and the demonic devouring ability caused Bevis’ expression to change slightly.

“Whatever it is, in front of my bloodline, all odd abilities need to bow down!” His eyes immediately turned crimson. A powerful and profound force from an ancient bloodline emanated from his body, even suppressing Leylin to some extent.

That unique aura that came from an ancient rank 6 bloodline was something regular rank 5 beings did not dare offend. Just this alone gave Bevis a huge advantage when battling Warlocks with bloodline sources of a lower rank than his own.

However, Leylin was different. As the ruler of a race, the Kemoyin Serpent Emperor had a high resistance to the pressure from a rank 6 being, and the suppression was far lesser than what Bevis had expected.

[Beep! Host affected by opponent’s bloodline suppression. All statistics have decreased slightly.]

Leylin was speechless as he saw his stats. The only decrease was in the unit place.

“Is the suppressive ability of a rank 6 bloodline so weak? Or is the Kemoyin Emperor too overbearing?”

*Chirp~!* Under Bevis’ disbelieving gaze, the blackfire phoenix flew before him without being affected in any way. Two wings that were like long flaming blades crossed each other, and terrifying black flames instantly devoured him.

“How is this possible? My bloodline is… rank 6. How can’t it suppress a mere rank 5 bloodline?” After the wave of black flames passed, Bevis looked to be in a sorry state. There was a thick layer of fog armour wrapped around his body, resulting in him receiving very slight injuries. The blow to his ego, however, was incomparable.

“Isn’t it just the bloodline of the Misty Fog Giant? It’s not as if it was the peak of ancient rank 6 beings or something… Is there a need to conceal this?” Leylin snickered disdainfully, and Bevis froze up, “How— how did you find out?”

“What do you think?!” A look of satisfaction hung on Leylin’s face, which only made Bevis want to vomit blood.

His bloodline had the innate ability of concealment, which was one of his trump cards. Even those other Radiant Moon Warlocks had not seen through this, and yet it was nothing in front of Leylin.

Fear of Leylin rose in Bevis’ heart. It grew increasingly intense, and much of it transformed into hatred.

“You must die. You MUST DIE!” Bevis howled.

*Rumble!* Large amounts of fog exploded, forming the figure of an immense giant.

This giant had four thick and sturdy arms, and a vertical eye at the top of its bald head. Its skin was coloured in the green of marble, large amounts of grey fog being produced from its pores. Its body seemed rather misty.

Since Leylin had seen through it, Bevis had nothing left to hide.

*Awoo…* The gigantic Misty Fog Giant’s four large arms were held high as it began to howl fiercely. The dense dog spread to form a large grey fog space.

‘It really is the Misty Fog Giant!’ Leylin’s pupils flickered.

Now that they were fighting, Leylin had nothing holding him back. He immediately ordered the A.I. Chip to forcefully break through the opponent’s force field to obtain the correct information on his bloodline. Everything about the Misty Fog Giant was presented to him in detail.

[Appearance of Misty Fog Giant, rank 6 being: Ancient times. Habitat: A wetland with dense fog, or in abandoned Magus Cities. Rumoured to be the descendants of the ancient Thunder Giant, with the ability to manipulate fog. Likes eating plants like green algae. Gentle nature. Special ability has been concealed.

Innate talents:

1. Fog Concealment: Covers up one’s aura and information about their bloodline.

2. Grey Fog Space: Creates a subspace that can be maintained for a short period of time.]

“AAAHH. Leylin! I want to kill you. Kill you!” Bevis snarled, the insanity in his eyes growing even more obvious. “ Arcane Art— Giant Transformation!”

His body crackled as his body grew larger, fusing with the phantom behind him. Two extra arms grew underneath his ribs, and with the execution of the Arcane Art, he turned into a real Misty Fog Giant.

‘Mm! It’s a head shorter than the one in the database. It should only be half-grown at rank 5.’ Leylin laughed, red rings of light fusing behind him. He dissipated, turning into large amounts of black gases that reformed into a terrifying Kemoyin Serpent Emperor. “Innate Arcane Art— Kemoyin Serpent Transformation!”

*Rumble!* Within the grey space, a giant serpent with a body over a hundred thousand metres long collided with a four-armed giant. Much of the void shattered under this power, the stray undulations causing the Morning Star Area nearby to shake slightly.

Chapter 650: Drawing Blood

“What’s the matter? Didn’t we agree before that he’d only stop his opponent? Why has it gone this far?” Jeffrey was a little stunned at the side. “This isn’t good. I’m afraid Bevis’ extreme personality has led to an emotional breakout at rank 6. Quickly, go and stop him! If not, His Highness Leylin…”

Even if the Warlock themselves weren’t as strong, metamorphosis to a rank 6 creature was definitely more powerful than that to a rank 5. Jeffrey was worried that Bevis would harm Leylin, which wasn’t good for the Warlock Union. After all, Leylin was in the Radiant Moon realm and was one of their executive members.

“That’s a rank 6 bloodline growing emotional. I’m afraid it will affect us as well…” Wayde, standing at the other side, grew very worried instead.

“There’s no need for that. His Highness Leylin is still there,” Offa waved his hands, seemingly very relaxed, “Not only he did see through his opponent’s bloodline, he even forced Bevis to fall into his own trap step by step. His Highness Leylin is truly growing more and more amazing… Perhaps he’ll give us many more surprises…”

“What?” Jeffrey and Wayde exclaimed involuntarily, “Does His Highness still have more strength remaining?”

“I cannot say,” Offa waved his hands as he watched the battlefield with more concentration.

The Misty Fog Giant growled, and large amounts of grey fog seeped out of its pores, forming armour and a weapon. It’s destructive power was great enough to shatter space itself with every attack.

Bevis’ heart was already filled with anger, and he even wanted to directly kill Leylin. This was very different from his previous intention of just teaching him a lesson.

His shame and anger at being discovered and irritation at his pride taking a blow had erupted. Especially after seeing Leylin’s unexpected and incredible strength, the flames of jealousy and insanity in the genes from his bloodline mixed together to form something even more terrifying.

The result was that Bevis’ rationality had all but disappeared, and he was prepared to kill Leylin here regardless of the consequences.

“What a pitiful child,” Leylin’s voice was transmitted from the enormous body of the Kemoyin Emperor. Layers of black runes constantly emerged from its scales, easily blocking even the Misty Fog Giant’s fog attacks.

Leylin watched the four-armed Misty Fog Giant in front of him attentively, and it seemed as if a mysterious radiance was shot out of his pupils.

“Eye of Petrification!” The Kemoyin Emperor’s gaze turned the four-armed giant sluggish. A layer of ash-grey stone instantly emerged on his skin.

“NO, how can my bloodline lose to this low-ranked creature?” Bevis growled frantically as large amounts of blood-red light burst forth from his body, forcing the petrification out.

However, the Kemoyin Emperor had taken this time to rush directly in front of him, its huge tail sweeping across the horizon. A power that seemed like Armageddon burst out from it.

An explosion sounded as the Misty Fog Giant was swatted away. The large amounts of fog in the surrounding area shattered, exposing the original starry sky.

“This rank 6 Misty Fog Giant bloodline, I’m taking it!” A whisper sounded in Bevis’ sea of consciousness. Before he could even figure out the situation, the Kemoyin Emperor had already opened up its maw, its two fangs ruthlessly piercing into his neck.

A terrifying attractive force was transmitted from its fangs, causing Bevis to shriek hysterically. Large amounts of fog shattered with a bang, and the Misty Fog Giant began cracking up inch by inch. Light flashed within the grey fog, and Bevis’ true body appeared once more.

Only, the current him had two large bloody holes in his neck, and looked battered and exhausted. His gaze towards Leylin was as if he’d seen some sort of demon.

“Ah…” When he gazed at Leylin’s pupils, Bevis seemed to receive a great deal of shock. He let loose a weird shriek as his body transformed into a ray of blood-red light that rushed back to the Morning Star Area with extreme speed.

“Indeed… small and weak…” Radiant flames emerged and Leylin returned to his normal form as well. The lack of battle experience and willpower was a shortcoming that had caused Bevis great losses.

With a card like the A.I. Chip up his sleeve, Leylin had abundant experience and strategies that were shrewd and ruthless.

“It’s more or less enough, time to go!” He sneered, looking at a point in space with a dazzling radiance in his eyes.

Soon after, his entire body turned into black flames that disappeared in the sky.

Within the Morning Star Area, Offa and the other two Radiant Moon Warlocks looked at each other in dismay. “His Highness Leylin actually discovered us spying on them? But this Tracing Pensieve is a piece of high-grade magic equipment…”

“Forget that. I’m more amazed by his battle strength. Even a Half Moon Magus like Bevis isn’t his match…” Wayde crossed his arms, and a strand of short golden hair stood up vertically like a steel spike.

One had to admit, Leylin’s military strength gave them a great surprise. Not only was Bevis at the Half Moon stage, he also had a rank 6 bloodline inheritance in the Misty Fog Giant. Originally, he was only second to Offa in the Warlock Union.

And he was defeated just like that? Didn’t that mean that Leylin had strength comparable to a peak Radiant Moon?

This conjecture was something too crazy for Wayne and Jeffrey to accept immediately.

“Moreover, His Highness Bevis’ bloodline seemed to be slightly damaged at the end. Should we tell His Highness Leylin about this and hope he returns that blood?” Jeffrey asked a little hesitantly.

“Do you think that’s possible?” Offa speechlessly rolled his eyes. Now that he recalled, he felt like he’d underestimated Leylin. From the start, he had obviously laid a trap for Bevis, who walked in like a fool. Leylin had played him step by step like a marionette.

‘What an interesting kid! He started by stimulating his opponent and causing him to harbour killing intent. Then he defeated Bevis openly and righteously, seizing his bloodline… Did he plan all this out before? Then… if we appeared, did he have other plans for it as well?’

The more Offa thought of it, the more his previous indifference was replaced with fear of Leylin. This junior’s tyrannical strength and meticulous planning had left him heavily surprised.

“Maybe he’s the one who’ll fulfil the hopes of the Warlocks.” Offa found growing expectations in his heart.

“Then what about us?” Jeffrey didn’t really know what to do. Bevis’ defeat was a totally unexpected situation to him.

“What else can we do? Just allow Leylin to go out, he’s attacking under his own name anyway. With the Morning Star Area’s fortress, even if it’s the Blazing Flame Monarch, can he break through our defences directly?” Offa flicked his fingernails, his tone carrying a will that did not allow any questioning.

“Also, increase the security of the Ouroboros Clan and Leylin’s relatives by a level, especially for Lady Freya. We cannot allow the Blazing Flame Monarch or any others to find even a single loophole, get it?” Offa looked at Jeffrey meaningfully.

“Yes! I will visit Lady Freya myself soon!” Jeffrey nodded with a bitter smile.

“Our rules cannot be broken. There shouldn’t be any desperate infighting within us Warlocks, that is our bottom line,” Offa said, “I’ll go and remind Bevis about this in the near future.” All the Warlocks present nodded in agreement.

After all, if such a thing happened internally to an organisation that was supposed to be unified, it would be a huge blow to their soldiers’ morale. Furthermore, if one person crossed the bottom line, the enemy would definitely counterattack with the same level of danger, causing both sides to suffer. Magi were intelligent people, they knew what to do.

The only thing that needed to be done was suppressing Bevis’ emotional craziness. After he calmed down, everything would become easy.

“We cannot relax our support for Bevis either. Send the skeletal remains of the Misty Fog Giant in the warehouse to him after this!” Offa suddenly said something that shocked Jeffrey greatly.

“Your Highness… Why?” Jeffrey’s jaw dropped.

“If Leylin advances to Breaking Dawn, what will we use to suppress him?” At this moment, Offa stroked his beard and said something that left a deep impression on Jeffrey.

“I’ve gained quite a bit this time!” On the other side, Leylin looked at the bloodline in the test tube in his hands that was emitting a misty luster. A hint of happiness emerged on his face.

“Although the Misty Fog Giant isn’t some kind of high-grade being amongst ancient rank 6 creatures, it creates bloodline imprints using its blood as materials, this explains its ability to cast ordinary rank 6 spells…”

It could be said that Bevis had fallen into Leylin’s scheme from the moment they met.

Moreover. because the opponent had displayed his killing intent during the battle, even if Leylin forcefully extracted his bloodline those Warlocks could not say anything.

After all, compared to Bevis who was in hot pursuit of him, Leylin was instead very ‘magnanimous’, even letting Bevis go ultimately.

Probably, even if the current Leylin were to draw blood from him, Bevis himself wouldn’t have the face to ask for it back, as it was too embarrassing.

“Seeing from the attitudes of Jeffrey and the others, we can still temporarily ease our worries regarding the bloodline alliance. Surely they will also try their best to contain Bevis, making him calm down. They won’t attack my forces!”

A thoughtful glint flashed across Leylin’s pupils.

These kind of things were mutual. Once Bevis exceeded the bottom line, igniting the flames of war with him, Leylin would definitely follow suit, even paying back tenfold.

Hence, so long as a Magus had a little rationality, he would not do something like this that caused both sides to suffer.

Chapter 654: Control and Discovery

The translucent figure being bound by the vines had a pair of deathly still eyes. Even though the assassination had been unsuccessful, there were no undulations whatsoever despite his life being at risk.

*Rumble!* A terrifying force from his truesoul formed five different rings of light.

“Radiant Moon Arcane Art…” His voice was hoarse, as if he had not spoken for a long time. The surrounding Morning Star Magi also gritted their teeth, power pouring forth from their point masses to support their Morning Star Arcane Arts.

This Radiant Moon evidently had made contact with these Morning Star Magi at some point and arranged a counter-attack!

*Pak!* Leylin instantly came before a Morning Star Magus, a giant serpent figure from his hands ruthlessly piercing through the other party’s innate defences, causing him to cough blood while quickly retreating.

The backlash from a Morning Star Arcane Art being interrupted caused that Magus to howl in agony.

“If the ten or so Morning Stars were to attack me together, I might find it slightly troublesome, but now?” Leylin looked towards Melinda. A terrifying rank 5 energy storm was swallowing the region around her.

However, Leylin could sense Melinda’s aura. She was fine.

“After so many years, it’s only these few Magi that are loyal to the Blazing Flame Monarch? How pitiful.” As Leylin’s eyes scanned past the area, the Morning Stars could not stand the immense pressure and the rings of light from their Arcane Arts collapsed behind them. They held their heads and escaped.

*Rumble!* Radiant Moon soul force spread brazenly about the battlefield. A few rays of light suddenly pierced through and dispersed the energy storm, revealing the figure of that rank 5 Radiant Moon Magus.

Although there was a cross-shaped wound on him that was corroding into his body, a terrifying Radiant Moon Arcane Art had taken form in his hands. “Void Flames…” The Radiant Moon murmured under his breath.

A formless flame energy emerged from the void that caused even Leylin’s expression to change. ‘Melinda and Joanna, those two idiots. How could they let their opponent finish his Arcane Art?’ he cursed, fingers pressing on the grey ring causing fog to permeate the area.

Melinda saw her opponent casting Void Flames from in front of her, but surprisingly her expression was as if she’d gotten away with something.

She began chanting, seriousness emerging on her face. Her right hand pointed in the direction of the Void Flames.

“Adhering to the ancient agreement of the truesoul, Void Flames! Devour everything before me for my sake…”

The formless flames crackled and flowed backwards, enveloping the very Magus who’d cast them within. Boiling heat spread through the area as the sound of an innate spell crumbling mixed with cries of disbelief and pain.

“Impossible… Why can you manipulate the Flames… You… You’re…” He was cut off at this point, devoured by the formless flames. His blood and flesh separated from his skeleton, and in the end even his bones melted down.

The energy from a truesoul being destroyed spread out, this Radiant Moon Arcane Art even targeted the soul!

Seeing the opponent’s figure being annihilated, Leylin removed his palm from his ring, pupils shrinking, ‘Controlling a Radiant Moon Arcane Art and causing it to act on the user? This is more difficult than interfering with it. Unless…’

*Swish!* Seeing that their Radiant Moon had fallen and the Blazing Flame Monarch still wasn’t showing himself, the remaining Morning Star Magi completely lost their will to battle on. Air exploded and light flashed as they fled or teleported away.

“This Radiant Moon should have been the Blazing Flame Monarch’s last line of defence…” Having done all this, Melinda seemed to be in a strange state. She seemed sorrowful yet relieved, as if a heavy weight had been lifted off her shoulders.

“The rule of the Blazing Flame Monarch hereby ends.” Melinda sighed, hand making a grabbing action towards the heart of Düz City.

*Rumble!* A large white palm appeared in the air, grasping the holy fire right at the centre. Under such an attack, even the tower genie was completely wrecked instantly.

Düz City quieted down, and the light from its large-scale defensive spell formation dimmed.

“Could it be… Is Düz City is going to have a different master from today on?”

“What about the Blazing Flame Monarch? Where is he?” The surviving Magi let out noises of disbelief.

Yet all of them had one premonition from the extinguishing of the holy fire. Today would be a turning point in the history of the central continent!

Groups of Magi wearing robes with lightning patterns on them arranged the defences outside in an orderly manner, gathering resources and the like. Occasionally, a few old people worked on decrypting the warehouses’ defensive formations.

These lightning patterned Magus robes were the signature of Jupiter’s Lightning. Besides them were Magi with a Gemini sign on their robes, doing the same thing.

Seeing Melinda and Clarke so brazenly ordering their organisations to plunder the area, Leylin was left speechless.

He hadn’t considered these matters when they’d set out. Even if he wanted to dispatch the Warlocks of the Union, he didn’t have the authority yet. As for the Warlocks of the Ouroboros Clan? They were too low-ranked, and would only serve to embarrass him.

Melinda approached Leylin and stared at the Magi of Jupiter’s Lightning outside, her eyes undecipherable, “My subordinates will set up defensive spell formations and guard them, which will help us gain some time.”

She had helped Zegna build Jupiter’s Lightning, and now the whole organisation was in her hands. If Zegna were still alive, he might have died of rage.

The Magi with a Gemini symbol on them belonged to Clarke and Joanna. Seeing the bulging sacks under their clothes, it was obvious that they had obtained many treasures.

Düz City was the core of the Blazing Flame Monarch’s territory, and the precious items within were innumerable. If not for the Blazing Flame Monarch currently being in a weak phase, staying somewhere else to avoid danger, Leylin and the rest would not have taken the area down so easily.

With the action of five Radiant Moons, the change in leadership of Düz City had occurred smoothly.

Besides Leylin and the rest who had obtained some great items, even their subordinates had gained ample rewards.

*Awoo…. Roar…* At this moment, Leylin saw a monster formed of several gigantic beasts charging forward, showing berserk determination and bloodlust.

“What is that thing?” Leylin stared at what seemed to be a giant mutated slime formed from gelatin and was stunned.

“That’s the biological laboratory of the Blazing Flame Monarch. I let out all the experiments being imprisoned there.” Melinda took out a mirror and tidied her long hair, not really caring about this.

“Such a dangerous thing…” Leylin was speechless. Some of these monsters were evidently as powerful as Morning Stars. One of them was laying low, and Leylin could sense its desire for slaughter.

Once let out, a calamity would descend on this region. Even Morning Star Magi would be in trouble if they were besieged by these creatures.

“It’s not our organisation nor our territory. Is there a need to worry about this?” Melinda blinked at Leylin, seeming innocent.

“Alright! Come with me, everyone. I’ve already analysed the coordinates of the Fiery World from the astral gate!” Joanna’s voice sounded, and all the Magi gathered at the heart of the room.

A flaming astral gate was there, already activated. This was the gate in Düz City’s astral laboratory, and the coordinates had been decoded from it. It was also why Melinda was confident in bringing Leylin and the rest to their final target, the place where the Blazing Flame Monarch was hiding.

The Blazing Flame Monarch was currently at their weakest. Leylin and the rest had already plundered Düz City, which would completely offend the Monarch anyway. If they didn’t want to be attacked in revenge, the only way was to strike first and eliminate the Monarch!

‘Perhaps this was also why this woman had us break Düz first, to compel us to follow through.’

Leylin shot Melinda a glance. The female Magus seemed to be very calm now, but he could see a trace of emotion in her eyes.

“The opponent has hidden the coordinates to the Fiery World within a pile of wrong data, but I still managed to find it!” With a tap by Joanna, a few sparks flew towards Leylin and the others.

[Beep! Discovered spiritual force information, determined to be astral coordinates! No records in database.]

The A.I. Chip immediately intoned. All the information in the spark was immediately transmitted to Leylin.

Melinda nodded, “The coordinates to this world was one of the prizes from this operation. We’ve agreed before on everyone having it.” Immediately after, the spark was flicked into the astral gate.

Blue flames flickered violently, forming something like a door. A terrifying boiling heat was transmitted from behind the astral gate.

“The last step in our operation shall be completed in the spatial crack of the Fiery World. Let’s go!” Melinda was the first to step into the astral gate.

“We’ve all left behind puppets or clones here. If the situation is off, we can immediately open the astral gate and return,” Joanna spoke slowly, “Outside there’s the chaos from the beasts, and we have subordinates keeping watch. We have ample time for warnings.”

Having said this, she walked in together with Clarke.

“Let’s go!” Leylin watched Jin who was in void form and rubbed his nose. They stepped into the radiance of the astral gate together.

Chapter 657: The Labyrinth’s Collapse

Void shattered, and a red figure appeared beside Joanna. Endless flames lay docile on his body, flickering with scarlet light. This was evidently a peak rank 5 Magus.

He solemnly grabbed at Joanna, pure golden flames turning into sharp claws that caused Joanna’s defences to break inch by inch.

“Blazing Flame Monarch!” Clarke howled with fury, arriving in front of her. The sharp, flaming claws ruthlessly grabbed him, causing the steel armour to break. Even the skin underneath had been roasted a charred black, revealing bright silver, metallic bones.

Within the Alanore Labyrinth, there was only one person who could move freely. And that was its owner, the Blazing Flame Monarch!

Clarke spat out fresh blood as he and Joanna were sent flying.

“Brother! BROTHER!” Joanna kept screaming, eyes instantly turning blood red. “HOW DARE YOU HARM MY BROTHER. I WANT YOU DEAD!”

Thin, translucent threads emerged from her hands, and even the void itself was cut through as they headed in the direction of the red figure in the air.

Fierce golden flames struck the translucent threads. Under the burning of the flames, the threads gradually melted. Not far away, Joanna turned pale.

“Joanna, get behind me.” At this point, Clarke stood up once again, as if he did not have a life-threatening injury on his chest, “Blazing Flame Monarch, I’ve waited for this day for a long time.”

*Bzzt!* Clarke’s hands were on his giant black sword, emanating the terrifying undulations from high-grade magic equipment. The sharp rays of light were bright and dazzling, and even the void was constantly crumbling in front of it.

“Sorrow of Gaia!” Clarke yelled in his anger, the phantom of a vast land appearing behind him. An aura of rot converged on his body, forming terrifying sword glints.

“Death and decay are not something a living soul can control.” The scarlet being in the air spoke slowly, a red sword with flames on it similarly appearing in its hands. “In the name of Fire, your only destination shall be the stillness of an eternal death.”

The whole world seemed to tremble and cheer as large amounts of fire elemental particles wound automatically around the surface of the flaming sword.

These two longswords that had surpassed the limitations of space connected in the next instant, the dark green force that represented death and wilting up against the scarlet fire. Their collision formed a storm that annihilated everything. Red sword light flashed in the roiling storm, and Clarke’s whole body fell backwards.

To be precise, ‘half his body’ fell back. Everything under Clarke’s lower abdomen had completely disappeared, as if he had been chopped in half at the waist. It revealed a mechanical backbone and translucent fluids.

The scarlet figure of the Blazing Flame Monarch was revealed once more as the energy storm dissipated. He stared at Clarke’s wounds and suddenly laughed.

“It’s not even a mechanical modification, just the puppet of a soul servant. The true Clarke should have died long ago.” He turned around, staring at Joanna who had tears in her eyes.

“A pretty good soul division technique. It’s no wonder the two of you weren’t separated when you came in, you are one and the same. Clarke’s your courage, longing and hatred; after removing these qualities, your main body is only left with weakness.”

“No, my brother isn’t dead.” Joanna cried out like a kitten whose tail had been stepped on, tears spilling out of her eyes.

“Don’t… cry… sister…” The half-bodied Clarke on the ground consoled her with a smile, but the voice grew increasingly rigid, and the sound intermittent. It eventually turned robotic.

“Ah, wait. I seem to remember only a little girl surviving during that massacre then. Was it you?” A strange smile appeared on the Blazing Flame Monarch’s face, “You actually placed all your hopes on someone else. Even if you’ve reached rank 5, you’re still trash.”

Words that were as sharp as a blade caused Joanna’s face to turn deathly pale. “No, I’m not…” She hugged her head, on the brink of a complete breakdown.

The Blazing Flame Monarch looked proud, and just as he was about to deal her another blow and upset her further, his expression suddenly changed.

Joanna was still hugging her head, but streams of black gas were dispelled from her body. A dangerous aura formed around her, one that even had him considering retreat.

‘What’s going on? Wait, she’s the descendant of that deceased clan. Could it be…’ The Blazing Flame Monarch’s eyes shrank, and large amounts of flaming shackles appeared and shot towards Joanna. He was one step too late.

Joanna looked up and began to scream. An endless terrifying undulation immediately enveloped the whole region…

*Thud!* The terrifying rank 5 fire elemental, the alligator-human hybrid Flame Sovereign King toppled down, the flames on its body extinguishing bit by bit.

The two bundles of soul flames gradually dimmed in its eye sockets. Soul light was constantly dispelled from the body, bringing with it dense fire elemental particles that were like fireflies. They quickly disappeared into the air.

*Chirp!* A high-pitched cry sounded and a large black phoenix descended from the skies. The flames withdrew to reveal Leylin who was within.

“The rank 5 Flame Sovereign King really was quite troublesome. I almost had to use my Arcane Art…”

Leylin stood at the edges of the lava lake. After the death of the Sovereign King, the black walls of the labyrinth at the other side of the lake pushed and pulled each other like toy building blocks, revealing a pitch-black pathway.

“It’s hard to tell how many stages there are in the labyrinth, unless…” Leylin stroked the ring on his hand.

A maze set up by a rank 6 Magus was something a rank 5 like him could only solve directly. It required another rank 6 to act to break it, or other special circumstances.

“AAAAAAHHHH…” An ear-piercing screech was transmitted to Leylin’s ears, the hatred and terrifying energy it held causing Leylin’s expression to change slightly. “It came from there… Did anything happen?”

*Boom!* One of the walls slowly crumbled following the explosion, and large amounts of black dust fell down.

“The labyrinth is already showing signs of collapsing. This power seems to be a unique type that’s rumoured to have existed in ancient times.” Leylin’s eyes glinted coldly.

While he was focused on the energy undulations, space suddenly collapsed around him. A scarlet figure appeared before him like before.

Flames seethed in the opponent’s hands, seemingly breaking their limitations to possess a terrifying heat. They caused the other energy particles to constantly draw back.There were only flames within this domain.

“The Origin Law of fire. So you’re the one who’s been spying on me,” Leylin snickered, his right hand unhesitatingly activating the silver ring.

Streams of fog dissipated, instantly forming a world of fog.

“Roar!* The phantom of a four-armed cyclops with hard skin emerged from the ring.

“The Fog Space of the ancient Misty Fog Giant.” The world of fog enveloped Leylin and the person who had launched a sneak attack. The opponent’s law of fire was already tangled up by the fog, using up its energy.

With the blood from Bevis as the basis, and via in-depth processing by the A.I. Chip, Leylin had successfully created a bloodline imprint of the Misty Fog Giant and sealed it within the ring.

Since it was a spell that could be activated using a bloodline, Leylin’s bloodline imprint had reached a might of rank 6.

‘Is this… the law of fog?’ Leylin could sense a deep-seated force in this world of fog. This was the law that controlled it. Due to its connection with the bloodline imprint, he gained some rudimentary control as well.

Large amounts of grey fog were like the most docile stream of water to him, allowing him to do as he liked.

“Crush him!” With Leylin’s command, great amounts of grey fog immediately turned into hardened rock, bringing with them the World Will as they rained down on the red figure.

“This isn’t your own ability, it’s an ancient rank 6 spell!” The tremendous force caused the scarlet figure to cry out involuntarily.

He was covered by the fog immediately after. Red light constantly penetrated through the fog, yet it grew increasingly dark.

“This is the real ancient Fog Space! If Bevis had used a spell like this, I might have long since been defeated or even killed…” Leylin sighed.

While Bevis did have the blood of the Misty Fog Giant, he had no A.I. Chip and it wasn’t as if he could endlessly consume his bloodline for spells. Leylin was different. After being purified by the A.I. Chip, the blood of the Misty Fog Giant now displayed its might like in ancient times.

“Damn it, there’s another one.” Another voice sounded from within the fog, and it soon turned deathly silent. The world of fog dissipated, returning to the scene of the lava lake from before.

“Another one?” Light flashed, and Leylin’s figure emerged. “Looks like it isn’t the first time he’s been at such a disadvantage, and…”

Leylin stared at where the scarlet figure had been. There was now nothing there.

“A rank 5 clone? Looks like the Blazing Flame Monarch has no helpers nearby, and has no choice but to do this himself…

“Good timing. I’ll make use of this.” Leylin waved his arms, and the fog that had not completely dispersed spread out, completely corroding the walls of the labyrinth.

*Crack! Crack!* The labyrinth walls that had already gone through immense damage could not hold on any longer and began to break apart inch by inch.

Much of the wall turned into powder, and this was still spreading further.

Chapter 660: Erosion of the Sun

“Let’s perish together!” Joanna had on an insane smile. It was as if death was not the end for her, only a beginning.

Many roots formed from her body, wrapping around her and the Blazing Flame Monarch. The faint image of the purple plant solidified, and the roots wound tightly together as the two fell into the half-dimension. Branches and leaves spread out, the bud at the very top growing and blooming.

With the Blazing Flame Monarch’s infuriated howls, a purple flower bud with unworldly beauty slowly blossomed in the half-dimension. A terrifying strength took form at the same time, forming purple light that spread in all directions. Even the world of fog was affected as it crumbled down.

“This is bad!” Leylin’s pupils shrank. The remaining fog force immediately created a thick wall-like structure in front of him, behind which Melinda squeezed in unceremoniously. Following that, purple light spread through the skies and drowned the area.

The half-dimension hidden within the labyrinth burst apart under the purple light, and many black holes appeared in the region, devouring the surroundings. The scene looked to be of the world’s end. The stray energy from the explosion still bombarded the protective sphere of the Fiery World, causing it to shake.

Once everything calmed down again, the original world crack now looked completely different.

Large amounts of irreparable spatial rifts had appeared in the place, and endless turbulence streaked past the void, causing what was now in ruins further damage.

Even the nebulae around the place, what was similar to his previous world, had completely dissipated in the explosion. Bits of dimmed starlight flashed every once in a while from the edges, as if fading away and reconciling to this fact.

A large bundle of fog dissipated in this shattered void, revealing the figures of Leylin and Melinda.

“As expected from the physique of an ancient clan. The destructive force from her self-detonation…” Leylin seemed to be praising it, yet there was still some regret in his words. He was very interested in studying this sort of physique, and had never expected the other party to so resolutely detonate herself.

The terrifying storm that formed as a result was enough for Leylin and Melinda to be affected even with the defence from the rank 6 energy of the Misty Fog Giant, and they cut sorry figures.

“The bloodline!” Leylin’s eyes turned red, and a small-scale vortex formed in his hands. Some of the items in the void seemed to be attracted by some formless strength and automatically reached Leylin’s hand.

Large motes of light condensed to form a droplet of purple blood with bits of gold shimmering within.

“So this is all that remains? What an overbearing spell!” Leylin sighed, stowing the blood away.

“Not yet! The Blazing Flame Monarch isn’t dead!” There was glee following Melinda’s gasp of surprise. This was the best situation for her, with the Blazing Flame Monarch heavily injured and unable to resist her claim to dominance.

“She’s a Breaking Dawn Magus after all. How could she die so easily?” Leylin nodded solemnly. He’d never dared to underestimate such a high-ranking Magus. On top of that, the A.I. Chip did not give any conclusion of sorts, and instead scanned the space for the aura of the Blazing Flame Monarch. This made Leylin even more acutely aware of the result.

Golden flames abruptly surged in the void, increasing in volume to form a giant blazing door.

The Blazing Flame Monarch walked out of this giant door, her detached eyes full of ruthlessness.

*Rumble!* The flaming door quickly shrank to form a golden Magus Robe that draped over her body, “I never thought a bug like you would interfere with the ‘reincarnation’ procedure this time. It seems like ancient clans like these and the bloodline Warlocks should all be exterminated…”

A peak rank 6 aura was being emitted from their opponent’s body, and Leylin and Melinda shared a glance as they laughed bitterly.

“The ability to be revived by flames?” Leylin stroked his chin, “Seems rather well-suited to the fire element. It even has a healing effect which shares some similarities to the Icy World’s Freezing innate skill…”

“We’re already in this situation, and you still have time to think about that?” Melinda didn’t know whether to laugh or cry in response. Yet, the Blazing Flame Monarch had already raised her right hand, and a longsword made of raging flames appeared in it.

“In the name of the Blazing Flame Monarch, I shall judge you!” Immense flames surged out with sword lights. These flames were not ordinary, they were from the law of fire!

Just the descent of a few wisps drew out all the fire elemental particles in the region in an instant. All the other elemental particles were tyrannically rejected and repelled.

With her rebirth from the flames, not only had the Blazing Flame Monarch managed to survive Joanna’s self-detonation, but she’d also healed all her injuries. She had regained her strength as a peak rank 6 Monarch.

“Get out of the way!” Leylin pushed at Melinda, and a large amount of crimson light surged out, “Bloodline Shield!”

*Rumble!* The flaming sword struck the shield, emitting a frigid sound. On the other side, Melinda tossed out a piece of magic equipment similar to a statue, blocking the Blazing Flame Monarch’s attack.

With Joanna’s death, Melinda and Leylin were the only two invaders remaining. Leylin’s rank 6 bloodline fog had left a deep impression on her, so Melinda transmitted a query to him, “Do you still have another bloodline imprint?”

“No. Do you think a rank 6 bloodline is so easily obtained? The amount of blood I had was only enough to create two imprints!” Leylin glared at Melinda, waving his right hand. He was speaking the truth. The ring on his hand had long since disappeared.

Upon hearing this, a hint of despair appeared in Melinda’s beautiful eyes, “I can’t take this lying down! Am I really going to die with Big Brother here?”

‘She’s going crazy again!’ Watching Melinda, whose voice had turned into that of a little girl once more, Leylin was rendered speechless. It seemed like the original Blazing Flame Monarch had discarded more than one portion of her soul, which was why Melinda had such bizarre emotions and a split personality.

“Despicable Warlock Bloodline and the trashes that I had disposed of before… Let me purge you completely today!” The Blazing Flame Monarch that had regained her full strength took several steps closer, the peak rank 6 strength causing Leylin’s expression to change.

Only when face to face with her did he realise how terrifying the might of a Monarch was. The opponent’s truesoul was like a scorching sun, tens of times larger than that of a Radiant Moon and of better quality. This golden soul force exceeded the strength of Radiant Moon soul force, and made even Leylin feel suppressed.

“Erosion of the Sun!” The Monarch raised her sword once more, the faint image of her truesoul appearing behind her. Black light formed at the heart of the sun, converging on the tip of the flaming longsword.

From the black spot, Leylin could feel a terrifying energy that could obliterate everything in its path.

“Opposing qualities huh? This is incomparably close to the antimatter theory in my previous world…”

“Purify!” Along with an exclamation, the Blazing Flame Monarch swung her sword out, pitch black light beginning to shoot towards Leylin and Melinda.

Full of destructive energy, it surged like a stormy sea and roared.

The world origin force of the Fiery World beside them boiled and disappeared into the Blazing Flame Monarch’s body, causing this attack to grow even more powerful.

“An attack befitting one at the peak of rank 6!” Leylin sighed, and then did not hesitate as he commanded, “A.I. Chip, begin defensive plan number 2!”

[Beep! Mission established, beginning usage of Host’s energy and forming defence.]

The A.I. Chip’s icy voice intoned immediately.

Meanwhile, a layer of black Kemoyin Scales appeared on the surface of his body. He tossed out large numbers of potions that formed a colourful defence. At the outermost layer, the Bloodline Shield changed its shape with the manipulation of the A.I. Chip, welcoming the black light headed their way.

*Rumble!* Space itself crumbled. Even a world crack could not withstand such a powerful explosion, and spatial storms were formed everywhere.

Leylin emerged from the explosion, much of his Magus robes torn apart. There was a trace of blood at the corner of his lips.

“So, Melinda, are you dead yet?” Leylin’s eyes flashed with wit as he glanced in Melinda’s direction.

White light flashed in the void, and Melinda’s head appeared. Her body had completely severed from below the neck, and on those body parts, there were signs of burns that had clotted and turned into scars.

“If I died, you’d definitely have died before me!” Melinda’s face was now as pale as a dead person, as if she had lost all blood.

“I can’t hold this for long. Do you have any other methods to deal with her? I have one more…” Melinda, who now only had a head, glanced at Leylin and seemed to have made up her mind.

“Yes!” Leylin pretended to struggle with the decision and spoke in a low voice, “But that’s my life-saving trump card. Once it’s used, I’m not going to bother with you!”

“You don’t need to. As long as you can successfully suppress her for a period of time, leave everything to me. All the benefits that I spoke of in the contract will be given to you.” Melinda gritted her teeth.

“Fine!” Leylin chuckled, and a few balls made of crystal appeared. Within these sparkling crystal balls was a dark red gas that was like a river.

*Boom!* *Boom!* *Boom!* Many of the balls exploded, and a strange power spread outwards.

“It’s no use! I’ve already grasped authority over flames! Any attacks below laws…” The Flame Monarch stopped abruptly, her beautiful eyes suddenly showing astonishment.

Chapter 663: Flame Laws

The structure of a rank 6 Magus’ blood and flesh as well as information on the modifications to their body gave Leylin much inspiration and sprouted fresh ideas. He had also obtained many other benefits from the Blazing Flame Monarch’s abundant life energy.

He pulled up his stats with a thought, and quite a few of the information on the A.I. Chip’s screen was refreshed.

[Beep! Discovered high-grade cell structure. Simulating… Host has absorbed large amounts of life energy. Vitality increasing!]

[Beep! Host’s soul has been strengthened. Spiritual force crossed bottleneck, reached Half Moon!]

[Beep! Host’s stats have changed. Regathering info…]

It was after these messages that the A.I. Chip showed Leylin’s new stats.

[Leylin Farlier, Rank 5 Warlock. Bloodline: Kemoyin Emperor (Complete form). Strength: 76, Agility: 62, Vitality: 176.9, Spiritual force: 2003.5, Magic power: 2003 (Magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force). Soul force: 200, Half Moon.]

Leylin had long since expected a rise in soul force, but the huge increase in vitality gave him a great surprise.

With a treasure like the phoenix egg, raising his soul force wasn’t an issue. It was just that his body couldn’t keep up.

It was funny now that he thought about it. Most Warlocks’ vitalities surpassed the growth of their spiritual force, but he was different. He progressed much too quickly, to the point that his spiritual force advanced by leaps and bounds and left his vitality far in the dust.

‘A Half Moon truesoul, and such soul force!’ Leylin focused on his point mass. His truesoul was perfectly round as before, but the cold light of his soul force already occupied over half of it. ‘A truesoul like this is very powerful, but in comparison to a rank 6 Magus, it’s quite lacking…’

Leylin sighed, thinking back to the truesoul of the Blazing Flame Monarch that was like a scorching sun. The soul force seemed to have solidified. A truesoul like this could be said to have reached a peak, and could exist for a long time even without the Magus’ body.

Soon after, he couldn’t help but burst out in laughter, finding himself too greedy. The path of a Magus was one of accumulation. Not only was the Blazing Flame Monarch of a higher rank than he was, she had spent tens or even hundreds of times longer than he had on searching for the truth. He was confident that, once he reached Breaking Dawn, his truesoul would not be second to hers.

“And this…” Leylin began to check all his profits. He’d been assigned many treasures from the attack on Düz City, a portion of the holdings a rank 6 organisation had amassed over time. Whether Morning Stars or even Radiant Moons, everyone would go green in envy at such wealth.

And yet, these things were all additional items to Leylin, not something he paid much attention to. What he was more interested in was the information recorded in the A.I. Chip.

“Soul splitting technique?” Leylin glanced through a document in the A.I. Chip while muttering to himself. He’d gotten this terrifying technique that could split apart a Magus’ truesoul when he’d taken advantage of Melinda earlier.

This technique could separate a truesoul into two parts, forming individual bodies that could think for themselves. It could also be used to discard unnecessary emotions or memories from the main body of a Magus, an extraordinary effect.

“Sometimes, psychological issues can be a hindrance to the advancement of a Magus. This technique is even better for Warlocks. Perhaps Offa and the others would be more than willing to take out all their wealth in exchange for this…”

Leylin stroked his chin. After obtaining this truesoul splitting technique, they could strip off the berserk emotions from their bloodline instability by placing it in another soul. To some extent, this was a way to completely cure the Warlocks’ bloodline instability. A rational Warlock still retained their advantages but had no weak points. It was a terrifying thought, but it had one small issue.

After the truesoul was split into two the separated soul was, in some way, an individual body of its own. It could even become like Melinda, forming a will of its own and becoming hostile towards the original Magus.

However, because they had originally been one body, Magi could not just destroy this parted soul, or else their truesoul would be affected. They could only choose to banish the soul or suppress it, which would leave a danger lying around.

‘Whatever it is, this technique is very valuable. If not for that being an emergency, Melinda probably wouldn’t have given this to me…’ Leylin thought about Melinda. The female Magus had initially been one with the Blazing Flame Monarch, but there seemed to have been some issues when splitting the truesoul which led to her returning for revenge.

‘She’s lost part of her energy and bloodline, and is also facing issues from the cracked soul which haven’t been solved yet. It’ll be difficult for her to recover to her original strength…’ Leylin’s eyes flickered.

This was a situation he had intentionally created. The conscient of the original Flame Monarch was done for, and Melinda had to heal the wounds to her body and soul. None of these were easy tasks. It would be a miracle if she could even remain at rank 6.

Leylin thus concluded that the Blazing Flame Monarch’s organisation would die down for a very long time. After gaining control of the body, Melinda wouldn’t be the same as the Monarch was before and it was unknown whether she would come after him in the future. He’d made the best choice in the situation.

“A.I. Chip, show me the database on the Blazing Flame Monarch!” Leylin commanded. Immediately after, a large file was projected in front of Leylin, the information within an incomplete mess.

Leylin hadn’t just devoured his opponent’s flesh and blood with his innate skill. He’d also managed to absorb her memories and her comprehension of laws.

However, due to a lack of time, the memories he had were incomplete. Yet, they were good references for the A.I. Chip.

Leylin’s eyes scanned through these incomplete memory fragments and came to the deepest ones. The few fragments here were like crystals that gave off a majestic aura, emitting burning hot rays of light.

Given that this was how the information was being displayed within the A.I. Chip’s database, it aroused Leylin’s interest.

[Beep! Comprehension of the laws of fire incomplete. Unable to scan and present as data, host needs to perform a soul force probe.]

The A.I. Chip’s explanation rendered him speechless.

This was the bit on the comprehension of laws that the A.I. Chip had separated from the remaining memories in the bloodline Leylin had forcefully obtained. However, it was currently in a strange state that even the A.I. Chip could not decipher.

“This is the issue of having different power systems,” Leylin sighed.

In his view, the world was one complete existence that had various focuses. His previous world was one that focused on atomic studies.

The Magus World, on the other hand, was a world of energy and laws.

In reality, there was only one real world. Atoms, energy and laws were all just the same thing viewed from different perspectives. These differences in perspective allowed Magi and the people of his old world to come up with different conclusions.

The A.I. Chip was a result of microscopy, and it could not decrypt things like the comprehension of laws. It was only something to be expected.

However, with its continuous upgrades and the establishment of the database on the soul, the A.I. Chip had made continuous progress. It now accepted the embodiment of energy and laws.

Leylin was very confident in the learning abilities of the A.I. Chip. Some day, it would be able to analyse anything in the universe, becoming the best tool to search for the truth with. For now, the current ability of the A.I. Chip to store the comprehension of laws separately already left Leylin satisfied.

Though it could not be sent to him, perhaps comprehending laws himself was the best way to go about it.

Leylin closed his eyes. Half Moon soul force spread out from his truesoul, making contact with the scarlet Law Comprehension Crystals.

*Rumble!* A vast current gushed forth, and Leylin felt like an ordinary being standing amidst a flash flood in the mountains.

Terrifying force weighed down on him from all sides, pushing and pulling at him with immense power. Many different scenes flashed before his eyes without end, detailing the comprehension the Blazing Flame Monarch had towards the laws of fire.

The red fire elemental particles seemed to be magnified a million times over as they appeared in front of him, their mysteries being unveiled layer by layer. Never had he felt as close to the fire element before.

This feeling came and left very quickly. In a few seconds, Leylin regained his senses from this comprehension.

[Host’s brain waves in a peculiar state. No records in database!]

[Beep! Host’s blood flow rate has increased. Increase in energy wave radiation.]

[Beep! Host’s fire elemental affinity has increased. Aptitude has been slightly strengthened.]

……

The A.I. Chip’s new prompts caused a smile to appear on Leylin’s face, ‘Comprehending the laws of fire can increase soul aptitude on top of increasing my elemental affinity?’

Leylin had never worried about his elemental affinity. His foundations were not half bad, and he’d never misstepped. Through the advancements in and strengthening of his bloodline, his control over darkness and fire exceeded that of most Radiant Moons.

However, his original soul aptitude was only at grade 3. Compared to grades 4 and 5, or even special geniuses, he still had a ways to go. His few advancements had only pushed him to the peak of grade 3.

Chapter 664: Descendant and Discovery

Not only did Leylin have a lot of information on methods to increase elemental affinity, he’d also attempted some of these methods himself.

There were ancient records detailing this field in the central continent, and the A.I. Chip had recorded the information down and used it well.

However, even the central continent that was touted as the cradle of the revival of the glory of Magi had very little information on soul aptitude.

It had been extremely unlikely for Leylin to find a physique from an ancient dead clan, and it might have been useful to him. However, Joanna had ended up self-destructing, something Leylin found a huge pity.

With what he understood, Leylin found that the power of laws could alter his soul aptitude. How could he not go crazy in excitement?

‘The power of laws is boundless and inexhaustible, and can even modify a Magus’ soul aptitude!’ Leylin’s eyes brightened. While he was a bloodline Warlock, he still paid much attention to his soul aptitude.

‘But…’ At the thought of what he had comprehended, a look of hesitation rose on his expression.

The Blazing Flame Monarch did not have complete authority over the law of fire, else she would long since have advanced to rank 7.

Her comprehension of laws was incomplete, and what Leylin had found from her memories was pieces of a fragmented version. He’d comprehended less than a tenth of the power of the laws of fire, and it was impossible for him to fully understand them and become a rank 7 Magus with this.

With the A.I. Chip’s lack of research and information on laws, it was impractical to rely on it to simulate the complete version of the law of fire.

“Hah… There’s no way around it…” Leylin sighed, “Profiting through that risk was already extremely lucky. Do I have to sneak attack another Magus that has comprehended laws and steal their comprehension?” He was unwilling to go up against someone who had completely grasped the power of a law and obtained control of it.

The World of Gods had a special title for existences at rank 7 and above; they were called True Gods. This was because once one completely understood the power of laws, even a regular human would step into the domain of divinity! The gap between the two was even wider than the gaps between ranks 1 and 6.

Hence, while Leylin and Melinda dared to grievously harm a Breaking Dawn Monarch, they definitely wouldn’t set their sights on a rank 7.

He wanted to live for a long time, hopefully peeking at and transcending to a state of immortality. Why would he intentionally seek death?

“Those things don’t matter yet. For now, I need to break the bloodline shackles as quickly as possible and break through to Breaking Dawn. After all, only peaking the power of my soul force will give me the foundations to begin to comprehend the power of laws…”

At the thought of what had happened during the comprehension process, Leylin’s expression turned grim. With his current soul force, analysing and comprehending the power of laws was much too difficult. Even though he had compiled all of the information, he had only felt a bit of the aura of the law of fire, and had not even understood 0.00001% of it.

Only Breaking Dawns could comprehend laws. Even being able to achieve what he had was because Leylin was talented and had the great help of the A.I. Chip.

“Whatever it is, I need to obtain the power of laws as soon as possible. Breaking the bloodline shackles will depend on it…” Recalling the meeting with the Wisdom Tree as well as its ‘gift’, Leylin’s eyes blazed as he immersed himself in understanding the law of fire.

Crimson light fluctuated around Leylin under a tree in the darkness.

His eyes were closed tightly, as if he was in contact with a world full of mysteries. Large amounts of this light surged around his body, the endless information forming a strange code as they hovered before his eyes.

He tried to stretch out and grab those flaming words, but the action was in vain. He could sense some flaming words continuously dig into his body like earthworms, causing him to tremble slightly. The comprehension of laws had begun.

*Bzzt bzzt!* Just as Leylin’s comprehension of the law of fire was about to begin, a massive amount of crimson light interrupted him.

“No! What’s going on?” Leylin almost roared. The state he’d been in was clearly one that was hard to come by, and it had been interrupted just like that. It filled him with a near-insane bloodlust.

“Wah! Wah!” Both his bloodline and the innate controlling ability of the Kemoyin Emperor laid a scene out before his eyes.

In an extravagant bedroom the dark subterranean world, a bed sheet had blood stains on it. A woman who was sweating profusely trembled as she held onto a wrinkled baby.

“Goo Gaa!” The baby with jet-black eyes still had amniotic fluid on its body. The umbilical cord had just been cut, and as if noticing Leylin peeping, the crying baby beamed up at him, causing the woman to be shocked.

“My blood! My blood has been born in Twilight Zone!” Leylin opened his eyes wide. All Magi had a strange sensitivity to their own blood, and given that the Kemoyin Emperor was the ruler of a race, Leylin’s sensitivity was even greater.

“Has the child I left to Celine been born?” His gaze penetrated through the ground and arrived at Twilight Zone. He hadn’t let the A.I. Chip control his interactions with Celine, intentionally leaving behind his bloodline with her. It was about time for the child to have been born.

Because these children were Warlocks, they would be different from regular humans. They would have some inborn talent, and could cause elemental storms or leak radiation at birth. Celine was a Magus herself and had defences against these situations. Most regular women would be done for.

The younger generation would mature quickly with Leylin’s rank 5 Kemoyin Emperor bloodline, and they would definitely be terrifying beyond belief.

With Celine’s influence, what kind of changes would be brought to Twilight Zone? Leylin’s eyes showed he was deep in thought.

And yet he was the same detached Magus after all, and he waited for a long time after observing the law of fire. With a slight sigh, Leylin placed his attention on himself, and the A.I. Chip’s prompts popped up.

[Beep! Host beginning to grasp unknown force, determined to be power of the law of fire. Fire elemental affinity increased by 50%.]

[Host’s soul aptitude has been strengthened. Recalculating… Determined to be upgraded to grade 4.]

‘My elemental affinity and soul aptitude have been upgraded after crossing the threshold of comprehending laws?’ Leylin was surprised by this. From his days as an acolyte to the current day, he’d only been able to raise his soul aptitude to the peak of his initial grade of 3. This one step he took into comprehending laws had pushed it up a grade, something with a terrifying meaning.

However, that would be it for Leylin’s current soul in terms of comprehension of the power of laws. He was only a Radiant Moon Magus after all, and his truesoul was still at Half Moon and hadn’t even reached peak Full Moon. It couldn’t support the study of laws.

In other words, Leylin himself wasn’t good enough to accommodate a greater understanding. He had to upgrade himself to break through, and that had to be accomplished by reaching rank 6, Breaking Dawn.

This discovery rendered Leylin speechless. Though he had stolen about 10% of the Blazing Flame Monarch’s comprehension of the laws of fire, he had only understood about 1%. The rest would have to be shelved due to him not meeting the prerequisites.

“My injuries have completely recovered, and I’ve gone through pretty much all of my profits. It’s time to return…” Leylin suddenly sighed, figure turning into black flames and disappearing from the area.

In an astral river, countless light-years away from the Magus World.

A starlike coiled up snake in the Purgatory World revealed the figure of the Snake Dowager. Every strand of her hair was a different serpent, emitting different kinds of energy. Her face was extremely exquisite, and her eyes held within them the life and death of worlds themselves.

Every inch of her body seemed to embody the law of darkness, and it was full of perfection and harmony.

Currently, there was a rare grimness in the Dowager’s eyes. “The Emperor of the Kemoyin has already begun to make contact with the power of laws? Its bloodline has begun to spread as well…”

The Snake Dowager could see the events in the faraway Magus World from across the astral river, causing her to sink deep into thought. Though the Kemoyins were only a small branch of her bloodline, they still represented a portion of her abilities and authority!

The imperial bloodline had left her on guard. This uncontrollable variable could one day become a power that would tear apart her divinity.

“Through the shore of clouds and stars, my bloodline shall all return to my embrace…” The Dowager’s voice was faint and tender, giving one the urge to lose themselves within it.

With what sounded like a prophecy, a tremendous illusory world slowly emanated from behind the Snake Dowager, and as if she was stepping through time and space, she entered the Magus World.

Chapter 666: Allsnake Curse

“A.I. Chip, conduct a full body scan!” Leylin commanded. He had just escaped from the Snake Dowager’s dream.

The Dowager was an existence that surpassed rank 7, and her power exceeded the limitations set by worlds. She could cross world borders and attack through Dreamscape, a strength that was unimaginable for Leylin.

When dealing with someone like her, it wouldn’t hurt to be cautious. Hence, thorough checks were a necessary thing.

[Mission established. Beginning scanning procedures. Atomic microscope has been authorised, beginning scan…]

Large amounts of blue light scanned every region of Leylin’s body after the A.I. Chip sounded, the images resolved to the cellular level. The atomic microscope scanned everything. The blue light took the form of countless threads that swept through him.

[Skeleton normal. Internal organs normal. Scanning bloodline and sea of consciousness…]

Leylin looked rather calm, but when the A.I. Chip’s rays scanned his blood and sea of consciousness his expression changed.

Tiny black runes wiggled out from the surface of his body, and after they emerged Leylin felt the blood circulation in his body abruptly speed up tenfold! The increase in blood flow caused his face to flush, and fine blood appeared deep inside his pores.

The black runes crawled to his forehead, forming the image of a little black snake. Around this snake was a ring of tiny pointed runes, resembling chains and a cage that kept the snake within.

“What’s going on?” Leylin felt the bloodline force in his body show signs of going berserk, and the rune on his forehead began to exert more strength. It was restraining him!

His bloodline force was rebelling against its owner, and restraining him. It sounded like a joke, but Leylin did not find it funny at all.

“Quiet down. Innate spell of control!” Leylin exclaimed.

*Hss—* The terrifying image of a Kemoyin Emperor appeared behind him. Currently, the phantom was encircled and bound by a circle of black chains as well. The massive Kemoyin Emperor hissed and roared, but it had no effect on the bindings.

There were even sharp barbs on the chains, and they pierced through his scales into his flesh. The intense pain was transmitted directly to Leylin’s truesoul.

*HSS—* The Kemoyin Emperor roared again, but this one seemed very feeble. Still, the will of a rank 5 ruler could somewhat control the rebellion of the bloodline force, and allowed the odd phenomenon in his body to calm down.

“What is this?” Feeling the binding rune on his forehead absorbing his bloodline force on top of suppressing him, Leylin’s expression grew grim.

He’d already guessed that this was something left behind by the Snake Dowager. She was someone who exceeded rank 7, an existence that had grasped laws. Even though she had been careless enough to let him escape, she still had enough time to leave something behind. As the source of Leylin’s bloodline, manipulating his bloodline force slightly was a simple task for her.

‘The rebellion of bloodline force… All those who walk on the path of bloodlines will eventually be shackled by the very bloodline itself…’ For some reason, Leylin suddenly recalled the time when he’d first obtained Kemoyin’s Pupil, more specifically the inscription by Great Magus Serholm.

[Beep! Host has been struck with an unknown curse. All stats decreasing.]

The warning from the A.I. Chip was bright red, showing the urgency of the situation.

“Show me the information!” Leylin grew grim as he felt the weakening of his body. The rebellion of the bloodline force as well as the suppression of a portion of his strength made him feel unprecedented weakness.

‘I was too careless before! Strength that depends on a bloodline might be very useful initially, but there are going to be some hidden dangers no matter what. If not for my bloodline having evolved to the Kemoyin Emperor and having gained some degree of independence, this mark could very well have caused me to lose all my strength and become subject to the whims of the Snake Dowager!’ Leylin’s expression was incomparably dark.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 5 Warlock. Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent (Complete form). Strength: 45 (76), Agility: 40 (62), Vitality: 100 (176.9), Spiritual force: 1013.5 (2003.5), Magic power: 1013 (Magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force). Soul force: 101 (200). Condition: Weakened by curse, stats lowering on all fronts. Currently at New Moon, future undetermined.]

Leylin now looked worse. These stats pulled him down to the level of one who had just stepped into Radiant Moon.

Though it had only been a short period of time, the curse had lowered his strength by about half, and there was a possibility of worsening.

Leylin looked at the ‘future undetermined’ in his status screen, and his voice was icy as he asked, “What does ‘future undetermined mean?’

[Based on evaluation of model, the curse will continuously absorb the host’s bloodline and increase its capabilities. The host’s stats are set to continue to decrease, and there is a possibility of a permanent drop in rank.]

The A.I. Chip quickly answered him, but Leylin had nothing to rejoice over.

“Decrease? To what extent?”

[Unknown. Possibility exists of a complete loss of bloodline force.]

The conclusion given by the A.I. Chip caused Leylin’s expression to grow even more serious.

‘Is it the bloodline shackles or a backlash? Or is this something the Snake Dowager chains her younger generations with?’ In an instant, Leylin’s mind came up with many possibilities.

This force was evidently linked to his bloodline force, and the closeness far exceeded Leylin’s expectations. In order to go further on the path of a Warlock, one would need to be modified by bloodline force, which was why it equated his own power.

However, when the Snake Dowager became hostile, Leylin finally knew the terror of the incomparably tame bloodline force when it rebelled.

Debts had to be repaid. Bloodline Warlocks relied on their bloodline force to amplify their progress, and be it in rate of advancement or battle strength, they exceeded their peers at the same rank. However, they were restricted by bloodline shackles, and once one met the source of their bloodline there was no way to fight back against them.

No. They, whose souls fused with the source of their bloodlines, would not even have thoughts of rebellion!

Leylin was sure that if Gilbert or any other Kemoyin Warlock was in his position, they would not even resist the Snake Dowager. Their wills were all subservient to her. This control extended past their bloodlines and into their souls. This was a powerful manipulation of souls! Unless one changed the soul, it was impossible to eliminate any influences.

‘Hehe… Once I have the intention of rebelling against you, you strike me down and make me a regular human? How overbearing!’ Leylin stroked his chin and suddenly began to laugh coldly.

‘But I will never let anyone take control of my freedom. Bloodline force? It’s my bloodline, and even though it originates from the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, it’s been altered and refined by the A.I. Chip. I even had it automatically evolve to become a Kemoyin Emperor, you can’t control me so easily…’

[A similar record has been found in the database]

the A.I. Chip intoned at this moment. With the accumulation of knowledge from Sky City and the Warlock Union, the A.I. Chip could be said to be a museum of the Magus World. No matter how rare and obscure a topic was, information could be found about it.

[Allsnake Curse: The Snake Dowager of the Shadow World has supreme control over all of her progeny. This is a blessing and also a curse, one condensed with bloodline force. Once a descendant has thoughts of disobeying the will of the Snake Dowager, the Allsnake Curse will appear and automatically absorb as well as seal off the descendant’s bloodline force, turning into the most powerful bloodline curse. Effect: Continuous weakening of power of Warlock, until target’s death.]

There was also a projection of an image beside this introduction, and it was a carbon copy of the one on Leylin’s forehead.

“Till death? I like it!” Leylin snickered, “A.I. Chip, based on this rate, how much time do I have left?”

[Beep! Based on current situation, host will fall from Radiant Moon in 26 hours, and in 267 hours lose Morning Star strength. 312 hours later, bloodline force will be completely lost and host will become a regular human.]

The complicated calculations were completed by the A.I. Chip in an instant, giving him a conclusion. “It’s too rushed. Is there anyway to slow the process?”

With its massive calculative ability, Leylin was given an answer.

[Host can suppress their own bloodline force and seal off their Radiant Moon strength. Such a situation can easily extend the period by three years in tandem with the Medusa’s Gaze potion.]

The Allsnake Curse was a curse that absorbed his bloodline force, which was why sealing his own strength would slow the effects of the curse temporarily.

Leylin nodded, but suddenly froze.

“Sealing off my Radiant Moon strength means I’ll be able to maintain this condition for three years, but I can’t use any strength at rank 5. In that case, if I were to meet a powerful enemy…” Leylin knew fully well that the more he used his own power, the closer he was pushing himself to death.

However, his enemies would not let him off so easily, especially the Snake Dowager. With the attacks from Dreamscape, he’d been forced to run for his life constantly, and this situation would force him to use his bloodline force. He had then suffered the backlash from the Allsnake Curse, which was probably her intention.

“In that case, she definitely won’t give up after one attack!” Leylin’s pupils shrank abruptly.

“Hss—” At the moment these thoughts emerged, his truesoul was distracted as he entered Dreamscape once more.

A terrifying gigantic white snake was spitting out its tongue, its gaze of one looking at a dead man.

Chapter 667: Mask of the Dreamless

“A.I. Chip, conduct scan!” Leylin ordered, and the A.I. Chip quickly sent a passage of information to him.

[Alabaster Devilsnake: Rumoured to be a descendant of the Snake Dowager that inherited dreamforce. Likes to torture its prey in their dreams before digesting them. Matures at rank 5.]

It gave him a thought. ‘Even the Snake Dowager needs to use a large amount of energy in order to send dreamforce to a faraway world. That’s probably why she just activated the Allsnake Curse and then left the rest to her children…’

*Hss—* At this moment, the Alabaster Devilsnake was flicking its scarlet tongue as its blood red eyes were fixed on Leylin. Its body rumbled as it moved abruptly, turning into a streak of white lightning.

‘There’s no choice but to act!’ Leylin laughed wryly, the energy in his body beginning to boil, “Dream spell…”

White lightning seemed to flicker through the void, and when things returned to normal Leylin was back in the real world.

At this moment, his face looked wretched. The Allsnake Curse on his forehead spread a lot of black veins, greedily absorbing his own bloodline force and turning the strength from his own body into a curse. It was a continuous cycle with no cure.

[Warning! Warning! Host’s bloodline force has reached the threshold and is about to drop from Radiant Moon.]

The red warning prompt the A.I. Chip sent out caused Leylin’s heart to sink. While he’d done his best to hold back his strength, in order to escape from Dreamscape he had no choice but to use dream spells and his bloodline force. It had provided the Allsnake Curse wtih an opportunity to act up.

‘No, this can’t go on! A.I. Chip, set up a maze in Dreamscape,’ Leylin quickly commanded. The possibility of being dragged into a dream and assaulted from all sides caused his face to turn dark.

[Beep! Mission established, beginning projection of guiding coordinates. Setting up Dreamscape firewall]

the A.I. Chip immediately intoned. That was the result of Leylin’s studies on Dreamscape. He could try to prevent others from pulling him into a dream, and while he did not know how well it would go, it was still better than nothing.

Making use of this borrowed time that would be hard to come by, Leylin immediately started on other plans, ‘A.I. Chip, begin procedure D-23, let’s forge the Mask of the Dreamless!’

This command was to make the necessary preparations for the Snake Dowager attacking through Dreamscape.

[Mission established! Beginning simulation. Materials required: 300g of Luk Alloy, tooth of single-eyed snake…]

These were all materials Leylin had found could isolate dreamforce in his previous experiments. A black gas appeared on his body with the A.I. Chip’s report, and the materials it had mentioned floated out from a flickering light in his waist pouch.

A bundle of demonic black light was formed, devouring the materials. Leylin looked calm as he watched the materials dissolve in the flames, occasionally making some seals and transferring some refining runes into the flames.

Just these few casual movements were extremely fluid, exhibiting the terrifying abilities of a Grandmaster alchemist.

With Leylin’s powerful control, it wasn’t long before a mask with only one half hovered above the flames. This mask was completely black, its fluid lines and decorative designs giving it a unique aesthetic. A strange aura was emitted from it.

The mask flew out and covered Leylin’s face, blocking the Allsnake Curse on his forehead.

Leylin seemed to change after wearing the mask, and now seemed to have some mysterious charm.

The A.I. Chip soon listed the ingredients and all sorts of information about the mask.

[Unique Magic Item— Mask of the Dreamless. Weight: 200g. Material: Luk Alloy, tooth of single-eyed snake. Effect: Prevents being spied on with dreamforce. Protects truesoul from invasions from Dreamscape…]

The icy cold mask covered part of Leylin’s skin, making him feel at ease, “Thankfully, I’d already been focusing on dealing with dream invasions, and had invented the Mask of the Dreamless.”

His fingers stroked the mask, feeling the complicated and intricate patterns. This mask was formed from simulations based on the A.I. Chip’s database. On top of that, with Leylin’s eye as a Grandmaster alchemist and his creativity allowed him to create this item.

It only had a singular function in blocking dream invasions, which meant it couldn’t be classified as a magic artifact or equipment. However, it’s ability did not lose out in value to some magical equipment either.

To Leylin, who’d altered himself for Dreamscape and was sensitive to dreamforce, the Mask of the Dreamless was something that finally allowed him to relax. ‘Unless the mask is destroyed, my opponent’s can’t just drag me into a dream and use up my strength…’

Leylin now fully comprehended the terror that was the Snake Dowager. Even while they were in different worlds, he could do nothing against her. Thankfully, with this as a buffer, he could now calm down and think through this matter.

“A.I. Chip, check the database of all the simulations I authorised and find a method to solve the Allsnake Curse.”

Leylin’s voice was low, and the A.I. Chip quickly began to operate as large amounts of information appeared in front of him. Countless formulae were used, and a faint image of the Snake Dowager even appeared in the virtual space.

With the countless calculations, the A.I Chip came up with a conclusion.

[Host has 3 options:

The Snake Dowager removes the mark of her own accord.

Host gets the blessing of a rank 9 existence, using their origin force to purge the Host’s bloodline.

Host completely breaks through bloodline shackles, severing all ties with the Snake Dowager.]

‘Plans 1 and 2 are impossible, there are too many uncertain variables. I can’t do anything for a high-ranked existence, so I’d have to rely on luck,’ Leylin touched his chin, light glinting in his pupils, ‘The only choice is to break through the restriction on the bloodline and break away from these shackles completely!’

The control and curse of the Snake Dowager came from the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s bloodline force. If Leylin could completely shatter the bloodline shackles and become an independent being, he would no longer be affected by her.

As he was now, this was the most feasible plan.

“But I didn’t expect to meet her so quickly. I’ll have to find a way to break the bloodline shackles. I can’t skip this, and I’ll have to go to Purgatory World…”

Leylin looked grim, ‘With my current state, I need to keep a low profile for a period of time…’ With this thought, he transformed into a bundle of black flames and disappeared.

In the Morning Star Area. Jeffrey wore a black swallow-tailed coat with not even a hair out of place, seeming like the most upright gentleman.

“Lady Freya is about to give birth. This is something worthy of celebration for our Warlock Union!”

“Yes! The rank 5 bloodline in our union now has been passed on! With the talent His Highness Leylin has shown, the future of his bloodline descendants is going to be bright…”

Offa laughed as he spoke. He was now waiting with Jeffrey above the castle for Leylin.

Flustered maids and servants ran everywhere in the castle. A layer of crimson energy spread through the area, gradually enveloping a room and still travelling outwards. The low voice of a woman sounded within.

“This is a rank 5 bloodline! Is it the Giant Kemoyin Serpent? What’s going on? Does the Kemoyin Serpent have an ancestor or something like that?” Jeffrey was rather curious about this.

“No. His Highness’ bloodline is the purest Kemoyin bloodline, there’s no doubt about it. Based on my observations, the bloodline he’s inherited might very well be that of the ancient Kemoyin Emperor, the ruler of the Giant Kemoyin Serpents!” Offa’s voice was soft, as if he was revealing some huge secret.

“Hss… In other words…” Jeffrey sucked in a breath of cold air.

“Yes! The royal family of the Ouroboros Clan has appeared. There is no leader more proper than the Kemoyin Emperor!” Ruling bloodlines held immense control over bloodline clans. This was the same case with the Snake Dowager over Leylin, and based on his Kemoyin Emperor bloodline Leylin had authority over the lives and deaths of the Kemoyin Warlocks under him.

His bloodline definitely ruled the Ouroboros Clan!

“The Ouroboros Clan will forever be subservient to the ruling bloodline to the day that the bloodline dies off. Unless that happens, betrayal will not occur for eternity!” Offa’s voice was still as low as before, “We have to be even more prudent when dealing with His Highness.”

“That I know, but… Bevis…” Jeffrey could only laugh wryly.

No matter what organisation it was, the appearance of talents like Bevis and Leylin were worthy of celebration. However, the two geniuses did not see eye to eye, which resulted in a great catastrophe.

To be honest, the reason they were here was to serve as protection and as a warning.

If not, Leylin would definitely not let Bevis go. If he were to do anything drastic the consequences were not anything they wanted to see.

Otherwise, even for the birth of a child with a rank 5 bloodline, there wouldn’t be two Radiant Moon Warlocks on guard duty.

At the mention of this, Jeffrey seemed to think of something and suddenly asked. “Lord Offa, did you see the news regarding the Blazing Flame Monarch?”

Chapter 672: Travelling Together and Appearance

“I was too naive. No matter how lax the professor from the Ennea Ivory Ring Tower could be in his requirements, a novice Magus like me isn’t competent enough…”

Leylin and Darlie sat facing each other in a fruit juice shop. Leylin was watching the passersby outside the French window as he listened to Darlie narrate her experiences after they parted ways.

Darlie was a talented Magus who had perseverance. She had a fault, however, in her youth.

Knowledge was the foundation of a Magus’ power. She was extraordinary for advancing to become a Magus at her age, but compared to those old freaks who’d amassed knowledge over hundreds of years she was nothing.

Hence, she had completely failed recruitment into the Ennea Ivory Ring Tower, being rejected at the start itself.

Her other female companions had fared the same way, and after the setback from the huge difference between their ideals and reality, they had long since returned to their hometowns. Some had even given up completely. Only Darlie had not let up, persevering and staying in Teljose City.

Soon enough, however, she was faced with a serious issue— she had gone broke!

Official Magi might seem extremely wealthy, but those who had just advanced had used up all their resources and magic crystals while breaking through. They weren’t particularly skilled in any area, and since they lacked magic crystals to purchase spell models and the like to grow in strength, it was an endless cycle. Magi were normally at their poorest after advancing, and the costs of Teljoce City were too much for someone like Darlie.

On top of that, she still needed to obtain more magic crystals in order to purchase things like spiritual force potions and spell models. Hence, after racking her brains, she had no choice but to swallow her pride and look for a job.

However, reality dealt her a ruthless blow. Darlie cared little for regular jobs, but she did not meet the requirements for jobs that needed official Magi. She had hit a wall many times already before bumping into Leylin today.

“It’s been just a few days, but you’ve already had so many experiences…” Leylin had the urge to laugh, but he forced it down.

Since he’d advanced as a Warlock, he was always stronger than others of the same rank as gim. On top of that, the A.I. Chip was a cheat that allowed him to amass knowledge that did not lose out to those old freaks. He’d never experienced such things.

In actuality, Magi like Darlie were the norm in this world.

“Is there anything I can help with?” Leylin asked kindly. He had some magic crystals lying around, and it wasn’t like they were of much use to him. They were effectively rocks to him, and he obviously wouldn’t mind showing some generosity.

“It’s alright. I’ve taken on a mission to gather starlight grass, and the rewards aren’t half bad. I’ll be able to survive for a while…” Darlie said in rejection. She was a strong and prideful child, and obviously would not accept such charity.

“Starlight grass, huh…” Leylin checked with the A.I. Chip, “That ingredient is only produced in Ebole Town. Though it’s not far from Teljose and it’s easy to gather it, a wave of disciples from the Primordial Spirit Slaying Sect fled there recently, making it more dangerous…”

“No wonder…” Darlie covered her little mouth, “I was wondering why the task was so simple, yet the rewards were so generous. Damn it…”

Seeing her finding this difficult, Leylin could not help but laugh, “I need to go there anyway. Let’s go together…”

“Mister…” Darlie grew extremely emotional, tears forming at the corner of her eyes.

“I really have something to do there!” Leylin emphasised. With a few days of soul and bloodline hints being transmitted, the Farlier descendant had come here, and was about to reach Ebole Town as well.

Leylin wasn’t someone with too much time on his hands. If not for such a thing, he’d just give her some magic crystals. Why would he waste his precious time and accompany her?

“Many thanks!” Darlie bowed deeply, a red flush appearing on her cheeks and spreading downwards.

The wheels kept turning, producing creaking noises. The uneven surface of the road left the carriage constantly shaking.

Within the carriage, Darlie was watching Leylin’s mysterious face that was covered with a black mask. She hesitated for a long time before she spoke, “Mi– Mister, my name is Darlie. May I know…”

As Leylin had kept his mask on all this while, Darlie had assumed that he was hiding his identity, which was why she had not asked for his name. Now, however, the two of them were going to Ebole Town together, and it seemed too lacking in manners if she did not inquire into this properly.

“Oh, I’m Leylin!” Leylin told the truth plainly. In his senses, the bloodline descendant was very close to the town.

However, the life aura on his body had been weakened to a maximum, and there was even an aura of death coming from him. If Leylin didn’t save him, it wasn’t likely for him to make it back to Teljose City.

“Leylin…” Darlie repeated the name a few times, and her expression suddenly changed, “The name ‘Leylin’, it’s the same as a Magus who’s in our history textbooks!”

“Oh?” Leylin stroked his chin. The Third Magus War and the rise of the Primordial Spirit Slaying Sect were very serious issues for the Magi of the south coast, and every detail about them had been noted down.

Leylin was mentioned, obviously. After all, he’d been the person who somewhat sparked all these issues. With Darlie’s own studiousness, she’d remembered it to this day.

“Hoho… I didn’t expect Lord Leylin to have the same name as that Magus in history. How interesting! Heehee…” Darlie covered her mouth, shoulders shaking slightly.

Perhaps it was because she was not wary of Leylin at all, or because she was charmed by the dreamforce surrounding him. She hadn’t even considered the possibility that Leylin was the same one from history.

“Oh? May I ask what the books say about him?” Leylin was rather curious of how the historians of the south coast evaluated him.

“Of course!” Darlie nodded, closing her eyes and seemed to recall content about him:

“Poison Sovereign King, Leylin Farlier of the Chernobyl Islands. A rank 2 Magus, and an important figure who caused the Third Magus War. Initially a student at the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy, he betrayed them and then fled to Four Seasons Garden. Countless battles allowed him to garner a reputation, with the most famous being the battle at the Eternal River Plains’ pocket dimension, as well as that at the Brambles Iron Door. Whereabouts currently unknown, he is wanted by both dark and light Magi. Evaluation: A rare Magus talent, seen only once in a thousand years in the south coast!”

It was as if she was reading the textbook itself, and the words she recited left Leylin laughing at himself.

“I never thought there would come a day that I’d enter a textbook!” Leylin touched the glossy and cold mask on his face, and couldn’t help but feel incredulous.

“What about your opinion of him?” Leylin asked her curiously.

“That Leylin?” Darlie’s eyes glazed over, as if a layer of fog had gone over them, “He’s a genius! There are rumours that he’s even a Potioneering Grandmaster, but he isn’t of high moral standing. I don’t like him!”

“Looks like I left behind a bad impression on the south coast!” Leylin could only shake his head, “Actually…”

“Actually? Oh, by the way Mister Leylin, why do you keep asking me questions about that fellow?” No matter how dim witted she was, she finally reacted.

“Oh, it’s nothing… just that we’ve reached Ebole Town!” Leylin opened the window on the carriage and nodded.

Starlight grass was a distinctive product found around Ebole Town. Irregular silver spots dotted its tender green leaves, sparkling with a charming light. It was hard to mistake it for something else.

Due to the threat of the Primordial Spirit Slaying Sect, which caused Ebole Town to lose all contact with Teljose City, the mission of gathering starlight grass now yielded very generous rewards.

“There are so few people in the town. I can’t even get people to buy from if I try…” Darlie felt helpless.

Since she knew how dangerous this place was, she was unwilling to stay longer. If she could purchase enough portions of starlight grass, she wouldn’t be at such a loss. However, the Primordial Spirit Slaying Sect’s bad reputation of going around collecting souls, not even leaving commoners, left the town practically empty. Many residents had left this area and fled, causing the town to become desolate. The Potioneers and those who gathered materials had disappeared.

“Ugh… looks like I’ll have to do it myself…”

Darlie lowered her head sadly, and then glanced at Leylin, who was beside her, “Sir Leylin, what are you here for?”

Leylin wore gorgeous clothing, just one of his gloves worth everything she was. Combined with his great bearing, he probably came from some ancient noble family. Why would a person like this find value in things like starlight grass?

“Me?” Leylin chuckled, “I’m waiting for someone!”

“Oh! You agreed to meet someone outside Ebole Town? If it’s convenient, could you tell me his name? I’ll look out for him,” she asked.

“Yes! He’s a younger generation member in my family. As for his name…” Leylin scratched his head. He had used the power of his bloodline to guide the descendant from the Farlier Family over. How was he to know the child’s name?

“Oh, there’s no need for that. He’s arrived.” Leylin’s eyebrows raised up, and he walked out. Darlie followed closely behind, her eyes showing her curiosity.

The scene of a chase appeared quickly in front of Darlie as she followed him out of town…

Chapter 674: Recognition and Ease

“No, he’s my assignment!” The rank 2 Magus of the Spirit Slaying Sect rejected immediately. Apprehending this Magus was the very reason he’d even come here.

“You’ve gotten this wrong. I’m not here to discuss terms with you, this is an order! Since you wish to die, let me help you!” Alric couldn’t be bothered to listen to reason, and he instead made his move. A violent, aggressive power crushed down on them, forming a domain of holy light.

*Rumble!* The forcefield of a rank 3 Magus left no way out for any Magi below that rank. The disciples of the Primordial Spirit Slaying Sect melted down in the holy light, their blood and flesh just dissipating away. Piercing screams sounded out.

“Lord Gargamel won’t let you off!” The silver spiritual force surrounding the rank 2 Magus flashed, abruptly forming a cloud of black fog as he planned to flee into the distance.

“What a bunch of noisy flies! Let Gargamel look for me.” Alric’s brows furrowed as his right hand began to grab towards the black fog. Boundless holy light converged to form a giant blazing claw of platinum. The cries of the rank 2 Magus sounded out as well.

With the flames burning it up, the black gas seeped out from the gaps between the fingers. Silver spiritual force light gradually dimmed, and eventually was extinguished completely.

In mere seconds, that arrogant sect disciple who left Darlie with no way out was annihilated.

The holy light vanished, turning into a gold-trimmed scholar’s cloak that appeared on Alric’s back.

Meanwhile, Darlie was completely frozen on the ground. Only after some time did she manage to yell out, “It’s Alric, Lord Alric! A rank 3 Magus!”

For the light Magi, Alric was synonymous with light and justice. His sort of strength and his terrifying influence were the life goals of all light Magi.

“You’re a descendant of the Farlier family?” Alric did not bother with Darlie, instead slowly descending as he looked at the Magus on the ground like he was looking at a corpse. His voice held the chill of millennia of winter, and would cause anyone to shiver in fright.

“Hehe… another one!” The Magus could not be bothered to move, or rather he knew that there was no hope of escape in front of a rank 3 Magus.

“You’re very unlucky.” Alric’s eyes were like two balls of flames, “If you were caught by the people from the Primordial Spirit Slaying Sect, they’d at most torture your soul for a century. I’ll instead torture your soul to death, extracting all your blood to prepare bloodline sensing magic so the Farlier bloodline will be destroyed completely…”

It was as if he was narrating something that happened every day. The cruel words laced with bloodlust left Darlie shuddering, ‘What’s going on? Wasn’t that young Magus being chased down by the Spirit Slaying Sect? How has he offended Lord Alric too?’ She felt giddy with confusion.

“Wait, the Farlier family? I seem to have read something about it… In the battle at the Brambles Iron Door before the third great war, Alric’s sole son Jojane died at the hand of Leylin Farlier. Because of the modifications he’d made to himself before, Lord Alric had lost the ability to reproduce further, and this turned into a blood feud…” As a top scorer, Darlie was familiar with this piece of history as well.

However, the consequences of her having the time to even think of this resulted in Alric fixing his attention on her, eyes full of a chilliness. She dropped to her knees, “My– My apologies, Lord Alric. I didn’t mean to…”

“Ha… haha!” The Magus on the ground began to laugh maniacally, “Alric, you’ll never have a kid even till your death. It serves you right to have no blood kin!”

“Damn it, damn it, damn it! You must all die!” With salt sprinkled on his wounds, Alric’s facial muscles began to contort as flames began to emerge from around his body.

“Die!” Light surged forth from his body, the milky white rays of death able to melt flesh and cause Magi to die an excruciatingly painful death.

*Clap! Clap! Clap!* Applause sounded from within the light, interrupting Alric’s attack. He could not help but shift his attention.

It was only then that he realised there was someone standing at the side, wearing a luxurious black scholar’s robe and a mask on his face. He had no aura undulations, which was why Alric had overlooked this man’s existence before.

This realisation caused his pupils to shrink, and suddenly left him with a bad premonition. A Magus that could conceal his aura so well would definitely be someone difficult to deal with.

“Who are you?” Alric glared at Leylin coldly, finding the face familiar the more he gazed upon it. The half of the face that could be seen seemed extremely familiar, yet there seemed to be a fog in his mind that made it hard for him to remember the name.

“Who am I? Alric, you should know best!” Leylin chuckled, and turned to encourage Darlie, “You explained it well!”

“That voice…” Alric’s brows were furrowed and the fog of confusion dissipated slowly. He had the feeling he was about to find the name he was looking for, hidden in the depths in his mind.

All of a sudden, Alric’s body trembled and he was instantly wide awake. Immediately after, Leylin’s face lined up with the one in his memories, causing him to bellow hysterically, “You’re… Leylin Farlier!!”

“Leylin Farlier?!” Two cries of alarm were heard from the sides, and the Magus on the ground’s eyes were filled with emotion as he stared at Leylin’s figure.

Darlie was completely horrified, ‘He– He’s the legendary Toxic Sovereign King? The rank 2 existence who worked behind the scenes and caused the Third Magus War? He’s Leylin Farlier?’

Her hands covered her mouth, and her brain halted.

‘Right… He never denied he was that Leylin. I was the one who wishfully treated him as someone with the same name…’ Scenes of her time with Leylin flashed in her mind, causing Darlie’s face to turn as red as an apple.

‘He- He’s very different from the legends!’ Darlie watched his back, eyes showing her worry. ‘Alric is a rank 3 Warlock! Can Mister Leylin…’

“Hah… hah… you’re Leylin Farlier. That voice and that face… Even if it’s half covered I won’t be wrong.” Alric huffed, his body twitching like he was an epileptic. He was so excited that he was practically frothing at the mouth.

“You finally appeared. Great, I can finally enact my vengeance!” He roared in a low voice, terrifying energy undulations exploding forth from his body that seemed to touch upon the Crystal Phase.

“Indeed, it’s sensible that hatred can drive one’s improvement. Alric, you’ve improved so much from before.” Though Alric’s improvement surprised Leylin slightly, those under Morning Star were still like ants to him. It was no big deal.

The terrifying forcefield of a rank 3 Magus caused the Magus and Darlie to lie on the ground like toads. The young Magus couldn’t help but yell towards Leylin, “My Lord, be careful!”

“Any amount of cautiousness is useless! The hatred from Jojane’s death, as well as the torture of the long wait… It can only be purged by all the blood in your body!” Alric roared, and holy light dazzled as it formed a gigantic cage ringed with pillars of light.

He had learnt his lesson from chasing Leylin down before. He knew that Leylin was powerful, and what’s more, quick. With just a slight misstep, Leylin could flee. In order to prevent such a disaster from happening again, he had to limit his opponent’s range.

“Die!” Having set everything up, Alric made his move. Boiling heatwaves converged in his hand, the light forming a gigantic statue of a goddess, her two wings spread to form a bow. A holy aura emanated from the bow that had formed.

A ray of light condensed to form the bowstring, and a terrifying energy undulation was released as Alric pulled back on it. Platinum flames converged, rushing forth from his fingertips to form a blazing arrow.

An explosive screech could be heard as the arrow was launched, leaving behind a glimmering white trail in the air.

“You’re focussing on long-ranged attacks? Looks like the lesson I taught you was deeply engraved in your mind!” Leylin shook his head and extended a finger, tapping on the flaming arrow.

This slight motion caused Alric’s expression to go dark, and the Magus and Darlie both were filled with concern.

“Unfortunately… Just this is far from enough” The flaming arrow struck Leylin’s finger, producing a crisp sound.

Immediately after, Alric’s expression quickly changed. The flaming arrow had fallen down, split in two. It charred the surrounding land before the flames went out.

“If that’s all you have, you’re too disappointing.” Leylin smiled at Alric, who in turn staggered back. It was only then that he realised that Leylin was no longer the rank 2 Magus who needed to keep fleeing from him.

His opponent was considered the greatest genius the south coast had produced in a thousand years. With hundreds of years having passed, what level of strength had he reached?

“What– What rank are you at now?” Alric slowly stepped backwards, two snow-white wings of light extending at his back. “That question isn’t important. You just need to die obediently…”

Leylin spoke without a care. Coupled with how he was dressed, he seemed very much like the stereotype of a huge rebel.

Chapter 677: Nonov

“Mm. Because of the materials used to make the Fallen Star Pendant, it can at best only become a piece of low-grade magic equipment.”

Although Leylin found this quite a pity, Krupp instead grew so excited he was about to froth at the mouth.

On the other hand, Darlie grew even more emotional. Seeing that the Fallen Star Pendant had really been upgraded to become a low-grade magic equipment piece, she was at first frozen before she pounced at Leylin’s feet. “Revered Lord Farlier, please take me in as your disciple… No, how could I qualify to be the disciple of such a great Magus? Please give me any chance regardless of what it is. Whether as a maid, a servant, or even a guinea pig, just give me a chance to learn from you!”

“You– You’re serious?” Leylin watched this female Magus. With her her thirst and pursuit of knowledge, she was very similar to how he had been back then.

Krupp had a stiff expression. It was nothing much for a Magus to become a disciple, but becoming a servant or a guinea pig would effectively render one dispensable to a dark Magus. This female Magus seemed to care nothing for her life. Rather, she was giving up her very life for the pursuit of truth!

“My Lord…” Krupp gaped but was unable to speak.

He was merely Leylin’s nephew. There was nothing beside that relationship that bonded them together. Before he was sure of what place he held in Leylin’s heart, speaking out like this seemed rather risky.

“I don’t have plans to teach anyone now, and I’m not lacking in servants either.” Leylin spoke indifferently, causing Darlie’s eyes gaze to dim. But Leylin’s next words brought her from the depths of hell to heaven. “But I give you permission to observe and emulate me for a period of time. How much you learn will depend on you.”

“Many thanks, my Lord!” she replied, tears lining her eyes.

However, Leylin had yet to finish speaking, “What can you offer me though, that is of equal value?”

“My everything!” Darlie’s tone was firm.

“Good. Swear it. Swear it on your soul and your honour, that from hereon out your power, your body, your soul and everything will belong to the Farlier Family branch head on the south coast, Krupp Farlier!”

Leylin sounded unenthusiastic, but Krupp’s eyes went wide, “What? Me?”

Darlie took a look at Krupp who was beside her, and immediately made a vow with her soul, “I swear on it!” With Leylin as a witness, it would haunt her throughout her life unless a Magus who comprehended laws aided her. Of course, the chances that an existence at or above rank 7 would help Darlie were pretty much nil.

“Patriarch… Why?” Krupp watched Darlie, looking puzzled.

“As the descendant of our Farlier family, you should help our family continue the bloodline!” Leylin chuckled, “Darlie is a great choice. She’s talented, and you’ve seen her willpower and good qualities for yourself…”

Astute as he was, Leylin had long since noticed Krupp’s slight crush on Darlie. This meant nothing to him, but as he was the real descendant of the Farlier Family he placed more importance on Krupp spreading his blood than his vengeance.

Having done this, he now felt that he’d done enough to make up for everything he owed the family.

Hearing Leylin saying something so shameless out in the open, a trace of a blush crept onto the faces of Krupp and Darlie, Magi as they were.

“*Cough cough*… My Lord, where are we going now?” Krupp directed the conversation elsewhere. He’d been running for his life ever since birth, and experiences like this one were rare. The only reason he’d felt anything for Darlie was that she was pleasing to the eye.

“Let’s go to the Abyssal Bone Swamp. I want to see how the academy is doing, and there are also some people I want to find out about.” Leylin smiled, considerately changing the topic, “It also looks like I need to show off some strength, display that the Farlier Family has a solid backing. It’ll be very troublesome if we keep getting harassed like this.”

“Troublesome?!” Krupp was first baffled, but his expression quickly changed.

An aged voice was transmitted to them, “Mister Leylin, could we trouble you to come out of the carriage?”

“Let’s go out, we have guests!” Leylin beamed, shaking his robes as he got to his feet. Krupp and Darlie exchanged a glance and lined themselves up behind him, seemingly with good chemistry seeing how they occupied his left and right.

The nightmare horse snarled in dissatisfaction and the carriage stopped. Getting out of the carriage, Leylin caught sight of a few aged Magi.

At the front was a white-browed old man with layers of wrinkles on a face that was covered with spots. He looked about to die at any moment, wearing a simple grey robe that contrasted the dazzling golden staff in hand. He seemed to be the speaker.

Beside him was an old woman wearing the clothing of aristocracy, her hair that had pearls and gems embedded within it tied in a bun.

The two stood on top of a large banyan tree which was blocking Leylin’s path. A large face emerged from the trunk. This banyan tree was actually a Magus, and its life force was the strongest amongst the three Magi!

The three immediately went on guard when they saw Leylin coming out. The one holding the staff was the first to speak, “Leylin Farlier?”

“That’s me.” Leylin’s body floated up, and he stood on top of the carriage. While the lack of an aura coming from his body gave no reason for it, the Magi opposite him felt a great feeling of danger.

“I am the Saint Nonov Ciel Andrew; you can call me Nonov. Beside me is Mistress Marjorie, and this giant tree is Lord Keefa!” The auras of Crystal Phase Magi became apparent as the old Magus introduced his party. All three of them were mighty rank 3 Magi whose spiritual force had crystallised!

Leylin could also sense scattered undulations from some bloodline treasures and other unique magical items, and there was even a high-grade magic artifact on them. It was apparent that they’d brought everything they had.

“Mm, you must be the leaders of the light Magi.” Leylin nodded.

“Yes,” Nonov said as he forced a smile. Even face to face he couldn’t sense Leylin’s aura. It was like his immediate vicinity was a boundless sea, drowning out any probes and leaving no traces behind.

“Is this about the issue with Alric?” Leylin asked casually. He could eliminate ants like these in one blow, but for the sake of the Farlier Family it was prudent to leave them alive to spread word of the terror he wrought.

“The matter with Alric was a personal feud between you and him. Though my Lord’s methods are a little… overboard… they aren’t unacceptable.” Realising that Leylin was not to be trifled with, Nonov immediately changed his plans. His conceding seemed quite pathetic to Leylin.

If he was considered weak, these Magi wouldn’t have bothered with such words and instead just killed him. They would cut the person who had tarnished the reputation of the light Magi up into a million pieces. However, realising Leylin wasn’t going to be pushed around, Nonov gave up his pursuit of enmity on Alric’s behalf.

After all, it was irrational to provoke a powerful Magus for the sake of a dead person, what more one whose family, organisation, and subordinates had all disappeared. It was all for the ‘big picture’. The casual sacrifice of Alric even left Leylin wanting to sneer in response.

This sort of thing was exactly why he was hellbent on becoming stronger himself, rather than depending on organisations.

“However, Lord Alric was still a colleague of ours. Shouldn’t Mister Leylin do something about this?” Nonov finally got to the point.

“What ‘something’?” Leylin watched the old man playfully.

“Mister Leylin was once a professor at Four Seasons Gardens, which means you were once a light Magus. As a light Magus, it’s our obligation to fight against evil!” Nonov seemed to be spouting righteous words. “The source of all evil in the south coast, the ancient demon that the Spirit Slaying Sect believes in, the Gargamel is alive. Is Lord Leylin willing to aid us in destroying the sect? I’m sure that once you contribute enough, Four Seasons Garden will be very willing to welcome you back…”

‘They can’t beat me, so now they’re trying to assimilate me to their cause’ Leylin chuckled inside, but Nonov had already begun stating his conditions. If Leylin were to attack the Spirit Slaying Sect and even kill the Gargamel, they would compensate him by admitting him once more into the Four Seasons Garden, even allowing him full control of it. It was indeed an enticing offer.

If Leylin was a peak rank 3 Magus, he would have put some consideration into it. However, there was no need to fake courtesy with his current strength. “I reject your proposal!” he exclaimed unceremoniously. Though the Gargamel had long since entered the list of beings he had to kill, he hated being threatened to do anything.

“What?” Such a blunt answer put the old man in shock, and his expression dimmed.

“There should be some enmity between my Lord and the Gargamel, no? Wouldn’t this be getting the best of both worlds? Or are you thinking of siding with the evil dark Magi?”

Chapter 678: Ease and Departure

“You learnt about that too… It seems like you know me quite well,” Leylin shook his head, “But did you know that the thing I hate the most is being coerced?”

His expression instantly darkened. “Furthermore, it’s better to deal with dark Magi than the likes of you. As long as I display enough strength to shock them, they become even more obedient than dogs, and won’t resort to sneaky actions in the shadows…”

“It looks like Sir Leylin is very prejudiced against us light Magi. What a pity…” Nonov spoke slowly, the golden scepter in his hand emitting even more dazzling rays of light.

“Are you done with all that nonsense? Like I said earlier, we should just eliminate him. He started out as a dark Magus!” Marjorie, who was beside Nonov, began to speak with a piercing voice.

*Sou sou!* The giant tree Magus under them did not speak, but large amounts of roots spread out from it to envelop the surrounding region. It formed a grid of roots in the area.

“Increasing your vitality by combining your life with plants’? How pathetic.” Leylin shook his head, seeing through the tree with a slight glance. While he didn’t say more than that, the look of pity in his eyes threw the banyan tree into a violent rage.

Boundless green light spread around the area. It was like it had formed a translucent crystal in the air, sealing the air around Leylin.

“As we discussed before. Keefa will be in charge of restraining him while you amplify our power. I’ll take the charge.” As he said that, Nonov took the lead, the golden scepter in his hands abruptly increasing in size to become a golden holy lance.

“Understood!” Marjorie answered quickly from behind him. All sorts of complicated and mysterious runes appeared from her body, disappearing into the giant tree and Nonov’s body. With that support, more of their spiritual forces crystallised, approaching the limit.

“Even after the amplification, they’re still only close to the limit of rank 3?” Leylin sighed, the disappointment evident in his eyes as he waved his arm.

*Rumble!* Black flames began encircling the horse carriage in defence. “Wait here, don’t come out and block me.”

Numerous tendrils that had come to probe the area sizzled, instantly burnt to ashes by the black flames. It caused the large banyan tree to let loose a miserable cry.

The black flames looked to be about to burn right up the roots, and the tree had no choice but to sever the affected ones, cutting its connection with them. Jade-green sap flowed out of the wounds in great amounts.

“AARGHORH…” The human face on the trunk let out roars that nobody could make sense of. On the other hand, the faces of Nonov and Marjorie changed.

“These flames burn the very soul! Lord Leylin seems to have obtained some amazing inheritance in his time away.” Golden light was produced from the lance, covering Nonov’s body as if some kind of golden armour.

“You think I’m relying on some inheritance? You think that’s what gives me my strength?” Leylin replied, disapproving.

“Heaven’s Lance, make a judgement for light and justice!” Nonov’s body seemed to burst into golden flames. He hurled the lance in his hands into the distance, and it seemed like a golden meteor was launched. The lance reached Leylin in the blink of an eye. Black even streaked near the tip of the lance, fine spatial cracks being formed.

“I must say, you’re quite good for a rank 3 Magus.” Leylin stretched out his hand as he yawned. In front of that pale hand, be it the golden flames or the spatial cracks, everything was destroyed. The terrifyingly sharp tip of the holy golden lance could do no harm to his skin as he grabbed it.

“It’s best not to show this stuff and humiliate yourself.” As if in answer to all the taunting from the three Magi, Leylin exerted a bit of force with his two hands.

The golden lance broke apart at the center, the screech it left behind sounding miserable. Golden sand fell from where it had broken apart, causing the main body to quickly collapse.

“No, how is that possible?” Nonov took several steps backwards, blood flowing from the corners of his mouth due to the backlash of having his holy lance destroyed. Two streaks of red fell from his eyes, “This is a treasure that’s been passed down in our academy! Even peak rank 3 Magi shouldn’t be able to so much as move it!”

“Let’s go! He’s even more terrifying than that Gargamel!” Marjorie pulled at Nonov, and the banyan tree below them abruptly pulled up its roots and fled like a giant, each step allowing it to cover hundreds of metres.

“Activate the interference formation we’d planned for the Gargamel!” Nonov seemed to have recovered, but his eyes still held a trace of shock. He took out a white handkerchief to cover the blood from the corner of his mouth even as he gave his command.

The earth rumbled as four pillars of light, red yellow, blue, and green, shot up around Leylin. Smoke and multi-colour light appeared in the air, forming a tremendous spell formation with runes snaking around its surface.

“Nonov, the enemy is far stronger than we expected. The four-pillared stone seal shouldn’t be able to hold him down for long. We’ll need to use our final treasure!” Marjorie exclaimed solemnly.

“Roar…” The banyan tree Magus under them thundered, emitting spiritual undulations of approval.

“In that case…” Nonov’s expression underwent several changes before he finally gritted his teeth and reached into his robes.

*Rumble!* All of a sudden, loud thuds sounded from the sealing formation, causing shivers to go down the spines of the three Magi. It was like some powerful ferocious beast had been set free in there, bursting forth with enough force to break it open. Bumps appeared in the barrier, and the runes on top of it shattered like glass.

“How is that possible? That’s our four-pillar rock seal, even the Gargamel was trapped inside it for a few minutes. How long has it been?” Marjorie let out a piercing shout.

“Prepare to strengthen the seal. Use the Aquatic Devil Seaweed and help me gain time. Quick!” Nonov looked exceptionally sinister.

“But that’s the last secret trick we have. There’s only enough of the Aquatic Devil Seaweed to be used once…” Marjorie obviously hesitated.

“His strength is the greatest catastrophe for us. I even suspect… quick!” Nonov coughed out blood.

“Fine.” Marjorie merely hesitated for a moment and immediately grew clear-headed, tossing a dried-up seaweed into the formation.

“Emissary sleeping deep within the sea, please heed my call…” With her chants, the small dried-up marine seaweed abruptly swelled in mid-air, as if it had absorbed a large amount of moisture. Even its surface grew wet.

Large amounts of moisture gathered within it and formed a dark green ball of plants, with all sorts of seaweed on it. The plant ball shifted above the sealing spell formation before it suddenly exploded, threads of black seaweed forming a web that covered the area.

“Alright! Even if it’s a peak rank 3, the Aquatic Devil Seaweed can still achieve…” The glee in Nonov’s eyes only lasted a short while. His eyes nearly popped out from their sockets and he lost all of his previous demeanour, “How is that possible?”

He could see a gap in the middle of the formation, be it the four pillared stone seal or the threads of seaweed. A Magus wearing dark-golden scholarly robes and a mysterious mask on his face walked out arrogantly. Immediately after, a black hole appeared in his hands, sucking in the surrounding seal and the aquatic seaweed.

*Pow!* A slight explosion sounded in the air, and in the blink of an eye, the spell formation and the devil algae seal had turned into a miniature model in Leylin’s hands.

“This is far beyond rank 3. You’re a Morning–” Nonov’s face immediately seemed to lose all blood, becoming so pale that it was frightening.

However, Leylin did not give him the chance to kneel and beg for forgiveness nor flee, “The tasteless games shall end now. I’ll return this to you!” He tossed the model in his hand lightly in front.

The seal that was compressed a thousandfold rumbled, abruptly blowing up along with the devil algae. Formless energy buffeted all directions, shaking the earth itself. Multi-coloured light rippled in the air, the magnificence concealing a deadly danger.

“I’m warning you right now. Don’t provoke the Farlier Family, or else…” Leylin gently landed above the carriage, and under Krupp and Darlie’s reverential gazes headed inside.

The demonic nightmare horse neighed and galloped wildly, several times faster than before. It even soared into the air after a while, turning into a flash of light that streaked through the horizon.

The terrifying explosions continued for a while in the place they’d left behind before gradually ending to reveal two figures, both in a sorry state.

Keefa, the gigantic banyan tree of a Magus, had already disappeared; he’d used his body to absorb most of the attack.

“Keefa!” Marjorie was not in a very good condition, but what had given her the greatest blow was not her injuries. It was instead that terrifying and invincible figure.

“It’ll be fine! Though his body was destroyed, his seed is still alive.” Nonov produced a green seed.

Chapter 682: Granting Audience and Captive

“Whatever the matter, Lord Leylin is Abyssal Bone Forest Academy’s greatest success and fortune!” the glance the leader of Lighthouse of the Night shot at Nyssa hinted at something, and no matter how hard she tried to conceal it a hint of glee appeared in her eyes.

The greater Leylin’s reputation was, the better it was for the academy. With his fame, the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy would definitely be able to expand enormously under her administration. She could even accomplish more than what all the previous directors had been able to. This was the petty and low reason for which Nyssa was trying so hard to invite him to join them.

‘If I could make use of their good relationship and get Leylin to become a famed professor at the academy…’ Just the idea had Nyssa trembling in her excitement; she was perhaps smiling even in her sleep.

“Also… I seem to see a lot of old friends from the light Magi here!” The green-eyed Magus stared at Nyssa with a half-smile.

“Yes, there are quite a few. Ennea Ivory Ring Tower, Four Seasons Garden… Practically all the large light Magus organisations have secretly sent people to make contact with us.” Since it was basically impossible to hide it from him, Nyssa just nodded and admitted it.

“Hu huu… looks like his reputation has terrified them…” The leader laughed in a strange manner, like an owl in the night.

The Magi of light and dark coexisted in the south coast. However, the light Magi were evidently much stronger and occupied most of the resource-rich regions, and the dark Magi could only eke out an existence hidden in the corners. The leaders of the light Magi had steadily suppressed them.

With the appearance of the Gargamel, there was now a three-way confrontation. The dark and light Magi might have temporarily stopped fighting, but the enmity between them had not been resolved, only inhibited by the existence of a powerful external enemy.

Now, with a Morning Star Magus who had started off as a dark Magus, this was more than enough for the old light Magi to be like cats on hot bricks.

At this thought, a sneer appeared about the leader’s lips.

“Director Nyssa and this lord here!”

At this moment, Krupp appeared before Nyssa, and it was as if the figure of a snake flashed in his eyes. The bloodline aura he had caused even the leader, who was a rank 3 Magus, to feel his heart palpitate.

“The Patriarch is willing to meet you. Please come with me!”

Krupp’s hair and eyes almost turned completely black, darkness elemental particles extremely dense as they strived to outdo each other and wiggle into his pores. Such a scene astounded Nyssa and the leader.

Having said this, Krupp led the way while Nyssa and the leader transmitted each other messages secretly.

“So this Magus is that lord’s grandson? The descendant of the Farlier Family?” The leader’s eyes were filled with curiosity. After all, a powerful rank 2 Magus was very rare in the south coast. Any one of them could take over an organisation and still hold immense power.

“He’s obviously only advanced very recently. While in history, it’s common for that to happen to the descendants of high-ranked Magi, but…”

A hint of hesitance appeared in his voice.

“Yes! This Magus isn’t Sire Leylin’s descendant, but only a branch from his brother!” Nyssa knew what he wanted to ask and gave the answer.

“A lateral relative?” His eyes went wide, before he lowered his head to chuckle, “I now have even more expectations towards Sire Leylin!”

“We’re here!”

Krupp brought Nyssa and the leader into a large hall. There, many Magi were already in wait, but there were two entirely different groups.

At one side were Magi, with many wearing black Magus robes. Their auras were ice-cold and evil. After seeing the arrival of the leader of Lighthouse of the Night, many drew close and greeted him like moths to a flame.

The Magi at the other side who saw this mostly huffed, not looking very good.

They were clad in white robes, with many decorations of plants that represented life on it. Light and a holy aura began to emanate from their bodies.

“He called them all at one go? I’ve been greeting the leader of the Lighthouse of Night all this while, but this…”

Nyssa gritted her teeth, and her expression became a wry smile.

With Leylin’s absolute power, that bit of authority she had as the director was probably even lighter than a feather in the eyes of the Abyssal Bone Forest professors.

Hence, after being ordered by Leylin, they carried out what he asked without hesitation and even gave her the misconception that they had abandoned her.

No! This wasn’t a misconception. Nyssa knew very well that as long as that man were to say that he wanted to be the director of the academy, she would immediately be made to renounce her position.

Thankfully, he had never been fond of power and status. Furthermore, the academy was just much too small for him, to the point that he might turn his nose up at it.

Nyssa, who thought about this, finally relaxed, the bit of worry she had disappearing.

“Everyone!”

Krupp stood on the platform in the middle of the hall with Darlie beside him. While she had not undergone bloodline modification, she’d been observing Leylin and learning from him. Leylin’s knowledge was abundant and he could give perfect answers to all her questions, which very beneficial to her without her being aware of it.

Flames flickered, and Leylin floated above the place where the master should be, black eyes scanning his surroundings.

A terrifying and vast aura that was like countless stars in the skies filled the hall. All the Magi that Leylin looked in the eye, whether the rank 2 Nyssa or rank 3 leader of Lighthouse of the Night felt a piercing pain in their eyes, and subconsciously lowered their heads, even bending their waists.

“Greetings, Lord Leylin…”

Having personally sensed Leylin’s aura and how terrifying he was, the Magi had no disillusions about his strength.

“Rise!” Seeing the many Magi who had bowed, Leylin raised his arms slightly.

Immediately after, the Magi below the platform felt themselves being raised by a warm draft, holding within strength that they could not oppose.

The Magi could not help but stand up straight, eyes full of astonishment.

“I’m afraid it’s true that this lord has already advanced to be a Morning Star!”

The leader of Lighthouse of the Night’s pupil’s flashed. He now had no doubt at all towards Leylin, who had easily defeated a top-notch master of the light Magi and even destroyed their final trump card, the Blade of Avarice.

Leylin glanced through. Lighthouse of the Night, Ennea Ivory Ring Tower, Four Seasons Garden, Skeleton Throne… Besides the representative from the Spirit Slaying Sect, everyone in the Magus World from the south coast had arrived.

These top-grade dark and light Magi organisations were very well-known back in the day. Now, however, they could only creep at his feet.

However, Leylin did not even twitch. The Magi under the platform could not tell Leylin’s expression under the mask and merely lowered their heads humbly.

Leylin continued to speak, “I wonder what all of the Magi here have come for?”

The Magi exchanged glances. The reason they were here was mostly to verify Leylin’s might and his attitude.

Based on what had happened, there was no question about his strength. Just displaying the tip of the iceberg had them gasping in admiration, and nobody dared personally test it out with a battle.

Besides that, this lord’s attitude towards the two factions seemed rather mild. It wasn’t good or bad, as if he had no ambitions to unify the south coast.

This discovery had many light Magi sighing in relief.

“Lord Leylin!” At this moment, the leader of the Lighthouse of the Night stood out.

“Speak.” Leylin extended his arm and made a polite gesture for him to go on. Inside, he was sighing a little. In his acolyte days, he’d once seen the leader during the bloodbath for the secret dimension.

At that time, just a gaze could cause him grievous injuries or kill him. However, the tables had turned. With just a look, he would immediately be stricken with terror and die miserably.

“Please forgive me for my boldness in saying this, but… have you… already become a rank 4 Magus?”

The leader of the Lighthouse of the Night hesitated but eventually asked.

Things like status had long since lost interest to him. The only thing that would attract him and cause him to invest his mind and body in was a thirst towards a higher realm.

Hearing this question, the hall quieted down. Everyone watched Leylin expectantly.

“This question…”

Just as he was about to answer, a smile appeared about his lips, “Please forgive me, but I will answer this later. Let us first meet a friend!”

“A friend?” The leader was stunned, and immediately noticed two translucent faint figures pressing on either side of a demonic being that suddenly emerged from the void.

“That’s… the Gargamel of the Spirit Slaying Sect!”

Between the two void assassins was a soul demonic being. It had a mask of a horned demon, and its body was as concentrated as a black crystal. Vast soul undulations was transmitted from its body, causing the expressions on these Magi to change.

This was a level that surpassed all of them who were advancing towards the path of Morning Star.

“Is that really the Gargamel?”

“Definitely! This strength that’s mixed with resentment and lunacy is something all Magi who’ve seen it even once can’t misidentify…”

Many Magi whispered incessantly amongst each other, and then watched Leylin with reverence in their eyes.

Chapter 683: Confirmation and Travelling Together

With the appearance of the Gargamel, the Magi present sank into a mysterious silence.

They knew very well how terrifying and troublesome the Gargamel was. Not only was it powerful at magic, it could support its body with vengeful dead spirits, allowing it to maintain peak condition at all times. Even when struck by the light Magi’s final trump card, the Blade of Avarice, it had only been injured and not killed. It only went low-profile for a while before making waves again.

If not for the Magi being unable to deal with it, the Spirit Slaying Sect wouldn’t be able to rise in the south coast to be regarded equal to the dark and light Magi.

Now, however, the sect chief, the Gargamel that the disciples fiercely believed in had been seized so easily. The demon that had caused so much terror was suppressed under the platform.

The huge contrast left the Magi questioning whether they were in an illusion.

However, they had no choice but to admit that this was reality after a few tests. Even Leylin’s subordinates had the ability to take down a peak rank 3 Magus!

Capturing someone at the same rank alive was more difficult than killing them. This was something known to all Magi. They would perhaps only have a slight increase in respect if Leylin had captured the Gargamel himself. However, this was his subordinates’ work, the effect on them was so great that it couldn’t possibly be better from Leylin’s perspective.

The two void assassins bowed slightly and disappeared into the void. Such strange methods caused many Magi to have changes of expressions. Now, they understood very well that with just a command, he didn’t have to do anything at all. Just his two subordinates could eliminate all the Magi here!

Recognising that, they no longer dared to have any thoughts about Leylin, fearing he would notice.

“Gaga… gege… you are… Leylin!”

A hoarse voice sounded from behind the Gargamel’s horned white bone mask. It sounded intermittent, but was evidently much more quick-witted than when he’d first seen it.

“Yes. How’s’ that pitiful Magi mother and daughter doing?”

Leylin asked indifferently. He was obviously talking about Old Devil and her daughter in Teljose City then. The old witch had made a deal with the Gargamel to revive her daughter, and even tried to offer Leylin up as a sacrifice.

Of course, after Leylin’s counterattack, they had suffered consequences and fused to form a strange being.

“Them? I ate those two useless pieces of trash long ago!”

The Gargamel’s speech became more fluent.

“Is that so…” Leylin seemed to be in a daze for a moment, as if recalling some distant memories.

“Ga ga!”

At this moment, two bundles of crimson flames emerged from under the Gargamel’s bone mask. Numerous runes burst on its body, and a layer of thick black fog spread.

“Crap! It’s gotten out of its bindings!” The Magi shouted in their fear and anger, bodies flickering with colourful innate defensive spells.

“The home of all living things can only be the tomb of the soul for eternity… the Gargamel!”

The Gargamel yelled as if chanting runes of sacrifice that constantly echoed.

*Boom!* Amidst the curse, the Gargamel’s body exploded and countless figures emerged from its body. There were the old, young, male, female, and the one common point they had were their vicious faces as well as eyes that were dripping blood.

“Keke, let’s destroy everything together. Soul Disaster!”

The bone mask exploded with a rumble and turned into powder that flew through the air. Bits of light fused with the figures from before, the terrifying aura they emitted causing even the leader of the Lighthouse of the Night’s expression to change.

The peak rank 3 Gargamel had now was treading on the threshold of Morning Star. The dreadful attack formed by ruining its own body meant he had no thoughts that he could survive as a rank 3 Magus himself.

He knew very well that once such a spell completely broke out and spread, the Magi in the hall would die, and even the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy would not be spared.

“I’m going all out! Though using secret techniques will consume much of our measly life force, it’s still better than dying here!”

The leader called out in a low voice, a layer of fine black runes appearing around his body. They were like tadpoles cruising through the air, as if about to collide with that soul body of nothingness.

*Weng! Weng! Weng!*

At this moment, blue starlight descended, and the leader’s body quivered. He found that his spiritual force had gone stagnant, and even the secret technique he was risking his life force for was forcefully being suppressed. He felt no weakness, and the backlash had evidently been pushed down and not consuming his life force at all.

“This– This…”

His eyes went wide as he watched the stars that spread from Leylin’s back.

The light blue starlight brought with it a cold brightness that penetrated through the layers of defence and ground of the Abyssal Bone Forest, arriving in the hall. This made it seem as if the top of the hall was a dome showing the night sky with bits of starlight projecting and showing inverted images of gorgeous lights.

Accompanying the lights was a terrifying pressure that caused elemental particles to be rejected. The night domain that the leader had always been proud of exploded with a rumble in front of the pressure like bubbles.

“Ahh…” “Ga ga…” “Zhi zhi…”

The numerous spirit bodies in the sky were like bugs frozen in amber, unable to move at all. No Magi were injured.

“This– This is…” The leader trembled, crouching down almost involuntarily, “The Morning Star Domain of a Morning Star Magus!”

Compared to the fake domain of a rank 3 Magus, the exhibition of a real Morning Star domain with prowess that was terrifying to the extreme made him seem to be a joke.

“Gargamel, did you think I really didn’t notice what you’d been doing?”

Leylin looked calm as he watched the many faint figures in the air. He grabbed forward casually, and a soul that looked dazed automatically flew over.

Immediately after, the look on the soul’s face became sinister, body covered with black and two horns growing on the tips of his head as it growled at Leylin unceasingly.

“You look like you’re going to implode yourself, but you actually hid your soul in one of the figures. As long one of these figures and vengeful spirits escape, you can use that body and revive yourself?”

Leylin coldly scanned the numerous vengeful spirits in the air.

“Very impressive. Perhaps regular Morning Star Magi might not notice and let you escape, but it’s a pity… you met me!”

Leylin clenched his right fist.

*Boom!* Large numbers of vengeful spirits were like popcorn as they popped, a silver vortex forming and pulling the many figures and their remains within.

“No~~~!” A very unwilling roar was heard in the air before it finally became softer and disappeared.

The many spirits formed from the Gargamel’s self implosion, as well as the one that Leylin had specifically picked out, all disappeared as they entered the silver vortex.

*Pak!* The Morning Star domain dissipated, and all that had just happened was like a dream, yet had happened in real life.

“Anye, greeting Morning Star Magus, lord Leylin Farlier!”

At this moment, the leader of the Lighthouse of the Night sounded. He knelt on the floor respectfully, looking as if he were a pilgrim.

“Greetings to Lord Leylin…” Now, the other Magi knelt like they had just woken from a dream, faces filled with excitement.

All that had happened just now and the appearance of the Morning Star domain made it clear that the Magus sitting at the main seat, Leylin Farlier, had truly entered the rank 4 realm.

In the south coast, after thousands of year, a Morning Star had finally appeared once more!

In that moment, some elderly Magi felt their eyes go blurry, filled with heat.

……

In front of the metal door where many light Magi were guarding, many peak rank 1 elite troops were with rapt attention as they did their job.

Not far away, there were many rank 2 Magi undulations transmitting from a few buildings.

*Sou! Sou! Sou!*

Three human figures appeared in the air, flying towards the metal door.

“Stop right there! This is the entrance to the pocket dimension of the Eternal Plains, and it’s protected by the Lighthouse of the Night. What do you think you’re doing?”

A spiritual force undulation was transmitted. Immediately after, the Magus standing leftmost hummed coldly, eyes emitting dark green light, “It’s me!”

“Revered leader!” The rank 3 Magus’ undulations dispersed, and the Magi who had been on their guard had their right hands on their chest as they greeted him.

Three human figures touched down, revealing two figures on top of that of the leader.

At the rightmost was a beautiful female Magus who had an exquisite face like a doll. Now, however, she and Anye automatically took a step back and allowed a space, as if not daring to stand shoulder to shoulder with the Magi between them.

The Magus in the middle wore dark golden, black scholarly robes with a cutting that was very proper. He had a very noble aura and had a black mask on his face with mysterious patterns on it.

Such dressing and to be accompanied by their own leader immediately rang the warning bells in this guard Magi.

Before, there had been no Magi that could stand on equal ground with their leader in the south coast. However, this situation had changed tens of days ago.

The guard Magus knelt respectfully and shouted the arrival’s name, “We welcome, great Morning Star Magus, Sire Leylin Farlier…”

“We want to enter the Eternal Plains pocket dimension. Make preparations immediately!” Anye ordered.

Leylin nodded casually and stood by the metal door with Nyssa.

“The Eternal Plains pocket dimension… it’s been so long!”

Leylin watched the large metal door before him, eyes full of nostalgia.

Scenes of the danger when he had advanced to rank 2 seemed to appear in his mind in that instant, every person extremely lively.

Chapter 685: Strengthening and Way of Escape

“Lord Leylin is extremely erudite,” Nonov said in praise, “Ever since the ruins appeared the seal has slowly been lifting. No matter what methods we think of, we haven’t been able to stop this process…”

“And you’ve come to me as a last resort.” Leylin’s snort had Nonov and Anye break out in cold sweat but he didn’t concern himself with them, instead stroking his chin as he fell into deep thought.

Although the subterranean world was rich in resources, with the violent invasion of the ancient Magi many of the tribes there didn’t have a favourable impression of humans. Although humans remained there, after so many years would they side with the humans or the subterranean world? The latter possibility was more likely.

The subterranean world was vast and boundless, and wasn’t lacking in powerful Morning Stars even in the first layer. There should even be rank 5 existences there.

Twilight Zone was only a very small part of this first layer, just like how the south coast was just a part of the surface world. Furthermore, even in spite of its long isolation, there were many terrifying tribes there.

Thus, it wasn’t hard to understand why Nonov and Anye grew extremely panicky seeing the seal wither away.

“A.I. Chip, based on the current rate, how much longer will the seal last?” A blue light shone from Leylin’s eyes before he had the answer.

With a series of calculations, the A.I. Chip gave an extremely precise answer. [Beep! Calculating with current rate of decay, estimated time to total disintegration is 28572h 34min and 12s.]

To the A.I. Chip which had already been renewed several times, this level of operation was only the simplest.

“You invited me here, what exactly is it for? If it is to strengthen the seal, I’m afraid I can only delay it for at most a hundred years’ time…”

After he finished calculating, Leylin stroked his chin and said to Nonov and Anye.

“How… How can this be? Sir is a Morning Star ranked Magus!”

Such an outcome caused Nonov and Anye to be a little in disbelief.

“Hmph! If it’s just to strengthen the seal. although it’s relatively harder, it’s not that I’m unable to do it, but now, the entire Eternal River pocket dimension has been completely developed for several hundred years, most the remains here have also been destroyed by you…”

Leylin snorted, watching Nonov and Anye, his tone was very hostile, “In fact, the entire Eternal River pocket dimension is a part of this seal. The Magus who set up this pocket dimension had long before installed the time when the pocket dimension would appear, he even used your greed and sped up this process artificially…”

“Until now, the breaking of the entire seal is already something that’s unavoidable!”

“We’re done for! We south coast, are we really going to be completely destroyed?” Nonov’s both eyes were slightly despondent. If it really linked to the underground, apart from his Ennea Ivory Ring Tower moving to a distant place and collectively migrating, there was no other better way.

On the other side, Anye’s expression was also very dark. Towards the viciousness of the underground tribes and their hatred towards humans, he who had the reference of historical books knew even more clearly.

Once they were attacked and occupied, probably not just Magi, even ordinary humans would face extinction.

Watching these two Magi who had sunk into a struggle, Leylin’s pupils were very calm.

In fact, with the Radiant Moon strength and the assistance of the A.I. Chip, if he made an all-out effort, not stinting on cultivating more precious materials, it was not impossible to entirely seal this pocket dimension. However, the crucial thing was, how would that benefit him?

Nonov and Anye were both rank 3 Magi, they were small and weak like ants before the underground tribes. Naturally, they would not wish to see them infiltrate the surface and threaten their positions.

But Leylin was different! He was already a rank 5 warlock! His military strength was outstanding and the underground world’s first layer was also the weakest underground world, he totally had the premise of associating equally with the underground powerhouses!

With the underground world’s rich mineral resources, their legacy that had been passed down from the ancient times and the entirely different spell system, they could definitely bring Leylin great benefits.

He believed, not just himself, even if it were other Morning Star existence in the central continent, once they knew about this passageway, they probably would not choose to seal it too.

“How? Have you thought about it? If you are willing, I can step out and strengthen the seal, gaining you a hundred years’ time…”

After a few minutes, Leylin spoke indifferently.

“Then… please, Sir!” Nonov and Anye took a glance at each other and in the end still gritted their teeth and requested.

No matter what, if there was another hundred years’ time, be it discussing a countermeasure or directly retreating, there was more allowance for them.

“Okay! Pass down my command, seal this area, I want to set up a strengthening spell…”

After hearing them say that, Leylin nodded but instead sent away the two Magi who wanted to stay and help.

A Morning Star light screen enveloped the entire central hall with a buzz. Blue radiance was emitted in all directions, isolating it from the outside world.

“Ancient combined sealing spell…” The blue radiance in Leylin’s pupils flickered, many materials were casually taken out from the space equipment.

According to his original intentions, it was naturally to open the seal as soon as possible and gain the benefits. However, his current condition was not good, the Allsnake Curse was like a sharp sword hanging above his head, causing him to have to end things here as quickly as he could and head towards the Purgatory World to resolve the bloodline’s shackles.

Hence, postponing the disintegration of the seal for a period of time was also something that was in accordance to Leylin’s interests.

“Perhaps, there might be a need to move the Ouroboros Clan here in the future, grasping trade with the underground world…”

Leylin had already drawn out a blueprint regarding the development of the Ouroboros Clan in his mind. The expansion of the entire Ouroboros Clan in the central continent had already reached its limits. Even without the appearance of the Flame Monarch, it would meet the resistance of other Magi sooner or later.

Although the elemental particles environment in the south coast was not much, towards warlocks that relied mainly on bloodline force, the influence in this aspect was much smaller than Magi.

Moreover, the entire central continent had not yet connected to the underground world’s passageway, what was discovered occasionally, were just a few totally sealed miniature underground space like that of the Twilight Zone.

Once a passageway that connects to the entire underground world was developed, even simply controlling trade between the two places would bring about huge benefits, enough to allow the Ouroboros Clan to make a rapid development.

”The top priority now, is still to confirm if this connects to that ancient completed underground layer of the underground world or the miniature sealed area like that of the Twilight Zone…”

Leylin stroked his chin, there was even a radiance constantly flickering in his pupils, “If the place this links to is really that ancient underground layer, as long as we occupy here, the profits gained by the Ouroboros Clan would definitely not a little bit less than the Monarch of the Skies that has control over the entire central continent’s airship network…”

“A.I. Chip! Export spell formation layout!”

[Beep! Mission established, beginning coordination with supplementary assignment…]

The A.I. Chip’s sound was as mechanical as usual, without the slightest emotions in it.

A complicated yet detailed formation diagram was rapidly exported from the A.I. Chip’s database and was being projected by fluorescent light onto the hall’s floor.

The spell formation diagram illustrated by the fluorescent light combined with the original patterns on the floor harmoniously, forming a brand new formation.

[Beep! Separating black hole spell formation deduction setup completed, estimated rate of success 98.99%!]

The A.I. Chip sounded again.

“Very good!” A piece of mithril with black spots was melted into juice before Leylin, spreading out evenly onto the ground at the position where the fluorescent light had originally shone.

With Leylin’s current alchemy grand master’s academic achievements and the A.I. Chip’s fine and detailed assistance, the entire setting up of the spell formation proceeded very smoothly and was thoroughly completed in almost half an hour.

Only, when setting up, Leylin would certainly not do it according to Nonov and Anye’s requests, he included many of his own smuggled goods in it instead.

The entire spell formation continuously rumbled with a buzz, streaks of silver radiance rippled on the ground.

[Beep! Spell formation energy operating normally! Compatibility of connection 91.673%!]

Large amounts of data floated across Leylin’s eyes, he could not help but nod secretly, “It is a linking technique that is acquired after all, to have 90% compatibility is already not bad!”

“Then…” Leylin took in a deep breath. “A.I. Chip!”

[Open up the connection assignment, attempting to establish a spatial link, searching coordinates!]

Accompanying the A.I. Chip’s sound, the patterns on the ground suddenly changed, its circulating speed was continuously increasing. Faint silver light emerged, undulating in mid-air, even slowly forming into a state of a semicircular arched door.

Opposite the arched door, was a patch of thick darkness and a mirror-like radiance was constantly emitted.

This was the smuggled goods Leylin had added. At the same time while strengthening the seal, Leylin also left a way of escape for himself, and could even reach the other side of the space with the prerequisite of not damaging the original seal by directly going through the crack in the spell formation.

“You guys guard here, no matter who comes, kill them all!”

Leylin flicked his hands and four translucent void assassins emerged. He faintly ordered a few sentences and these four assassins immediately vanished into the void.

Possessing rank 3 limit strength and with the addition of this kind of ability to go through the void, void assassins were almost invincible existences in the south coast.

Four void assassins along with the spell formation outside that Leylin had set up, even if the dark and light Magi joined forces, they would definitely not be able to fight their way in.

Although Leylin was more reassured towards Nonov and Anye and he also knew that they did not have the guts, he would not entrust his hopes on their reverence towards him just like that.

Countless historical examples have all proven that this was something very foolish, Leylin would certainly not do that.

Chapter 686: Underground and Rescue

After preparing his backup plan, Leylin swished his robes and entered the arched door in mid-air. An icy membrane rippled as he passed through it. The moment he materialised, Leylin realised he’d stepped into another place.

A dark, frigid aura permeated the air, one that was specific to the subterranean world. The density of darkness and earth energy particles was even greater than in Twilight Zone.

“This is the other end of the spatial tunnel, huh?” Leylin swept his gaze across the surroundings. He was currently in a palace hall of sorts, where bizarrely styled sculptures were scattered around the vicinity.

Once the light in the spell formation subsided, a thick layer of dust could be observed in the area.

“Inextinguishable Flame!” Leylin pointed ahead and a bright and beautiful flame floated in front of him.

‘This place seems to have been deserted for a very long while. Is it the depths of an ancient ruin?’ Leylin scanned the surroundings with his soul force, before realising that the whole area seemed to be protected by a layer of mysterious energy. This mysterious energy even suppressed the soul force of a Magus.

However, given that his truesoul was at Half Moon, he could still cover a sizeable portion of the area. It wasn’t long before he discovered several passageways leading out.

‘I hope there aren’t any complex spell formations outside, this will become very troublesome.’ Leylin walked towards a large door, the unadorned yet aw-inspiring stone standing over ten metres tall. On the left of the doors was the sculpture of a devil, on the right that of a beautiful angel.

*Ka-cha!* *Ka-cha!*

Leylin stretched his hand forward as he pushed the door. Suddenly, two powerful streaks of lightning flashed and struck Leylin, but was repelled by Kemoyin Scales.

A pitch-black tunnel appeared in front of Leylin and without any hesitation, he stepped forward.

“I never expected that I would chance across some Magi on an expedition. This will save me loads of time!”

The corners of Leylin’s lips curled upwards as he blended in with the darkness, before moving at a speed that defied the logics of physics.

…..

On the other side, a group of adventurers were running for their lives, escaping from something in the tunnel.

“Quick! It’s catching up!”

This group of adventurers had a warrior adorning armour, an archer carrying a wooden bow, and the one that made up the most numbers were a group of Magi garbed in robes and carrying strange tools. This party composition was still rather decent. However, this small party now were scurrying away in fear from something behind them, their clothes torn and tattered. Traces of blood tainted their body, revealing profuse injuries.

*Dum dum! Dum dum!* Behind them, in the darkness, thuds of heavy footsteps were heard.

Upon hearing these noises, the people in the small party had their colour drained from their faces as they continued to flee at a faster speed.

*Crash!* A dark streak of light flashed, carrying a black long spear. It immediately penetrated the innate spell defense of one of the Magi, pinning him to the floor.

“Xander! Damn it!” The leader, a brown haired youth, turned back and saw his companion pinned to the ground with blood streaming out of his mouth. However, he gritted his teeth and continued fleeing.

“Run! Hurry and run!” His eyes turned bloodshot as he screamed at the top of his lungs.

At the same time, a blazing flame of unwillingness and regret gnawed at his soul bit by bit. “We were too careless! With our combined strength of three stars ranking, this vestige is way out of our league! Damn it! The danger level here is at least five stars! As long as I manage to make it out, I will definitely slay that damned asshole!”

“No! Xander! The female archer slinging the bow on her back halted immediately as she knelt beside the Magus pinned to the ground. She then took out a green vial of potion and poured it on his wounds.

“It’s no use!” The leader roared, but he never stopped running.

Tens of seconds later, that blood curdling scream of his female party member sounded. The leader’s face turned even more pale as he sped up.

*Dum dum! Dum dum!*

The footsteps sounded behind him, like that of a death god who had come to reap their souls. Although the footsteps were slow, the speed was extremely fast. Not long later, the youth heard several more wretched cries behind him.

It was only until now that he realised, to his astonishment, that not one of his companions had remained.

“No! I can’t die here! I have to be a five stars adventure and even the crowned King Adventurer! I have goals yet to be fulfilled, and to return the glory of my family, the revenge, and also my…”

Another beam of black light shot towards him and stopped his train of thoughts. Although the youth had attempted to maneuver out of the way, he was still grazed by that black light, causing him fall to the ground and cough out a pool of blood.

*Dum dum! Dum dum!* Along with the footsteps, a giant figure emerged from the darkness.

It was a giant that stood tall at over three metres, with two long shafts of spears slung on its back. Complex runes covered his body, giving off a metallic lustre.

There was a grim expression on its face, as if it belonged to a dead creature. Only two scarlet rays of light were projected from its pupils.

“It’s… It’s here….” The youth teeth clattered. This undead creature that stood in front of him was a defense mechanism of the vestige. Previously, when the group had broken through a tomb like room, it had started to chase them.

The undead giant had a powerful physical attack, with a high resistance to magic spells. It led the youth to despair; he could only watch on as his party members perished one by one under the hands of this giant. Ultimately, he was the only one left standing.

*Dum dum! Dum dum!* The giant walked over as he unsheathed one of the spears on his back.

“No! I don’t want to…. Please…” Tears poured from the youth’s eyes as he start to turn deranged.

*Whoosh!” The spear thrusted forward, but funnily enough, it remained hoisted in midair. The anticipated pain did not come, which caused the youth to reopen his eyes.

He saw a black shield protecting him at the front, engaging in a deadlock with the spear.

“I’m…I’m saved!” The youth collapsed weakly and laid on the ground, with tears of joy flowing from his eyes.

“Ahoooo!” The giant withdrew his spear and turned his body to the back, howling towards the darkness. Very soon, he staggered half a step backwards, as if some sort of ferocious predator was in front of it.

“Interesting!” ‘Although it seems to be a body made of flesh and blood, there seemed to be some modifications added to it. It’s rather akin to a metallic bodied demon right now huh? Even it consciousness was wiped out, with the only defense mechanism within it remaining…”

Leylin stepped forward from the shadows, blue light shining from his eyes as he scanned the giant in front of it.

“Moreover… These runes on the body, it seemed really similar to that of Branded Swordsmen…”

Leylin always held onto part of the Branded Swordsman’s inheritance, but it was extremely lacking of information. Even after the simulation and conjecture from the A.I. Chip, it could only reached the strength of a rank 1 Magus, which was not of much use.

Right now, after the A.I. Chip had upgraded several times and even added troves of information from the Great Library, it could raise the power of Branded Swordsman from rank 1 to 3. However, for Leylin who had the backing of the Ouroboros Clan and the Warlock Alliance, these Branded Swordsman were relatively useless to him. Hence, Leylin did not mass produce these Branded Swordsman cannon fodder.

However, at this moment, Leylin could clearly see the runes of Branded Swordsman on this giant.

Although the the style is slightly different, with modifications made on top of the original school of thought, this is no doubt the runes of Branded Swordsmen.

Just from looking at the runes and the energy that it radiated had gave Leylin many fresh ideas and inspiration about the Branded Swordsman.

Perhaps, after combining the knowledge found on the continent and in the subterranean world, the A.I. Chip might be able to produce runes which can create Morning Star Branded Swordsman.

“Arghhhhh!” Although the giant has discovered how powerful Leylin was, the defense mechanism inside its consciousness still made it reach out his hands.

Two black spears soared towards Leylin like two dragons.

*Peng!* *Pa!* A layer of black scales emerged from Leylin’s palms. As astonishing scene was created accompanied by sparks and screeching sounds.

The two black spears that the giant hurled had been caught firmly in Leylin’s palms.

“Hmm! The explosive power isn’t bad, with the strength at 50 degrees of so. It is rather similar to a rank 3 Magus attack!” Leylin nodded his head, but the youth at the side had his eyes bulging out.

During the escape earlier, he had seen many of his companions perish under the mighty black spear. Even magic defense spells proved to be no defense against it.

However, Leylin had managed to catch it in his hands.

“This Magus, is he a monster too?” The youth looked at Leylin’s appearance, garbed in luxurious black robes with a mask. Leylin gave off a regal yet mysterious aura, yet he did not seem to be a savage or tyrant.

“Groarrr!” The giant was stupefied momentarily before giving off a huge roar.

The sound waves involuntarily forced the youth to cover his ears. At the same time, black energy particles which could be seen by the naked eye surged towards the giant like water to a sponge, as the runes on the giant’s body began to flicker.

“Groarrrrr!’ With the howling noises made, a spell began to surface. The image of a dark creature’s head appeared, baring its razor sharp fangs as it was sent flying towards Leylin.

“Rank 3 spell — Darkness Crunch?” This spell seemed to be missing on the continent for thousands of years. Only the Great Library in Sky City had mentioned of this before.

Leylin rubbed his chin. A lost and forgotten spell need not necessarily meant that it was powerful. It could be due to not keeping up with the times and entered natural selection. He would definitely not make the assumption that anything ancient is powerful.

The blue light in Leylin’s eyes flashed and the A.I. Chip made its calculations.

Seconds later, the principle of this rank 3 spellcasting and even the spell model had been conjectured by the A.I. Chip.

“So this is how it works! Although this spell isn’t too bad, but it requires a huge amount of darkness elemental energy particles. No wonder the central continent had phased this spell out!”

Chapter 687: Arthur Empire

With the A.I. Chip’s deductions, Leylin instantly obtained the spell’s model, and learnt all of its weaknesses.

‘The darkness elemental particles just aren’t concentrated enough in the central continent. Perhaps it can only be used in a paradise for dark Magi like the subterranean world.’

“Fight darkness with light!” A holy white radiance was formed at Leylin’s fingertip. While he was a dark Magus himself, it wasn’t like he couldn’t use any life or light element spells.

In reality, with enough spiritual force and access to spell models, Magi could employ spells of any type. However, there was a difference due to vitality and elemental affinity. Leylin might be extremely proficient with darkness spells, even having an added bonus to their power, but he would find it difficult to use light and life element spells, and the power could even be diminished.

Now, for instance, the light-type spell that Leylin was casting consumed a lot of energy to produce a spell half as strong as one by a regular Magus. He’d long since solidified darkness elemental particles, something that only made it harder for him to use light spells.

However, with Leylin’s current strength, even a small portion of his power would cause the spell to be a bane to all darkness.

Leylin seemed to move exceedingly slowly, but somehow arrived above the monster before it could do anything. The light-tipped finger tapped the centre of the monster’s skull.

“Awoo!” A bit of light shone above the monster’s head, before it began to flicker and become more dazzling.

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!* Like the sound of glass breaking, many cracks appeared on its head and it then exploded, melting into nothingness amidst the white light.

“Mm! Light-type spells can still restrain darkness-type spells, but that also depends on the strength of both parties.”

Leylin had his own understanding of the relationship between elements. If darkness elemental particles were to be likened to fire, then light-type energy particles would be like water.

While a ladle of water could extinguish sparks, it could do nothing against a sea of fire.

On the other hand, if the fire was intense enough, a few droplets of rainwater would be evaporated.

“Awoo…” After the monster head was easily smashed by Leylin, the black giant took several steps back. In its dull, mechanical eyes, traces of terror could be seen.

He let out a few meaningless howls and made to escape.

But how could Leylin let go of such a great guinea pig?

“Stay here!” Along with Leylin’s slight smile, a few black shackles appeared in mid-air and bound him tightly. No matter how the giant kept snarling, there was nothing he could do against these chains.

Soon after, his figure shrunk in size till it entered a crystal ball in Leylin’s hands, like a bug that was frozen in amber.

“Mm! The hoarding spell works, which means he isn’t some living being but a magic being without a soul!”

While it was just a short period of time exchanging blows with him, Leylin now had an understanding of the composition of the giant.

He had evidently gone through the refining of a Branded Swordsman and had even reached a very high level. His body had already gone through elemental modification and become crystallised and somewhat translucent.

This material was the best to make magic beings. After elemental modification, flesh not only retained its original defensive and offensive abilities, it could use spells without obstructions.

In just a short period of time, this was all Leylin could tell. For things on a deeper level, he would need to do more experiments and dissection.

“This… lord, thank you for… your help!”

At this moment, Leylin noticed the young adventurer collapsed on the ground at the side. He was evidently a Magus, though he had a very low rank. This was all the strength he had, and yet had come to explore. He was rather lucky not to die from the mechanisms or curses.

“Hm? This language?” His thanks meant nothing to Leylin, but the language he spoke in delighted Leylin.

“It’s very similar to the Twilight Language, though there are minute differences in pronunciation. There’s no need to learn a new language!”

Leylin was surprised, but then found this reasonable. Twilight Zone was a part of the subterranean world, and was only isolated because of the battle between two Morning Stars. Before that happened, they must have been using the same language and writing as the subterranean world.

“Mm. What’s your name?” Since the issue with language was solved, Leylin had no desire to search his soul.

The information he needed was too high-levelled, and someone with such a tiny role would not know much.

With Leylin’s Dreamscape force field, he was confident he could make this person reveal basic information on the culture and geography unwittingly.

“My– My name is Jo– Jorgian!” The young Magus was silent for a while and then stated his name.

“Your name is very unique!” Leylin commented. It wasn’t unexpected for the social customs of the underground world to be different from Magi on the surface.

“By the way, where is this… What’s the world outside like?”

Leylin asked without holding back. A hazy force field was produced from his body. This was the ability he had gained after undergoing dreamscape modification, and he possessed powerful illusory strength.

Ever since he had gotten this, Leylin would not search souls or any similar methods unless it was truly necessary.

A Magus who played around with souls would not have a good name in the Magus World. When unnecessary, Leylin still wished to maintain his reputation.

A good reputation was still a benefit. If used well, he might even obtain unexpected rewards.

“This is the Thunderbird region, and rumoured to be the holyland of the Lyas family…” After Leylin’s words, Jorgian first looked daze, eyes losing focus, before he began to disclose everything unwittingly.

The more he heard, the more Leylin looked solemn.

“Poor little guy! He’s been enticed into adventuring into someone else’s restricted area…” After he’d listened to everything, Leylin watched Jorgian, eyes full of pity.

‘This little guy has definitely fallen into some huge conspiracy…’

However, this was none of his business. He’d found out that this was the territory of the Arthur Empire underground, and this was a massive empire. There were large numbers of other races outside, and had a surface area countless times larger than Twilight Zone.

In the Arthur Empire, there had never been a lack of Morning Star ranks. There were even rumours of Radiant Moon Magi.

Such good news allowed Leylin to confirm that there was a huge possibility of this place being the complete first layer of the underground.

“Hm?” After Leylin got all the intel he wanted, Jorgian immediately looked alert, and then turned sorrowful, “My apologies… at the thought of my companions, I became absent-minded…”

In his memories, Leylin had only asked why he had come to these ruins. He, who thought back to his comrades, was lost in thought.

A sad feeling rose in his heart, and he did not suspect any changes to his memories.

When it came to manipulating memories, Leylin was at the level of a grandmaster. This little Magus had had his memories altered and yet not discovered it at all.

As long as Leylin wanted to, he could work out a brand new set of memories from childhood to adulthood for any Magus below Morning Star without the other party noticing.

This was obviously something normal Radiant Moons or even Breaking Dawn Monarchs could do, but with the A.I. Chip’s abilities to simulate reality, it just took more time and effort on Leylin’s end.

“Alright, Mister Jorgian! I understand all you’ve gone through. Forgive me for my bluntness, but this is a place you really shouldn’t be in. It’s better for you to leave with me!”

Leylin took several steps forward. In exchange for the intel he had been given, he didn’t mind saving the boy on the way and send him out of the ruins.

“Mm, thank you so much, my lord!” Jorgian’s eyes were full of gratitude as he followed closely behind Leylin, as if afraid he would be left behind.

After all the dangers today, he knew very well that if Leylin did not bring him along, he would be trapped in the ruins sooner or later and die by the hands of the mechanisms.

……

*Hualala!* Numerous pitch-black lightning formed a cage with all types of beasts roaring.

A black dot the size of sesame constantly grew in size amidst the lightning and eventually turned into two figures, dashing out while braving the lightning.

“Alright, we’re out!”

Leylin shook his robes and put Jorgian, who was in his arms, down.

“We’re… out?” He still looked dazed. He had never known how dangerous the ruins were. Things had been smooth-sailing when he had entered, but while exiting, they had met with many dangers, especially the lightning jail at the exit. He’d remembered that when he had first arrived, there was no such spell pattern sealed here.

Seeing this, he was extremely relieved. If not for Leylin, he would probably die in the ruins even if he had nine lives.

Jorgian couldn’t help but look at the black structures behind him. The ruins were now like a monster with its mouth wide open, swallowing the lives of all adventurers.

“My lord, do you think… we should… leave now?”

Jorgian asked carefully. He’d grown to understand Leylin’s terrifying abilities after following him around.

“That’s not possible now.”

Leylin shook his head.

“Why?” Jorgian could not understand, and his expression quickly changed.

A few streaks of blue figures appeared around them at some point, surrounding them.

Chapter 696: Breakthrough and Success

“I will first use the Destiny Spell Formation to amplify the power of Destiny’s Coin, and then draw out the power of fate from the coin all at once. I had previously narrowed down the location of the Purgatory World in the vast astral realm to the Calm Jade constellation already……”

“Staking everything on the destruction of Destiny’s Coin, the attempt this time– It has a 70% chance of success!”

A blazing light shone from Leylin’s eyes, and he held up his hands: “The power of destiny! Please guide my way and lead me to the Purgatory World!”

Bang!

At the moment of Leylin’s chant, the radiance of Destiny’s Coin was at its highest point. The entire laboratory was wrapped up in the dazzling dark golden light.

The power of destiny reached its peak at this moment. At this moment, all of the astrologers in the entire Magus World raised their heads in amazement, sensing that the undulations of the river of destiny was shifting.

Threads of dark golden light continuously touched the door to the Star Realm, the image of the Calm Jade constellation grew ever smaller on the surface of the silver mirror, moving slowly towards the location of the Purgatory World.

Ka-cha! Ka-cha!

The Purgatory World, however, was the world where the laws of the Snake Dowager existed. Even though it had merely calculated the coordinates, fine cracks constantly appeared on the surface of Destiny’s Coin.

[Warning! Warning! Destiny’s Coin is rapidly destroying itself! Countdown: 1.1s! 1.0s! 0.9!]

The A.I Chip quickly produced a blood red countdown frame.

At this time, although he was continuously drawing closer to his goal, the Purgatory World had not yet appeared.

“Ah…… It’s not enough! It’s still not enough!” Leylin’s face flushed red and he suddenly commanded: “A.I. Chip! Commence the overload of the Destiny Spell Formation!”

[Beep! Further amplifying the Destiny Spell Formation, currently overloading at 200%! 300! 400!]

Along with the A.I. Chip’s voice, the energy stack around the Destiny Spell Formation immediately let out an ear-piercing explosion. The terrifying power of amplification emerged once again.

Crackle! A vast amount of energy unceasingly flowed about in all directions. Many runes even exploded, and the entire Destiny Spell Formation collapsed in a flash.

Just before the spell formation collapsed, the frightening power of amplification had appeared on the surface of Destiny’s Coin.

Bang! First, the skull which represented misfortune on one side of the coin exploded. Shortly after, the destiny bird seemed to come alive, unfolding its wings and letting out a resounding cry.

Destiny’s Coin suddenly exploded into fragments.

At this time, a ray of dark golden light slashed open the display of the Calm Jade constellation as if it was a sharp sword. This caused the Astral Gate to show the edge of a dull-colored star on its surface.

[Beep! The Destiny Spell Formation and Destiny’s Coin have been destroyed! Discovered the Purgatory World’s coordinates!]

The A.I. Chip’s voice sounded out and made a cheerful expression appear on Leylin’s face.

“Success! The wish of all Kemoyin Warlocks! There is even a method to resolve the bloodline shackles!” Leylin resolutely clenched his fist.

[Beep! The Purgatory World’s coordinates have been targeted. Initiating the opening of the space portal!]

Accompanying the sound of the A.I. Chip, a blue gate of light opened up before Leylin with a loud rumble.

A frightening feeling was transmitted from the gate, giving Leylin a sense of formidable oppression.

The Purgatory World! It was a very formidable world in ancient times. Until now, it had never declined, and it even contained the violent existence of the Snake Dowager and other powerful laws.

“Taking this step, there is no possibility of turning back!” Leylin smiled softly, and stepped entirely into the radiant light.

Bang! The blue rays of light exploded with a flash, wrapping up the entire laboratory and bringing it along.

……

A blue ray of light, like a meteor, streaked across the vast Star Realm.

In this blue light was Leylin, looking at the dull star which was growing larger and larger in his field of view. It finally transformed into an enormous world.

This world was shrouded entirely in a dense grey fog, and he couldn’t see clearly. He could only see pieces of the continents and the ocean with great difficulty.

Any of these continents could be comparable to the size of the central continent of the Magus World. The faint atmosphere of great power was emanated, making Leylin shiver a little.

Rapidly, the power of the Astral Gate brought him to the border of the Purgatory World, which was outside of the world boundary.

However, when Leylin wanted to enter the Purgatory World, there was a sudden change!

“Who is it? Where has this outsider come from, who dares to offend my majesty!” A frightening amount of energy undulated outside the Purgatory World and took shape. An enormous shadow appeared, and even the storms and turbulences of space all avoided it.

There was a strong and overbearing atmosphere. The power of laws constantly undulated from the shadow’s body.

This shadow possessed very large and deformed wings, its entire body was as huge as a mountain. A giant skeletal hand reached out towards Leylin and grabbed him, as if it was a giant snatching a fly.

“There are Rank 7 and above laws here! Damn it! There are obviously many strong people, but they are unexpectedly vigilant against outsiders?”

Leylin’s expression changed, and soon after the golden-red patterns on the Dreamless Mask continuously flashed with light. The bloodline of the Alabaster Devilsnake from earlier was released.

“En! This is the bloodline of the Alabaster Devilsnake! Although it was once the master of the Shadow World, now it is part of our Purgatory World!”

Accompanied by the voice of another woman, an enormous eye with vertically slit pupils appeared.

A profound intent was issued from the giant eye above. Soon after, a great amount of black lightning engulfed the giant eye, and struck the enormous hand which had grabbed Leylin.

“Apologies! Complying with the contract is the foundation of order! In accordance with the contract we had previously signed together! The bloodline of the Snake Dowager has the right to enter the Purgatory World!”

Within the mass of black lightning, the enormous skeletal hand shattered to pieces, which made the shadow let out an infuriated roar in response, “Damn you, Trial’s Eye! I won’t let you off, one day…… One day……”

“Chirp chirp……”

Just when Leylin had let out a sigh of relief, accompanied by a cheerful chirp, an enormous grey bird flew emerged from the Purgatory World.

“All who belong to the Trial of the Contract, are the enemies of this bird!”

The giant wings of the bird seemed the shield the whole world from Leylin’s view.

“Sss……” At this moment, an even more violent thought was projected over, making Leylin feel that he was surrounded by a pack of wolves.

The phantom of a ball of snakes as large as a star was forced out from the void.

Many giant snakes roared directly towards Leylin. An indistinct figure appeared from within the coiled snakes. With one look, Leylin’s bloodline nearly rose in rebellion.

‘Snake Dowager! Although it is only a phantom…’ Leylin’s pupils constricted.

“Oh? It looks like this descendent appears to be quite interesting. Even the Snake Dowager is in a hurry to get her hands on him?” The bird bantered ridiculously, as if it was a person.

“In that case……” It fanned its huge grey wings and the obstacles in front of Leylin disappeared. A terrifyingly powerful space storm followed this, which rapidly increased its speed. In a moment, it had crashed through the world boundary.

“Bird! You dare! ! !” A rather angry voice came from behind Leylin’s back, along with the monstrous hissing of the gigantic snake.

It seemed as if many stars behind him had all exploded, and all of the terrifying energy contained within made the whole space begin to faintly tremble. The gigantic Purgatory World silently endured the aftermath, showing off the foundation of a truly powerful world.

“The beings that appeared earlier should only be merely conscients and clones, and unexpectedly they were this terrifying!”

There was a trace of bitterness in the corner of Leylin’s mouth, and also the sense of being very fortunate.

The process of crossing the world boundary was viewed by the unusually sensitive Rank 7 existences in the Purgatory World as if bandits had conspicuously trespassed into their own home. It was impossible to not be discovered.

Fortunately, although the Rank 7 laws overseeing the Purgatory World were not little, they seemed to be full of contradictions with each other, which finally gave Leylin a precious chance to take advantage of them.

“Descendent of my blood! Return to my embrace!”

At this moment an enormous will swept across Leylin, and made his mind tremble.

“Entering the Purgatory World and smoothly blending in, was instead easy to handle. The stone outside is very dazzling, but if I fell into the river above, to resolve it again, it would not be such an easy matter! And……”

Forcibly suppressing the rebellion of his bloodline, a puppet suddenly appeared from Leylin’s hands.

“Haha……” The puppet laughed sweetly, and it continuously undulated a Soul Force and bloodline power which was extremely similar to Leylin’s.

“Go!” With Leylin’s voice the puppet clone floated in midair, and moving to and fro like a meteor, took a different direction from Leylin.

“I hope that the puppet will win me enough time! And also!”

[Beep! The Dreamless Mask is activating, concealing the bloodline for the second time!]

Accompanying the A.I. Chip’s voice, was a layer of fine white snake scales, suddenly appearing from the surface of the Dreamless Mask. Mixing with the bloodline aura from earlier, the undulations exclusive to the Alabaster Devilsnake concealed Leylin’s Soul Force and bloodline power in a flash.

“In the Purgatory World, the clan of snakes that the Snake Dowager is in is also an enormous species. Even the other side surely cannot thoroughly distinguish between every Alabaster Devilsnake?”

[Beep! Collecting the laws of the Purgatory World! Initiating adjustment of host undulations!]

With the A.I. Chip’s voice, many laws of the Purgatory World were collected to be analyzed, and slowly altered the undulations coming from Leylin.

Very quickly, Leylin’s entire self resembled the natives of the Purgatory World, and no longer had the incompatible feeling of an outsider from another world.

“Everything has been completed!”

Leylin breathed a sigh of relief, his face shortly flushing red.

The confrontation of the different laws just a moment ago had left him with a not inconsiderable injury.

“All that could be done has been done, and next, it depends on luck!”

Leylin was just like a fallen meteorite, and now, the enormous wills following on his heels had completely lost his presence.

Chapter 697: Drifting and Analysis

A flaming star shot down from the skies, smashing into the waters with a huge splash.

“Ugh!” The icy cold water immediately left Leylin clear-minded, and a salty taste attacked his senses.

‘This is… an ocean…’ His mind was quickly reinvigorated, ‘Those existences above rank 6 saw me, but I was lucky enough to get through the barrier into the world. I even had to let my substitute clone leave… In that case…’

“This is the Purgatory World!” Seeing the dark lustre in the horizon as well as the chaotic will unique to Purgatory, Leylin’s lips quirked up in a broadening smile. “Haha… I’ve succeeded!”

Leylin had finally taken the first step on his path to breaking the bloodline shackles. The elation in his expression grew more and more pronounced.

As a foreign entity, Leylin would obviously affect the world barrier while traversing into the Purgatory World. Those existences above rank 6 had sensed this, hence Leylin wasn’t surprised that so many conscients were present there, even making some preparations.

However, the events had far exceeded his expectations. Not only were their more beings in the Purgatory World than he’d expected that comprehended laws, they weren’t all in the same camp. He’d even noticed a few familiar faces.

“It’s not just the Snake Dowager, but the Trial’s Eye and the Nefarious Filthbird are here too? I wonder if it’s their main body here, or just a clone…”

Leylin floated on the surface of the sea and was pushed along with the waves. With the checks by the A.I. Chip, his injuries were slowly recovering and he would soon regain his ability to move.

Floating on the ocean was very dangerous and could attract bloodthirsty sharks or other high-energy beings. However, Leylin had no aura undulations at all and was like a block of wood. He wasn’t bothered by anything at all.

While recovering, his thoughts were still moving quickly.

“Trial’s Eye and the Nefarious Filthbird. They’re a group of old mortal enemies, and I never thought I’d see their true bodies… Even if they’re clones, they probably possess about half the strength of their main bodies!”

The ancient Trial’s Eye was commonly used by Magi to make contracts. As an arbitrator and protector, it spread its might across multiple worlds.

This extended to even Breaking Dawn Monarchs and all the way down to acolytes. While making contracts, Trial’s Eye could be summoned to bear witness. Of course, the Trial’s Eye that different Magi summoned were fundamentally different.

However, in Leylin’s point of view, Trial’s Eye was not doing all of this for nothing. Through safeguarding these contracts and judging those who violated them, it did gain immense benefits too.

The laws it comprehended could very possibly be ‘Contract’ and ‘Trial’ or something to that effect. Hence, through these activities, it not only amassed more comprehension towards the rules but could even obtain the attention of the world origin force to increase its strength.

On the contrary, the Nefarious Filthbird likely comprehended something like ‘Betrayal’ and ‘Chaos’. Hence, the two of them became arch enemies and engaged in battles that spanned across several worlds.

Now, Leylin had found the projections of their conscients in Purgatory World!

This meant that a very capable clone or even real body of these two beings were now in Purgatory World!

“What kind of secrets were being kept in the ancient Purgatory World? It’s not just the Snake Dowager but also Trial’s Eye and the Nefarious Filthbird, amongst other beings, that have set their sights on this place…”

Leylin pondered silently over the effects the appearance of the Trial’s Eye and Nefarious Filthbird would bring to his plans, and whether they would be able to help him.

“Based on what I saw, the Trial’s Eye seems to be a protector of laws, which was why it helped me out and let me off leniently after seeing I was a descendant of the Snake Dowager. The Nefarious Filthbird was clearly opposed to the eye and, after seeing that the Snake Dowager had not protected me and even wanted to kill me quickly, changed its initial plans and sent me into Purgatory World…”

Leylin’s eyes flickered with wit as he analysed the scene multiple times.

“If I really had to divide them, Trial’s Eye is probably on the Snake Dowager’s side. Of course, I can’t rule out the fact that it was just following the contract. The Nefarious Filthbird obviously thinks nothing of the Snake Dowager. There’s hatred on both ends… As for that strange beast with destroyed wings that appeared at the beginning, it’s probably sitting on the fence…”

“Of course, this could be misleading. However, these beings are very arrogant. It’s too unlikely that they’d team up to cheat a mere rank 5 Warlock like me, and the possibility is almost negligible… but it’s not bad to be on my guard against it…”

Leylin felt himself getting a headache. Having to deduce so many secrets regarding these beings as a mortal human himself made him feel like his brain just wasn’t doing enough.

“A.I. Chip, how’s the analysis of the surroundings and world law?”

Leylin shut his eyes and let his body drift along the waves and communicated with the A.I. Chip inwardly.

[Beep! Scanning of surroundings completed. Constructing elemental diagram!]

The A.I. Chip quickly projected the image of an elemental composition diagram.

“Mm! The water elemental particles are very dense, which is understandable since this is like an ocean. On top of that, there’s darkness and fire-type elemental particles. As expected of Purgatory!”

Leylin read through the analysis of the surroundings and couldn’t help but nod. The concentration of elements around was slightly lacking compared to the central continent, but they were almost on the same level. That really made it worthy of being called an ancient powerful world.

[Beep! Deduction of host’s location complete!]

The A.I. Chip projected a map in front of Leylin. This was a scene of Purgatory World that he had seen from outside the barrier. Within was a hazy continent and gigantic ocean, and on the image, Leylin was situated near to a continent in the ocean. He was represented as a dazzling red dot!

“Though I know my approximate location in Purgatory World, I don’t know which continent to go to…”

Leylin laughed wryly. The map the A.I. Chip had used was everything he had seen before, and it was much too simple. Considering the startling area of Purgatory World, any mistakes here would reach a terrifying extent.

“A.I. Chip, check my stats!” Not bothering with these longer, Leylin commanded again.

[Beep! Mission established, beginning scan. Collecting host’s stats.]

The A.I. Chip quickly intoned the results.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 5 Warlock. Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent (Complete form). Strength: 32 (76), Agility: 35 (62), Vitality: 59 (176.9), Spiritual force: 875 (2003.5), Magic power: 875 (Magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force). Soul force: 88 (200), Half Moon.]

Though it was just a confrontation between a few tremendous conscients, Leylin had been caught in the cross fire and almost died.

The terror of rank 7s and above were something he couldn’t stand up to as he was now.

“Due to the Curse Mark of Ten Thousand Snakes, my stats keep dropping! On top of that, I’m grievously injured. If I still had my vitality from before, I’d probably be able to recover in a few hours. It looks like I’ll need around two days…”

Leylin observed the beautiful starry sky and sighed slowly.

Meanwhile, he could feel that his body was like a sponge, with the darkness-type elemental particles in the air and even moonlight being absorbed into his cells, restoring his life force.

“This… Kemoyin Serpent’s devouring ability, or a natural occurrence in the Purgatory World?” Whatever it was, Leylin was rather stunned at this discovery. Purgatory World truly was most suitable for the Snake Dowager and her clansmen. If not for that damned Purgatory chaotic intent that resulted in a bloodline illness, it could even be comparable to the Shadow World before.

[Beep! World law analysis at 2.16%. Determined to be not letting foreign creatures and souls have too drastic reactions.]

At this moment, the A.I. Chip’s newly investigated conclusion was placed in front of him.

“In other words, the Purgatory World has nothing against the entrance of the powerful? It’s no wonder the Snake Dowager, Trial’s Eye and the rest chose to come here!”

Leylin suddenly understood.

Most worlds’ latent wills were very opposed to foreigners. All those who entered would feel a terrifying malicious intent. Even their bodies would be suppressed by the World Force and cause them to drop in rank.

A situation like that would be very obvious in the Magus World or World of Gods.

However, Purgatory World seemed rather exotic as well. It accepted all foreigners and its degree of openness was second only to the Dreamscape. When he had just entered, Leylin had not felt any pressure whatsoever from the World Will.

After he completely adjusted the frequency of his aura and soul undulations to the Purgatory World, he was more like a native. There was no longer the feeling of being pressured and spied on by some malicious intent.

“What a mystical world! However, the will of Purgatory World was initially already very chaotic. That’s normal!”

Leylin nodded. For World Wills, all from outside were locusts that would even take over their precious origin source. Hence, they were very against this. Some Worlds even had their natives in chains, and then expelled them after their strength went past a certain level.

Only Purgatory World with chaotic intent like this could tolerate the existence of foreigners like the Snake Dowager.

“Even then, perhaps the Snake Dowager wouldn’t brazenly absorb the world origin. If not, no matter how chaotic the will of the Purgatory World is, there would be a powerful opposing force. That might be my chance…”

Chapter 699: Beholders

“An Exemplary!” The leader of the merfolk cried out involuntarily, his eyes now holding a trace of reverence towards Leylin. However, he wasn’t all that surprised either. From what Leylin had done, it was evident that he was no ordinary person.

“We are people from the Eden trading company. If you don’t mind, you could come up our ship and get some rest. I believe the rest will be delighted to chat with an Exemplary…” The leader of the merfolk spoke reverently.

This was the reason Leylin showed his strength. In a primitive world in an era during the age of discovery, there must be sins everywhere behind the scenes. The law of the jungle was utilised to the utmost.

If this was just Leylin alone without any power, he would be robbed and then thrown to the bottom of the sea.

Just the luxurious material of his clothing could be the cause of his death.

The moment he showed his mysterious strength, the treatment he got immediately changed.

Without making certain Leylin’s strength and his background, the Eden trading company would not dare lay a hand on him.

“Many thanks!” Leylin expressed his gratitude aloofly, refusing the drawbridge that they let down for him and instead flying onto the deck.

Standing on deck, Leylin was slightly surprised by these crew members’ strange appearances.

The few sailors beside him all looked very strange. There were some similar to the merfolk that Leylin had seen, but their tails had turned into two legs. They wore what labourers did and clearly did not have a high status here.

Besides the merfolk sailors, Leylin saw another type of creature.

This was a person escorted by the merfolk that evidently had a higher status. However, their appearance was totally different from a regular human being and they only had a large pupil. The pupil alone had a diameter of 1 decimeter, and around its socket, large amounts of tendrils hung down, forming something like limbs.

Appearance-wise, it was very similar to the Beholder Leylin saw in games in his previous world.

“Alright! Though I’d long since guessed that this world wouldn’t be made up of humans, this appearance is really quite rare…”

Leylin ridiculed it in his mind. Perhaps due to adapting to the environment or some other reason, there were multiple different tribes but they all had bodies similar to humans. A head, four limbs, a torso became the most common structure of all beings, and there were at least one or two races similar to humans.

Like the merfolk he’d seen, while they maintained having a tail on their lower bodies when in water, that instantly turned into humans’ legs once they got on shore.

Creatures that were completely different from humans like the Beholder did exist, but were never that common.

Leylin had already named this being the ‘Beholder tribe’. In Purgatory World, it was unexpectedly this sort of race that was in charge and enslaving those similar to the human race.

“Revered Exemplary, please accept the sublime respect of I, Geiger Guguno Axde.”

One of the Beholder’s tendrils went upwards, and Leylin suddenly received spiritual undulations. The greetings within seemed to be rather flattering.

“Greetings!” Leylin obviously had a more profound understanding of the usage of spiritual force, which was why his usage of it was effortless.

However, what he found strange was that this Beholder tribe used spiritual force, which was similar to brainwaves, to communicate.

“Perhaps this form is because they’re highly intelligent creatures!” Leylin nodded inside.

“You must be someone of the Ceraph Continent, yes? It is only at that area that there are humans!”

The gigantic Beholder pupil stared hard at Leylin, and he could even see an inverted image of himself in the eye. After a short moment the Beholder sent spiritual force that held information.

“My apologies, but I must keep my origins a secret. I promised my Mentor that before I gained any fame, I would not reveal my history!” Leylin answered righteously, but that only made the other party more grim and respectful.

“Your mentor must be an amazing Exemplary!” To become famous far and wide was extremely difficult even if on just one continent. To be able to do that meant he must be an extraordinarily powerful Exemplary.

“Mm! He is indeed an elder worthy of respect, full of wisdom and resolution…”

A hint of nostalgia rose in Leylin’s eyes, and he then asked Beholder, “I met with some troubles at sea and had to float on the surface for a long time. May I know where this is?”

“Oh, this is the end of the shipping route of the Hail Continent, which makes it very close to the Hail Continent. You came so close but still got into troubles, and I can only say that you and your boat have very bad luck…”

The Beholder seemed to say without malicious intent. Noticing the slip of its tongue, many tendrils waved around, flustered, “Oh, my apologies! I didn’t say that on purpose. It’s just that there are far too many storms and ferocious beasts in the ocean, and because there’s no law or regulations, even the Golden Deity Fleet can’t say they’re safe until they reach the port and stand on land.”

“I understand,” Leylin waved his arms, but a hint of of sadness and lingering fear showed on his expression. “I’m quite tired. Would it be possible for me to have a room and get some rest? Also, please send me to the nearest port. I’m willing to pay for it with something of equal value…”

While speaking, Leylin astutely realised there was someone spying on him from the shadows. This should be the Exemplary that he had discovered previously.

Their strength was not half bad and seemed to be at peak rank 3. They also had a few powerful magic artifacts and unique magic items.

“Seems like this is the protector or owner of this fleet who’s at rank 3?”

With the A.I. Chip’s adjustments, his aura was also at around rank 3. With his Mask of the Dreamless, he was rather charming.

“This…” Beholder seemed to hesitate, but immediately after, a streak of concealed spiritual force undulations was transmitted that caused it to change its words.

“No problem! We were planning to make a stop at the nearby Elias Port, and you can get off there. On our ship you are our most esteemed guest, so please don’t mention anything about paying…”

Beholder’s eye squinted which seemed to be a way of expressing its respect…?

“Alright!” Leylin nodded, and under the guidance of a merperson that the Beholder called out, entered the hold of the ship.

“My lord, here is your room. If there’s anything you need, please tell us!”

The merperson humbly lowered his head, and once Leylin got familiar with his room, retreated.

“It’s not bad!” Leylin looked around his surroundings. This was the higher levels of the ship, and besides important personnel, perhaps even the leader of the merfolk did not have the authority to stay here.

Light blue shells and red coral decorations adorned the room, making it look beautiful.

Inside, there was something like a bed that was covered with the fur of some unknown being. Just by looking at it, it was obvious that it was soft and smooth.

What attracted Leylin’s attention more, however, was the large blue pearl at the heart of the room.

In the A.I. Chip’s scan, the pearl seemed to be breathing, sucking in the turbid air in the room and, after going through some unknown transformation, released pure oxygen and was even able to clean the air. This eliminated the fishy smell of the ocean.

“A.I. Chip, scan!” Leylin commanded.

[Beep! Mission established. Beginning scan.]

The A.I. Chip intoned loyally, and immediately after, probing undulations scanned through and did not miss any corners.

[Scan completed! Yet to find any suspicious items or spying spell formations.]

The A.I. Chip intoned.

“Alright, looks like they aren’t playing any tricks. I just need another layer of protections so I can be at ease though.” With a tap of his finger, a blue rune appeared and rapidly disappeared into the wall.

In the blink of an eye, a resplendent blue layer of light appeared within the hold of the ship and quickly disappeared.

[Defence and warning spell patterns completed. Activation of comprehensive control. Simultaneous detections ongoing.]

Once the A.I. Chip sent information over, Leylin could finally completely relax.

“Hah…” He lay on the soft bed and huffed out a sigh, “At least I managed to regain a portion of my mobility before they found me, or things would have gotten complicated!”

“However, after recovering up to this point, the rest of the injuries aren’t that bad. I can even use external items…”

At this thought, Leylin’s palm touched at his waist. Silver spatial rays flashed and a dark red healing potion appeared in his palm.

WIth Leylin’s attainments as a grandmaster at Potioneering, as well as the vast amount of resources provided by the Bloodline Union and Doze Imperial City of the Blazing Flame Monarch, he’d long since made a huge quantity of potions at the grandmaster level that he constantly kept at his side to deal with any unexpected situations.

The expedition into Purgatory World was of utmost importance, and he obviously brought everything along.

“With my vitality and rank as a Warlock, high-ranked potions probably won’t do much for me unless they’re primordial potions…”

The dark red potion didn’t taste all that good and even had a spicy taste that seemed to sting his nose. However, without even a flinch, Leylin drank it.

The potion worked quickly. A flush first appeared on Leylin’s face, before the sound of cracking was heard everywhere in his body, as if his bones were breaking. At the same time, it was flourishing with life like a plant.

After treatment using potions was used a few times, Leylin no longer had the feebleness of before.

Chapter 702: Thornback Ironwhale

“Could this be… the Thornback Ironwhale?!”

Traces of fear could be felt in Geiger’s spiritual force, “How’s that possible? How can there be deep sea predators here when we’re so close to the coastline?”

The Thornback Ironwhale was a large being unique to the deep sea. Every single one of them had immense strength upon maturing, but their most terrifying characteristics were their temperaments. Once one set its sights on a target, it wouldn’t lose track of it until it managed to seize it.

The Thornback Ironwhale’s terrifying aura overwhelmed even the Godric’s, and it was the reason for Geiger’s fearful expression.

“Watch out!” Just as Leylin gave the warning, the Thornback Ironwhale charged forth, its large metal thorns piercing deeply into the Godric’s body.

*Moooo!* The Godric cried out in pain. As the two gigantic beasts collided, huge tremors travelled throughout the ship.

“Ah…” Under such tremendous force, Geiger collapsed to the deck, unable to hold his weight. His numerous tendrils wrapped around the mast like vines.

Geiger was still in quite good shape. In the moment of the collision, there were a few merpeople sailors at the sides of the deck that had been sent flying off by the huge crash, letting out piercing screams as they fell into the waters. Along with their kinsmen in the sea, they were drawn into the battle between the two gigantic creatures. In the end, they were turned into mincemeat. All that was left of them were traces of red on the waves.

Usually, the chains fastened around the Godric were immensely helpful for sailing. Now, however, they were no more than a huge burden. Noticing this, Geiger immediately commanded, “Break the chains!”

A few sturdier mermen soldiers pounced on the control valve with furious eyes, using a thick hammer to split it open.

*Crash!* The Godric’s gigantic chains then broke away, and the tremor on the ships lessened greatly.

“Turn the ship at full force! Leave this sea region!” At some point, Geiger Dole’s voice could be heard at the bow of the ship, body floating in the air. Great spiritual force undulations swept the area and even forcefully took control over the merpeople sailors, causing them to begin to work with reddened eyes.

*Creak! Creak!* The large ship suddenly turned around and left the two large beasts behind.

Water kept splashing into the air, and terrifying sounds could occasionally be heard from under the sea. Even though they were under the effect of magic, a lot of sailors trembled in fear.

“Prepare the cannons at the bow of the ship! We need to eliminate that Thornback Ironwhale, or it won’t let us off until it sinks us to the bottom of the sea!” Geiger Dole exclaimed as he flew towards the scene of the battle. Geiger had evidently regained his composure and scared the sailors witless, making them work even more intensely.

“Hurry! Prepare it!” Geiger’s large vertical pupil was filled with blood vessels, and its tendrils seemed to turn into powerful whips that kept hitting the merfolk, hurrying them to carry a large and heavy harpoon that was around 5 meters long above the cannon.

“The Thornback Ironwhale has the metallic skin ability, with an effect similar to physical damage reduction. We need to use this!” Geiger produced a few black and white spotted stones and began to rub them together as if he was starting a fire. A layer of black and white light suddenly enveloped the steel fish.

‘Oh? It’s using temporary enchanting techniques? What is the medium? Is that a sacrifice or a scroll?’ Leylin’s eyes gleamed as he watched from the sidelines.

The enormous monsters kept roaring at the other end of the battlefield, causing huge waves that resulted in the ship swaying violently.

The Godric of the fleet was no match for the Thornback Ironwhale. Although it had the potential to reach the Morning Star realm, the sad truth was that after being treated as a slave for many years and being specially sealed, it could no longer completely develop its bloodline power.

The same didn’t apply for the Thornback Ironwhale. For all of its life, it had grown up in the treacherous deep sea and was extremely experienced in fighting.

Hence, at the very start of the fight, the Godric had a huge chunk of its flesh bitten off by the Thornback Ironwhale. That was not all, the whale’s sharp iron thorns also left many wounds on the Godric’s body.

An enormous amount of blood flowed out from the Godric without stopping. The blood shed by the merfolk from before was nothing compared to this, as the entire region was dyed red with the Godric’s blood.

*MOOoo…* The Godric’s thunderous voice gradually became weaker, and there was even a pleading note in its voice.

“Damn it!” At this moment, Geiger Dole had rushed to the site to support the Godric in battle. After witnessing the scene unfolding in front of him, his large pupil immediately went completely red with rage.

The Godric was still the valuable property of the Eden trading company. If anything happened to it, or worse, if it died, then the amount that needed to be paid in reparations would be astronomical, enough for the company to go bankrupt. Geiger and his crew could be sent to some barren or dark region to be forced labour. On fleets like this, there was a shipment of very valuable goods which absolutely could not be lost.

Geiger Dole immediately acted in violent rage. A great deal of formless spiritual force turned into whips as it was pulled from the void. The seawater in the surrounding area converged to form a large wall of water.

“Mm?” At this moment, Leylin froze on the deck, as if he had discovered something.

“Is there any problem, Lord Ley? What do you think of this situation?” Geiger transmitted to Leylin after noticing his actions. Although he was extremely busy, he’d kept his eye on the area.

“Oh! There’s a stalemate right now, and with your father and the Godric working together you have an advantage.” At first, Leylin consoled him. However, he then spoke in a solemn voice, “Nevertheless, the Thornback Ironwhale has a high resistance against spiritual attacks. You need to be careful!”

According to most theories, the larger a monster that relied on its physical strength, the more it would be lacking in terms of the spirit and soul. This Thornback Ironwhale was obviously an exception to that rule. Not only did it have a high resistance against Geiger Dole’s spiritual force attacks, it could also reflect them back at him.

“The Thornback Iron Whale already has the steel willpower trait. If it goes crazy again…” Geiger was filled with unease, “Mister Ley…” He looked at Leylin expectantly.

“Mm, don’t worry. Since you went out of your way to help me, it’s only natural for me to return your kindness!” Leylin nodded, and hearing this made Geiger relax considerably. He then began to operate the cannons himself, and aimed at the giant Thornback Ironwhale that was fighting both the Godric and Geiger Dole.

With a loud bang, the giant cannon roared. The force of the recoil sent the ship backwards by a large distance, and even caused the stern to sink slightly below the water.

A thunderous explosion, like the roar of a monster, rang out. A black ray that was tens of meters long shot out, striking the triangular fin on the Thornback Ironwhale’s back.

*Roar…* Large amounts of blood spurted out, and the whale let out enraged howls.

*Pak!* At this moment, a chain filled with runes was pulled until it was stretched out.

“Now’s the time, pull!” At the other side of the chain was the ship from before, Geiger’s spiritual force undulations intensified to the limit as he howled in anger.

The ship was pulled with such force that the hull started to shake abruptly. A game of tug of war was now happening between the Thornback Ironwhale and the ship, hindering its movement. As this opportunity revealed itself, Geiger Dole launched his final attack from the air.

“The King of Evil’s True Eye, Death Ray!”

Tremendous amounts of dark red rays appeared from Geiger Dole’s large vertical pupil, piercing into the eyes of the Thornback Ironwhale. It suddenly closed its eyes and its body started to convulse and thrash wildly, as if it was having a fit.

*MOOOO!* The Godric immediately roared, and charged towards the Thornback Ironwhale.

After shooting that ray, Geiger Dole seemed to have spent all his energy. He slowly fell to the deck, even the tendrils on his body no longer able to help in maintaining a standing position.

“Father!” Geiger immediately came over, using his many tendrils to help his father stand up.

*Roar!* Following its berserk howls, the Thornback Ironwhale’s eyes flew open once more. However, there was now a significant amount of blood pouring out from both eyes.

“The Thornback’s Bloodthirsty Berserker transformation! I never thought it would awaken its bloodline!” Geiger Dole stared at the outburst of strength from the Thornback Ironwhale as it sent the heavily injured Godric flying; his complicated feelings couldn’t be masked by his spiritual force.

Geiger Dole saw the crazed Thornback Ironwhale charging towards the ship and immediately came before Leylin, pleading with him, “Mister Ley, please help us!”

“Don’t worry!” Leylin revealed a good-natured smile from behind the Mask of the Dreamless, and arrived before the giant cannon.

Due to the iron chains and the harpoon anchoring it, the whole fleet’s movement was restricted. It was as if there was a deep sea demon that was tugging on the chains, trying to pull the entire fleet into the sea.

‘This World’s paths of power seem to be reliant on awakening one’s bloodline innate abilities as well as on sacrifices… I can’t use anything too outstanding, otherwise it’ll raise suspicion…’ Having decided what action to take, Leylin came beside the chain and placed his palm on its surface.

The ice cold metal was shaking slightly, and only now was Leylin able to deeply understand the immense strength of the Thornback Ironwhale while in its enraged state.

The best spell model for the situation was transferred to him by the A.I. Chip, and immediately after a dim layer of light covered his hands. “Metal Animation!”

The whole length of the iron chain seemed to transform, and it began to ripple like a wave down from the top of the chain until it reached the other end.

Chapter 705: Offerings and Beast Spirits

Port Elias not only had the title of the Pearl of the Hail Continent, but also housed so many different races that even Leylin was left overwhelmed. That was not all; both sides of the busy road were filled with multiple shops, selling anything from the lowest quality armour and protective gear to the highest grade equipment such as high-grade sealing scrolls and other things. Everything one might need was present in these shops.

Based on Leylin’s understanding, the beings in Purgatory World were of varying races, each relying on their physical bodies and bloodline specific innate abilities to battle. There was no need for them to train themselves; their bloodlines would increase their strength with the simple passage of time until they reached their peak.

Of all the systems, only two were used throughout the whole world: sacrificial offerings and beast spirits.

These offerings meant sacrificing something, or someone, to a certain dignitary. After obtaining their blessing, an inhabitant would have their power increased in some form, be it a pure boost to their strengths or mysterious new abilities.

The path of offerings was more like an exchange in Leylin’s eyes. The natives would offer up items that were of value to their chosen dignitary, and in turn, they would these dignitaries help the natives increase their strength. Such methods were very similar to the gods in the World of Gods, while still being somewhat different.

Since he hadn’t delved deeply into the subject, he couldn’t be certain what exactly the difference was. Perhaps it had to do with the devotion that these beings held for their chosen dignitaries, but they did not request the beings to bring offerings every day or at fixed intervals. There were even some that could rely on their support even though they hadn’t offered anything at the time; although there was the need to have offered something of extraordinary value to the dignitary prior to that. This was a distinct difference from the gods of the World of Gods.

‘It looks like even power systems from the World of Gods were assimilated during ancient times, and those past rank 6 in the Purgatory World have made some changes to them…’ Leylin touched his chin.

In this enormous universe, the Magus World and the World of Gods were like two extremes. They were the greatest in size and held the most powerful beings.

These two worlds had real information about existences up to rank 8 in power. The primordial entities deduced that only when one of the two managed to seize the other’s resources and gain their laws, power systems, and their knowledge that they could advance to eternality, to rank 9.

This was what sparked the Ancient Magus War. Having already advanced to the peak of rank 8, there was nothing else that would attract the attention of the Magi in the myriad other worlds. Only the guidance and understanding necessary to reach rank 9 would ignite their desire to fight for it, no matter how slim the chance!

Of course, as these two worlds were about equal in power, the result was that both sides were severely crippled. The collective strength of the Magus World deteriorated greatly, and the World of Gods had gone so far as to completely seal itself.

It wasn’t just these two worlds that were involved in the war, countless smaller and weaker worlds suffered from collateral damage as well. Their unique strength and advancement systems had been leaked, and through real battle experience the systems were refined to become more accessible.

The path of offerings was something Leylin believed was an evolution of the system of faith that the gods used. They removed the restrictions between gods and their followers, and turned it into a system of equivalent exchange. It was only after these changes that it fit the Purgatory World’s circumstances.

After all, not every world’s laws were suitable for the spread of religion.

As for the second common method, the path of beast spirits, Leylin had previously listened to some explanations about it from Geiger Dole.

As the Purgatory World was a home to various races, with numerous ferocious beasts and high-energy entities occupying it, some intellectual beings invented the concept of hunting these ferocious beasts and extracting their souls. After doing so, these would be sealed into the user’s body, summoned during battles using certain techniques.

Since sealed beasts differed in strength, it created different ranks for these beast spirit masters. On top of that, when one’s beast spirit magic reached a higher rank, the corresponding beast spirit masters would be able to seal even more spirits.

Ancient legends even spoke of a beast spirit master who had reached an unprecedented realm. He had sealed innumerable beast spirits at the level of Morning Star all over his body, and had enough power to destroy a whole continent!

The energy from the sealed spirits could even aid in the cultivation of a beast spirit master, allowing them to reach a higher rank faster.

“Offerings and beast spirits are the main power systems in Purgatory World,” Leylin mumbled to himself, his eyes scanning for shops with related material.

These two strength systems could be considered the main paths to power of the sentient races in the Purgatory World. Looking at how vast the world was, it wouldn’t be strange to find that smaller branch races had their own systems. Leylin wouldn’t even be surprised if there were magic inheritances here.

With a long period of data collection, and adding on the current lightspeed thought process of Leylin’s own brain, he’d learnt much of the common languages in the Purgatory World with the help of the A.I. Chip. At the very least, daily conversations were already no issue.

‘Here it is,’ he though soon after setting his sights on a shop that looked like a huge open clam. He then walked in.

He could sense a powerful aura pervading the shop, and given its location and the attitudes the pedestrians had towards it he reasoned that this shop would have something worthy of his attention.

‘Welcome to my shop, revered Alabaster Devilsnake, descendant of the Dignitary Snake Dowager!’ A voice sounded in Leylin’s head the moment he entered the shop. It surprised him; although he was still using the Alabaster Devilsnake’s bloodline to conceal himself, it was very rare for someone to have the ability to even notice that layer of concealment.

The shop owner clearly took him for a member of the Alabaster Devilsnake family, and sounded rather humble. After all, Alabaster Devilsnakes grew to rank 5 upon maturity. In addition to their being descendants of a dignitary, they had a very high status.

“Where are you?” Leylin surveyed the interior of the clam, which was just a white space with multi-coloured lights floating in the air.

Information appeared in Leylin’s mind. This was not spiritual force, but an even more mysterious kind of communication.

[Beep! Detected soul force undulations coming through. Deny or accept?]

At this moment, the A.I. Chip’s prompt was transmitted.

Now, Leylin had found a lifeform that could use soul force directly.

“State your name!” Leylin’s lips did not move, but mysterious soul force was sent out. There was even a chaotic luster in Leylin’s eyes, which let him immediately discover the energy core located in the middle of the white space.

A green bundle of light was hidden within the layers of the void, with countless green soul force threads that linked it to the room.

“The customer was able to find my core?” At this moment, the information transmitted from the core held a trace of alarm. “Also, this energy is soul force?!” It was clearly shocked by Leylin’s ability to use soul force and was extremely afraid.

“This is the first time I’ve seen someone do something as stupid as allowing others into their own body,” Leylin placed his hands behind his back and began to browse the shop’s items, occasionally using soul force to communicate with it.

“Don’t you know that once someone who can use soul force discovers your soul core, they could destroy you in an instant?”

Once the words left his mouth, Leylin felt the whole place shudder, especially the core. It was then that a trembling soul appeared.

“Lord Alabaster Devilsnake, please forgive me!” A little white person came out of the core and grovelled at Leylin’s feet.

“Don’t worry, I’m just an ordinary customer,” Leylin couldn’t help but console this being after seeing it on the verge of fainting.

‘Ordinary customer? Can ordinary customers use soul force? Do they posses such a terrifying aura of power?’ The little person’s thoughts were bitter, but it could only follow behind Leylin carefully.

“Though your methods can scare other races who don’t know about the soul force system, this is still far too risky!” Leylin lectured it as he grabbed a blue bundle of light.

A roaring snarl was transmitted from the bundle of light. Through the blue screen, Leylin could faintly see a small and exquisite sea fish. Its mouth was like a sharp pike which shone with a little luster.

“This is the Golden Pike Trout. This beast spirit is very suitable for beginners seeking to become beast spirit masters!” Seeing Leylin seemingly interested in the beast spirit, the little person immediately went beside him and began to introduce the fish with a fawning expression on his face, “If my Lord likes it, I can…”

Suddenly, the thought that drawing in a person that could take control of his life and death had the little person apprehensive and in fear. Perhaps even if Leylin wanted to take everything in its shop for free, it would be forced to agree.

“No thank you! This sort of thing is useless to me.” Leylin waved his arms.

“Do you have anything with a general introduction to the pah of offerings and beast spirit spells? The more detailed the better!”

“Yes, yes I do!” The little person smiled and waved his arms. Two tremendous red bundles of light flew over. The rays dissipated and revealed a cow horn bugle and a pink shell.

Leylin picked up the bugle horn and immediately received a prompt from the A.I. Chip.

[Discovered spiritual force data interface. Accept or deny?]

Evidently, the two items were like crystal spheres in the Magus World, acting as a medium to store information.

Chapter 712: Good Feelings and Goodbye

“You and I are of the same type, and I had the ability to save you. How could I just leave you?” Leylin spoke in a righteous tone.

“Fool,” the snake girl snorted coldly, but it pleased Leylin inwardly to notice her gaze softening considerably. She continued in a gloomy voice, “Mixed bloods like you are actually very rare.”

Listening to Leylin’s words, the snake girl immediately became uncommunicative. Her expression grew so damp it seemed like she could drip water. Leylin secretly nodded to himself as he saw this scene, ‘I wasn’t wrong. A half-breed will always suffer discrimination, no matter what world you live in.’

Leylin understood from the snake girl’s bitter expression that she had suffered a lot. However, she was still able to show incomparable concern for those who were similar to her. He took advantage of this ‘misery loves company’ attitude to gain her full trust.

“Oh, that’s right, I still don’t know your name.” Leylin smiled sunnily at her.

“Belinda. Yours?” Belinda stared at Leylin, focussing especially on his facial scales. Her eyes grew dreamy.

“My name is Nick, my lovely lady!” Just this little praise caused Belinda to flush, showing her lack of experience in dealing with others.

“So, Belinda, what do you intend to do next? And what was that at the port? Why were you attacked?” Leylin asked her as if he had no idea about what had happened. He acted as if he wasn’t the one who spread information on her.

“Nothing, just the final struggle of a group of Beholders.” The mention of the earlier incident caused Belinda’s expression to turn cold. It was evident that she felt extremely resentful.

Leylin understood her feelings. After all, her organization hadn’t planned to act against Port Elias. At most, their plan was to turn the port into a hub and use it to smuggle some goods. Thus, it was normal to feel resentful when their plans went down the drain.

“Nick, I have a question” Belinda looked at Leylin with a solemn expression, “Are you a follower of the Snake Dowager or a part of the Beholder crowd? Or do you believe in other dignitaries?”

Identifying which dignitary you followed was an extremely serious matter in the Purgatory World. The hostility between opposing factions often led to battles to the death.

“I am a wanderer. I have yet to choose an Exemplary” Leylin naturally caught the hidden meaning behind these questions and answered without the slightest hesitation, “I am, however, more inclined towards the Matriarch. After all, she is our progenitor”.

The Matriarch! This was the title that the snake descendants, in the Purgatory World, mainly used to address the Snake Dowager.

“Since your belief is skewed towards the Matriarch, there is no risk of conflict between your belief and mine in the Beholders!”

Leylin expressed his understanding. It seemed as though the Snake Dowager and the Trial’s Eye made an alliance.

“I am under the command of the Trial’s Eye. I came to Port Elias to receive some resources to use in the rebellion against the powers of evil and chaos.” Belinda told Leylin of her origins. She explained the conflict between the Trial’s Eye and the Filthbird and went through the history of how civilization had developed in this world.

And in the Purgatory World, where the two Exemplaries’ original bodies were located was an endless conundrum.

There was no peace at all between the Sacrificers on both sides. Every time they met, there would be a fight to the death.

“No wonder you were attacked. Port Elias is the territory of the Nefarious Filthbird,” Leylin showed a shocked expression.

“The Port is a territory of the Chaotic power. There isn’t much hope for them!” Belinda saw Leylin’s expression and snorted coldly.

“Oh? What do you mean?” Leylin asked interestedly.

“I already reported what happened to my superiors. The organization will surely send support. The head of the organisation is, at the very least, a Rank 5 Sacrificer!”, a flash of gloominess appeared on Belinda’s face, “Port Elias dares to forcefully seize our goods and kill our members. This is the Hail Continent’s territorial waters. No matter how powerful Elias’ backer is, this place still belongs to us”. At this point, Belinda was very confident.

Port Elias had been sneakily founded through the Bird’s influence. It had not received approval from the Hail Continent’s Holy City nor the Snake Dowager. After all, the Snake Dowager had allied herself with the Trial’s Eye.

As a result, even if Belinda and her compatriots destroyed the entire port later, and even killed the Governor of Elias, nothing much could be done. The most Port Elias could do was to secretly order the arrest of Belinda and the others.

“A Rank 5 Sacrificer?” , Leylin was rather curious. He had seen the frightening abilities of a high-ranked Sacrificer from the Elias’ governor and witnessed the capacity to go through your limits without any bottlenecks.

‘This kind of high-ranked Sacrificer should be the favourite offering of hostile Exemplaries.’ Leylin stroked his chin as the corner of his mouth curved into a smile.

Since Leylin decided to practice in the Path of Offering and the Beast Spirit Magic, he gained some understanding of these two cultivation techniques. Although it wasn’t a lot, the information he got, the practical data and the A.I. Chips deductions allowed him to gain deep knowledge on the two systems.

In the Path of Offering, choosing an Exemplary was the most important step. It was also important to choose one whose doctrine aligned with your beliefs. Sacrificial rites were based on equivalent exchange; as long as an offering was made, power would be lent by the Exemplary you followed. But truly devout Sacrificers would be able to receive greater benefits.

Moreover, worshipping opposing Exemplaries was an incredibly stupid thing to do. Even if such a Sacrificer managed to not get targeted, his benefits would be greatly reduced.

‘As for myself, becoming a Snake Dowager or a Trial’s Eye Sacrificer would be courting death. The best option is the Nefarious Filthbird.’ Leylin thought to himself, ‘Furthermore, if I make a great sacrifice when I first communicate with the Exemplary, I should be able to reap great benefits. I might even receive the Unspeakable Baptism.’

Presumably, the Bird was enemies with the Trial’s Eye and the Snake Dowager. Consequently, it would be happy to see Leylin grow strong and break through the Snake Dowager’s seal.

The Bird was not an almighty Rank 9 so it couldn’t remove Leylin’s Allsnake Curse. But perhaps, it would be able to temporarily suppress the curse.

Leylin himself could only suppress the curse for 2 years, which was too short. Possibly extending the suppression time would become a great advantage.

Even though Leylin had gone through a great amount of thoughts, on the surface he only seemed to hesitate for a moment, “Belinda, you should be a high-ranked Sacrificer under the Trial’s Eye, right?”

“Yes, that’s right. I am already a peak Rank 3 Sacrificer and should be close to breaking through. Too bad I wasn’t able to finish this mission.” Belinda admitted it without the slightest hesitation.

“Why don’t you follow the almighty Matriarch? She is our benevolent and beautiful progenitor”, Leylin had an expression of incredible disbelief.

Although the Snake Dowager had allied herself with the Trial’s Eye, it was still considered a betrayal for a descendant to believe in a different Exemplary. If she ran into a more radical snake, it might try to eliminate Belinda, the ‘Disgrace of the Mother’.

“The Matriarch? It is true that she is everything to us but she is just too aloof and remote. We belong to the lowest rung of society so we only need fairness and justice. And the only one who can give us that is the God of Contracts.”

Belinda laughed coldly at some unknown thought and became excited. Her expression revealed that she was remembering an unbearable event of the past. It was probably the oppression she had once suffered from the purebloods, something she could never forget.

“As a mixed-blood, don’t tell me you have a good impression of those so-called ‘pureblood’ Alabaster Devilsnakes.” Belinda stated as a layer of translucent tears appeared on her eyes.

Leylin pretended to become silent in response.

“Well, let’s not speak of these unhappy memories! I have already issued the signal and reinforcements from the head of the Order will arrive very soon. You should leave!” Belinda exhaled a deep breath, glancing at Leylin.

“Alright.” the organisation was approaching and, since they had different beliefs, staying any longer would arouse suspicion.

Besides, he had made a lot of profit today. Not only had he eliminated hidden dangers, he had even established a good relationship with Belinda. In the future, he would arrange another ‘coincidental meeting’, so there were no problems at all.

Chapter 713: Threat and Action

[Beep! High-energy magnetic field discovered. Determined to be from a Rank 5 being. Host is advised to be careful.]

The A.I. Chip’s immediate prompt surprised Leylin.

‘Looks like I can’t leave even if I want to at this point,’ a mysterious smile rose at the edges of Leylin’s lips. Still, he pretended to be oblivious to everything, planning to leave after bidding Belinda farewell.

Just as Leylin was about to move, tremendous soul force undulations full of Just as Leylin was about to move, a streak of tremendous soul force undulations full of astounding strength and intent was transmitted over, “Wait, he can’t leave!”

A figure gradually appeared from the surface of the water. A layer of transparent distortions gradually dissipated, revealing a large Beholder.

This one, however, was different from Geiger. It had three different giant eyes of varying sizes. The three eyes were in triangular formation, with the central one connected to a few fleshy-red channels. Pure white tendrils drooped to the ground, forming the Beholder’s legs. A great and powerful aura emanated from its body.

‘This one should be an Elder Eye of the Beholders,’ Leylin judged inwardly.

An adult Beholder had the strength of an ordinary rank 3 Magus. Elder Eyes usually had strength at Morning Star.

This Beholder was even more uncommon. Besides the power from its own race, it was a powerful Sacrificer! The power of judgement emanated from its body, causing Leylin’s eyes to narrow.

“This Beholder should be the leader that Belinda mentioned. Doesn’t that mean it is a rank 5 Sacrificer?”

As a Rank 5 Sacrificer, this Beholder had strength comparable to a regular Radiant Moon Magus. What was most terrifying, however, was that its body had been fully branded by the Trial’s Eye and even the A.I. Chip was unable to scan and determine its stats.

“Greetings, Lord Bayclark!” Belinda knelt reverently while pulling at Leylin’s clothes to do the same.

“Greetings to Sire Bayclark!” Leylin merely bowed slightly. This made him seem arrogant, and a hint of disapproval was evident in the Beholder elder’s large eye.

It glanced towards Belinda, transmitting tremendous soul undulations. Fury was evident within its eyes and it criticised her, “Belinda! Your actions today have tarnished the glory of our master. And it’s not just your failure at Port Elias’ stronghold… All your decisions so far have been rash!”

“Lord Bayclark!” While still kneeling, Belinda straightened her back, “Your subordinate is responsible for the failure at Port Elias, but allowing Nick to leave was a very ordinary matter. He might not be a subordinate of our Master of Order, but he is a descendant of the Matriarch.”

“And a fellow clansman of yours,” the Beholder added coldly, “I have long warned you to not be too kind towards those of your kind with mixed blood. They can only bring trouble!”

“Lord Bayclark, I can vouch for Nick. He’s on our side, he helped me at the port.” Seeing Bayclark’s eyes flash with red, Belinda gritted her teeth and spoke on Leylin’s behalf.

“Alright, I’ll let him go. I hope your luck continues, or else there’ll be another pair of vertical pupils in my collection!” Bayclark twisted his body and turned towards Leylin, “Or should I say, two pairs.”

Belinda was badly frightened by this rank 5’s threats, ridicule and lack of trust.

Leylin obviously wasn’t the same. Outwardly he seemed indignant at this, his face and ears turning red. However, he was making a calm analysis on the inside, ‘It arrived far too quick. That means it was already nearby, perhaps it was the commander of this operation while Belinda was the one in charge of Port Elias…’

Numerous sea tribes arrived as Bayclark and Belinda conversed. Mermen, octomen, and sharkmen, each outfitted in custom-made armour, brandished their assortment of weapons that included pikes and choppers. There were even magicians among their rank, neatly spread out into rows that formed a huge legion of staffs behind Bayclark.

“Followers of the Master of Order! Evil, chaotic power has taken over Port Elias and even killed our companions. This entity has committed the worst sin under the skies. What should we do?” The Beholder elder turned, transmitting tremendous soul force undulations and radiating it in all directions.

“Eliminate them!” “Suppress them!” “Burn them to death!” The marine people in Bayclark’s legion raised their weapons and roared.

“Very good! You are all devout believers of our master!” The Beholder elder’s slit eyes seemed to be filled with traces of red, “I hereby order all of you to attack. The target is Port Elias!”

At that, the clamour from the cries of these beings was enough to disperse the clouds in the sky. The surface of the water split apart amidst their thundering voices, countless enormous sea creatures revealing expansive level backs.

All the troops climbed atop the enormous marine beasts in an orderly manner, making them look like terrifying war forts.

“You, mixed blood of the Alabaster, believer of the Mistress! You must come with me and use the blood of chaos to prove your loyalty!”

“What right do you have to do that?” Leylin exclaimed in annoyance, pretending to be a hot-headed person.

“What right do I have? Well, I can kill you whenever I want to,” Bayclark chuckled, while vast soul force wrapped tightly around Leylin. This was clearly a threat. Leylin was playing the role of a mixed blood with at most Morning Star strength, so he immediately paled.

“Belinda…” he looked at Belinda who was still kneeling and giving him a pleading look, “Fine, I’ll do it!”

“That’s the spirit! Chaos is an old enemy of your Matriarch too. Your actions will surely earn her favour.” The Beholder elder released his soul force. It went near the coastline where a large golden octopus appeared, which let Bayclark stand on its head.

“I merely approve of some of the Matriarch’s ideologies. I don’t follow the path of sacrifices. A bloodbath won’t bring me any benefits.” Leylin looked grim as he mounted a large marine beast with Belinda.

Belinda was apologetic, and she transmitted over to him, “I’m sorry, Nick. I I dragged you into this. When the time comes, just protect yourself. Leave the rest to me.”

“It’s not your fault,” Leylin smiled with difficulty while a trace of coldness flashed in the depths of his eyes, ‘A rank 5 Sacrificer, and someone with a high position in the organisation, would make a great gift for the Nefarious Filthbird.’

A curfew had been imposed in Port Elias due to the recent events.

Streets that were usually bustling with life were exceptionally quiet. Boat wreckage and blood could be seen floating in the ocean, and the houses that had been wrecked in the incident were left desolate, yet to be repaired.

Groups of troops jogged around in an orderly manner on the streets, occasionally charging into shops and demanding they be allowed to search the area. It was pure chaos.

At this moment, an urgent alarm rang out and a piercing defensive air signal sounded.

From a high vantage point, one could see a large wave of giant marine beasts with countless figures on their back surging forth like a tide on the surface of the waters. Aggressive beings approached the port from the sky as well.

This scared a few of the free merchants, and they secretly put away their goods and escaped. After all, they could not afford to provoke either organisation. Doing so would only lead to a horrible death.

Merchants were not the only ones. Even the most evil pirates ran from such a dangerous place. They would rather fight the local troops trying to run away than stay here any longer.

Just as the chaos was about to escalate, the bright cries of a hawk sounded out. A large Nighthawk beast spirit spread its wings as it circled above the port with a figure on top of it. Terrifying power descended that was at the peak of rank 4, and the pier finally managed to regain its calm.

A swishing sound could be heard as something surged towards them. Soon, numerous streaks of light flew in from various locations to stand behind Elias’ Governor, bowing in greeting, “Lord Governor!”.

They all had Morning Star-ranked strength, but they could not conceal the worry in their expressions.

“They are Trial’s Eye’s followers. I can sense that nauseating smell coming from their bodies even from here.” A white-haired elder with a hook-like nose and hawk beak spoke coldly.

“This should be about what happened this afternoon. I’ve already asked for support from the headquarters. However, they are too far away. Even if they used a teleportation spell formation, they would still need to use it several times. It seems our enemies have been preparing for a long time,” Elias’ Governor looked grim as he clenched his fist, causing the air to explode with an ear-piercing shriek. It seemed that he had been thoroughly enraged.

Chapter 718: Giant Tortoise and Sacrifice

*Swish!* A brilliant blood-red arc of light cut through the air, wiping out the massive flames. The outside world looked extremely distorted from within it, and it gave one a momentary feeling of isolation. It was clear that this streak was moving at great speeds.

The ray of light vanished in an instant and all became still, but it did not seem too abrupt. A black silhouette revealed itself, and beneath it was an enormous iron hammer with many iron chains firmly sealing a large number of runes.

‘This place is at least a thousand miles away from Port Elias. It should be far enough.’ This was naturally Leylin. After snatching Bayclark, he had been afraid of arousing too much suspicion so he’d used a lot of concealment and bewitching spells, quickly fleeing from the scene.

Although he did not know how much effect the spells he cast had, it was always better than nothing. Leylin finally let out a sigh of relief after making sure that he’d fled this far without being followed.

‘However, for the sake of safety I should settle this as quickly as possible.’ Leylin’s figure descended unhurriedly, arriving at a lonely island.

This island was very small, and was comparable to a single drop of water in the middle of the vast ocean. It also looked desolate, with no vegetation or fresh water sources that could be found.

However, Leylin nodded his head in satisfaction, especially after sweeping the area with his soul force, ‘This should be a good place, especially as it keeps moving.’

While laughing softly, Leylin lightly stamped his right foot, causing the ground to hum. A tremor was sent through his foot, which grew larger and ended up forming a small earthquake and a tsunami.

*Rumble* Broken rocks rolled over the coral reef, and a small fissure appeared. By the time the earthquake had calmed a little, even stronger vibrations began to sound out.

An oppressive hiss from an animal, like the cry of a dragon or the roar of a tiger, sounded out from the dark sea.

*Crash* All of a sudden, Leylin’s isolated island began to move. The black rock rose higher and higher from the sea, with kelp and black shells attached to it. In the end, the small island became a huge and irregular piece of circular land.

*Crash* On one side of the island, numerous rocks fell to the bottom of the sea, revealing a large, pitch-black hole. Promptly, a snake-like head stretched out from this hole.

The howl from earlier had evidently come from this monster’s throat. Its body was immense and its eyelids were still covered in algae and green moss.

[Beep! High energy undulations have been discovered, scan completed!]

Accompanying the A.I. Chip’s voice, a complete image of this monster had already been projected in front of Leylin.

This monster was an impressively huge tortoise whose length reached tens of thousands of meters. Leylin’s ‘island’ was actually part of its shell, and since the monster had been floating motionlessly for far too long, it had started to show vestiges of life.

“It’s a miracle of life, or should it be called the beauty of this world? It really is quite fascinating!” Leylin murmured a few words of praise. This type of giant tortoise could sleep for thousands of years at a time. If this island had been discovered by ignorant people, even a city could have developed on the tortoise’s back.

“Good day, your Excellency. Sorry to disturb your rest. I was wondering if you could give me a ride? I’ll be sure to make it up to you later.”

The A.I. Chip had determined the giant tortoise to be rank 4, but it still had to be subservient to him when faced with his Half Moon truesoul. Thus, it began to slowly move through the depths of the sea.

‘Very good,’ Leylin nodded his head, and his body automatically descended into the bottom floor of the coral island. It was as if the floor had melted under him. ‘A moving target is clearly less likely to be discovered. Now, I have to dispose of this fellow, lest it becomes a hidden danger.’

Soon after, a small yellow light radiated out to clear out an expansive underground space. The walls fused to become a marble-like material, the structure evidently stable.

Leylin sat cross-legged on the dry floor, with a very solemn expression on his face, “A.I. Chip, transfer the content on the Purgatory World’s Sacrificers.”

[Beep! Establishing task, commencing transfer……]

Along with the A.I. Chip’s feedback, a large amount of data was very quickly gathered and saved in Leylin’s memory bank.

The path of offerings had a very long history in the Purgatory World and had become the main strength system after many years of decisions.

In the past, Leylin had believed that this kind of sacrifice was a technique from the World of Gods. However, there seemed to be evidence that the technique had appeared before the end of the Great War.

Although the origin of the path of offering could not be verified, it had gone through such a long period of development that it was very rich in core content.

The so-called Sacrificers offered sacrifices to a higher existence, which required that the receiver have some comprehension of laws. This way, amplification power could be sent down through their subconscious communication channels.

The higher existence would amplify the Sacrificer’s strength. Even if it was for a limited time, it was still an extraordinary thing. With the correct sacrifice it was possible to almost borrow the power indefinitely. Assuming the Sacrificer could endure it, of course.

The Sacrificer’s rank could be improved through continuous sacrifices, and once they reached rank 4 they could perform a ceremony to permanently increase their attributes.

After the ceremony, the Sacrificer would be branded by their chosen dignitary and their sacrifices wouldn’t be accepted by others.

After many amplifications, the Sacrificer could receive power that surpassed their race. Take the Governor of Elias for example, his physical prowess exceeded even Melinda who was a mixed blood rank 4 Alabaster Devilsnake.

Furthermore, not only could rank 4 Sacrificers borrow power first and sacrifice later, they could also try to summon a clone of their dignitary.

From what Leylin understood, the sacrifice represented the limits of what you could get from the dignitary. So high level sacrifices meant receiving greater attention and a quicker response from the dignitary.

This was why he had to run far away after capturing Bayclark. Since he was a rank 5 Sacrificer, he was sure to capture the attention of the Trial’s Eye.

A Rank 5 Sacrificer could even borrow a tiny bit of the power of laws from their Exemplary, such as the golden lightning and trial power.

Relying on that, Bayclark was not weak for a rank 5. Leylin’s own strength just surpassed his greatly.

‘According to the A.I. Chips speculations, a rank 6 Sacrificer can borrow the dignitary’s power over laws. It would be possible to borrow up to 90% of this power if the Sacrificer and the dignitary are highly compatible. Their strength would surpass the power of the Blazing Flame Monarch…’ Leylin’s expression became rather imposing.

‘Of course, the path of sacrifices has its disadvantages as well. After all, the power of laws can only be borrowed, and not retained. No matter how harmonious the relationship is, Sacrificers cannot rely on this to reach Rank 7. Those dignitaries won’t allow others to grasp their laws. Therefore, rank 6 is the peak for a Sacrificer. However, there may be exceptions…’

As if he had thought of something, the corners of Leylin’s mouth curved into an excited smile, and his entire being seemed to be eager to try something.

[Beep! Transmission of Sacrificial Array has been completed!]

A complex spell formation formed in Leylin’s mind.

This was not just the Sacrificial Array he had recorded, but one that he had modified and optimised with the A.I. Chip. Not only could it accept more sacrificial power, but it could also minimise any loss.

If Leylin was willing to sell this modified version, it would make him extremely rich. Of course, he wouldn’t do such a thing.

‘The decisions made in the first sacrifice are incredibly important and the offering is a crucial point. The better the offering of the first sacrifice, the more attention and benefits will be given by the dignitary.’

Leylin’s spatial pouch flashed, and many resources appeared. He began to draw the modified Sacrificial Array whose power surpassed the Purgatory World’s most powerful secret techniques. It was all thanks to the A.I. Chip and the enormous amount of labour and resources that Leylin had poured into it.

“Also…” After arranging the Sacrificial Array, Leylin looked at the surrounding walls and swept his palms across them. Layer upon layer of blood-red lightning runes automatically emerged.

“Summoning across worlds!” “Powerful binding!” “Annihilation ray!” “Breath isolation!” “Location interference!” A great number of advanced ancient runes steadily emerged on the wall, which were the same standard as those used in astral laboratories.

Although Leylin was prepared to practice the path of offerings, it was still necessary to be cautious. By the time he was finished, he looked a little tired even though his soul force was still frighteningly vast.

*Crash* The black runic chain was broken, exposing the Elder Eye Bayclark within.

Bayclark’s soul force was currently sealed, to the point where he couldn’t even express himself. His three vertical pupils were filled with terror.

“We meet again, Elder Bayclark!” Leylin faced Bayclark and greeted it.

Bayclark trembled in fear when he saw Leylin, especially after he noticed the Sacrificial Array.

[Beep! Sacrificial Array has been completed, simulated success rate is 100%!]

At this moment, the A.I. Chip transmitted some information…

Chapter 719: Seals and Restoration

[Sacrificial Array completed! Please choose the target of the sacrifice!]

Several strange symbols emerged on the A.I. Chip’s screen. These symbols seemed to transcend the three-dimensional screen, possessing a strangely ancient feeling, with an aura of the power of laws.

Leylin looked silently at these runes. The A.I. Chip illustrated 7 runes in total, one for each continent’s dignitaries. Among the 7, there were a few that Leylin was naturally familiar with. A vertical eye rune, a twisting snake rune and a rune of a giant bird spreading its wings.

“Trial’s Eye. Snake Dowager. And the Nefarious Filthbird.” Leylin murmured the names of the three dignitaries represented by the runes. These three had left the deepest impression on Leylin, albeit not the most pleasant ones.

“Sacrifice target selection: Nefarious Filthbird!” Leylin held out his hand and lightly touched the rune of the giant bird spreading its wings. The rune was, almost instantly, copied into the previously empty core of the Sacrificial Array.

A foul and chaotic power seemed to have penetrated the barrier through deep and unknown channels, reaching this place. Threads of grey mist lingered above the array, and it was possible to hear faint crowing sounds coming from within.

Seeing this scene, even though he was firmly sealed, Bayclark’s body reacted slightly in anticipation of a fight. After all, being sacrificed to the Order of the Eye’s greatest enemy was unacceptable to this pious believer.

Unfortunately, no one would listen to the barking of a loser, be it in Leylin’s previous life or in the Magus World.

“Almighty Ruler of Chaos, the Flapwing, the free will that soars in countless dimensions! I, Leylin Farlier, call you reverently…”

Leylin chanted in the complex and obscure ritualistic language, which created faint undulations of soul force.

From the movements of the soul force, the ritual language acted like a mysterious key which opened a giant door somewhere. The entire Sacrificial Array rumbled, and the giant bird rune seemingly came to life and let out an elated chirp.

A large amount of grey light condensed and the space seemed to faintly warp. When it finally reached the limit, it loudly exploded.

*Crash* A grey flame suddenly emerged from the core of the Sacrificial Array.

“Almighty dignitary, Your Excellency the Nefarious Filthbird. Please accept my offering.” Leylin’s eyes held a trace of indifference, and the Beholder on the ground was pulled into the core of the array by an invisible string.

*Rumble!* The little flames suddenly grew to engulf the entire Beholder.

“Ah…… I curse you…… Curse you……”

In the grey flame, the huge Beholder began to melt like a wax sculpture. Even his truesoul was corroded. Leylin could still hear Bayclark’s dying curses ringing in his ears.

Just this sort of thing could not change his expression even slightly. Leylin’s eyes, however, were fully absorbed in the sacrificial process, and he occasionally still made adjustments.

It was very clear that for a beginner Sacrificer, it was nearly impossible to get a strong rank 5 being as an offering, let alone a Beholder who was a rank 5 Sacrificer of the Trial’s Eye.

The original Sacrificial Array that Leylin had bought in Port Elias wasn’t anything special. Although it was enough to get someone to rank 4, it was inadequate for the current situation.

When the Beholder Elder was completely melted, a horrifying energy overflowed from the wax, while an unbearable lamenting cry sounded from the Sacrificial Array.

‘Really…’ Leylin speechlessly shook his head, and proceeded to further strengthen the array with his soul force.

Since this was a high-level sacrifice, the laws of the world had finally been attracted when the Beholder was almost completely melted.

The high-spirited chirps of a bird followed. Then, the runes set in place by Leylin began to flash explosively. Some of them even started to fall apart. In the end, the Sacrificial Array produced a piercing light.

The grey flame became scarlet red in a flash, and the blood-curling screeches of the Beholder Elder increased in pitch.

*Bang* The blood-red flames completely swallowed up Bayclark, a rank 5 Sacrificer and Elder Eye. A huge amount of wax concentrated into a ball, constantly twisting and changing shape while it broiled within the scarlet red flames. Finally, it became a clever-looking little grey bird.

“We meet again, almighty Flapwing! Your Excellency, the Nefarious Filthbird!” This was obviously the Nefarious Filthbird’s clone, and Leylin bowed in greeting without delay.

The little grey bird’s eyes were rather glassy, but soon it was occupied by an intelligent personality. It looked at Leylin, its eyes expressing an obvious smile.

“We meet again. Snake Dowager’s blood descendant, Kemoyin Serpent Emperor.” A greatly changed and mechanical voice rang directly in the bottom of Leylin’s heart.

The little grey bird fluttered its wings, while seemingly very interested, “I am very satisfied with your offering, but your heart still seems to harbour some distrust.” The bird obviously pointed towards the strong binding and isolation runes on the walls.

Leylin just smiled slightly, “Please forgive your humble subject’s precautions. However, I believe that for a mighty dignitary like yourself, these are just like fine rain and cannot harm you at all.”

“Sly little fellow, you act as though this isn’t the first time you summon me. Nonetheless, I sense leftover marks of the Trial’s Eye’s contracts.” The little grey bird said this with certainty, after sniffing Leylin’s body.

Leylin’s eyes flashed with an expression of sudden understanding. This must have been back when he was a rank 1 Magus and he used the Nefarious Filthbird Feather Solution to clear the Trial’s Eye’s contract.

But, after improving his knowledge, Leylin was sure that the Nefarious Filthbird Feather Solution was merely some kind of medicine’s name. The main material was definitely not the feather of this entity, otherwise no one would let Leylin use it.

Certainly, the Trial’s Eye’s contracts used by rank 1 and rank 2 Magi were not high-level due to limits of these Magi’s strengths. Thus, they could still be erased by Leylin’s accidental use of the Nefarious Filthbird Feather Solution.

Although he had only borrowed a millionth of the bird’s power, the bird still keenly perceived it.

“Yes. At the time, I was able to break the bonds of the Trial’s Eyes. I need to thank the dignitary for your power,” Leylin respectfully expressed his thanks.

“You don’t need to thank me, young man. Breaking the bonds of the Trial’s Eye is my mission and duty.” As a result of this introduction, the Nefarious Filthbird regarded Leylin with much gentler eyes, “You did the right thing. If you had not immediately offered this Sacrificer, the Trial’s Eye would have found you within 10 hourglasses’ time.”

At this point, the Nefarious Filthbird sent another message, “Now, it can no longer find you. Furthermore, everything that pertains to you will be concealed by chaos and filth, thanks to my power of chaos here.

After hearing this, Leylin’s expression relaxed considerably.

As expected, to fight against a dignitary, Leylin could only borrow the power of another one. The Nefarious Filthbird’s concealment made his earlier risks worth the trouble.

“So, Magus, tell me your request.” The Nefarious Filthbird spread its wings, looking incomparably solemn.

“Almighty Ruler of Chaos, please, may I ask if it is possible for you to remove the Allsnake Curse from my body?” Leylin restrained the excitement in his heart, and asked in a dignified voice.

“The Allsnake Curse comes from the Snake Dowager. We are of the same rank, so I am unable to completely remove it.” The little grey bird shook its head but, just when Leylin became disappointed, it continued, “However, the Power of Chaos is enough to postpone the flare-up from the curse. Do you want to suppress it?”

“Please, go ahead.” Leylin gnashed his teeth. It went without saying that entering the Purgatory World was already a risk, so he would not reject this offer.

“This seal will consume half of the sacrifice’s power.” The little grey bird looked deeply into Leylin’s eyes, and shortly after the terrifying grey power of chaos began to pour into Leylin’s body.

The immense power of chaos spread through his skin and flesh, then extending to his sea of consciousness and soul.

[Beep! Invading energy detected, eliminate?]

A red warning box popped up from the A.I. Chip.

‘No,’ Leylin gnashed his teeth, ‘But continue monitoring.’

[Removing resistance! Initiating monitoring mode!]

The A.I. Chip dutifully sent back.

A great quantity of chaotic power spread through Leylin’s body. In the end, it converged in his forehead, forming a silver seal around it.

The Allsnake Curse seemingly squirmed, but very soon it was suppressed by the vast amount of chaotic power.

[Beep! The Allsnake Curse’s seal has been reinforced! Estimated time to outbreak: 20 years!]

Leylin’s status box was very quickly refreshed with new information.

[The host’s Sacrificer Rank has risen! Current Sacrificer target: the Nefarious Filthbird! Rank: 4]

[Detecting that the host’s bloodline power has been released, the sacrifice strength has increased as well. Host’s stats have fluctuated greatly, re-collecting data!]

Soon, the A.I. Chip showed the new stats.

[Leylin Farlier, Rank 5 Magus, Bloodline: Kemoyin Serpent Emperor (Complete Form). Strength: 51 (76), Agility: 46 (62), Vitality: 135 (176.9), Spiritual Force: 1575.8 (2003.5), Magic Power: 1575 (Magic Power is in synchronisation with Spiritual Force), Soul Force: 158, Status: Rank 4 Sacrificer strength is increasing in force! Estimated time to the Allsnake Curse outbreak: 20 years!]

“Freeing part of my bloodline force, and the growth in rank as a Sacrificer, has actually restored so much of my strength.”

After seeing his stats changing greatly, an ecstatic expression immediately appeared on Leylin’s face.

Chapter 720: Feather of Chaos

The Allsnake Curse caused all of Leylin’s stats to fall and sentenced him to die in 2 years. These problems felt like a rope constantly tightening around Leylin’s neck, stifling him. But now, with the Nefarious Filthbird’s help, Leylin finally felt less pressed for time, allowing him to relax a little.

“My Laws of Confusion Seal can delay the Allsnake Curse from flaring-up for up to 18 years. After 20 years, even if you contact a rank 8 being again you won’t be able to strengthen the seal and postpone it any further. Unless, you are able to find a Rank 9 Everlasting One…”

The Nefarious Filthbird’s voice was heard again. However, the small grey bird in front of Leylin seemed to have become slightly illusory, as if it had consumed too much energy.

“Thank you, almighty dignitary.” Even if the curse wasn’t completely resolved, Leylin still thanked the Filthbird sincerely. After all, if it wasn’t for it, he wouldn’t have 20 years to solve his problems.

“There is still half of the power of sacrifice left. Tell me your other requests.” The bird spoke within Leylin’s consciousness again.

Leylin pondered for a while and spoke of his plans, “Almighty Flapwing, I hope to obtain something to conceal myself. After all, I am bound to go deeper into the Hail Continent if I want to completely remove the Allsnake Curse.”

He had already discovered long ago that, in the Purgatory World where the path of offering was prevalent, there was still a fatal weakness in any disguise he could come up with.

The weakness was the existence of a dignitary’s clone when one sacrificed. As long as the Sacrificers reached rank 4, they would be able to summon the clone of a dignitary. And, if those clones were intelligent, they would definitely be able to expose Leylin’s disguise.

During the previous skirmish, both the Elias Governor and Bayclark were only able to summon a phantom of their dignitary and not a complete clone. Hence, Leylin was able to conceal himself. However, he knew it was impossible to avoid them forever, especially in the Hail Continent. Therefore, suitable methods for concealment were necessary, and they had to be able to deceive the dignitary’s clones.

Furthermore, these existences may have some special detection methods. In particular, the Snake Dowager, who was the source of Kemoyin bloodline descendants, would have such methods. There might be some kind of special reaction towards her own descendants.

Although Leylin had already prepared all sorts of countermeasures, it still did not stop him from adding another insurance.

“You are very intelligent,” the Nefarious Filthbird nodded in approval, “Once you appear within a range of 5 kilometers from one of our clones, you will definitely be unable to escape our detection.”

“I bestow upon you the Feather of Chaos. The one who holds this item receives the protection of chaotic power. As long as you don’t come into contact with the dignitary’s real body, you won’t be discovered. “

The small bird’s silhouette became even more faint. In the end, it transformed into a grey illusory feather that floated in front of Leylin.

“Snake Dowager’s descendant, Kemoyin Serpent Emperor. Travel the Hail Continent as you wish, and tear the Dowager’s godly status apart.”

The grey Nefarious Filthbird’s clone vanished. Only a residue of its conscient reverberated in the secret chamber. In a flash, the Sacrificial Array exploded with a bang and turned into flying dust.

“I gained more than what I expected.” Leylin let out a long breath, feeling rather glad.

Doing business with the Nefarious Filthbird was like dancing on a tightrope. Leylin had no choice but to consider all worst case scenarios.

Luckily, due to the arch-enemy relationship between the Nefarious Filthbird and the Trial’s Eye, it was very willing to see the Trial’s Eye’s ally, the Snake Dowager, be defeated. This was the foundation of the deal between both sides

Leylin’s own power and his meticulous arrangements were the most crucial part of his plan. Even had the Filthbird’s clone suddenly turned hostile, he had the confidence to break the Sacrificial Array and escape from it instantly.

With a common enemy, and since Leylin himself could escape, the Nefarious Filthbird was willing to see him as a pseudo-ally.

Furthermore, Leylin still wasn’t able to completely trust the Nefarious Filthbird, since there was only a mutual relationship of wanting to use each other between them. Of course, the Nefarious Filthbird still had the greater advantage and their interests did not clash. Therefore, it was possible to maintain their agreement.

For instance, for Leylin who was an insincere sacrificer, being promoted directly to rank 4 level by the Nefarious Filthbird was a very good testimony that they could work together.

There would never be a lucky person who became an Everlasting One in the world. Only through careful, meticulous considerations and anticipating worst case scenarios would one be able to guarantee success.

‘Rank 4 Sacrificers can already begin to amplify their body’s attributes through attracting the dignitary’s energy into their own body, and solidifying it permanently.’

Leylin muttered to himself, “This kind of promotion often comes with a price. The whole body might be branded by the Nefarious Filthbird’s energy which creates a tissue and cellular transformation that cannot be opposed. Ultimately, one might even be controlled by them. A.I. Chip, conduct an all-round inspection of my body’s energy structure.”

[Beep! Mission established, beginning to scan!]

The mechanical sound of the A.I. Chip echoed. Soon after, fine blue light continuously swept across every part of Leylin’s body.

[Discovered unknown energy structure! Determined to be the Nefarious Filthbird’s energy branding! Eliminate?]

Without spending much time, the A.I. Chip responded.

Leylin had long prepared for this outcome. Hence, he did not look surprised at all, and he commanded very calmly instead, “Show me the image.”

Soon after, Leylin was looking at the image of a cell that was magnified several times on the A.I. Chip’s screen. At the center of the cell was something that looked like a sea urchin, with peculiar energy waves of confusion.

[Beep! This energy is the crucial element to suppress the Allsnake Curse. If eliminated, it would trigger irreversible changes. Probability of Allsnake Curse showing advance in effect: 99.99%. Eliminate?]

The A.I. Chip’s sound caused Leylin’s expression to become slightly gloomy, “It seems this would be the kill switch that the Nefarious Filthbird imposed on me. Although currently it’s only used to threaten others and maintain its own position, I still need its strength. I need chaotic power to suppress the Allsnake Curse.

Numerous rays of light continuously flashed across Leylin’s pupils. However, he commanded, “Focus on monitoring. For the time being, maintain the original shape.”

[Beep! Mission established, activating real time monitoring procedure within the body!]

The A.I. Chip loyally carried out Leylin’s orders.

“No matter what, I still profited this time. Not only was the Allsnake Curse’s effect delayed, I even obtained something to rely on when I infiltrate the Hail Continent.” Leylin murmured, stroking the walls with his palm.

A layer of black liquid flame emerged from his palm, spreading rapidly as if it had life of its own, consuming the entire place almost instantly.

Soon, the binding runes and Sacrificial Array vanished without a trace under the black demonic flames, and even its aura was burnt away. After the place was thoroughly cleaned up, a yellowish radiance emerged from Leylin’s body and blent into the surrounding walls.

A circular light floated above the coral island with a whoosh and, shortly after Leylin’s figure quickly flew out, “Thanks a lot, big fellow.”

Leylin looked at the large turtle and waved his hand while smiling. Afterwards, a slight green ray of light flew out of his fingers in a flash and merged into the turtle’s forehead.

Although that fine green beam was like dust when compared to the turtle’s huge head, Leylin still heard a hint of pleasant surprise from the creature’s whistles, especially after the ray merged. Its turbid eyes seemed to become somewhat quicker, and there was a hint of kindness in its expression while looking at Leylin.

“This is a gift from a wise man of ancient times. Although it only has a faint external aura, it still has exceptional effect in raising creatures’ wisdom. I know you want more but, unfortunately, I still have a need for these. I cannot give you anymore.” Leylin smiled. His body transformed into a long black streak that vanished into the distant horizon, leaving the turtle with a regretful expression.

The turtle howled in Leylin’s direction as if it was seeing Leylin off. The loud howl sounded continuously, even causing huge waves to form on the surface of the sea, which continued for half an hour.

Ultimately, the turtle’s body gradually sank to the bottom of the ocean, leaving behind a huge white whirlpool.

…..

The strong wind whistled into Leylin’s ears hauntingly.

Leylin’s expression turned solemn. Although he had already thought about how to sneak into the Hail Continent, even when the plan had yet to be implemented, he had some slight concerns.

“Partial AI #1, report your position!” Leylin pressed his temples and a faint blue radiance was revealed from his pupils.

[Beep! Current coordinates: Taking the main body as the origin, southeast; 786.67 nautical miles!]

An unusual message was directly sent by the A.I. Chip.

[The people around the area are all agitated. Possibility of a conflict between military forces. It is advised that the main body arrive immediately, otherwise the puppet’s identity will be exposed.]

At this moment, a warning sign was transmitted from the A. I. Chip again, making Leylin’s speed rapidly increase.

Although using the A.I. Chip to control the shadow puppet allowed it to imitate all of Leylin’s actions and even his aura to the point of being impossible to check its authenticity, it would still be exposed once it made a move.

By that time, even if Leylin managed to rush there and kill them all, he would probably still be unable to stop the news from being transmitted. Consequently, he would have to abandon the identity he had created, Nick.

The most important point, however, was that the plans he had previously set up would have to undergo modifications. The risks would be greater and this was something Leylin could not accept.

“What exactly happened that caused things to escalate to this degree?” Leylin carefully observed the report sent by Partial AI #1, and everything that happened after Port Elias’ military campaign appeared immediately before his eyes.

Chapter 721: Loss

The organisation that Belinda belonged to was obviously subordinate to the Trial’s Eye. They had been preparing to act against the Nefarious Filthbird, using Port Elias as a transport point to offload a large amount of prohibited goods.

However, with Leylin cutting in, this plan was dealt a fatal blow before it could even begin.

With Leylin’s disclosure of the information about their operation, the Port Elias setup had been completely exposed. All the people in charge of the different organisations were nabbed in hiding, and only Belinda had been able to escape with Leylin’s protection.

For the Trial’s Eye’s organisation, this was an intolerable humiliation! The loss of goods and intel was something they could not bear.

Hence, Belinda’s superior Bayclark had brought a huge army and hastened over, planning to destroy Port Elias in one go.

With Bayclark’s strength as a rank 5, the governor who was only at rank 4 could not even resist.

Originally, everything should have gone smoothly. In the Hail Continent, the governor didn’t have any support.

However, it was a huge pity that a plan was just a plan and there could always be other variables. The moment Leylin laid his eyes on Bayclark, only tragedy awaited the Beholder.

With Leylin’s deliberate plans, the governor and a few higher-ups of the Nefarious Filthbird’s organisation had escaped. Even the rank 5 Sacrificer, Bayclark, had turned into an offering for the Nefarious Filthbird, temporarily solving his personal issues while Bayclark’s truesoul was destroyed.

Even in the Purgatory World, a rank 5 was very rare, especially one with the status of a Sacrificer. In his organisation, Bayclark had high standing and managed this region. The loss of someone like him was a huge disaster for Belinda and the others!

Though Belinda had done all she could to save the situation, and had pushed the troops in order to reach a rest point, a paradoxical situation had been unavoidable despite her best efforts, landing her in her current dilemma.

No! This couldn’t be called a paradox, but a conspiracy!

When Belinda had stepped out as a leader, she immediately turned into an offering or scapegoat in the eyes of the Morning Stars.

“Why? Why did things turn out like this?” Belinda half-leant against the corner of a wall, arms hugging her shoulders as if that would bring her even the slightest bit of warmth. With her body, she wouldn’t feel any cold in temperatures above absolute zero.

It had been a subconscious act. She was currently in a cold, dark, humid room. There were multiple reinforcement runes on the walls, and the door was a cold steel grill. A few marine folk surveyed her icily from not far away.

Morning Star forcefields undulated from their bodies without any restrictions, and they were clearly the marine tribe that had gone to battle together with Belinda before. Now, however, their target had changed and they even kept Belinda on house arrest.

The accusation was laughable, ‘colluding with the enemy’! Belinda did feel like laughing, sending troops to Port Elias was a joint decision by the higher-ups, but they’d changed the narrative and said she’d bewitched Bayclark to do it.

Belinda’s calm actions after being caught by the leader of the allied forces was also taken as proof of trying to win the support of the enemy. What other reason could she have for doing this than to collude with the enemy?

Besides, compared to the Beholder race and marine tribe that had from the very beginning believed in Trial’s Eye, someone like her who was a descendant of the Alabaster Devilsnake just did not fit in. Was she not a readily available scapegoat?

It had to be said that whenever it came to suspicion of there being spies, outsiders like her were the first to be attacked.

“Belinda, are you feeling better?” A voice was heard from her side, causing her to raise her head slightly.

Through the dusky light, she saw the figure of her kinsman. After seeing who it was, a wry smile appeared at the corner of her lips, “Nick, you’ve been captured too?”

The shadow clone controlled by Partial AI #1 was watching Belinda ‘worriedly’.

When the marine tribe had suddenly turned hostile on her, Belinda practically turned into a wooden puppet, not resisting arrest. With only the strength of a shadow clone, the partial AI also didn’t dare make a move lest it was caught.

Thankfully, perhaps because they were afraid that the two would resist violent methods and cause needless deaths, they were only under house arrest. Their truesouls weren’t sealed or anything like that, and they were even placed together.

[Target is now in a poor mood and in a state of bewilderment. If appropriately consoled, it is possible to improve her impression of the host.]

An analysis presented itself to the shadow clone. However, its orders were merely to prevent ‘Nick’ being exposed as Leylin. Without Leylin’s explicit orders, emotional issues like this were the most difficult for Partial AIs to deal with. Hence, Nick merely stood around in a daze, as if similarly shocked.

“I’m– I’m sorry for dragging you into this, but don’t worry, Nick. Our organisation believes in the master of order and is the most fair and just. It will definitely prove our innocence, and you’ll soon regain your freedom…” Seeing Nick in this state, a hint of disappointment showed in her eyes, and she could not help but hug herself tighter, her whispers sounding from the gaps between her arms.

“This girl hasn’t given up yet?” A translucent figure penetrated the wall full of seals and shackles, entering the room.

Seeing the state she was in, a strange smile appeared on his lips, “Why is it that I always have to be the one to shatter the purity and fantasies of children?”

The translucent being melded into Nick, and the A.I. Chip took over Partial AI #1. From the outside, it looked like Nick’s eyes went blank for a while before returning to normal.

Nobody noticed this change, and having recalled the shadow clone and Partial AI, ‘Nick’ was Leylin once more.

After getting the warning from the Partial AI, Leylin had hastened to reach this place in the shortest time possible. The guards and spell formations outside were no issue for him. When it came to spell formations or runes, the research by Magi in the Magus World was leaps and bounds ahead of the marine tribes.

Leylin had regained most of his strength, and he could do all sorts of things with ease. Most importantly, he was now a rank 4 Sacrificer of the Nefarious Filthbird and had the Wings of Chaos. This made it even easier for him to break through the seals set up in the name of the Trial’s Eye.

These two were not just arch enemies, but their strengths restrained each other. Of course, when compared to Leylin, the marine tribes outside were useless.

“Belinda!” Leylin spoke slowly in a low voice, “At this point, are you still harbouring fantasies towards the marine tribes outside?”

“Fantasies? No! Even if they’re driven by benefits and greed, the master of order will come and save me…” She spoke resolutely. With her devoutness to the Trial’s Eye, he felt like her only being a rank 3 Sacrificer was a waste.

“Yes! Anyone can see how foul the marine tribe is. It’s not just the dignitary, Trial’s Eye. Even the higher ups know that…” Leylin spoke nonchalantly, almost with a hint of sarcasm. Without waiting for her to speak, he continued, “But… so what?”

“With the situation right now, where Bayclark has disappeared and the operation has failed, someone will have to take responsibility. Bayclark is an Elder Eye of the Beholders and has a great amount of power; he clearly fought with all his might. There’s a chance that he might survive, and nobody would dare offend a rank 5…”

“What’s left is to find people to take responsibility, such as you. The marine tribe is very harmonious, and if they really had to incriminate someone, it’d be you.”

At this point, Leylin saw that her shoulders were trembling even more violently. He added on, “However, the losses incurred by this is something your higher-ups definitely don’t want to see. Hence, this matter cannot really be pursued. A scapegoat is needed, or rather a sacrifice has to be found.

“At this point, is there someone more suitable than you? As an outsider with no background, you don’t have a group to back you up either like the marine tribe…” Leylin started to sound like he was ridiculing her.

“No! Even if they’re all like that, the mighty master of trials, the dignitary of fairness and justness, will definitely not abandon me…” Belinda raised her head, her scarlet pupils filled with insanity and hopelessness.

“I won’t say more about that.” Leylin shook his head, “But I hope you are aware that if the Trial’s Eye is in favour of absolute justice and fairness, it would long since have fallen and disappeared into the dust of history. To survive up to this point and spread its ways in so many worlds, it must know compromise. In order to uphold fairness and justness to a certain extent, the master of trials is already quite successful…”

“No, I don’t believe it! I don’t!” The despair in her eyes immediately dissipated and she crumpled to the ground like a ball, boneless.

“Hm? She can’t take this blow? Or has she thought of something?”

Leylin shook his head inwardly, ‘Is her mind too weak, or is there some particular injury to it?’

Chapter 722: Bewitching and Black Conversion

*Rattle!* At this moment, the steel fenced door was abruptly pulled open, and a circle of higher ups from the marine tribe walked in.

The leader’s face had a few blue scales on it. He looked towards Belinda coldly, and read from a sheepskin scroll, “Belinda, the headquarters has decided that you’ve turned your back on the Master of Order, profaning the glory of the dignitary. We judge you to have committed the crime of colluding with the enemy.”

“No, no! This is impossible!” Belinda completely crumbled down.

“Nothing is impossible!” The marine tribe leader tossed the document in front of her, the seal from the headquarters at the bottom right corner. It emitted dazzling lights, and wasn’t something that could be faked.

After seeing the scarlet words of judgment on it, Belinda had almost completely given up.

“Even… even if the headquarters is infected by chaos and filth, I still have the dignitary. I’m still a Sacrificer…” Belinda trembled, a sacrificial spell formation appearing at the tip of her finger. Compared to Leylin’s, there was only a rune of an eye at the heart of the formation.

*Pak!* The eye cracked and the spell formation dissipated, not giving a reply. This situation signified that the dignitary, the Trial’s Eye, did not accept Belinda’s offering. In other words, she had been abandoned.

Of course, the common people did not know that on the path of offerings, ‘equal exchange’ meant that even if the dignitary broke off the connection with the Sacrificer or did not accept their offering, what had been given would not be returned. This was a trade of equal exchange, and since the Sacrificer had offered something up it wouldn’t be returned.

It was similar with the governor of Elias. If he gave up his belief in the Nefarious Filthbird, or it did not accept his offerings, then he would at most not be able to obtain a boost from it. However, the results from previous ceremonies were permanent and remained.

This was unlike the priests of gods. Once gods abandoned them, they would lose all their status and magic power. That way had its own advantages and disadvantages.

“No! NO, why? Why did things turn out this way?” If the decision from the headquarters had pushed Belinda to the verge of collapse, this was a fatal blow.

“Why… not just the headquarters, but even the mighty dignitary did not believe that I’ve been slandered and treated unfairly…”

“Cheer up, Belinda! The mighty dignitary definitely knows the truth, but you need to make a sacrifice for its sake.” Leylin quietly stood beside Belinda, gently patting back of her hand that was on her shoulder.

In all organisations, the members would need to make sacrifices for the big picture. It was a normal thing, and if they didn’t do so they would be criticised by the public. In these days, it seemed like if a superior wanted a subordinate dead, the subordinate had no choice but to die.

Everything was for benefits. The benefits of a collective group took priority over personal gain. When met with this situation, complaining wasn’t even possible. One would have to take the initiative and rush to sacrifice oneself, else it would bring trouble to their family and friends.

Of course, if this person did not care for their lives, nor their friends and family, and had nothing to be concerned about, things would become difficult to handle.

However, these people were usually unstable, posing as a threat to their communities, and needed to be eliminated.

For the current situation, the Trial’s Eye had made this decision despite knowing that Belinda had been maligned. Belinda would thus be sacrificed.

Perhaps after pacifying the marine tribe, the headquarters would send people over to tidy up, removing any malignant tumours and people who could not be controlled. After decades or a whole century, there would be political change and Belinda might even be given the title of a ‘saint’, revered by the later generations and turning into a leader. However, if the person was dead, what was the point?

However, Leylin could not deny the point of the organisation’s actions.

In a physically weak world, joining forces to form organisations was the way of the powerful. When one member’s benefits were sacrificed, they could do nothing but exhibit enthusiasm for it.

However, this was different! When a person’s personal strength was immense, then they would have the right to go against the organisation. In a world where extraordinary strength existed, individuals who were powerful became important.

Especially in the Purgatory World, where a few dignitaries governed all the continents, murder and plunder was the best proof of this concept.

Hence, besides obediently dying, there was no other better option for her. Of course, she still had other options, like how Leylin was preparing to work some magic.

“There’s no slandering or conspiracy. This is the truth! Belinda, you colluded with the organisation of the Nefarious Filthbird and entrapped Lord Bayclark. We are going to punish you.” Seeing Leylin stand out, the marine tribeman’s pupils shone with dissatisfaction.

This was a natural feeling when a subordinate dared go against a superior’s authority.

“Alright! I’m not of your organisation and obviously can’t commit the crime of colluding with the enemy. I wonder when I can leave?” Leylin spread his arms and laughed.

“You must be a believer of the Nefarious Filthbird, and must be communicating with the enemy organisation with Belinda. You must be punished as well!”

The leader did not even blink as it spoke. Leylin almost wanted to give the leader applause, as he had guessed a truth that not even the Trial’s Eye knew about.

It had to be said that the leader had gotten it completely right by luck.

“What’s with all the bullshit, just kill them!”

A Morning Star beside it already had shining undulations of a beast spirit summoner.

For them, leaving Belinda and Leylin around was just going to create more issues. They’d had to contact headquarters before, and now that they had the permission to there was nothing left to consider.

“In that case…” Leylin shrugged his shoulders. Suddenly, his aura changed, turning from a little rabbit to a large, fierce tiger.

*Hssss—* A tremendous Alabaster Devilsnake phantom suddenly squeezed out behind him, producing ear-splitting roars.

*Rumble!* *Bang!* Terrifying explosions reduced the room to fragments.

“Kill them! Don’t hold back!” The leader yelled out, and a large shark-shaped beast spirit appeared, roaming in the air.

Light flashed, energy undulations from sacrifices and beast spirits constantly appearing. It caused even this islet to begin shaking slightly.

“Wahaha… you’re all liars. Liars!” At this moment, Belinda, who had been under Leylin’s protection, suddenly seemed to go mad, and her face flushed unusually.

“I was treated that way and even by the Trial’s Eye! What value does my faith and persistence have?” Along with her complaints and questions, two rows of bloody tears flowed from her eyes.

“In that case, let filth destroy the world!” An evil aura emanated from her body, and large amounts of dreamforce filled the surroundings, even turning black.

‘Could this be… the rumoured black conversion?’ Leylin wanted to say something, but he stopped himself.

“It’s not the time to say such stupid things. Let’s go!” The dreamforce that was summoned by Belinda abruptly converged in Leylin’s hand. It seemed to be weaved subtly, transforming into an even more powerful force.

A large black net brought with it an oppressive force that gave rise to despair as it enveloped the islet. Deafening roars were heard everywhere, but whether it was the rank 4 sea shark beast spirit that belonged to the marine tribe leader, or the attacks from others, nobody could take on this large black net.

Hazy dreamforce even caused the guards to lose their sight and crumble to the ground.

“Sinphobic Flames!” With Leylin’s soul strength, countless black flames appeared on the large black net. Differing from his phoenix fire, the black flames held a large amount of hatred within.

The sea species that had been burnt by the flames grew despondent, their bodies losing life undulations while their carcasses were preserved.

“Those flames target the soul! Careful!” The leader roared, and the Aquatic Shark beast spirit he summoned feared the black flames immensely.

After all, when it came to this kind of spirit body, the Sinphobic Flames were like their natural enemy.

In the span of one attack, all of the marine folk below rank 4 near the islet had been annihilated by the black flames. The net then constantly shrunk, trapping the Morning Stars in a tiny space.

“This strength… this strength…” The leader now looked deathly pale. If he had known Belinda had this ability and Nick was so vicious, he would have employed more gentle tactics.

However, it was too late at this point. The leader still tried till the end though.

“Wait… Belinda, we’re willing to send out a joint declaration to free you of all injustice, and we’ll even repent to the Master of Order. Please don’t…”

“Haha… haha… do you think I’m the same as before?” Belinda laughed madly, body filling with some red patterns. The dark dreamforce was being extracted unceasingly.

‘Vampiric Berserker transformation? Or is it an attack that consumes the bloodline?’ Leylin shook his head, not hesitating as he made use of her dreamforce, increasing the black flames in the large net.

At this moment, a strange undulation was transmitted as a rank 4 Sacrificer tried to summon a clone of the Trial’s Eye.

“Dream on!” Leylin sneered, and with a flash of his Feather of Chaos, chaotic power spread out, disrupting their coordinates and causing the Sacrificer that was summoning the clone of the Trial’s Eye to cough up fresh blood.

Chapter 723: Plans and Setting Foot on the Continent

Their final struggles taken care of, the truesouls of the many kinsmen of the marine tribes were corroded by the black flames and they all died with a loud rumble.

“You did well, annihilating so many Sacrificers of the Trial’s Eye. Here’s a reward!” The chaotic force of the Nefarious Filthbird was projected into Leylin’s mind with a royal declaration, great amount of chaos power descending through subconscious communication.

[Beep! Discovered large amounts of the law of chaos. Absorb?]

“No! Store it all.” With Leylin’s command, the large amount of chaotic force turned into grey crystals that he secretly stored. The black flames gradually died out, revealing an islet that now had no other traces of life.

“Keke… so they all died just like that? I thought they’d be more fun…” Belinda laughed maniacally.

Leylin appeared behind in her in that instant, light shining in his hands.

“What are you doing?” Belinda shrieked. Immediately after, her eyes rolled back as she fell unconscious.

“Mm… The bloodline consumption was so huge that even her mind is exhausted.” Leylin shook his head. She had obviously gone half crazy. If not for that, no matter how discreet he was in gathering the chaotic power she would have noticed it.

……

“Ugh…” With a light hum, Belinda slowly opened her eyes.

What entered her sights was a scene where abundant stars filled the skies, as well as the flickering firelight from a bonfire that lit up the area.

Slight crackling sounds sounded from the fire, and a few grilled fish that were skewered on tree branches were stuck in the ground beside the fire. An aroma of greasy food spread out from the fish unendingly.

“You’re awake! Would you like some?” Leylin chuckled as he handed a branch with a few grilled fish on it to Belinda.

Belinda took it without thought, her eyes still filled with bewilderment. Immediately after, the betrayal of the marine tribe as well as the decision from headquarters, even the memories of the failed offering to the dignitary of trials emerged.

“Ah…” The snake girl exclaimed, the grilled fish falling to the ground.

“Was all of that real?” Belinda raised her arms, watching the little sacrificial array branded into her skin. Now, however, the rune for the Trial’s Eye had completely dimmed; there were even cracks on it. She went quiet.

The frailness of her body was proof of her crazed slaughter before, and it caused a wry smile about her lips, “I’d thought my faith was strong… I didn’t expect it to be so fragile.”

“I think you did very well already!” Leylin smiled, passing over another portion of grilled meat, “Whatever it is, you’re alive. That’s the greatest blessing!”

“…” Belinda sunk into silence for a long while before she took the meat from Leylin.

“Thank you.” The sound was as soft as the buzzing of a fly. If not for his exceptional senses, he wouldn’t have been able to hear it.

“Why did you save me? Did you hope I’d be your mate?” Belinda asked after a silent meal. The question left Leylin stunned.

‘Mate? Ah, she’s of another race and even a snake at that. Her ideas of this sort of thing are a little different.’ Leylin nodded without a change in expression even as such a thought coursed through his mind. “That’s the smallest part of it. It’s more because we are of the same species. Mixed-blood Alabaster Devilsnakes are dwindling in number, and I can’t just watch you die…”

“My life is very complicated, and I even betrayed the Trial’s Eye. I’d bring you many troubles if we work together!” Belinda seemed to have recovered from her previous shock, once more the strong, able woman she was.

The branch in her hands snapped as she huffed, her whole body relaxing as she seemed to have come to a decision.

“Since I’ve already offended the Master of Order, we can only hide in the depths of the Hail Continent…” Belinda calmly analysed, “Though the Matriarch and the Trial’s Eye are allies, they wouldn’t send out a bounty just for this. With our bloodline, going to other continents would only lead to discrimination. My own situation is a good example!”

“It’s not an issue for me. I’ve been travelling around the archipelago; I’ve been thinking about going to the Hail Continent…” Leylin was in favour of her decision.

In reality, that was his main goal. If not, why would he spend so much effort on saving her?

“We will enter through the borders of the nearest continent and then traverse through the Serpent Plains to reach the Holy City. I have connections there, so they might be able to help us…” Belinda stood up, “In return for your help, I will find you a mate with a bloodline purity that does not lose to mine. Of course, if you’re certain about your choice, that’s not a problem!”

“Alright,” Leylin touched his chin, appearing ‘embarrassed’. He was actually rendered speechless at her using such a simple method to thank him.

“Beast spirit summon— Godric!” A layer of blue patterns emerged from Leylin as he stood by the coast. Their rest was done, and the figure of the quick-witted Godric appeared. It was just that the injuries from the last battle left it dull.

Healing beast spirits was a very advanced technique. Only a few high-ranked beast spirit masters in the Purgatory World could do such a thing, so even if Leylin had methods to heal his beast spirit he couldn’t show them now,

The large Godric mooed as it turned into a streak of light. It spread its two large fleshy wings on the surface of the waters, its expansive back as flat as land.

“Let’s go!” Leylin said while jumping on.

Belinda soon followed as well. Her scarlet pupils scanned the Godric and she shook her head, eyes full of pity, “Godrics mature to rank 4 beasts, but they’re very difficult to control. Those merchants capture young creatures and then seal or even extract their souls. That’s jus…”

Following that, she glanced towards Leylin, “I see that the beast spirits you have on you is meagre… don’t you have a healthier beast spirit? Injuries to the soul will only grow more serious in such a state, and even healers won’t be of much help…”

“I’m merely a rank 3 beast spirit master,” Leylin touched his chin, slightly embarrassed. He had bought this Godric at the port, using it as a temporary substitute. He had no plans of healing it, and at most was prepared to make use of this trash once more. “I’m more proficient in innate spells and the manipulation of dreamforce.”

“Mm!” Belinda nodded, evidently recalling Leylin’s astounding skill at using dreamforce.

“Since we’re companions for now, we should be honest with each other. Let me reintroduce myself. My name is Belinda, and I’m a rank 4 beast spirit master and rank 3 Sacrificer. Of course, my identity as a Sacrificer is of no use…”

The Godric flew along the shipping route quickly, leaving long trails of white lines. Belinda gathered her disheveled hair and smiled at him.

“A rank 4 beast spirit master? I don’t think I’ve seen you use your beast spirit though?” In the crazed state before, she had even ignited her bloodline source and yet did not summon her own rank 4 beast spirit, which left Leylin surprised.

“My beast spirit is a little special. If possible, I won’t use it in my whole life…”

She forced out a smile, her facial muscles stiff. She clearly recalled some bad memories, and Leylin tactfully did not question her further.

“My name is Nick, and I’m a rank 3 beast spirit master! I’m more proficient in physical battles as well as using the Alabaster Devilsnake’s bloodline force.” Leylin replied with a very sincere expression on his face.

“Which port are we going ashore at?”

“Though the Hail Continent doesn’t get information from the outside that often, some ports might have long since announced for our arrest. We can probably only choose coasts with no beings around. Thankfully, we’re using a beast spirit, so there won’t be issues with anchoring and maintenance.”

Belinda naturally knew more about the Hail Continent than Leylin. After all, no matter how hard Leylin tried to gather information, it was all theoretical. Nobody would know the place better than its inhabitants.

The Gordric’s low moos continued to sound as the two gazed into the distant coastline, looking to be deep in thought.

……

Two days later, beside a wasteland.

The black rocks outside emitted a pungent smell. Leylin was bored to death, leaning on a rock while quietly in wait.

A large port showed itself in his line of sight, pure white marble carvings, lighthouses, and all sorts of noticeable buildings exuding an incomparable beauty.

The whole port was bustling with life, and large numbers of beings of other races could occasionally be seen walking the streets.

After sneaking into the Hail Continent, Leylin and Belinda had stealthily hidden themselves near a port so they could gather important information, maps, and supplies. Belinda had volunteered to make some inquiries for more information.

Knowing she was more experienced and familiar with this than he was, Leylin sensibly did not oppose her.

“Catch!” A linen pouch flew over as a loud shout sounded.

*Thud!* Leylin extended his hands and caught it, “What is it?”

“A map, and some other necessities.” Belinda currently wore a thick cloak, covering all her characteristics as a demisnake. She was obviously very cautious.

“How is it? What kind of information did you get?” Leylin asked impatiently.

“So, are you finally scared?” Belinda, on the other hand, teased him.

Chapter 725: Dreamscape Forest

Under the radiant light of a purple moon, two dirt-yellow figures were galloping across the fields at a fast speed.

These two yellow figures were naturally the two yellowish-brown earth lizards. The two figures sitting on their backs had their entire bodies tightly wrapped up, only exposing their scarlet pupils which flashed coldly from time to time.

“This earth lizard is a rather good way of getting around!” Leylin looked at the lower limbs of his mount. Above the lizard’s barbed feet was a translucent membrane, rich in energy particles which converged around its surface. With this, it could very easily traverse jungles, swamps and other complex terrain.

“When we cross the Dreamscape Forest, we will arrive at the Whiteriver Valley. That’s where my family is…” Belinda’s voice did not carry a single trace of joy.

“Dreamscape Forest? Why the name…” Leylin had some misgivings, and soon looked all around him. Their surroundings were all grasslands, and there was nothing like a forest nearby.

“Dreamscape Forest, Dreamscape! You mean…” Leylin’s pupils constricted slightly. His thoughts drifted to the Alabaster Devilsnake’s bloodline skill and he thought of a possibility.

[Beep! Spatial undulations detected ahead, determined to be Dreamscape access points.]

The A.I. Chip’s mechanical voice transmitted over as well.

“That’s right. We’re also known as the Alabaster Devils, my clan stays in the cracks leading to Dreamscape, and we often lure travellers in to prey on them.” Belinda’s voice was cold.

Leylin’s thoughts, however, drifted to the A.I. Chip’s introduction of Alabaster Devilsnakes, ‘They enjoy tormenting their prey within Dreamscape before eating their meal!’

Traces of dark red fog appeared, making the surrounding area foggy and hazy. By the time they had passed through this fog, a strange forest immediately appeared in front of Leylin. The black branches and tree leaves criss-crossed, and there were many giant trees without a single leaf showing their bare form, like a grotesque withered arm waving about without stopping.

[Beep! Host has entered a Dreamscape zone!]

the A.I. Chip transmitted in reminder.

‘Dreamscape zone… This isn’t actually dreamscape, nor is it the Hail Continent. It’s instead an intersection of the two places, resulting in a myriad of strange events… And now I’ve entered using my real body!’ There was a strange expression in Leylin’s eyes. Rather than his most recent experiences in Dreamscape, he was thrown back to his first time researching this world, with his real body fully entering it.

Even though he was physically protected and dreamforce should have less of an effect on his truesoul now, if something were to happen then it would be very difficult to escape.

“The bloodline of the Alabaster Devilsnake will temporarily protect us from the attacking Nightmare Creatures. Follow me closely!” Belinda shouted as she advanced forwards in front of Leylin.

‘The Alabaster Devilsnake bloodline!’ Leylin allowed a layer of white scales to cover the surface of his body. As expected, after entering the Dreamscape zone, these scales became even more brilliant. They seemed to come to life, breathing in the dark red dreamforce. It was like a traveller had returned home, and there was not the slightest sense of unfamiliarity.

The earlier oppressive feeling that Leylin had felt from the Dreamscape Forest also disappeared without a trace.

‘Alabaster Devilsnakes are darlings of Dreamscape. As expected, they are direct descendants who inherited a part of the Snake Dowager’s ability with Dreamscape.’ There was an admiring look in Leylin’s eyes, ‘A.I. Chip! Scan the entire area and establish task: Probe the Alabaster Devilsnake’s ability to travel to and from Dreamscape!’

[Beep: Task established, beginning data collection!]

The A.I. Chip faithfully implemented Leylin’s command.

A pure-blooded Alabaster Devilsnake could travel through Dreamscape to the outside world; this was how one had originally attacked Leylin. A mixed-blood like Belinda only inherited a weakened form of this ability, and could merely communicate with Dreamscape and draw upon the strength of dreamforce.

Although Leylin did not belong to the Alabaster Devilsnake bloodline, he possessed the blood of a rank 5 Alabaster Devilsnake, and was even in such a good environment to use it. Using the A.I. Chip to find a way for a real body to travel through Dreamscape would be very beneficial for him.

‘If I grasp this technique, I’ll be able to enter and leave Dreamscape anytime I want, anywhere I want. Perhaps…’ There seemed to be fires blazing in Leylin’s eyes.

Freely entering and leaving Dreamscape would require a huge amount of dreamforce as well as the resources of an enormous world. But the important thing was that he could use the infinite space of Dreamscape to travel to different worlds!

After all, limits such as distance and time were simply a joke in Dreamscape.

‘It seems like the transport array was a lie. Belinda wants to use Dreamscape as a springboard to travel directly to the Serpent Plains…’ Leylin concluded in secret.

Of course, using Dreamscape as transit wasn’t easy either. Forget the monsters and dangers that lurked there, just the extremely indefinite nature of Dreamscape gave Magi a great headache. It was likely that Belinda’s ancestors spend countless painstaking hours to explore the region and find this passageway.

The Dreamscape’s drop point was just a hair’s breadth away, but it could completely defeat their purpose. If the hadn’t possessed the Alabaster Devilsnake’s Dreamscape ability, they wouldn’t have dared to experiment so boldly.

Leylin sped up his earth lizard and moved to Belinda’s side, “Belinda! Is it possible to enter this Dreamscape Forest at any time?”

“Of course not! Although the Dreamscape Forest has always been in the wilderness plains, only those with the Alabaster Devilsnake bloodline and the special opening ceremony can make the Forest appear. Otherwise they could travel the entire wilderness and only see the grasslands and sand…” Belinda hadn’t even turned to give him this immediate answer, “This is how…”

A spiritual force message immediately entered Leylin’s mind, full of information about incantations and signalling runes as well as special refining techniques. Seeing this, Leylin immediately realised how much Belinda’s clan had sacrificed to open up this safe pathway. And now he’d gone so far as to give this huge secret to him?

Leylin remained silent for a while, then asked, “Aren’t you afraid that I will sell this secret to other Alabaster Devilsnake clans?”

There were definitely other Alabaster Devilsnake clans in the Hail Continent. There were ten noble Alabaster Devilsnake clans, each varying in size, and these clans also had their respective branches and extended relatives.

Because of their open-minded nature, there was a large number of mixed-bloods and illegitimate children. This led to a huge number of bloodlines draining out, and it was only because of this that Leylin dared to impersonate a mixed-blood Alabaster Devilsnake.

According to what Belinda said, her family was only a branch of a pure blooded clan, and only her father, the head of the family, was a pure-blooded Alabaster Devilsnake. The rest were all mixed bloods or young children.

“Do as you wish! I’ve already given the information to you anyway, so it belongs to you.” Belinda seemed very casual, and her attitude shocked Leylin deeply.

‘It looks as if Belinda’s preparation to break off her relations with her clan will not be some easy matter. However, does this really concern me?’ A sly smile slowly curved at the edge of Leylin’s mouth.

‘This could be my chance. Not just for a bloodline, but also for research materials on Dreamscape, and even beast spirits and sacrifices among other things…’

“Haha……” At this moment, a yellow figure flashed in front of Leylin’s eyes.

Although the earth lizard’s speed in the forest was already very fast, the yellow figure clearly effortlessly surpassed them, flashing past them like a phantom.

“What is that thing?” Leylin asked in shock.

After a startlingly brief glimpse, he had seen the full view of the yellow figure from earlier. Wearing an outfit of ridiculously wide-fitting trousers, with clothes that were brightly coloured strips of cloth, this being had a face painted with oil colours. It looked like a clown from a play, but it managed to run at lightning quick in spite of cumbersome wooden shoes.

No! He couldn’t call it running. This clown was actually kind of floating, leaving many afterimages in its wake.

“Nightmare Creatures! They are a special patrol of the Dreamscape Forest.They don’t normally appear,” Belinda looked very imposing, “But if they drag us into the real Dreamscape even if we’re mixed-blood Alabaster Devilsnakes it will be hard for us to escape. After all, we’re not purebloods and don’t have the ability to freely traverse it…”

‘Nightmare Creatures?! Are they after me?’ Leylin was shocked, and an idea flashed in his head.

After all, he didn’t have a true Alabaster Devilsnake bloodline, and even his ability to to link together with dreamforce came through consuming the Alabaster Devilsnake bloodline. As a result, this anomaly of being discovered by the Nightmare Creatures could be understood.

“Haha… Haha……” They continued to advance towards Leylin, and the yellow clown appeared more and more frequently.

“Go away!” Belinda’s face was very impatient and she suddenly roared, scarlet ripples loudly exploding forwards, splashing on the trees and grass.

By the time the explosion had passed, the forest across them had been cleared into a bare pathway. The yellow clown that had been there had vanished without a trace.

“Coo coo……” The sound of fluttering bird wings could be heard, and soon after a gigantic black tree next to Belinda came to life,

“Ahh!” Belinda’s earth lizard was quickly bound up by vines, and let out a high-pitched lamenting call.

“Eternal Light!” A scarlet light suddenly appeared in Leylin’s hand, making the vines shrink back swiftly as if they had seen their natural enemy.

“Let’s go!” Belinda flew behind Leylin, and his earth lizard began to flee at the speed of lightning.